
Bindu Priya <bindu.priya@kyndryl.com>

Speaker 1  (00:02)
Yeah, we can install 

Speaker 2  (00:04)
Ok. The government substance move. Could you please switch on camera? 

Speaker 1  (00:10)
Yes 

Speaker 1  (00:21)
Yeah, yeah, we can stop. 

Speaker 2  (00:24)
Okay, just a minute. 

Speaker 2  (00:40)
Ok yeah, Prakar, we will start with quick introduction. Then we will get into the project then we will go for a technical discussions. I will introduce myself. 

Speaker 2  (00:52)
So my name is Santosh Kumar. I do carry almost like 13 years of experience software engineering and a mill relats. Yeah, so we can start with yours. 

Speaker 1  (01:06)
Sure. So myself, prakhari, around 14 years of experience in data engineering and combining with the E I'm L they started with the data engineering, and then I switched to the a I'm L. So currently, so I worked mostly with the um. 

Speaker 1  (01:25)
Haws, Azure database noflake, and then on the ML side I have worked with the Lam RAG systems pipelines. Yeah, so these are the things that I've all known. So my current time working with emphasis from last 3 years, but before that, I working with mAugust hanle and the sci, which is mostly the banking domain hot. 

Speaker 1  (01:49)
I'm currently working with the educational domain. So here we have an application which is used by the teachers and the student to get the assessments and then they can review that Based on the review, they can clear to the next grade here. I have built-in the chatbots majorly where we have the documentations from the organisation and then we have dumped it down and then we have the rack pipeline built-in using the effects and weddings and using a prompt engineering. 

Speaker 1  (02:25)
Then we are asking the questions accordingly and getting the response. Um, we have used the encoder model also like bird there before sending it to the Before sending it to the dlms and also there is another application which have worked on on the same project, which is led to the giving the feedback to the agents, so there we have the rank getting the transcripts. We are sending it to the encoders, and then the elections. 

Speaker 1  (02:56)
And then we are ranking based on the parameters that they have assigned. We have the ARB team, which is doing the all the kind of they are the smashed predictions labelling along with that they are monitoring the um. They use cases also okay along along with that I have worked as an individual contributor as a lead. 

Speaker 1  (03:20)
Also. But here I am working as an individual contributor working with the US client. They have their jail system so 50 days of print, 3 months of psi. 

Speaker 1  (03:32)
Tokyo okay, my battery is about 

Speaker 1  (04:06)
Yes, sir. 

Speaker 2  (04:11)
Fine, since you have mentioned about it. So what is the texture? You are using financial system. 

Speaker 1  (04:20)
For the rat system, we are using the prompts. Basically, vector dbs embeddings. 

Speaker 2  (04:25)
What kind of effective 

Speaker 1  (04:27)
We're using the work with the pine code. Leaving immediately chroma. Also you know, but mostly I work with pine code. 

Speaker 2  (04:39)
So now basically, is your documents, or is it only PDF or what kind of 

Speaker 1  (04:47)
Yeah, PDF dog dogs. Also, some transactions also from the videos. Yeah, majorly, these are the things Screen the texture tone. 

Speaker 2  (04:59)
Could you drink water the pipelines as part of this rank about 

Speaker 1  (05:05)
Based o* t** r***, while building 

Speaker 2  (05:08)
Is that system right? So you would have come up pipeline side 

Speaker 1  (05:13)
Um yeah, I mean, on the pipeline. What we are doing is we were Dim the chunkkin or the Chunky, and then the embedding, then sending the embending to the vector Devi. For that pipeline we have created uh using the umbilical. 

Speaker 1  (05:32)
Using the lancham basil, using that framework. So once it's done, then we've created sending all the vectors, all the all the embeddes of the vector space, and then we are quering it through the templates on the templates we have built-in the multiple models also because for each model we have different tests, different cases. And then the user query that, and they will get the response 

Speaker 2  (05:58)
Thank you. Okay for Delhi while building. Okay, so where are this? 

Speaker 1  (06:05)
Yeah, initially they were in the file system. But they have been transformed to the database. 

Speaker 2  (06:13)
Which database? 

Speaker 1  (06:14)
Because it was A This database we were using so that can price a data tables. 

Speaker 2  (06:23)
I mean, removing documents to the table. 

Speaker 1  (06:26)
Correct. Yeah. 

Speaker 2  (06:31)
From there, your printering, these documents for checking correct. 

Speaker 1  (06:36)
Yeah, Chunky, and then no matter what. 

Speaker 2  (06:39)
Ok, what kind of strategies you have used opportunity? 

Speaker 1  (06:44)
Um, for the Chunky's right. So we've used the The number of tokens that we have assigned and the overlapping so simple Taxes taxes, splitter, we have used for chunking. 

Speaker 2  (07:03)
Okay, what is tokenization? 

Speaker 1  (07:05)
Location is nothing but each word. I mean, we are Keeping that sentence into a world. Okay, and each word contains a token. 

Speaker 1  (07:17)
So Does water? 

Speaker 2  (07:21)
What is lemon juice? 

Speaker 1  (07:23)
The limited is like we have different words like eat eating and something. So it just transform it to the one word. So just I eat to Put in the vacuum camera. 

Speaker 2  (07:36)
Ok, so basically like you have a documents you are chunking it that will break down to world sanctuary. So these words you are converting into empathy, correct, yeah, so what was the chunking size you have used in your house? 

Speaker 1  (07:51)
Chunking size was yours using around 2 to 3000 um. Were I mean that were tokens? And it was around 10:00 of overlap. 

Speaker 1  (08:08)
Ok, I'll be 560. 

Speaker 2  (08:09)
What okay? What is the embedding you have used model? 

Speaker 1  (08:14)
We're here to use the open aim, betting the text largely. 

Speaker 2  (08:21)
Ok, I have a question here so you are saying your checking is around 10:00 2025 100 is an overlap, and what was the dimension of the embedding? 

Speaker 1  (08:33)
Um, it was around by default 3000 but we reduced it to something around 2000 or something. 

Speaker 2  (08:48)
Okay as I know, like emptying support, empty model is about like 1 568, that is exactly called yeah. 

Speaker 1  (08:56)
It was a basically the large one. Yeah, here, using the large model. That's why the chunking was 3000 yeah, for the small one. 

Speaker 1  (09:06)
It's 1500 

Speaker 2  (09:08)
1800 pokem. Yeah, fine. So now like you have got a chanking and you have seen meetings. 

Speaker 2  (09:15)
How have you preparing them in today? We 

Speaker 1  (09:18)
How are you preparing the vector dbo K so we have created the indexes. Okay, the indexes we have multiple For the multiple behaviour, we have created the indexes and those indexes. In those and excessive, we were keeping the embeddings basically, so 

Speaker 2  (09:41)
When you say indexes, what does it mean actually what it contains? What I do. It contains 

Speaker 1  (09:48)
Indexes is not water elsewhere, does it contain? It's just a name, okay, just a you can prepare it. File folder and with some matter data. 

Speaker 1  (10:00)
That's all, it contains nothing. 

Speaker 2  (10:03)
Okay, so what was the total document? Size. 

Speaker 1  (10:08)
Document size? I am not aware because we have the database right? Of the big team. 

Speaker 2  (10:14)
Ok. In that case, if you see any new document comes, how do you handle it? Yeah, same document document file is same, but content would vary. 

Speaker 2  (10:23)
So how do you handle it if you don't if we don't know about that document. 

Speaker 1  (10:27)
Yeah, that time we need to do the reindexing of the vector dbs, just in case if our embeddings are getting changed or wow, the electric database is getting updated, so in that case, we need to do the remedy. 

Speaker 2  (10:43)
Train tax okay, yeah, so you are using chromoda. 

Speaker 1  (10:50)
Hi, I've walked on that. But not much. 

Speaker 2  (10:54)
Not much, I see. Okay fine. So now what was the size of this vector db? 

Speaker 2  (10:59)
TBC says. 

Speaker 1  (11:00)
Size of the vector dv. 

Speaker 2  (11:03)
You have junk it right somewhere you are storing. So what was the size? 

Speaker 1  (11:09)
Not sure about the size 

Speaker 2  (11:11)
Okay, wow, what was the token size total token size? 

Speaker 1  (11:16)
Token, sorry tokal tokensized in the sense. 

Speaker 2  (11:19)
Not tokenachi, Chand says. I'm sorry for chunk, says total like you had got all the final documents right? You chunk it out and you are ready for storing them. 

Speaker 2  (11:29)
Embedding, along with chance to this vector db. So what was the Total size of the chances 

Speaker 1  (11:37)
Ok, so um. The we were making it a 3500 overlap. 

Speaker 2  (11:47)
No, that is a chunking graduate. When I say chunks, like group of words right? You will You will be storing as a vector dv in the vector db. 

Speaker 2  (11:57)
It's a Jason, you wrap this chunk. Embedding metadata as a Jason object, and you'll store it right? Okay. 

Speaker 2  (12:05)
So you would be having some like let's say, if documents are 500, it can take up to 100000 chunks right now so that you will be storing, right? Like how many were there like that? 

Speaker 1  (12:20)
Yes, similar, same way, I am 500 or something. We had that took you talk about the token, right? 

Speaker 2  (12:26)
Yeah, Toto tokens, not tokens, actually chunks. Chunks is chunks, is a group of tokens, right? 

Speaker 1  (12:33)
Hmm, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (12:36)
Basically a list of words or something like that. That is why one channel, like how many were there like 

Speaker 1  (12:42)
Devotee were not much because we were doing the summarization. Also, in between, so around 5:00 to 4:00 to 500. 

Speaker 2  (12:53)
Okay, no problem, so yeah, once you do with the chunking like what else you are doing like. So I mean, let's say we are, we are storing the data in a dab. What is the next sequence of action, which in a pipeline 

Speaker 1  (13:07)
Yeah, then we were doing some the prompts. We are sending the prompts to the from the prompts where getting the embeddings, and then we are doing the similarity search on that vector dv, and then with that similarity, we are again sending it to the Olympics. 

Speaker 2  (13:27)
Ok, what are the index methods deployed over there? 

Speaker 1  (13:31)
What are the index methods? Not sure about it. 

Speaker 2  (13:39)
Okay, now yeah, how this, when you Put a query like how it gotta get the relevant information from the Vett BPB. 

Speaker 1  (13:48)
Yeah, I mean, we have this applied. The top K. What do you say retrieval, ok? 

Speaker 1  (13:58)
Set approach. 

Speaker 2  (13:59)
We have used yeah, but what is the technical things behind top we have when you say top K5 is something. It could have right. How it got a fetch the data limit. 

Speaker 1  (14:10)
Yeah, based on the scores. Right, but I've invited you as the scores listed out down there in each of the rows. So based on that, it automatically fetched the top rows to bid in the top score, but we have to sort it out basically. 

Speaker 1  (14:27)
And then we get the 

Speaker 2  (14:29)
No, yeah, basically, like it. Gonna give some score, right? Similarity score something like that. 

Speaker 2  (14:34)
So based on what it get the value 

Speaker 1  (14:38)
Based on what it get, the value Do you think similarity? 

Speaker 2  (14:44)
Yeah, I think. 

Speaker 1  (14:46)
Cuisine similarly. 

Speaker 2  (14:48)
Yeah, similarity. So let's say you have finded documents and it is having almost a lakh of a chunks. Now you can Put one query so that query will be converted embeddings right now so when it has to go through all the chunks and get the relevant K documents okay so some mechanism there in the rank which pull and speed up the things of the retrieval local. 

Speaker 2  (15:16)
What is the technique? Cousin similarity helps you to find the similarity. Okay, but your query will be compared with each and every chunks. 

Speaker 2  (15:33)
In the vector dv one by one 1 / 1 something like that. It's a root source approach, but there are other mechanism also to speed up this comparison and get the relevant Talks are information from the NDP. 

Speaker 1  (15:52)
Even it's based on the index that we do 

Speaker 2  (15:55)
Yeah, have you heard about? 

Speaker 1  (15:58)
Yes, I heard of the error yeah. Ok, I heard only I am written about it. 

Speaker 2  (16:08)
Ok, any indexing mechanism? You are aware H. N. 

Speaker 2  (16:12)
Yes. 

Speaker 1  (16:13)
Hf IVF. 

Speaker 2  (16:15)
IVS. Okay. Okay, no problems like test on like indexing. 

Speaker 2  (16:20)
It alleged, and it's approximately here. Yeah, it was never right. So it deployed, try to put that data, that's okay, not an issue. 

Speaker 2  (16:30)
Ok, fine, your rack pipeline is ready. Now like how do you make it product? I said 

Speaker 1  (16:37)
How do I make it a production ready, right? 

Speaker 2  (16:42)
Bring. 

Speaker 1  (16:44)
Ok, so We have the Ok, we have the ML floors, ok in play, but I've not worked on the production side, but I'm just she calling it. We have the multi flowers which usually take the best version and on the database. We have deployed it 

Speaker 2  (17:07)
See a bell flow is for the melops right? It tells like when you have different models, which are running in experimental basis which could be the best or best out of these models can be picked for the production a bell flow is for them. Right? 

Speaker 2  (17:24)
Okay, so. But yeah, so in RAG system, let us say, RAG is just a service. Once that we said somewhere you have to deploy and integrate with your application, your saying right like you are worked on the chart. 

Speaker 2  (17:37)
So how do you integrate, how do you what was the like action next set of actions which we can take up to productize the things 

Speaker 1  (17:50)
Do not sure about it. 

Speaker 2  (17:54)
Okay. Scan. What are the splitting mechanism? 

Speaker 2  (17:59)
You are aware at the land chain. 

Speaker 1  (18:01)
On the langchain, I know about the tax later on. 

Speaker 2  (18:06)
When do we go for text? We go with a character texture. 

Speaker 1  (18:15)
When we have the Ok, so when we have long tech, long set of data, ok And when we are short set of data, so for the short set of data, when we need character by character, we need the character. Maybe the Characteristics have a tax one, which is very huge, so in that case, we need the tax platter. The giant crazy chance. 

Speaker 2  (18:43)
Yeah, so apart from this recursive characteristic, what are the other advanced customised splitting mechanism? You are aware 

Speaker 1  (18:54)
Yeah, I mean I have to recall it. I don't remember it. I 

Speaker 2  (18:59)
Maturity would semantic checking 

Speaker 1  (19:03)
Yeah, I heard of it. There are semantic chunking models just to get the context of that. Chung, okay, don't that in that case, not the exact word. 

Speaker 1  (19:15)
But the summarization of the 

Speaker 2  (19:18)
What it doesn't? What exactly why do we use that semantic checking how it's going to be beneficial? 

Speaker 1  (19:24)
Yeah, I mean so far. Let's say we have 1000 words. It will summarise to some 100 or 200 words. 

Speaker 1  (19:32)
So that's my visit for fusion substantially. 

Speaker 2  (19:37)
Okay, how do you do the reranking? 

Speaker 1  (19:42)
How do you do the re ranking? Giorgi is using the okay not sure about it. 

Speaker 2  (19:49)
We heard about PM 25. 

Speaker 1  (19:52)
Yeah, BM25 is the better version of the idea? 

Speaker 2  (20:00)
What is bmbs? 

Speaker 1  (20:06)
Not sure, sorry. So it comes into a hybrid search 

Speaker 2  (20:12)
T of IDF right, what is the T of idf? What it does. 

Speaker 1  (20:15)
Yeah, T FI DF. Yes. The use of it is that it will If the if the word is very unique, it will go into give the loan rank, and if the probability of the world is unique, then it will give the highest score to that number. 

Speaker 1  (20:34)
So that's the use of the It comes into the What is what do you say? Count vectorisation of the back of work. I'm sorry for contact. 

Speaker 1  (20:54)
Not the end of the year, but 

Speaker 2  (20:56)
Thank you, sir. So, have you get a chance to overcome any agent, a framework agent, a agents, building agents and all 

Speaker 1  (21:06)
Building a agent. I have not worked, but I'm learning that 

Speaker 2  (21:11)
Okay? Okay, could you please explain the architecture of transformer? 

Speaker 1  (21:17)
Architecture of Transformers we're talking about the You are talking about the GPT, right? Encoding decodes basically 

Speaker 2  (21:27)
Yeah, I'm asking the same algorithm which is part of like attention on unit. 

Speaker 1  (21:32)
Attention organising it's based on the decoder is ChatGPT is based on the decoder. And if we talk about the other models, but ALBERT distil but all those things, they were comes at, their, they have their encoders and the decoders both okay. So in that one, we have the embeddings, then we have the attention head forward forward feet. 

Speaker 1  (21:57)
Okay, so 

Speaker 2  (21:59)
What are the components? Basically, what are the can highlight? Some of the components launched attention transfer algorithm. 

Speaker 1  (22:07)
Yeah, I mean, so each word will going to be tagged with all of the word just to see what word it predict. The next okay so his will be going to be connected with the next word next high predicted word okay. So that how it works using the attention head and the forward feed and then the for the next embedding, it will, for each word it will basically check for the next word it will going to Put in 

Speaker 2  (22:35)
Yeah, what exactly like encoder into decoder is 

Speaker 1  (22:41)
There is no difference translation. Okay of the world um, just to predict the next word. That's it. 

Speaker 1  (22:52)
Ok, sure. 

Speaker 2  (22:53)
Now again, encoder, and we have a decoder. Two things, right encoder is doing something okay and decode is trying to 

Speaker 1  (23:02)
Understand that. 

Speaker 2  (23:03)
Physical understanding in this generative Fine, so can you talk about some of the hyper parameters? The parameters 

Speaker 1  (23:13)
Yeah, hyperparametres like we have done with the weights. Weight training with the R square for the linear thing we have done the R square. We used to check the R accuracy for the study. 

Speaker 1  (23:25)
For the classification we use to check the accuracy. 

Speaker 2  (23:29)
Talking about classical activity in the while using the LLM right, so we wanted to control the behaviour of the Generation, so there are set of parameters. You would have heard about K. P. 

Speaker 2  (23:43)
Are you could also be like some parameter to control the randomizations? These are some of the typical parameters. Okay, so you can okay. 

Speaker 2  (23:57)
You're smoking not enough. Yeah. Talking, so have you got chance told on classical emb? 

Speaker 1  (24:08)
Yeah, I've worked in another classical. 

Speaker 2  (24:11)
Ok, ok, so what is your favourite tomorrow algorithm? 

Speaker 1  (24:16)
Mostly I've used the random forest deposits more rogust. 

Speaker 2  (24:22)
Ok, random forest, what is the basic problem where random forest trying to solve? 

Speaker 1  (24:32)
Um, it is helps to make the decision first. So if the data has some missing values, okay, it handles the outliers, it handles all the things that the linear model has problem like data balance is genuine. So all in all those things, the random forest were efficient. 

Speaker 1  (24:55)
Are there several things Came to recall it, sorry. 

Speaker 2  (25:03)
Basically, random focus is trying to solve 

Speaker 1  (25:06)
Feature in photo, pyongy. 

Speaker 2  (25:09)
Thank you. So how it is differ from decision tree? 

Speaker 1  (25:17)
How it is important how it is different from the decision tree. So that's what I told you the advantage, I mean the decision tree it is other threshold. Okay, just to take the decision, whether yes or no, but random forest is More enhanced version of the decision 

Speaker 2  (25:38)
Oh, what is forest in the Yeah, random forest fortis, forest. 

Speaker 1  (25:43)
They didn't have anything right? So it's going to have the multiple. We can get the multiple trees, but the ideal is then this let's say so it will go into create a all the scenarios with all the so trees, nothing. 

Speaker 1  (25:58)
But uh nodes and the particular notes we have right? 

Speaker 2  (26:02)
What are you calling? 

Speaker 1  (26:04)
The features 

Speaker 2  (26:06)
Yeah, yeah. Forest. We call, like the mechanism of having one room no 92 Child node right? 

Speaker 2  (26:12)
What do you call dad? 

Speaker 1  (26:15)
Training, we call it as a train. 

Speaker 2  (26:18)
Stumps, something with stamping stumps, like group of stumps it for a great rate. No problem, okay. Yeah, so can you just tell me at high level how this random forest works? 

Speaker 2  (26:32)
Mechanisms? There is some mechanism technical mechanism. 

Speaker 1  (26:39)
Random forest basically works on the thresholds. Ok, so let's say we are multiple features with age, ok salary, so it'll be going to pick one. Um, one feature, it will go into have that tree based on that feature, let's say age. 

Speaker 1  (26:57)
So, if 

Speaker 2  (26:58)
Not talking about like that. One explain how it is looking. I'm not asking not the There is something called Dagging, and odright. 

Speaker 1  (27:10)
Yeah, bag of words. 

Speaker 2  (27:13)
Talking, what is packing? Thank you. 

Speaker 1  (27:16)
Begging is nothing but tells the frequency of the words that the tax contains. 

Speaker 2  (27:23)
That is bank of hurt pmwags. Vacuum we are having P voter that is a bag of vote over, so there is something called backing bagging and boot force, or some approaches there. What it got to happen like it create multiple trees, we call it as random forest trees. 

Speaker 2  (27:43)
Then, it tries it applies something called aggregations and working mechanism will be applied over there and it asks multiple decision tree which is the right one. Then, it takes whichever maximum. Having 

Speaker 1  (28:01)
Auding right so that enzymes, we called it as right Write ensemble technique. 

Speaker 2  (28:08)
Yeah, so here like banking means like somewhere, like voting technique will be deployed to pick the right for classification. Do you have any idea like what could happen in a regression? Yes. 

Speaker 1  (28:21)
In case of regression 

Speaker 2  (28:23)
Yeah, because random forest supports both right. It could be regression or classification. 

Speaker 1  (28:29)
Yeah, for the regulation view of the logistics regression ray. 

Speaker 2  (28:33)
Now, here, random forest, while doing regression right, it has to come up with a final single number, it could be integer or a floating or whatever it may be, how it got to agree it that well. 

Speaker 1  (28:47)
Based on the decision that it took right surrendum forests in the aggregating of all the taking the votes. So sorry I didn't get your question. So you're asking The linear. 

Speaker 2  (29:01)
Remain classified classification. Let's say there are 100 to trees. Okay, so in undertry, there are around 70R saying, oh yes, okay, since S is dominated out of 100. 

Speaker 2  (29:15)
So my final result for the classification will be yes or no, in case you, sir. Okay, but in regression there won't be yes or no right. We are looking for a numerical value. 

Speaker 2  (29:28)
Okay, how that will be finalised? 

Speaker 1  (29:33)
Ok, based on the data modelling, based on the data time balance rally. 

Speaker 2  (29:38)
Go to God, basically let me tell you like basically it happened. While looking at looking at the beam are waited, mean I think it could take the average of those respected values, and it could also be weighted me. No problem. 

Speaker 2  (29:55)
Yeah, so I just want to ask a couple of questions on the python side, do you have a share screen over there? Yeah, sure. You have, can you share your screen? 

Speaker 1  (30:09)
Jamshed. 

Speaker 1  (30:22)
It's not giving me the option to shell him. 

Speaker 2  (30:24)
Okay, no problem. Get you this potential. Ok, I'll share my screen illegal. 

Speaker 2  (30:52)
Can you see my 

Speaker 1  (30:53)
Supreme Jenkins. 

Speaker 2  (30:56)
Yeah, I'll give you control. Okay. 

Speaker 2  (31:10)
I want you to reverse this number. 

Speaker 1  (31:15)
You introduce to reverse this number There's a reverse method. That we can use 

Speaker 2  (31:32)
No, I don't want to use the existing one. Basically, I'm looking for a index based approach. 

Speaker 1  (31:39)
Okay, come. Yeah, so we've to write. I mean, using the file for look right. 

Speaker 2  (31:47)
That is somewhere time consuming. There is something called index indexes. Traverse index, something is there? 

Speaker 1  (31:57)
Ok, travelling, on the other hand was numbers. I mean, I don't know only 2 approaches either. 

Speaker 2  (32:05)
There is something called You would have heard about it. That's okay. Not an issue, okay. 

Speaker 2  (32:16)
So like you take the same number here. I want you to traverse it and I want something result like 14. 9 35, sorry. 

Speaker 2  (32:33)
16, right? 1695I want output should be like this. You should use a list comprehension. 

Speaker 1  (32:42)
Ok, and try. In the list comprehensive, I knocked on 35 

Speaker 1  (33:06)
Is a durabilation? Myntra assembly method can do List comprehension. Minister. 

Speaker 2  (33:26)
Ok, no problem fine, so now I want you to get something like this like number or Even 

Speaker 1  (33:43)
Or even? 

Speaker 2  (33:46)
The 9 hour. Okay. Based on the number, we should get me something like this. 

Speaker 2  (33:51)
You can use whichever approaching comfortable. 

Speaker 1  (33:58)
Okay, 1 hour for even ok. M qui, you take this 

Speaker 2  (34:05)
This guy is a base 

Speaker 1  (34:07)
Data, okay. Sorry to write. One is hot and dehydrated. 

Speaker 1  (34:15)
Okay. Further vacuum at the airport condition. Send, write it as Same, okay. 

Speaker 1  (34:44)
So we are at least 1 hour. We can. Can you give me the let's say Innovate. 

Speaker 1  (34:56)
Enumerators, enumeratal. Oh, no Kim one is satisfied. 

Speaker 1  (35:19)
If you're in I want to go to 0. The give me the most Remove nalgata. Update update the title of the camera. 

Speaker 1  (35:45)
Map here, okay. What the dictionary is here with t MI is something like that I do. 

Speaker 2  (35:56)
No, no problem, that's fine naturally. So I could also see, like, experienced on ajura in database right? Ok, what are the AI services you are used in a job. 

Speaker 1  (36:19)
The AI services right? So I have not on the Azure, but on the EW side we are moving our data to beddraw, ok and Eid in the Azure, I have used the database and adf pipelines. 

Speaker 2  (36:39)
Ok, petrols, you are used right? 

Speaker 1  (36:42)
Yeah, for the agent. 

Speaker 2  (36:45)
So what are the features here used to as part of petrols? 

Speaker 1  (36:49)
Bedrog. 

Speaker 2  (36:50)
Thank you. I think we take an example like I wanted. I want you to build a system. 

Speaker 2  (36:56)
This system will be on idbas okay. Ok. It should have a storage. 

Speaker 2  (37:06)
Stories account should have some functions. And it should also include the trigger mechanism Once it's trigger, it should trigger the other function, which should talk to the TV and get the relevant data. Hey and Should do some kind of rack information like retriever or Chunky, whatever it may be. 

Speaker 2  (37:31)
Finally, it should display in A Any website or it could also be an absorver right in relatives. We are having. Okay, tell me like how do you decide what are that different? 

Speaker 2  (37:48)
Services you want to choose as part of your base. 

Speaker 1  (37:51)
Yeah, use the lambdas, okay, S3. So once you dump the file, it will automatically trigger the lambdas, then we have can have the so based on the London if you're going to trigger the functions and just to have that we can orchestrate it also using the step functions, then yeah, these are a few things that I am going to use it for. Building the pipelines and Yeah, when? 

Speaker 1  (38:25)
Sorry. 

Speaker 2  (38:28)
Ok, hey okay, can you give me a minute? Just give me a minute, okay. 

Speaker 1  (39:19)
Think for this. 

Speaker 1  (40:18)
Ah, yes, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (40:19)
Sorry, I got some Yeah, okay. Where you 

Speaker 1  (40:29)
40AW. Yes. 

Speaker 2  (40:31)
Okay. Okay. So now like, take an example like we have a Amazon bedroom. 

Speaker 2  (40:37)
What are the different you know, like? There are other services in the Amazon bedroom also, are you aware about those? 

Speaker 1  (40:46)
No, for the agent one, it's kind of new to me some mistakes. 

Speaker 2  (40:52)
Right? Because in Amazon bedroom, we have something called knowledge manager. Okay, and we have something called flow executor. 

Speaker 2  (41:02)
Are you no, so what are the models you have used Amazon bedroom? 

Speaker 1  (41:07)
We've used the agentic one only ok. 

Speaker 2  (41:10)
No, no models, actually, the agent means that it's just a piece of code which talks to the LLM right? LLM is model. Give up by LLM provider like GPT provides an open. 

Speaker 2  (41:22)
I provides GPT mode, okay? 

Speaker 1  (41:28)
We are talking about the Gmail 

Speaker 2  (41:29)
In terms of Amazon, having For we are using Yeah, that available is. We have only the Titan models right? Some of the anthropic models. 

Speaker 2  (41:46)
Okay. I think I'm done. So do you have any questions? 

Speaker 1  (41:52)
Yeah, can you tell me about the company and the role? 

Speaker 2  (41:56)
Okay, company, you know like company kinder. You would have heard already from the HR kendral. Ok, so, you know, like previously, we were with ipm. 

Speaker 2  (42:06)
We spinned off from the ipm on 2020I think, so. Now, yeah, mostly like companies focusing more on agent kii, AI solutions as a separate vertical only we have different business. This is one of the no vertical business certificate. 

Speaker 2  (42:23)
That's very like the hiring is happening this part. So we are looking for a candidate who is good at classical Chennai. Okay, and who can solve some of the real world problems statements, what customer is looking for you know. 

Speaker 2  (42:39)
So yeah, so these are about it. Yeah. 

Speaker 1  (42:42)
Okay, yeah, I got Sir, thank you. 

Speaker 2  (42:47)
Thank you, Brother, nice, thank you to you. 

Speaker 1  (42:51)
Yeah, thank you. Bye. 
