
Speaker 1  (00:00)
And then you can start with your introduction. Yeah, my name is saluni Sharma. And based on the Bombay Hyderabad, I join Pankaj. 

Speaker 1  (00:09)
Last year, I'm working as a manager data scientist here, and before that, I was working never deloy, so I have approximately 5 years of experience working in GenAI, before that, I was working as a data engineer, and I worked on ML Jaci, multi agent architecture and all those things. So yeah that's pretty much about myself. And you can introduce yourself 

Speaker 2  (00:34)
Here, so myself prakr, by around 14 years of experience, started with the data engineering and to AIM L. So I'm working with emphasis from last 3 years, and before that, I were, you know, the mogust angle, and I hope in the healthcare domain. Also So, majorly, I have worked on the banking domain. 

Speaker 2  (01:00)
So, for Bombay Sunday, I have worked majorly for 9%. And recently, I am working for the education demand so my text tack is basically This data bricks On the Em side, I work with majorly genius agent using and the public family side. I have family is measured Then, we have chemical application, which is moving into the education domain where we have an application of the ID which is used by the student and the teachers and we have created the idiot pipelines. 

Speaker 2  (01:44)
So basically, our data is coming from the car offer to the CDC's and CDC to THE multihop architecture to the batch and the stream. And then we have the chunking and budding names. So this will we have this chat box created out of the multiple inputs, data to different formats? 

Speaker 2  (02:05)
We have chunking it down and writing it, and then we're asking the user query, I have the user is given the query based on that query. What response to them? That's one of these cases, which is an internet project. 

Speaker 2  (02:20)
Apart from that, I have bought on the agenda here using a landlorge. On the other application I have also walked on one application, which is the Agent feedback system. I have used the We are getting the transcents, and in the Delta. 

Speaker 2  (02:41)
Tva, in the Gita Greeks send that we are. We are created on several models, but was one of them. And then we are writing it with matter, not a condition That was the end of the project. 

Speaker 2  (02:55)
And Apart from that major layer work of the data breaks, vitamin flows for the tracking Denied. And with launching background But for that, I have tuned the database jobs also. The models also, and we are exposing several apais, also to the To the clients for like rajas parameters for one of them Apart from that I've got on the data engineer side. 

Speaker 2  (03:31)
I can talk about that. I've won the pace park museum on the database itself. And I walked off the on to MyGate, I also got the project there. 

Speaker 2  (03:41)
Yeah, that's pretty much. 

Speaker 1  (03:45)
That's good. Okay, prakad. This role is majorly focused on ms. 

Speaker 1  (03:49)
ISO are you comfortable with it? Yeah? So we can start with turn off your MA project. 

Speaker 1  (03:57)
You can explain me the requirement the end-to-end architecture. What was your role in that particular project? What was the models you were using, and what was the end result? 

Speaker 2  (04:09)
Yes, sure. So as I told you it was a chat got one of the applications of the chat got where we're receiving the multiple data from the multiple sources. One of them was a Kafka, and the one was a conference pages, some other internal documentation. 

Speaker 2  (04:29)
Set it down to the To the cockcape, and then we have the deposit. As the CDC species captured the change at a capture, and then we are the batch structure and the steaming streaming data that is coming up into the Earth 3 layer The streets PRPR having the one of the idiots jobs that is pulling off the data from the sk. It's a trigger past that we have completed during the A. 

Speaker 2  (04:57)
D. L. Yes. 

Speaker 2  (04:59)
That is, once we receive the data. We trigger the ideal job and to that pipeline. We receive the data to the database Delta a in the general table. 

Speaker 2  (05:10)
So the documentation that we have the chunking layer in the Chunky layer. We have configured the text fund having sentence aware Chunky with the separators were provided like Newland I'm converting the large document large sentence to the smaller paragraph for paracent. That we have had it, and then we have the ambedding layer for the. 

Speaker 2  (05:40)
Metding layers, we have. We are using the bleaching models that's one of the things. And once we have done, I'm getting there is ready, because we are, we have to make sure that there should not be drift in the data. 

Speaker 2  (05:54)
Along with t Drift in the feature as well. Then, the user can query user the user query. We are embedding that data, and then we're fighting the top relevant data using the top K we were using the encoders at the cross encoder growth by encoding the cross encoder growth, because the data was huge. 

Speaker 2  (06:17)
And with that top kick, we were finding the right thing. Okay, and then we're sending the data to the user so that you can see the relevant answer. And there are several issues were there, as we are exposing. 

Speaker 2  (06:32)
The different KPIS like, answer as well. 

Speaker 1  (06:35)
So this to be a Genia project, was it a ML project? 

Speaker 2  (06:39)
No, it was not annoyed project. 

Speaker 1  (06:41)
Yeah, I want you to know about some ML project that you have done. 

Speaker 2  (06:46)
I did it a long time back. On the other side we were at the edl. The ED side I can talk about the so the requirement was that we have a front office and from the front office we were getting. 

Speaker 2  (07:02)
We were confirming the confirming the traits and from that trade we are generating the adifs of documentation so that documentation we need to verify whether it's genuine or not. Okay, there are several I mean, we've used NLP analytical liberal for checking the relevance of the data using limitation and the stemming also, we have removed the stockford subject, and we have come up with the token basically, and then we are checking it with the actual actual data. So based on that, we have given several charts several dashboards. 

Speaker 2  (07:46)
That was the project. 

Speaker 1  (07:49)
Okay, what is the difference between lambertisation and stamming? 

Speaker 2  (07:53)
Yeah, so in the stemming, we were removing the I Hg and the other objectives And the This is what the stamina limitation is that we are out of those goods. We are giving the journalised war. Let's say the better is good. 

Speaker 2  (08:23)
That's the librarian. 

Speaker 1  (08:29)
So, uh, you did data pre processing and you created dashboards on top of it. Uh, did you use any models also? 

Speaker 2  (08:37)
Always, we have used the multiple models. We were using the logistic. Regressions, we have T FI DF for 2 well. 

Speaker 2  (08:45)
Do you think all those things are going to be values for the website? And then we will using the This is the red forest model. We have majorly used 

Speaker 1  (09:01)
Logistic regression. 

Speaker 2  (09:03)
Hey, initially, we have started with the legislation because we have already 2 conditions binary conditions. Yes, or no for metro north. So, but then we Jeth word, what is the data? 

Speaker 2  (09:16)
And what is the test under test and the train accuracy of the precision areas. So all those we have checked, let me switch to the random forest. Because of the It was not coming, but the accuracy was not up to the mark. 

Speaker 1  (09:34)
So what was Yeah, how's your data labelled? Like, what was your Y variable? And what were your egg? 

Speaker 2  (09:43)
Yay, it was a chicken supervised data because we were sending a sample gear to the airb team to verify whether the predicted data that generates for the model is correct or not. So they were labelling it on, and then we were receiving that data about that data, we are doing the model. 

Speaker 1  (10:04)
Do they target enable, in this case, what were you finding out? 

Speaker 2  (10:08)
Yeah, so the target variable was assistant method condition with the different Have different classes? They have different categorization. They have done okay, I don't remember the exact name. 

Speaker 2  (10:23)
Basically you were checking the matter of a tradition to together. Okay? 

Speaker 1  (10:27)
Okay, it's okay, but what were the metrics you were using to evaluate? 

Speaker 2  (10:36)
So there were several Kale divergence. We have AKPI is I've been accuracy recall. These are the specificity, and then we have the I mean, I can recall it with these things only. 

Speaker 1  (11:07)
Can you tell me when do you use accuracy? And when do you use precision or when do you use recall? 

Speaker 2  (11:14)
Are you so accuracy, please majorly tells us what the model actually is accurate enough to or not. The name tells, but it's not the sufficient matter to validate the data, then we move to the precision and then end the recall. The precision is really checking the true positive rate, and then the recall is basically checking the I mean false negative. 

Speaker 2  (11:43)
So in case if the false negative is low, that means our equal value will be high. Okay. And then yeah, that's that's actually the question of the recall. 

Speaker 2  (11:55)
And similarly for the recession is the checking, the False positive. Okay. 

Speaker 1  (12:08)
Okay, so what's this project in production or it was abused? In which environment which environment you are using 

Speaker 2  (12:22)
It was in the CAC D The CST have written a lot of stages there for checking the feature testing and everything and then deploy there. 

Speaker 1  (12:40)
Are you using any cloud? 

Speaker 2  (12:45)
I don't think we're deploying anything at the cloud we were using. For this week, we're not using that 

Speaker 1  (12:55)
So you trained logistic regression, and then you train random forest right? Okay, how much data did you use to train the models? 

Speaker 2  (13:03)
Sorry, Kamal. 

Speaker 1  (13:05)
How much data? What was the volume of data that you used to train your models? 

Speaker 2  (13:13)
Ok, volume of data. And it wasn't really I mean. It is around in the GB. 

Speaker 2  (13:28)
Who's gotten up in the down to the training test? 

Speaker 1  (13:34)
Okay, how much time did it took to train the models? 

Speaker 2  (13:38)
She took around for or 2 hours. Put it to train the model. We reduced our time over time. 

Speaker 2  (13:49)
Thank you. 

Speaker 1  (13:53)
Uh, okay. So can you tell me how does render forest works? 

Speaker 2  (13:58)
Yeah, so it works on the principle of the Ensemble method or the what you say bootstrapping and the batting, so what happens is, it creates that chase in parallel with all the features. There is a features red members. They're in the Redmond forest. 

Speaker 2  (14:20)
It will pick those particular features and treat a drew out of it. Then, paddle pedal treats, and then it will create a boating through the voting mechanism itself, whether the what is the highest majority of the answer, and then it will return that so basically inside the turn off forest. Usually check the Guinea purity and the this Information gains or information gain, and also its check the randomness randomness variances, so there's a formula right using that number of trees were going to be increased, they there 2 parts of the Williams, one is the irreducible, and the other part is the reducible. 

Speaker 2  (15:09)
So the reducible part is the number of trees will be high. That means the variance could be low. So that's how we have to create. 

Speaker 2  (15:18)
We have to set those parameters parameters in the sense of the number of estimators, okay, that will be the number of trees that we get clear and the lead how many leagues that we want to sample leaves that you want to create. So all those things we need to find to do this Yeah, I mean, these are things. And also 3 of the random forest has the feature feature selection. 

Speaker 2  (15:47)
Also explain ratio through all those things. I've worked on that and long-term. 

Speaker 1  (15:56)
So, uh I want to train my random forest model. Okay, I provide it a 10000 rose. Okay, now how does it internally work? 

Speaker 1  (16:05)
Suppose I have given number of estimators is 5, so will it pass all the 10000 rows to all 5 models, or will it divide and then pass? And if it divide, how does it divide the data? 

Speaker 2  (16:19)
Um, okay. So you're passing 1000 data to the random forest. Right, so random forest, I think it works on the column. 

Speaker 2  (16:27)
Call it will pick the feature basability, pick the features, and then if we create a 3 basable logic so 1000 data will come after the Tree of those trees, which will go to create the No, there's an option, I think, in the random forest, those we can Of the number of data that you wanted to initially. It will start like it will check the antropy. And crop, you of the parent and on topy of the Child is the concept of the this, I am talking about the information game that we do to create, and the higher the gain, the best prediction it will go to gain. 

Speaker 2  (17:14)
So I mean, the 1000 will be divided into the number of Rose that we have given the random forest so first will take 10 other people to pick them and based on that, it will cut the entropy. I'm sorry, Guinea and the information gain, and then it will come up with the answer, and then it will do the aggregation of those answer and then quickly 

Speaker 1  (17:40)
Okay, got it. Have you worked with any image models also? 

Speaker 2  (17:44)
ISI worked with the C? N. N. 

Speaker 1  (17:52)
Okay, and what all vector did, please? Have you worked? 

Speaker 2  (17:56)
Yeah, I've got it 55.4°. I pay exercise for the local and promoting measurement. 

Speaker 1  (18:09)
How good year will python? 

Speaker 2  (18:12)
I'm using it for last day later seats on day. 

Speaker 1  (18:16)
They'll do a small pipeline exercise. You can share your screen and open any online python net 

Speaker 1  (18:44)
You can paste it. I've shared one string. You have to paste it. 

Speaker 1  (18:53)
So this is a string. You have to return each character with its respective card. He is coming twice, so you have to return a 2 and B is coming twice, so B3 like that. 

Speaker 2  (19:09)
Representing the correct 

Speaker 1  (19:12)
Yes You can't use any predefined products. 

Speaker 2  (19:52)
You can't use the map also. 

Speaker 1  (20:02)
You can create your own dictionary. 

Speaker 1  (21:55)
Can you freak the 

Speaker 1  (22:22)
You can stop sharing Okay, I am good with all my questions. Do you have any questions for 

Speaker 2  (22:33)
They can tell you about the project on the role 

Speaker 1  (22:37)
Okay, so this is the event specific requirement, and they are building surveillance detection models, so that's what I know. And And this is for financial domain. Yeah, so you'll be leading AN team with the ML Engineers. 

Speaker 1  (22:56)
Yeah, that's what I know about it. So I don't have much 
