"Dhariwal, Priyarshi" <priyarshi.dhariwal@capgemini.com>
Sudhakar Nujiveeti <sudhakar.nujiveeti@valuelabs.com>
Speaker 1  (00:00)
We're working as a lead there. But here I'm working as a individual contributor. And majorly higher work with the database of like adf pipelines, majorly and I worked on the onpromised side as well, and then with the EWS I have worked with the lot of modules like step functions, lamdas, okay and your S t's on the issue side have worked with adfs pipeline database on database. 

Speaker 1  (00:30)
I have work with the data pipeline ML flows. Okay, and then your Job for workflows, apart from that, I have worked on multi hop architecture, which is injecting the data to the bronze silver and golden layer. And on the GenAI side I have worked on mostly chatbots is in the rap pipelines I have built-in the pipelines. 

Speaker 1  (00:53)
Uh designed as well, along with that, I have worked with the um one application which give the feedback of the agents who were there on the call. So we have that classification model for met and not met criteria. And also I have worked on evaluating these models, creating the multiple matrices out of it like K divergence, psi, okay, error rate hallucination rate relevance rate, precision accuracy recall all those things and showing them in the dashboard and also we are generating the report every day to check the model deafness in our application. 

Speaker 1  (01:34)
Yeah, these are the couple of things that I would want. 

Speaker 2  (01:39)
Yeah, good. So among that, what are your day-to-day activities for this? 

Speaker 1  (01:46)
Okay yeah, so my day-to-day activities getting the requirement from the product owners, and then we get the epic basically, and then I create a documentation around it. And once documented then I work on those implementations, or maybe the team can do that. So majorly right now, doing, but mostly in their development part, only 

Speaker 2  (02:11)
Wow, okay, so how would you rate yourself? 

Speaker 1  (02:17)
Paisal gram varg around forensic or more than 4 

Speaker 2  (02:21)
Ok, ok, yeah, good. So yeah, so this is your custom. Try. 

Speaker 1  (02:28)
Yeah, first. 

Speaker 2  (02:30)
Okay, so then I will go with the basics questions for price for as well as the python. Okay. So after that, the next one, you will be getting more difficult. 

Speaker 1  (02:42)
Look at the capture. 

Speaker 2  (02:45)
Okay, so what do you optimise s**** Pop jobs? 

Speaker 1  (02:50)
After a month optimise, your 

Speaker 2  (02:53)
Roh close pork job. 

Speaker 1  (02:55)
Obviously close party. So there are two things that I'll consider first. Is it a data issue or a cluster issue. 

Speaker 1  (03:02)
So on the cluster issue I'll check whether the jobs are weight in the waiting stage or in the running stage if they're in waiting seat, that means it's a cluster issue. So I'll try to tune that cluster. First and in the tuning, I'll make sure that they have this sufficient memory executors course basically and those things I'll try to withhit and try, I'll try to tune them. 

Speaker 1  (03:22)
And if it's a data issue that I can see in the dabs, so in the dads, if they're more shuffling happening, okay, or what kind of join they're using, so majorly, if there is a possibility to add the broadcast joint, I can do that. Depending on the size of the table, okay, keeping ideally, we keep it as 10 to 20 MB of size of the data, who broadcast it so that the worker not have sufficiently default. Silica, mine, okay. 

Speaker 2  (03:54)
Ok, so how do handle that data scheme? 

Speaker 1  (03:58)
Yeah, so for the data squeness, there are 2 is either. We can go for the salty or we can turn on the aqe and the aqi we have to set some parameters like skewjoin and the fractions of the skewers, all those things, and the coal is also so these parameters we can tune it, and then we can reduce some of the squares from the data. 

Speaker 2  (04:26)
So what will pass if the jobs are out of memory in 

Speaker 1  (04:32)
Yeah, so out of memory. If it is coming on the driver side, I'll make sure that I'm not 

Speaker 2  (04:38)
Story sorry, sorry, sorry, Prakar voice is breaking. 

Speaker 1  (04:43)
Is it? Is it fine now? 

Speaker 2  (04:44)
Voice voice breaking I guess still I think. 

Speaker 1  (04:50)
Thank you. Let me switch my network. Let me switch my network. 

Speaker 1  (04:56)
Is it fine now? Hello, is it fine now? Hello, yeah, is it fine now? 

Speaker 2  (05:08)
Yeah, much. 

Speaker 1  (05:09)
Should I know I switched on the different network? 

Speaker 2  (05:13)
Ok, ok, fine? Ye? 

Speaker 1  (05:16)
So where I was okay squeweness, right? So I'll handle the squunes based on the salting, or maybe I can turn on the aqi on the aqi. In the EQ, you have to specify the several parameters like xunness joints, ok, is equal to true, and then we can tune it. 

Speaker 1  (05:35)
The Coles is equal to true and other parameters like the fractions also squeeze fraction number of partitions. So all those things. If we specify them, we can tune that skinness in the data. 

Speaker 1  (05:47)
Ok, also, we 

Speaker 2  (05:49)
So yeah, so how do you avoid that out of the memory error? 

Speaker 1  (05:56)
Yeah, so I can see whether it's coming in the driver. Is it causing in the driver memory, or is it causing all the worker memory? So on the driver memory, I'll check. 

Speaker 1  (06:06)
I'm not accumulating or fetching all the data into the driver. Okay. Using the collect method or anything using a distinct keyword so if those things have been happening, I will try to avoid those in the court side as well. 

Speaker 1  (06:19)
And if it is happening on the worker side, then I have to tune the memory, okay, giving the accurate or enough executors to with the exact memory, to have that processing power for that particular data. Okay so how I will do it? I will specify using the Fine-tuning using the multiple hidden trial error like giving some memory to the executive's memory. 

Speaker 1  (06:47)
Then, with the course. And then I'll try to keep executive memories a executive number of executors keeping it as 5 in the ideally, and if it is a based on that, I tune that keeping the less executed or the maximum executive based on the tune. 

Speaker 2  (07:06)
Ok, so Yeah, so for it, the job run time is doubled. Okay? So there is no code has been changed. 

Speaker 2  (07:16)
So what do you think we will be taking 

Speaker 1  (07:21)
Yeah, there, if there is no court change happened, and suddenly the spike has been seen on the job side. So in that case, okay, there's no then there might be the cluster issue because the job is taking. Something which is maybe there are some issue with the resources they are not getting the enough resources. 

Speaker 1  (07:48)
Maybe something there is a bottle, lack. Okay, so that I'll check, maybe so I'll try to use that. 

Speaker 2  (07:57)
Where to check the data volumes also 

Speaker 1  (07:59)
Yeah, data warning houses spikes. Yeah, go and good. Yeah, so I'll check. 

Speaker 2  (08:10)
So how do you validate the migrated? Data. 

Speaker 1  (08:15)
How will I validate the migrated data? Yes Can you elaborate more on Either it is the error sequel data 

Speaker 2  (08:27)
Thank you. So yeah, so what are the things you have just used to get the data from migrated from the bicepa for the transformation? So what are the conditions you are using? 

Speaker 2  (08:43)
I mean, so you are using some rocons or checksoms or so you have to validate the sample comparisons from the data right? Yeah, so that's what 

Speaker 1  (08:55)
Okay. So for the migrating thing like if we are migrating from, let's say high table to the Delta table. So in that case, first initial check, we do the counts count, check the number of columns, okay, and these are 2 specific things. 

Speaker 1  (09:11)
And then we check the data. Also okay, so what is expected and whatever was there in the source and then on the relative table? Is it all same or not? 

Speaker 1  (09:21)
These are the basic validation, but looking at the data, specifically, we have to change our matrices. Also, if it's a sequel data, it's a file data. If it's a file you project the check some because while transforming it, the file should not be changed. 

Speaker 1  (09:40)
Okay, so keeping that in mind these are the things that I can recall it. But there are multiple parameters also 

Speaker 2  (09:57)
So What are the differences between with the multitreating and multiprocessing? 

Speaker 1  (10:04)
Ok, multitreading is basically executing one task or paralysing the task among the different threats. Let's say if we have One task to let's take an example of the sperm right in the distribution. Y so let's say if I asked the spark to I mean, give me the sum of those numbers. 

Speaker 1  (10:32)
So what is wide number of files for each file? It will go into process that may be a different threat. Will be going to execute on that. 

Speaker 1  (10:38)
And then it will combine the data and you may be the result. That's something is ready, then follow the multi processing. It's a work processor which is doing all the jobs. 

Speaker 1  (10:48)
Okay, and then giving the output 

Speaker 2  (10:54)
UK the same? How do you optimise the code pitan code performance? 

Speaker 1  (11:04)
How will I optimise the python code performance? 

Speaker 2  (11:16)
So consequenting the Data Structures also, you have to check the generator things from the outside. 

Speaker 1  (11:28)
Ok, sorry, I didn't get that question. Sorry talking about the python improvement. Are you talking about the processing time we have to litency time? 

Speaker 1  (11:37)
We have to increase Hamein bhi, if there is some code fixture that we need to do. Or maybe something else If you can specify that I cannot accord. 

Speaker 2  (11:53)
Okay, so the same high wheel comes with again with the iceberg. So The difference between the between that persisted memory only and memory and disc 

Speaker 1  (12:06)
Membrane. So okay, if you're persisting the memory only which is a cache only that is keeping all the into the ramp, okay. So that is needed for the small set of data. 

Speaker 1  (12:19)
But if we have a large data set for the multiple completion, if we are doing transformation, then that case what it will do is if it is not able to store that data into the memory, it will use a disc also in the underlying disc. So it will go into switch between between the disc and the memory to fetch that data and to the competition. So there's a Mon memory architecture there storage and the executive memory. 

Speaker 1  (12:47)
So we can switch switch that I mean, the spark automatically switch the data between the storage and the executive, keeping them money. Story has been. 

Speaker 2  (12:58)
Okay, for the final one, don't change. So why we have to choose the per cube, portfolio over the csv. 

Speaker 1  (13:08)
So required to do we use 

Speaker 2  (13:12)
Why pocket? Referred to over Ch.B. 

Speaker 1  (13:16)
Pi pi spark is preferred over CS. V. 

Speaker 2  (13:19)
Yes, yes. 

Speaker 1  (13:21)
Baais park truffon cswey. I'm a cswey. Is a file format and price park is a competition engineering. 

Speaker 1  (13:28)
So these days. 

Speaker 2  (13:30)
Not only the spicy foods are cute. 

Speaker 1  (13:32)
Bark file okay. Ok, CS V is kind of very bulky in the bulky. In the sense they have, it's stored in the format of row and column file structure but the park is stored at the as in the form of column, okay, having that matter data. 

Speaker 1  (13:53)
So which is very fast for the aggregation aggregating. Uh, the results so that why we use a parking in the data bricks by default. It use a park only for keeping their files. 

Speaker 1  (14:08)
Along with that, they are other advantages like we can have the Delta changes also easily captured in the market instead of the ESV. Sorry, these are the few differences that I can recall. 

Speaker 2  (14:24)
Yeah, Hoke. Yeah, I just yeah, completed the things from my Do you think it's from global 

Speaker 1  (14:33)
Can you tell me about the project and Hi. 

Speaker 2  (14:39)
Yes, so that will be discussed with you. Sudden, okay so yeah, because I am also the same project. Which you joined, okay, so better? 

Speaker 2  (14:53)
We will get the information from the Sudha. Once you got selected for this level of doctor. 

Speaker 1  (15:03)
Understood here. 

Speaker 2  (15:04)
Yeah, but overall, you are good. 

Speaker 1  (15:06)
Ok, thank you. 

Speaker 2  (15:12)
Yeah, thanks. 
