"H, Maulika" <maulika.h@capgemini.com>

This content was generated by AI


Speaker 1  (00:00)
So that's what it's like in capital meaning. So we're actually focusing on the data breaks and Microsoft project and we work across the globe. I'm working at an architect. 

Speaker 1  (00:12)
With that, I just wanted to get it through it. Then we'll start this discussion. So what your total experience 

Speaker 2  (00:21)
Metro technologies 14 years, but with detail engineering, around 8 plus a year. 

Speaker 1  (00:29)
Data engineer, Raj data engine. 

Speaker 2  (00:31)
Rajat engineer around take plus 

Speaker 1  (00:36)
Okay, do you have any said I joined? How many? Sorry, 10 years 10 years Currently, you are based out on which look 

Speaker 2  (00:51)
Noida. 

Speaker 1  (00:54)
Ok, good. So with that, can you introduce your help? And what's your role and responsibility? 

Speaker 2  (01:04)
So Mysore prakher IR on 40 years of experience working with the emphasis correctly from last year before there. I was meeting Immediately started with data engineering Currently, I'm working with the AI or superior using the AI also The technical term vacuum is a data breaks His problems with the US side as well with S3 at candles. These are the service that I do. 

Speaker 2  (01:41)
And apart from that, currently working on the application, which is more into the educational domain, but overall, my experiences in banking domain Spurt application is Used by the teachers and the students and it's deployed within the state of us and users curriculum. Used by both teacher and student and architecture is like the data that we get from the Casta craft that we have multiple batches at streaming Jobs driving. In add it to the night, please shift on ESG to ST with Canada and leather stores. 

Speaker 2  (02:24)
Can we move the data, transform that data, and then we have government? One of the when we have this defined data, send it to the Look at an export I've got a lot of fun application, which is linked to the chat box, internal organisation Chatbot. Where's the birthday I'm going to show you the apps. 

Speaker 2  (02:42)
There's a Chunky on the wedding players I fight in some of the racks, there will be security layer and guarding prompt engineering. Also, yeah, that's pretty good for myself. 

Speaker 1  (02:57)
If you don't mind, can you share your skin very, you can roll this architecture like, then we'll start the discussion. 

Speaker 2  (03:23)
To start with the counter Then, we agree. Captured in the 3 disease 

Speaker 1  (03:33)
You, can you, can you open this ppt guide like You can create in PPT so it will be egical, so major 

Speaker 2  (03:45)
EPT. Part money. I don't think B.P Twill work in this one. 

Speaker 1  (03:53)
Just see if you have PowerPoint used Our Toronto, are you? 

Speaker 2  (04:04)
Yeah, I have just 

Speaker 1  (04:18)
Just try to focus on using this actual strategy in case if you're comfortable in a zone because you are working on. Mostly you are working in a choice. So what are the services You are using one scenario, so even you can prove that. 

Speaker 1  (04:36)
So think in this way you are deploying one of this new project, okay? And it's the green field solution, so client text anything to issue client is funny taken. They are facing 2 challenges. 

Speaker 1  (04:49)
One is related to data quality. Because the data from multiple vectors and data is not second. They are not getting data on time for a reporting, so they have multiple system drp. 

Speaker 1  (05:04)
They have Adi, they have sharepoint some unstructured data like images and files, J files. They have using the indologenous system right now we need to come up with and to end. I mean, so data solution, they are looking the automated way we need to create the automated pipelines. 

Speaker 1  (05:23)
It should support increment and overload the they wanted to store last 5 year. Any historical data 

Speaker 2  (05:32)
So last 5 feet 

Speaker 1  (05:35)
Yeah, they will provide, like maybe 200 data quality 2. We need to implement those data quality route, so these data quality rules will be applied on multiple columns. Same rules may be applied on multiple tables and multiple, so our solutions will be reusable. 

Speaker 1  (05:52)
They're looking acid type 2 solution in President and final finally, for reporting, we are looking some power pay reports. They have something in mind. In future they will use some Generative AI or ability, I mean, data science. 

Speaker 1  (06:12)
So that's the I mean to end. That's the high level requirement and two things. When we are perpending any solution, it should be reasonable. 

Speaker 1  (06:22)
We need to create configures based framework. Okay? And I think requirement, you need to capture 

Speaker 2  (06:36)
Yeah, sure, so the deposit that I'm going to do is one is the data volume. How many tailors that we need to create? 

Speaker 1  (06:48)
Yeah, sorry, before that one more point. They are not interested, because they are mostly luge, only just for your so they are not interested to use any other services so we need to focus. I mean, mostly on the database. 

Speaker 2  (07:04)
Okay, hear me, I just thinking of the edfs, and we'll see if we can do the incremental order depending on the size of the file. And the tables that we have, so I'll go with this approach. If the volume is high. 

Speaker 2  (07:19)
Okay. 

Speaker 1  (07:19)
The way we first you draw this one, then you can explain. So in that way it will be easy right for you. 

Speaker 2  (07:32)
I've not used. I'm not comfortably using this book. Is there any way I can draw something here? 

Speaker 1  (07:40)
Suitch, 2 riology, in which tool you are comfortable. Put through this diagram for example, you know, you need to work on this architecture. Don't play Studio. 

Speaker 2  (07:52)
I mean, I just draw it on the simple paint. Okay? Then 

Speaker 1  (08:00)
Normally so if you need to show this slide right? Based on your experience, so how you're doing, you are creating in bank. And you're saying 

Speaker 2  (08:09)
I just live, but the went, I mean to the architecture, or something. When the PBT we usually great for the prompt You just give the instruction I can create that 

Speaker 1  (08:32)
The prompt will give this very basic level credit. You need to customise, you need to create correct, so 

Speaker 2  (08:59)
Can I draw it here? 

Speaker 2  (09:19)
So let's say I have So I'll so you want me to check for the their different files right? Different file formats, we are receiving correct. 

Speaker 1  (09:35)
Got different file, but we have different sources to we have returns like we have E and P we have API, we have Jason file, we have some images or video. It's your point. 

Speaker 2  (09:47)
I'm assuming that we have only one location. Let's say 

Speaker 1  (09:52)
Oh, J is one thing for that so being an architecture you will not assume, right, so you will be sure because when you are discussing the client think this way I am your client. So now you should be like, 100%. Sure, whatever you are explaining, correct, otherwise you will get some counterpost correct on client. 

Speaker 2  (10:14)
Okay. 

Speaker 1  (10:15)
So you used to be sure, right? Whatever I mean, ideally you are suggesting you should be sure, okay, your 100% sure why you are having properly resources, no otherwise. 

Speaker 2  (10:25)
There are multiple systems like S3. It can be from 

Speaker 1  (10:29)
Here, you can ask if you have any questions in the scenario you can ask, okay, like a clarification. Definitely, I will get, but once you are clear like you got the requirement, then you should be sure, okay. 

Speaker 2  (10:41)
Thank you. Let me think of that. So is journey, is there any other system that we are communicating with, like mysteries or external locations or just 

Speaker 1  (10:54)
So, as of now, whatever resources might spend, like 560 source system, those are sources, but in future it could be because our solutions should be scalable, right? 

Speaker 2  (11:05)
Yeah, let me expand this one. And then I'll Go to the other previous And tell me, happy Instead of bronze, their silver layer condom near multical systems share 

Speaker 2  (11:52)
Okay, so I'll first check the file size. Okay, and then I'll look for whether we can go for incremental or the full load. If it is incremental, I'll make sure my bronze data will go to have the all the history and historical data. 

Speaker 2  (12:10)
So 

Speaker 1  (12:10)
Complete you completed the diagram or still you will extend dimension. Okay, let me completely, yeah, first complete then. 

Speaker 2  (12:23)
The bronze. 

Speaker 2  (15:37)
555. 

Speaker 2  (15:51)
Did there is 2 box? 

Speaker 1  (17:45)
So what are this? Okay, let's start with the discussion here. So what are these integration pattern? 

Speaker 1  (17:51)
You use when you are reading the data from files. But they just managed patterns are available. 

Speaker 2  (18:00)
Yeah, I've been just patterns are literally coming from the car data coming from the Kafka. From some radius location, actually location. These are a file system. 

Speaker 2  (18:11)
I mean, ingestion source system. Basically, let me receive the data from And those data for one of the pipeline we for the incremental load, we just dump all the data to the bronze. Depending on which taken, you want to update the data. 

Speaker 2  (18:31)
So for that particular source system, we just there will be multiple pipelines. So for one of the pipeline, we just jump the data to the bronze layer, appending all the data, historical data, and then we have this primary keyword, column matter data, all those things, please store it okay in the DPS on and the debates itself. And from there, we get up, what are the primary key? 

Speaker 2  (18:58)
What is the instrumental column that we have? And the latest data, we keep it in the silver 

Speaker 1  (19:05)
So I'm sorry one question I am when you are joining. Sorry, when you are adjusting data profile system about API ospoint oriented, there are many way we have manage. Identity or service principle. 

Speaker 1  (19:18)
So which pattern do you like in connection? 

Speaker 2  (19:23)
Okay, so in the idiot pipeline, we create the Datasets, okay, uh, for connecting with the stories or internally utils locations. So all those things will give the confirmation service integration disabled 

Speaker 1  (19:39)
What are the service integration are available? 

Speaker 2  (19:42)
Lady, F there are multiple levels the file systems when your Internal ADF S location. So these three basically will Have created the data set for it for them. I'm not aware the other did you 

Speaker 1  (20:03)
Did you work on any framework? Because you already, you know, using the pice park and python, can you explain me how to create this injection or transformation data quality framework in biassing classes and councils? 

Speaker 2  (20:20)
Are you talking about the spice park? How we are connecting with the other resources or something 

Speaker 1  (20:27)
Yeah, so for example, you need to bring the data from multiple source system. You are using the urge of data place and our radiables database line, so you will write some transformation or exist or data quality. So in pice park or python, so how you will create what's the approach? 

Speaker 1  (20:46)
You will also 

Speaker 2  (20:48)
Jamie, their multiple, either. You can use the auto cloud. For injecting the data 

Speaker 1  (20:54)
Improvement, but he photograph 

Speaker 2  (20:56)
Auto cloud is basically your format in the data mix where you can incre. It can give the notification whenever the file arrives. And it will go into inject it and it will go into the transformation that notebook you have to specify at format is cloud 5 okay, the location check point once the file is there in the location, it will automatically come in the database and then we can do the transformation. 

Speaker 2  (21:26)
Okay, where can we see my handling? Are all those things we can as part of the configurations? 

Speaker 1  (21:32)
Can you give me one ceremony? 

Speaker 2  (21:36)
Yeah, I mean, let's say if my source table has, let's say 10 columns, and suddenly 11 column comes and but in the target there is only 10 columns, so there are options that we can do one is that if you want to implement that column without breaking the pipeline. Therefore, actually, and whether we want to skip that new column, whether we want to break the pipeline. Okay, when we have the add new column, something like that, there are other 

Speaker 1  (22:06)
Should you get, did you get a chance to work on these classes at hongsan in ice park and python? 

Speaker 2  (22:13)
Yeah, I mean, I'm working on the screen. 

Speaker 1  (22:15)
Give me one scenario. Radio implemented this classes and functions 

Speaker 2  (22:20)
Where I will be 20 classes and functions. What is that 

Speaker 1  (22:25)
So you will just now. You mention that you are using red classes and function and price packet. 

Speaker 2  (22:30)
I'm in the library. Sorry, I was talking about the library. 

Speaker 1  (22:36)
Yeah, so give me a scenario. So you need to create a inflation framework and transportation framework or data quality framework. So now this framework unique to build in spiceman, how you'll build this one. 

Speaker 2  (22:48)
Yeah, I mean business schemes, right? I will make sure that my target and source column are converting those schemas. If there is a string, if it is back at it and a Levi's need the string, I need to write a custom function to transvert that data type from Walkup system. 

Speaker 2  (23:10)
Is this that work you're looking for asking for something else? 

Speaker 1  (23:14)
Yeah, I would be end-to-end because there are a lot of other like you need to connect from source system, then you need to do some quality, check. You need to transcing the data, right? So how actually overall your process will work. 

Speaker 2  (23:28)
Yam is the notification notifications notebook itself. We have to specify while connecting it with the source system, we have to specify what source system we have. If it is faster, then we have to specify formal craft card, or maybe if we are getting a party file, okay, all those things we need to specify and then Cool once we have the 

Speaker 1  (23:52)
Ayurveda data awareness model you use based on your experience. 

Speaker 2  (23:57)
I'll work with this park file overseas. Okay, these are the majority we are using it. 

Speaker 1  (24:05)
So we have enorm and Kimber approach right in data modelling. Sorry, so we have enorment Kimble. Data modelling correct, so can you explain me you did not 

Speaker 2  (24:20)
I didn't open. I 

Speaker 1  (24:21)
But the maximum, but the maximum volume you processed, based on your experience over a large project. 

Speaker 2  (24:29)
Maximum volume it is around Rs. 3, the count that we usually receive in billion billions, okay, one billion of data size. I am thinking it's around will be 500 GB or maybe more than that not TV. 

Speaker 1  (24:47)
And what are the source system we already explored? 

Speaker 2  (24:50)
Show systems, we have used ADB 2's dB CTC dB 2. Then, we are working with yes a DLS and yeah, these three major 

Speaker 1  (25:04)
Are you serving notice filter or your immediate available? 

Speaker 2  (25:07)
Games have been notice period But it Silikram. 

Speaker 1  (25:14)
Your last working day. 

Speaker 2  (25:15)
Yeah, it's in September 7th of September. 

Speaker 1  (25:20)
11, September. Okay, so Prakash, I have done I noted your skill set. So HR wins. 

Speaker 1  (25:30)
I mean, connect with you for our next step before closing. I just wanted to check. Do you have any questions for me or you are good? 

Speaker 2  (25:39)
Can you give me the feedback? Also, I'm not able to convey what I was wanted to look. 

Speaker 1  (25:45)
No, I think actually freedom. You'll get from H. There are a lot of parameters, right? 

Speaker 1  (25:52)
But in general, so what I'll suggest wherever you are working. So just try to get hands-on, experience out there in 5 price park python, go data fix and being a data architect, at least you should be comfortable whatever you are proposing that solution even though small solutions, whatever solution you are creating so if you are discussing with client so you should be comfortable and you should be sure okay, why I am proposing this one client will ask, for example, you are saying Kafka. Definitely question will come, why Kafka no? 

Speaker 1  (26:28)
What are the other services available like? Admi some other services are available Okay, thank you. Anything else any other question here? 

Speaker 1  (26:39)
No thanks for you. Okay, but thanks for your time and have a good day. 
