shipra.singhal@coforge.com

Speaker 1  (00:01)
This can do a little talk about Um, um, I'm a project which I have worked on. So I have run 14 years of experience in data and engineering, and the IMF I've worked on building the RAG, please Chatbot system and agents. In chatbots. 

Speaker 1  (00:20)
I have built-in the end 2 and pipeline. Changing a bedding pipeline using a pipe cone, reduce manual search efforts by 60%. Okay, top retrieval and prompt engineering cane air risk vector. 

Speaker 1  (00:37)
Okay, I don't know how to do the key nearest vector. And in an agent, I have worked on the process Transcript used for Birth for cleaning, okay, alarm for scoring evaluate thing across multiple K. P. 

Speaker 1  (00:59)
I's. There are multiple KP I's Kr divergence. Okay, and other things I don't know. 

Speaker 1  (01:08)
I love for scoring evolution across multiple KPI is okay ER C at CL acuracy relevance, contact utilization hallucination. Latency cost and similarity. Okay, tools I have used is the Lengthy glansmith weighed and biased custom dashboard regas deep Eventually, evaluation tour. 

Speaker 1  (01:40)
Tpis are dragas, kpis, okay, relevance, fatefulness, answer relevance, contact recession. So write pipeline or no Junkin, I know tokimization also is split. Text to nation has a split text monitoration, the normal text. 

Speaker 1  (01:58)
I'm betting model is text to vector okay? Set a dividend extra data switch optimized for work research. Ian and search, I don't know filtering prediction drag. 

Speaker 1  (02:14)
As API is deployed in AWS at cashing logging, more Trammel flows. Okay, the ICD I can start involved on And chunking types are the correct splitter? Okay, recursive text letter. 

Speaker 1  (02:34)
Token splitter. Cindy's semantic chunking. And document is structured based. 

Speaker 1  (02:41)
Okay, I don't know any examples. Reranking. After a traverse. 

Speaker 1  (02:49)
A reranking is a buying code or the cross and coder BM point is the hybrid search using the hybrid search dance and is partnering. BM25 versus T of I DFT of I df 3 importance, is it going to frequency of the reality? BM25 is improvement over the T FI D for length compilation, suspension control Transformer architecture is yeah, you know that you gave me attention and score SoftBank function, okay, and to V. 

Speaker 1  (03:23)
Each word look at each other. Party heads are I'm 2 words, I mean, the words are divided to the multiplied, then QK weahed window. Feed forward is linear gelu. 

Speaker 1  (03:38)
A linear function that we have used Layer bird is large base and large base is 12 layer, and large is 24 layer. Biodiversity hyperparameter, hyperparametter in everyone, which is temperature top K top P Top tier, I don't know, ok, okay? Max token. 

Speaker 1  (04:06)
All precise random forests are now reserved bagging of gas camera aggregation of gas variance, oga from logarier, I know Problem is in the agent feedback system is we have to collect the Transcript clean process, reprocess text. But for fridge, irrelevant content. It's structured data to wear them. 

Speaker 1  (04:34)
The late feedback across multiple Better meter. And the challenges are No, ID Transcript. Maintaining noisy Transcript, maintaining consistency alarm output Optimizing latency using cashing cashing for repeated queries. 

Speaker 1  (05:00)
Okay, structured from for the consistency. Problem was that data was inconsistent, so model accuracy dropped for za. Typhi. 

Speaker 1  (05:11)
Work with a business team. Okay? Redesign feature extraction pipeline, improve data quality. 

Speaker 1  (05:20)
And then we will even talk about the classic model S Pam, with a classification with the marginal maximization. Okay, decision tree Rule base is splitting. Random forest name insemble to reduce overfitting nearby's pro blab probiotic model for text neural network, deep learning for complex pattern. 

Speaker 1  (05:48)
Modification, depending on data size linear, attain, the complexity Where are the TV uses the ENN approximate neural and nearest neighbor transformer has embedding layer multi selfish at the station, feed forward network and positional embedding. Random forest, we know right. Then, we have IVF I rented identify the cluster by choosing the closest centroid. 

Speaker 1  (06:24)
Okay, from choosing cluster rate, calculate similarity between all the points retrieve top K similar item inverted file indexing. Okay, still, we are not considering. That's a part of the fias's hms, w's hierarchical navigat, bulk, small world principle of escript, placed and NSW begins search from random strategy point at each step, evaluate the character neighbor and move to the one closest to the query. 

Speaker 1  (06:58)
Half hold one, no neighbor is closest to the query limitation is if you start from 7 Okay, and hard no one throws it to the carry. So solution is here to navigable, small world search begin at random entry in the topmost layer at each layer, the algorithm of the closest neighbor across the down the search layer 0 densest nearest neighbor is identified. If rape perform is still weak, slow response time, do achieval quality for the slow response tune ENN parameter. 

Speaker 1  (07:36)
Okay, and FA is as such an SW we have the search construct EF construction EF search and the screw search IVF is enlist and probe cluster search maxim cluster reduce. Vector dimension used batching caching, use hybrid search if accuracy law batter checking reduce overlap tissue, better embedding switch mode, small, large increased talk care at re ranking betaf, and coder. 
