
Speaker 1  (00:03)
So around 27th, we are working with emphasis from last 3 years. I'm before that I was working with Morgan standard and Jen packed and then CVS, and then previously working with the NIIT. So I have mostly worked with started with our data engineering. 

Speaker 1  (00:22)
Then, I moved to a iml, and then on the aml, from last 2 and a 1 years. I'm working with a GenAI in the chatbots and everything but yeah, so this is currently I am working with data bricks, majorly data breaks and then Azure, radio pipelines. All those things we have created the pipelines also Hello, along with that, I have a good exposure to these snowflake. 

Speaker 1  (00:47)
On premises data also. So things Yeah 

Speaker 2  (00:58)
To continue with the in CM model, when you have to train these classifications, you have to train any technology, how we can train. Let's say we have to train computer trade layer. 3 classified dogs get more 

Speaker 1  (01:15)
So you have the supervised data. So basically, you know, the conversation layer. We have the first, the conviction layer is there. 

Speaker 1  (01:22)
Then we have the flat. This input layers basically hidden there, and then you have the flattening, and then you have the software function, and then you will get the classification. Basically, so those layers we have to, we can train with the multiple functions like Sigma sigma function, railway function and galo function with all those things we have to try and find the optimised output of that. 

Speaker 1  (01:47)
And then accordingly we can train them. 

Speaker 2  (01:52)
So when we are training, so how we can enter the hyperparameter and how we can say model training rate direction or more 

Speaker 1  (02:01)
Okay, so I've not worked much on that. But I know conceptually for the hypertensing part, we can use a great search. We can in the in the database we have the ML flows there. 

Speaker 1  (02:12)
We can have the hyper tuning, so we can specify what model we want to train. Yeah, so at the database, we can do that with hypertension hypertension hypertension with the data bricks that we can do is them will flow. 

Speaker 2  (02:31)
Origins U vegan advanced? I mean it's so how will you impact that training? 

Speaker 1  (02:35)
Yeah, learning rate is the most efficient part of the training so we have to make sure that we have to specify the what you say, the mini and the maximum learning rate and based on that it will automatically comes up with the actual parameter base because what we are logging in the America for all the models we can see the results in the ammul flow tracking. So if we are getting the correct R square, if we are training on the prediction side R square will be well valued there. And if we are working on the this classification model, then we can see the value of the this or all those things we have. 

Speaker 1  (03:20)
So based on that we can see confusion matter basically. 

Speaker 2  (03:25)
Showing the continuum, there is a precision record, so 

Speaker 1  (03:29)
How do we? 

Speaker 2  (03:30)
Decide what? 

Speaker 1  (03:33)
A precipitation is basically how much the model is actually predicting and out of prediction how much the model has predicted. So this is a recall. So basically we have to enar application. 

Speaker 1  (03:46)
We are focusing more on the recall value because we don't want to miss the incorrect values from the model. So that's why we are using the legal value there. So these are 2 matrices that we basically use. 

Speaker 2  (04:01)
LLM uterine plus LLM of Christianity. 

Speaker 1  (04:06)
In the database itself, we are creating the so like, we have the data. Okay? All kind of data like the documentation conference pages and the other policies documents also. 

Speaker 1  (04:20)
So there we are starting it with the one fear of the data ingested in the multio architecture from the ingestion layer we in The Bronx layer. We have all the raw data. Then we are transforming it to the server layer then to the golden layer. 

Speaker 1  (04:31)
And out these are things done is being done on the area pipeline, then we have a chunking layer embedding layer. And then we have the prompt layer in between and with that one we have passing the context along with the user query into the lm and to get the response out of that Chatbot. So once we have that so basically we are we are exposing the other matrices, like hallucination rate, okay rate and see P95, and then we have the precision recall accuracy groundness. 

Speaker 1  (05:02)
All those things we are calculating. Based on that, we are finding refunding that model again with the top K of the data that we are retraving. Okay, with the top K values, basically I am talking about the retrievals, so we retrieve the retrievals with the if we want the relevant and the diversified data, then on their several matrices are. 

Speaker 1  (05:23)
There, so we tune them. 

Speaker 2  (05:24)
You should try to be the model correctly. So how you can do fine to be the model. 

Speaker 1  (05:29)
Yeah, fine. Tuning is basically done with lot of ways. Okay for initially, if we don't want to update the weights. 

Speaker 1  (05:35)
Okay basically alarms we can do use on the prompting so we can add the matter prompts in between and on the metaprompts we can specify okay what is your role okay tool for met and everything all those very specify because we want to take care of the cost as well so considering the small model for these matter prompts and then the big model for the later stage for the LLM, then we then we pass those things along with the flow that we are having with the chunking embedding layers. So also we have to take care of the incremental data that we are retrieving. 

Speaker 1  (06:09)
So every other every month, we have to re indexing the data of the of the embedding models that we have. So all those things we usually do. Similarly, similarly 

Speaker 2  (06:24)
Missus retrograde generation, correct, yeah. So how that a rent pipeline is generated and how we retreat the data 

Speaker 1  (06:31)
Sorry. 

Speaker 2  (06:32)
How to how we like do you amid you open how we did the data. 

Speaker 1  (06:37)
Yeh, Abhi thi conversation retrieval, basically we are using a land chain in the land chain. We have the conversation retrieval QA so these are the classes basically, but we have several parameters to get the data out of the model. One is the The MMR which is a chain type, then we have the top K top P ok. 

Speaker 1  (06:57)
And then we have the groundness. Okay, the ground data that we have and what the model has predicted. So based on that, we have the recall recession and recall precision values that we have to predict based on 

Speaker 2  (07:17)
AI system also 

Speaker 1  (07:21)
Yeah, so that's a previous model that I've worked on. So initially, what they have what happened is, so whatever the call we have. We are getting the transcripts of the call that we have retrieved. 

Speaker 1  (07:32)
And once we have that data, then we switched that data with is teaching that data with the these are unstructured data to the structured data. And then once we have that data in between, we have the bird model. Also, because we want, we want to remove the unwanted data like laughing and everything whatever the call we have. 

Speaker 1  (07:51)
So once we have the structured data, then we have the again, we have the chunking layer embending layer, and then we have the chatbots in there to get the tribal data. 

Speaker 2  (08:02)
So how it will work. 

Speaker 1  (08:04)
Yeah, it's basically. 

Speaker 2  (08:06)
The multi agents come lately super rate by 2003. 

Speaker 1  (08:09)
So basically we are classifiing the model with the matter, not one condition. So we have therefore several matrices, where we model. It's saying that whether the candidate is empathise or not. 

Speaker 1  (08:19)
Okay, self services, there are several matrices. And once we have those values with each one of them. We have the metal output condition with all those pipelines. 

Speaker 1  (08:29)
It has gone through, so once we have that data, and then we send this data to our a rbt for these kind of sample data, they are labelling it again. And once we have to receive that, then we need tune that data into the model. 

Speaker 2  (08:42)
Open 102 which model you read to inner lm? 

Speaker 1  (08:46)
Yeah, with these sticks, firms and everything. 

Speaker 2  (08:56)
How to avoid? 

Speaker 1  (08:58)
Yeah, hallucination is, let's say we can In each of the layer okay, we have to specify what the data we are retrieving starting with the chunking layer. So your chunking is not correct. Obviously we are getting the hallucinated data. 

Speaker 1  (09:12)
So we have to restrict that restrict that with the actual chunk size and the overlap size, we have to specify based on the structure data that we have created. And then we have the embedding layer embedding layer. We can make it hybrid, basically tense and the spars, okay with B25, with a tear of idea. 

Speaker 1  (09:30)
And then with the dense part, we basically use the BG model. Okay for the cost optimisation purpose, and then we have all those things. Then, it has created the embeddings of that. 

Speaker 1  (09:43)
Then with a similarity search we receive the data. Okay, once we have that retrieval data is present. Sorry. 

Speaker 1  (09:50)
I have forgot your question. So you need to talk about the That hallucination, okay. So once we are, we have to check. 

Speaker 1  (10:00)
What is the similarity we are retrieving if it is not correct with the ground data that it has to then we have to make sure that our embeddings are not correct. So we have to tune that also. So second thing is, with the sidition of the data. 

Speaker 1  (10:13)
Are we passing the current data or not? Okay so all those things. Also, we have the evolution dragas matrices, we have to see So based on those we take a call, whether we are getting well generated or not. 

Speaker 1  (10:30)
We have the 0 shot in few shots. 0 shot t***, completely vague query that we pass. But with a few shots, we pass the examples. 

Speaker 2  (10:39)
And they have a few or the chain of thought and create quiz water. 

Speaker 1  (10:44)
A chain of thoughts are basically one prompt to the other. We're passing a queries and validating it with the other prompt. 

Speaker 2  (10:52)
What is the European temperature? 

Speaker 1  (10:55)
For the temperature is basically used to generate the What you creative text out of the LLM, so if we reduce the temperature, it will automatically give the actual data, what we are far, but if we increase the temperature it will automatically generate a data with the more kind of creative data. 

Speaker 2  (11:18)
So heavy worker and Chatbot or anything is created in the 

Speaker 1  (11:22)
Nai stops you more than currently on the same 

Speaker 2  (11:34)
We have database, we have employee personnel in frustrating employed. Person leaves how many lives they do? They salary influence of their medical history? 

Speaker 2  (11:43)
Reply to influence in their now. We want to create a checkboard where employee can ask query like, can you tell me my whole last month to suggest sleep or my last particular history? I want to upgrade something like that or not general. 

Speaker 2  (11:55)
What are the medical insurance policy? I see here to Let me ugly can ask any question, so that information might be there. But Policy Document to everyone or say person for the database. 

Speaker 2  (12:08)
So how we can create that now. 

Speaker 1  (12:11)
Yeah, um, we take two things into condition, consideration cost and the latency. Okay? And 30 seconds accuracy. 

Speaker 1  (12:24)
So based on these 3 parameters, we decide what we want to achieve. Okay? So in the chunking layer, we have okay, then we have the embedding layer. 

Speaker 1  (12:36)
And then we have the LLM basically, ok, so if they're injecting the all those data into it. Okay. So I'm considering this as an unstructured data, I'll create that into the structured data in. 

Speaker 1  (12:51)
Let's say I am getting the js N ok format. I'll try to in the chunking layer. I'll try to at the matter data. 

Speaker 1  (12:58)
Ok, I'll try to add the um one chunk. One Chang per document, ok. And then this is chunking layer. 

Speaker 1  (13:12)
Then, based on those two things, I'll decide the chunk size. Ok, are the overlapping Ok, so in the chunking, there is done ok, and then I'll see if there is a need for the metaprompt. To check the my context is getting retrieved or not. 

Speaker 1  (13:32)
Ok, so it should not It should have the conceptual contextual data within the chunk itself. So that if we have the, if we don't have the cost budget, we can add the multi prompts with some small LLM in between then I move to the embedding layer in the bedding layer as I told you that we're using the vectors. Vector vector search from the big side, but also we can add the feature store. 

Speaker 1  (14:05)
Ok? And those features too basically getting it. The data from the original documentation, which is coming from the Delta table, which is your original source of truth. 

Speaker 1  (14:17)
Along with that, I'll figure out ok whatever the retrievals that we're retrieving. Retrieve from the similarity search along with the actual data, adding BM25 plus your, let's say BG layer. Ok, these two things. 

Speaker 1  (14:33)
Once we have retrieved, then all those things we passed into the LLM LLM we will decide on these two things. Okay, what model we want to consider? So for the lower cost and the latency is high in the accuracy we will decide. 

Speaker 1  (14:44)
Basically the open aim will work best with GP. T. GPT-4 mini. 

Speaker 1  (14:52)
Ok, sorry 5 mini that we're using. Currently, so once we have those data with the feature, a store retor store LLM then we retrieve the data. On the sick, we can consider security side as well. 

Speaker 1  (15:05)
All the documentation, everything, so we can expose that data to the end points using a fast apier, any other way using a micro services. Also, we can do that, so once we have those endpoints, retrieve them, we can We can see the latency from the end point or also from the layer that we have provided. These are these two things we will do. 

Speaker 1  (15:32)
Yeah, either way it can come from the Kafka or maybe from the uploaded, the file based, it could be. 

Speaker 2  (15:39)
The period documentary documents. 

Speaker 1  (15:43)
Ok, so if you're getting the P dm, I'm assuming that the user can upload it okay on some location, either. We have the calfka in between built-in. That is um, subscribe to your topic. 

Speaker 2  (15:58)
School decision, pregnant service overwhelmed, and we are cleaning chat today with our policy operator will come in the background side. Only usability has a query, you can get to recent query. 

Speaker 1  (16:08)
Okay, now I'm talking about earning. Okay, that's that's okay. In the calfka itself. 

Speaker 1  (16:13)
We can subscribe to the topic. Okay, that also we can create the jc document out of or maybe we can add some layer into it. It will convert the document into the Jason, ok. 

Speaker 1  (16:25)
On audiobook and weekly weekly weekend treat the road document. Then the document can contain images and texts that we can disagree. 

Speaker 2  (16:56)
Hello? Hello? Hello? 

Speaker 2  (17:12)
Hello? 

Speaker 1  (17:27)
So The data can come from the car. 

Speaker 2  (17:33)
Are you? 

Speaker 1  (17:36)
Adl si Rs 3 location. 

Speaker 1  (17:57)
So I'm assuming the data is present in adls or S3 location from that one. We can create the notification service. Ok, notification either it can go to the area of pipelines, ok, or maybe it can go to the Kafka. 

Speaker 1  (18:09)
Okay. From the Kafka, it can go to the topic. We can subscribe it and then the main purposes is to get the data in this layer chunking layer. 

Speaker 1  (18:17)
So it can go through the ideas location or maybe with the kind of. Yeah, once we have retrieved that data, we have 2 ways, either we can descend directly to the embedding layer, we can create the Delta table out of it, because we want to analyse based on this data, because we will get the multiple columns out of it. That And then we can have the embedding layer on any of the column that we have stood in. 

Speaker 2  (18:48)
So how to facilitate how to do advertisement will go to this ambedu data from database it will increase. However, it will decide. 

Speaker 1  (18:58)
So on the chunking layer, if we're storing the data into the detector. 

Speaker 2  (19:00)
Immune project, we had 2 shots of database. One has database where there are some personal information like this. Our national We are documentation, but user can ask any query like. 

Speaker 2  (19:10)
Can you tell me what is the way medical? Favourite national policy in icf. That is that it information but kind of kind. 

Speaker 2  (19:16)
Tell me my last last surgery. So how available decide which solves data source look. And so 

Speaker 1  (19:24)
Okay, we will use both embedding search and as well as the Delta table both we will use. But, if he is asking for the salary slip so there in the metaprom we have to specify what is role and what he don't know. Okay if we don't know if we will specify okay, I don't have the information on the base lip. 

Speaker 1  (19:42)
If you can upload it. I can tell you about that, but those things we can take a call here itself after them. Material. 

Speaker 2  (19:51)
We know the selection flowing database, so analym will go there and bring him database will not be there. It will not find Before calling evidence should be decided, which relationship should do. 

Speaker 1  (20:06)
I mean, see. This is all the data is there in. I'm assuming already it is there in the embedding day everything so I'll specify the condition ok if my day if the data is able to file if he is able to find the data okay there in the embedding layer along with the feature store I am assuming so if the data is there, then it will retrieve that ok in between. 

Speaker 1  (20:27)
I'll pass the prompt prompt, okay. Vidhi with the actual input of the salary slip, ok? And your embedding layer data, which is similar similar data Along with the Delta tabled feature stored data So along with the information context information that the user have asked with all with the actual data, along with the context, if I am Meta prompt is able to answer it. 

Speaker 1  (20:57)
Okay, I get the response it's good. If it is does not, then I have to specify either I can root it to the no information or I can ask user to upload it something. So metroprompt, we have to do is specifically Um, he's so overfitting condition is basically the when we have the outliers, ok in the in the data. 

Speaker 1  (21:27)
And data is not able to predict ok, and let's say the example of the random forest, which is more prone to the optimum outliers. We basically use that model random forest model for this For this overfitting, where we are checking the Prediction is not able to find the relationship between the data that we have a basic correlation with the data. So that's what the outlier means. 

Speaker 1  (22:00)
Basically. Yeah, overfitting if the data okay, the model knows each and every details of the data, let's say, okay, that leads to the overfitting. And which is not a good way, um. 

Speaker 1  (22:16)
Also, there is a bias terms also which it knows all the list. All the feature relationship, okay? The model know all the features relationship between the among with the target data. 

Speaker 1  (22:30)
Sorry with the target data. It knows all the relationship with each of the feature column 1 column 2. A can you tell me about the technical stack and the role that you're hiring for 

Speaker 2  (22:47)
So guide the rolling for a youthful primary role is that you have to The manager teams say some team member are looking at him one side. So we have to day-to-day life day work. We have to help them. 

Speaker 2  (23:01)
Technically, if they stuck somewhere, you have to do contribute, or they have to support these guidance, also, they have to But I can do the locality, if anything there 

Speaker 1  (23:15)
Yeh, I'm working on the same role. I'm good. Thank you. 
