gaurav@senpiper.com, hrglobal@senpiper.com, prafull.ranjan@senpiper.com

Speaker 1  (00:01)
I have looked at your resume, but let's not go into details about each and every experience that we have posted what I want to understand is last one year what you have been working on and What your current? Current, what is your current role current project current team structure? All that thing, right? 

Speaker 2  (00:23)
Yes, sure, so currently I'm working with M. Emphasis from last 3 years, actually, and it's an educational domain. Let us work with the bank accounts domain. 

Speaker 2  (00:35)
So my team size is around eight people, including QA M from master and developers, and my role, is working as an individual contributor now, but I worked as a lead before. And to think that I'm looking home last year is on the same application where we are trying to build the GenAI kind of application, which is a Chatbot also I have worked on optimisation tuning using in the data breaks itself. And the latest also we have, I mean, tried multiple modules multiple models. 

Speaker 2  (01:19)
Okay? Apart from that, I came from the background of the data engineering as well. Have a good exposure to the park and adf pipe. 

Speaker 2  (01:29)
Azure ADF pipelines ok, AW. Sut. 

Speaker 1  (01:37)
Ok, let's talk about the Chatbot that you mentioned. Which platform are you building that on and what is that Chatbot? Can you please explain what is the architecture? 

Speaker 1  (01:47)
What is the use case of the Chatbot? 

Speaker 2  (01:50)
Yeah, it's an internal Chatbot for getting the responses out of the documents that we have scheduled internally. We are going to have the kind of conference pages, different transcripts, transcribes. Conference pages as a told you some documents around it. 

Speaker 2  (02:12)
Okay, everything in a different format. Okay, that's comes into the into the bronze layer, which is actually very useful, guilty of architecture. So from that one, we try to create the unstructured data to the structured data, and then we have a checking layer and wedding layer. 

Speaker 2  (02:30)
And then we have the electoral We are using the data bricks provided vector store along with the feature store. We are using and then we have the queries LLM built-in. Then, we have, we are exposing those endpoints, those chatbots to the end points and the user can query it. 

Speaker 2  (02:52)
So this is the actually architecture and the injection layer is started with the Kafka, with ACDC changes, and then it moves to the S3. And from S3. We are reading that creating the pipeline also, so that is coming up from S3 to the Delta table. 

Speaker 2  (03:11)
Um, that's how we are doing. It also, if there is so we have several mattresses for the changes driftness. Ok, and the latency also I mean, all those regas. 

Speaker 2  (03:22)
Mattresses we have exposed so kind of that we are checking it we're. Evaluating that also we are and we have the ARB team, which is kind of we send the sample to them, and then we come up with the labelling of the data. Whether the data is correct or not. 

Speaker 2  (03:39)
So based on that, we find Let's me. 

Speaker 1  (03:44)
And this is the whole project, or this is the module that you are working on. 

Speaker 2  (03:48)
Is the module that I'm working on? 

Speaker 1  (03:51)
Ok, and what about the rest of the team you mentioned 708 people right? What are the other people working on? So what is the overall end to when ecosystem looking like? 

Speaker 2  (04:01)
Yeah, so we are working on the same thing, but on different parts. Okay, because we have a data engineering team as well. So created the pipelines. 

Speaker 2  (04:13)
Okay, greater the responses, fine-tune the responses. All those things we are doing altogether. 

Speaker 1  (04:22)
And This is done on the data break, so you are using Peter feature store and the database playground. Everything you are reutilising, right? And these there is Is in the data breaks? 

Speaker 1  (04:39)
I think there is something to extract information from document as well. Are you leverageing that component? 

Speaker 2  (04:46)
Extracting, we are using the text trackrary mujhe. 

Speaker 1  (04:52)
The royal data brings I think they have introduced something for extracting data from unstructured documents. 

Speaker 2  (04:59)
For morning structured document, we have the library also. 

Speaker 1  (05:04)
Yes, libraries final, I was just more keen around. Have you tested that the information extract information extraction model 

Speaker 2  (05:16)
The agents I mean, if you're talking about the library, the unstructured library I have used that, but is it 

Speaker 1  (05:23)
No, no I am talking in terms of data. Preets specific in the database specific ecosystem. If you remember on the agent section, you get a lot of prebuilt agent like knowledge assistant document, pass text classifiers, where there is something called information extraction. 

Speaker 2  (05:44)
Yeah, I mean you're talking about the GenAI, right? Genius, yeah. 

Speaker 1  (05:49)
Largely, not really no. This is different. Okay, that's fine. 

Speaker 1  (05:54)
Since you brought up the topic of genie, did you have you used genie? 

Speaker 2  (05:58)
Yes, we're using. 

Speaker 1  (06:02)
Saini, for what? Where exactly are you leverageing gene? Can you please explain that? 

Speaker 2  (06:07)
Yeah, kind of the tuning if we need to perform okay on each layer. I mean, for the code also, we are using it optimising everything there. 

Speaker 1  (06:20)
We're using that genie code feature, right? The AI assistant that is present in database. Have you created genie spaces? 

Speaker 2  (06:29)
Jennifer Genny spaces. No, I am not. 

Speaker 1  (06:37)
Okay, that is fine. So recently Data breaks has introduced something called Lake base. Did you end up exploring that? 

Speaker 2  (06:49)
Lakes face. 

Speaker 1  (06:51)
Lake base. 

Speaker 2  (06:52)
Leg base no I heard of snowman or not. Excluded. 

Speaker 1  (06:57)
Have you heard about this? No Okay, and all your pipelines, the data engineer pipe, the engineering pipelines that you talked about. Everything is in data breaks or are there any other ETL tools involved in this whole workflow? 

Speaker 2  (07:14)
Azure won't be ADF pipeline. 

Speaker 1  (07:19)
Okay, adf pipeline, what does it do? So what is the purpose of that? 

Speaker 2  (07:23)
Yes, so as I told you, we have the data comes up in the S3 okay, so we have the idea of pipeline which we are retrieving the data from the S okay, and then we are doing the transformation to the notebooks and to send it to that Delta tables. 

Speaker 1  (07:44)
An adf is the tool that you are using to bring in st data, right? And the orchestration of the whole pipeline, where is it happening? Is it adf or data breaks? 

Speaker 2  (07:57)
Workstation is in the ADF itself, ok, so what tables we need to perform everything is there in the area? Okay? 

Speaker 1  (08:08)
Okay? And the so since we are working on the AI Space in data, where it's as well so model life cycle, where are you? What are your leveraging? 

Speaker 1  (08:17)
Have you started using unity catalogue to register your models and promote it to next environment? Can you extend that workflow? So how this ML opts looks like in your organisation, or in your current project. 

Speaker 2  (08:31)
Ok, so for mlops, use for the tracking ok, we are registering that model. Then, we are using that model to the through that API, and we are loading it again and then we are also sending some of the matrices. To the evil floor and if I talk about the unity catalogue, we have different Environments set up for Deb Q and product. 

Speaker 2  (09:03)
Also, we have Delta shared some of the tables to brought to Q and Q to Dev. Also, we are the role level filter and: level masking for some of the information we have done that. Yeah, so all those things we are leverageing. 

Speaker 1  (09:22)
Indeed. So two things, 11 when you mentioned that we have different environments for drug test and prog you're talking about catalogues right, generally, unity, catalogue, you have different catalogue for them. For accessing data of broad, you said that there is Delta share done between these 

Speaker 2  (09:41)
Tables. 

Speaker 1  (09:44)
Is that needed? You can just Share a catalogue, and it can be read from a different box face, right? Without Delta, sharing? 

Speaker 2  (09:53)
Yes, but we need it for our development right? Because most of the data is there in their production. 

Speaker 1  (10:03)
It's just fine, so suppose this scenario I have a workspace which is development workspace. Then, there is a second box space which is test and third, is production. All your data is in sitting in production workspace, under a catalogue called production fraud or production. 

Speaker 1  (10:18)
Whatever that catalogue can be shared with my debt workspace directly without doing any sharing Delta shall Puzzle. 

Speaker 2  (10:28)
Doubt no, no, no I haven't. We usually don't do that because we can make the changes even if we can. Anybody can make the changes in that table. 

Speaker 1  (10:38)
Rehabilitation exists. I'm talking about you can make it read on you. 

Speaker 2  (10:42)
If it is read, only then it's fine. I mean I don't know the business structure why we're using it. But I'm talking about how we're doing it. 

Speaker 1  (10:52)
Okay, that is right and for deployment. What are you using for engineering? Since we have engineering like background as well. 

Speaker 1  (11:00)
So you might be understanding what is happening in engineering spacing, your project. So what are you doing for deployments of engineering workloads, and then what are you doing for deployment of your machine learning models, or agents or chatbots, or that sort 

Speaker 2  (11:16)
So for the ML side, we have the multiple models, okay, different versions that we are, I mean, in the ML flow itself. We have the multiple version that has been created for all the model for the end of the code changes we have the CIC D and the CIC D we have in the junkins it will automatically test our function test cases and everything and then it creates a build out of it. That's how we're doing it. 

Speaker 2  (11:46)
That's a separate trend also. Yeah, I mean. For the for the APIs thing Some of the teams they're using the because I'm not consuming those Opa! 

Speaker 2  (12:04)
APIs, so they have a different team who is doing it to the Not so maybe the microscope they are using or not. Sure, but This is what we are doing. 

Speaker 1  (12:21)
Ok. You completed data engineering certification right back last year, correct? Can you have you or you used this lake flow collectors and lake flow pipelines? 

Speaker 2  (12:37)
Lake flow connected and late flow pipeline are not used. 

Speaker 1  (12:43)
Do you know about spark declaratory pipelines? 

Speaker 2  (12:47)
Did you are talking about the ditts? 

Speaker 1  (12:51)
Yes, that's a new name of dlt, correct, and you use them. Yeah. 

Speaker 2  (12:56)
I have used them. 

Speaker 1  (12:59)
Okay? Okay, in terms of cluster, which cluster are you using? Which version 

Speaker 2  (13:08)
Time which cluster we are using? 17 dot something I do. 

Speaker 1  (13:15)
And is it an emblem, or is it a normal one? 

Speaker 2  (13:18)
No, for the models, we are using the ambulance, but for some other jobs dlts, we are not using the M. 

Speaker 1  (13:30)
And in terms of performance or performance optimisation of your jobs, anything in specific that you have done If I have a job which's running, it is taking a lot of time and it can be a spice park code, right? Let it be engineering or a health aside. Irrespective, what are the steps that you'll do to troubleshoot? 

Speaker 1  (13:52)
What is going wrong? And what are the some of the best practices that we should always take care of while creating this ice park? 

Speaker 2  (14:01)
Yeah, I mean, the job is taking long time. Okay to execute and we need to check the data size. Basically we need to check if the problem is there in the cluster size or on the data side okay from the cluster side, we usually check. 

Speaker 2  (14:19)
The if there is auto, scaling or something set up or not, we said that we check the basically the jobs are in waiting state. For how long they are waiting. So that's what we try to increase the cluster size. 

Speaker 2  (14:36)
Ok, so that are they getting enough executors to run, that's the one thing. Second thing is, if I talk about the the data side, if there is a problem, then we need to check the tax, we need to check whether we can have, can we see the skinness in the data. If we have the skulus, we have to, we usually use the aqi provided QS join configurations that we will reduce also. 

Speaker 2  (15:06)
If we have recently what I found one issue where we are using the broadcast joints. The broadcast the table was huge, so we cannot broadcast that because that was throwing the error so instead of the broadcast, we have added some new configuration, which is This Forward, that. This is the size of the first thing was the coolest size. 

Speaker 2  (15:34)
The partition size basically, that should not should be in 256 mbv. College size issue not be extend more, so we are using how 1 500 value where we have provided for that call is Advisory partition size, we have provided there are some others, so these are the confusion that we have provided along with that we have removed the broadcast from that table. And so that helped us to produce the computation time of the job. 

Speaker 2  (16:18)
There were some other changes we have done. On the later side there are distinct job duplicates, so we have added. What are the columns that we need to retrieve all those things? 

Speaker 1  (16:36)
Okay, and how comfortable are you with the normal data? We are housing concepts, joints, facts, dimensions. 

Speaker 2  (16:44)
Hey, so basically we are using the fact and dimension tables only. 

Speaker 1  (16:52)
Ok, and so there is a scenario. Just assume that you have been given a task to design the medallian architecture of this company. Ok, and where your team is stuck now is In the silver layer where the enterprise data model is going to be created, which modelling technique should be used. 

Speaker 1  (17:16)
So there are 2 contenders, one is, if you look at the database documentation, they say it can be either 3 and have or your data work. 

Speaker 2  (17:27)
Technique. 

Speaker 1  (17:28)
So that's where you are at, what will you do? And how will you approach this? Which model will you finalise? 

Speaker 1  (17:34)
And why? 

Speaker 2  (17:35)
Siri, what was a problem statement Hindu? 

Speaker 1  (17:40)
You understood till this point right for us. Silver layer? You need to finalise the modelling technique. 

Speaker 1  (17:45)
That's the problem, state. 

Speaker 2  (17:47)
Morning technique. Okay. 

Speaker 1  (17:49)
Yeah, and 2 options which data breaks provides you is either you can go with 3 and a or data wall. 

Speaker 2  (17:58)
Okay. 

Speaker 1  (17:59)
So that's where this quick. 

Speaker 2  (18:02)
All the security 

Speaker 1  (18:05)
No, not for security purpose, normal. That's the data near right silver layer. 

Speaker 2  (18:10)
Yeah, and see. Ok. 

Speaker 1  (18:14)
So how will you approach this? What are the things that you will Analyse, and then what will be your recommendation? 

Speaker 2  (18:26)
Sorry I didn't get that question. Data vault and 

Speaker 1  (18:30)
TM F3 nf. Do you know 3NF and data world? 

Speaker 2  (18:40)
Dynasty, Concert chilli butter notifications required. That's for the security. 

Speaker 1  (18:49)
Okay, so let's let's take a step back. The medallia architecture, what are the layers and what each layer corresponds to? Can you tell me that? 

Speaker 2  (18:58)
Yeah, I mean, bronze is the Ingestion layer where we Put all the documents, all the data and the silver we just transform it. With adding some constraint and everything, the Transform data with t Removing the all sorts of things like duplicates and Other things, if we are getting some wrong values, we correct them, basically transformation. And I'm on the golden air. 

Speaker 2  (19:32)
We expose the aggregated data. That's what the amount of architecture, but we are data fault fits in idol. 

Speaker 1  (19:47)
You are aware about the 3 enough. 3 normal form. 

Speaker 2  (19:52)
Yeah, I mean, that's a part of the transformation. Not sure. 

Speaker 1  (19:58)
Cricket provocates. Otherwise, okay, the second 1 the second scenario is while you are building ingestion till the end of serving their time, so you have to implement the lambda LAMDA architecture. Are you aware about the lambda architecture? 

Speaker 2  (20:16)
Do talk about the adiwsi or 

Speaker 1  (20:20)
No, in general, in the Big DATA world, there is something called named architecture. 

Speaker 2  (20:27)
Okay, you talk about survival architecture. 

Speaker 1  (20:31)
No, no, it's a combination of your speed layer Vs batch layer. That's what right? Every every time you if you have to design both the things parallelly that's that's called lambda architecture, it's a processing design pattern that handles your volume in batch and streaming together. 

Speaker 2  (20:53)
Ok, ok. 

Speaker 1  (20:55)
Ok, so that is fine. Let's not go there. And how much exposure you have will data quality? 

Speaker 2  (21:04)
Data quality quality of the students. Yes, I mean 

Speaker 1  (21:09)
Normal in general later quality dimensions. How will your major data quality? If you have a table, how will you? 

Speaker 1  (21:19)
And then you have been given to identify the quality score quality index of your customer data. What is the are the things that you can do? 

Speaker 2  (21:29)
On the Jenny, I sight, right? Or generally talking about? 

Speaker 1  (21:33)
General genaye quality means different thing in GenAI. Is it? 

Speaker 2  (21:39)
No, we basically check the relevance of the data that we are extracting from the From the problem. From Delhi. Is that the question 

Speaker 1  (21:53)
No, no, and in general. 

Speaker 2  (21:56)
Ok, data quality. We usually we have the QA right, so MM. We take it manually. 

Speaker 2  (22:06)
Basically, what are the fields that we have data quality, we have the If you're talking about the sonar cubes vulnerability, everything Can you specify which area you want? 

Speaker 1  (22:20)
No, I was talking about the completeness accuracy, the standard traditional data quality dimensions, not the one liability. And 

Speaker 2  (22:28)
All those that when you talk about the precision recall, everything or something different. 

Speaker 1  (22:35)
Okay, that's fine. So just a quick question, where, since men have you started working on this AI? 

Speaker 2  (22:42)
Space for the genius, I am working from last one and a 1 years. 

Speaker 1  (22:52)
Ok, and any any particular reason that you did data engineering certification last year 

Speaker 2  (22:59)
Yeah, that was the ask from the company. But they were providing it society. 

Speaker 1  (23:10)
Ok, ok, so the reason I'm asking holistic questions more Prakhar is with your experience. It's it may start as an individual contributor role, but we are also looking for someone who can expand his business, and if you know the engineering, that's an added bonus, and that's where if you are wondering that why I am asking all these Questions which is all across engineering, AI governance space. That's the simple reason. 

Speaker 2  (23:58)
Yeah, okay, ma'am, also exploring, okay. 

Speaker 1  (24:03)
On data breaks, what are the new features you have recently tried? Are you following data bricks as a platform? 

Speaker 2  (24:14)
You am in my application is built on the top of the database. Only inside the database only. 

Speaker 1  (24:24)
Any new feature that you have used in last 6 months? 

Speaker 2  (24:30)
We're using everything what the database have workflows ok? We have the dashboards and we have the ML side we have the model serving. Sorry, this feature is stored. 

Speaker 2  (24:45)
Okay. Desu I mean, I don't know. I mean, if there is other things that I need to be, I know of but 

Speaker 1  (24:54)
Yeah, I did ask about lake base or genius spaces. You're not aware about that, so 

Speaker 2  (25:00)
I'll left. 

Speaker 1  (25:01)
The dashboards, the data bricks a ivia dashboards. We are talking about, right? Do you have a bit who is creating those dashboards? 

Speaker 1  (25:11)
Or are you guys creating by yourself? 

Speaker 2  (25:13)
No, no, we have the BI team. 

Speaker 1  (25:16)
There are doing there is something called database agent dashboard agent. Have you used that? 

Speaker 2  (25:23)
No, why don't you start database? 

Speaker 1  (25:26)
Go and database dashboard agent that is just a simple prompt. You can get the whole dashboard created. 

Speaker 2  (25:33)
For you, if you give me But not sure if you know 

Speaker 1  (25:40)
This is geni, what database is done is now they have done. They are branding everything under the genie umbrella. The genius space is one concept genie code which is which was called AI assistant earlier. 

Speaker 1  (25:52)
Now they are calling it as genie code and then there is something called data bricks dashboard agent which helps you develop dashboards, so dashboard agent will not help you code. It will only help you develop dashboards. 

Speaker 2  (26:05)
Chili was available was using those but I was not aware of their names. 

Speaker 1  (26:10)
Dumped. No worries, I think I'm done I mean any questions from your side, prakr. 

Speaker 2  (26:17)
Anu, no, I'm good. 

Speaker 1  (26:19)
Oh, cubic thanks a lot for your time. 
