kavitha.mc@srushtitechsolutions.com, swetha.dn@srushtitechsolutions.com, venkatesh.m@srushtitechsolutions.com
abhishek.ivaturi@infosys.com, madhurilakshmi.j@infosys.com

aishwarya.k@genpact.com, yukti.malhotra@qmail.quesscorp.com

Sudhakar Nujiveeti <sudhakar.nujiveeti@valuelabs.com>

Speaker 1  (00:00)
Encounters revenue and how you go about mitigating them. 

Speaker 2  (00:04)
Yeah, I mean, when we are talking about the major problem that we come up with the long-running jobs, that's the initial that's the major problem that we have. So we have to tune that job. Okay. 

Speaker 2  (00:14)
First, we need to look whether it's a cluster issue or a data issue on the cluster issue. We try to increase the memory. Okay? 

Speaker 2  (00:21)
Depending on the memory that we are having, we can go with the in the database, there is a feature of water scaling that we usually do keeping the memory on Twister to the maximum pluster and once we finalise. Okay, it's not a cluster issue. It's a data issue, then we go to the core and look for the Is park tuning basically so on? 

Speaker 2  (00:42)
Is park tuning we check what kind of joints we are doing? Whether we are performing the filters or not okay? How the so we go for the query we check for the query planet there. 

Speaker 2  (00:52)
We check for the scan file scans how many file scan by default? Does park use the column pruning or the filter grooming method which will automatically filter out the rows then again if still it is taking lot of rows then we check the filter condition if we can add something we arrange the order joints and the filter joints also then we look for the partitions if the table has okay. Sometimes what happens is that the old archive data is already there, so we try to clean that also replicated data optimise it. 

Speaker 2  (01:29)
Sometimes the partitions we have having the small files. Okay, so small, that's called the small file problem. We try to optimise. 

Speaker 2  (01:37)
We run the optimised command just to remove the old files. Okay, the retention replication file basically. We are keeping the retention factors too. 

Speaker 2  (01:49)
Along with that, once all these things are done partition system, then we can go for the joy on the joint side. We look if we can make some tables go home broadcast to the broadcasting other table because right now we have the auto joint threshold that we keep is as 20 MB file size if it is seating that we cannot go for the broadcast, but these are things that we consider also we find tune that way with a scheme. We can check whether we have the students in the data. 

Speaker 2  (02:19)
If we have, then we check for the key. Okay, particularly if that is creating a huge data in one of the files and we try to split that data to the sorting or there are some features in the Aq that we can add-on it in the spark job with a spark for it. Aqi is by default, so we have to give the tunes. 

Speaker 2  (02:40)
So N is equal to 2 or maybe the coolest factor as a scale factor as a point to something. And along with that, we have to add-on the college number of colases that they can perform or the shuffles. So these are the few things. 

Speaker 2  (02:55)
Also, I'll check for the shuffleness, shuffle, in the in the data. If it is happening very much, then how can I reduce it so that way, using a tax, I can figure it out. 

Speaker 1  (03:08)
So yeah, so yeah, I'm sure you must be familiar with broadcast. Concept, right. So yeah, so we can you briefly explain, you know, what is broadcasting and what scenarios would you consider? 

Speaker 1  (03:21)
You know, a broadcast joint. 

Speaker 2  (03:23)
So the scenario that I'll choose is the my table is small enough to go and into the storage, the executor executor not because what happened is that it's the driver's job to take that broadcast table and Put it down there in the worker notes so that there could be a little, because if there is a litacy problem that can be reasoned network problem that can be reduced, because otherwise every time the executive will come and fetch that table, take that data from the driver and then execute that data. 

Speaker 2  (03:54)
So that's the problem that's a advantage of using the broadcasting. 

Speaker 1  (03:58)
Okay so yeah, can you talk about, you know? Some of the best practices and techniques that you normally use to make sure you know your spark, drop, sparkrops run faster and more efficiently. 

Speaker 2  (04:12)
Yeah, as I told you right. The filter condition join orderings? Okay, joins basically how we are performing. 

Speaker 2  (04:20)
Lecture? What is my driver table? What is my other tables? 

Speaker 2  (04:24)
Okay, number of columns that we are extracting. So we cannot expose all the data to the user, but also we have to make sure that our compute size should be less little should be reduced. So based on that, we keep only small columns to expose it to the user. 

Speaker 2  (04:42)
That way other, we will try to use the spark as much as possible. What does that mean is that we have to make sure that we are not using the spark of sequel? Every time we have to use the We have to convert that into the pice bar job, and in some way if we are using pandas, because pandas working the single cluster, I'm talking about the ML C. 

Speaker 2  (05:07)
ISO we have to convert into pice park then into the pandas for the aggregating the data apart from that joins. 

Speaker 1  (05:17)
Have you used a cashing impositive? 

Speaker 2  (05:20)
Yes, definitely. So, using the cashing box. I mean, we can catch that data. 

Speaker 2  (05:24)
Okay? In between, because I do not want to data frame to compute every time from the start. So we catch that in between so next time when it come, it will take me already build data from them. 

Speaker 1  (05:42)
How do you decide, especially, we are saving you want to design a new partition? In what do you follow any standard formula or you know standard process to decide on you know what is the number of partitions you know your cluster will require. 

Speaker 2  (06:00)
You're talking about the the US equal partition or 

Speaker 1  (06:05)
This equal. Yeah, I am talking about the sequel partitions. So 

Speaker 2  (06:10)
Yeah, based on the filters, right, so based on these queries that we have in the we are using. So we figure out what are the columns that can be eligible for the partition? Let's say if we are using it based on the country, the country can be the one of the column for the partition, but majorly, if we are getting the data every day. 

Speaker 2  (06:32)
So what we do is we keep the partition as the date twice. Okay, month wise, majorly and then we store that data. So depending on the filters we 

Speaker 1  (06:47)
And to decide on how many number of partitions, how do you decide? 

Speaker 2  (06:51)
Yeah, I mean just to check for the long-running jobs, okay? So it is taking time so by default, it's 200 but we can increase it to the N number. So ideally we keep it as 2002 3000 range of the partition. 

Speaker 2  (07:05)
If we have a large data set. So that way, we do it use in the repartition method. 

Speaker 1  (07:12)
So can you explain bucketing? And you know what scenario you know, bucketing? 

Speaker 2  (07:17)
Yeah, for the high cardinality data, where we cannot keep the like the order ids working into the partition. We keep it as a bucketing, so bucketing works in the fashion of the Hassan, ok, so it just tries to hash those ids and keep this into the buckets so that we need to specify at the time of writing the data. So if let's say, if we are doing it, make 3. 

Speaker 2  (07:42)
Buckets, okay. So it will keep that ID into the 3 buckets. Okay, based on the hash of the time. 

Speaker 2  (07:49)
Well, at your 

Speaker 1  (07:51)
Yeah, so you mentioned briefly about the small files issue, so and you mentioned that he would use optimiser. Any other techniques that you would you consider, especially to handle small file issues that you are getting an output but in a large number of files with small 

Speaker 2  (08:07)
Yeah, so there are two things on the database side. They behave differently on the snowflake behave differently. I worked on the snowflake side. 

Speaker 2  (08:15)
What happened is if there is a small file, what happened is they have the concept of the clustering and the liquid clustering, okay, so in their sequel, we can specify okay. If we don't know the columns, that will going to be participating in the uh Partitionally, we will try to try to use the auto otherwise. We can specify the column name for the cluster cluster as something and then we can specify the column name. 

Speaker 2  (08:42)
But that will come up with the they can be used as the mechanism of the clusting in the snowflake. So what happened is, so in the partition we have this folders created, okay, and those folders. We don't know how many files, how many data we have. 

Speaker 2  (08:58)
So sometimes in the partition we have long size of file. And on the some other folder we have the small size. Okay, just to remove that and because it if we have the small file, there will be a overhead on the executive. 

Speaker 2  (09:14)
Because they are two things. One is the high volume 1 is the small volume, so all the executive will going to execute on the file size first. And then the small size, so just to mitigate that terror we have to use the clustering mechanism. 

Speaker 2  (09:29)
Okay? So if we have to specify the cluster: name and how they will work is they will go into split the data, let's say, if I'm doing the clustering on the order ID it will split. Let's say 1 2 50 on the 11 file 5200 on the other side. 

Speaker 2  (09:47)
So that's how it will. Uh clusterize my data. Okay? 

Speaker 2  (09:54)
Yeah, on the other side which is about the data breaks. We can use the partitioning method, but we do not have the clusting mechanism there. We can use the bijli. 

Speaker 2  (10:06)
The issue comes up with the optimise keyword where we have long set of archive file that is also getting red by while picking the data into the memory. 

Speaker 1  (10:20)
You mentioned that you have also handed in the cleaning data, right? So can I know the use case? You know what kind of swimming data pipeline were you managing? 

Speaker 2  (10:31)
Yes, so in my application, which is a teacher and a student based diagnostic test. So whenever they do the test, we get the notification of some some feel so that we need to inject into the data into our snowflag database. So that way, we have created a streaming. 

Speaker 2  (10:50)
Then, the streaming, we have on the database. We have the on the multiop architecture. We have created the streaming table. 

Speaker 2  (10:57)
And then for the silver and for the Golden layer we have created actually Delta DL T pipeline, ok, keeping the bronze as a steaming then on the silver side, we are reading the steaming table, and then we are aggravating the data into the golden table. 

Speaker 1  (11:11)
That's pretty okay. So what happens when you have relate events coming into a pipeline? So What was streaming by people? 

Speaker 2  (11:22)
Yeah, we have the water market. We have to mark water market. Specifying the window size of 10 minutes, or maybe we usually keep the 10 minutes of wind so let's say, if the event term late, also, they will be updated in the same window. 

Speaker 1  (11:42)
You know, significance of schema evolution, you know, in data engineering, you know, why. 

Speaker 2  (11:48)
Scheme evolution right? Yeah, let's say scheme. Regulation is used in the merger scheme used as the auto auto cloud. 

Speaker 2  (11:58)
There is a concept of the auto cloud in database or in the pipe. So what happened is, let's say right now I'm having 10 columns in the next set of files I have 11 columns. Okay so if I keep injecting that data, the data looks job will fail. 

Speaker 2  (12:15)
So what we usually do is we will keep the option as the mergest teama as a parameter while reading the data. So what happened? Is it will it will add the new column at the end? 

Speaker 2  (12:29)
Without breaking the job, that's how it works. 

Speaker 1  (12:35)
Talk about your ML pipeline experience. So I think in your current projects you are involved in an ML pipeline development, correct. Right. 

Speaker 1  (12:44)
So yeah, can you talk more about it? You know, in what kind of challenges you know, and what was your involvement in as part of this email pipeline development? 

Speaker 2  (12:53)
Soybeah walked on the rack pipeline. Okay? So the rack pipeline we have multiple sets of documents of the organisation that we are injecting it in a different format and then we have the chunking layer. 

Speaker 2  (13:06)
Okay, the chunking layer we were splitting the data using the recursive character splitter. And then we have them bedding layer in between so we were using the BG model LLM model, and then from the embedding, then it is going to be vector dB so for the vector dB were using the quarter so we have treated that pipeline and we have tried it multiple approaches all for the fine tunes. So once we have that data in the vector databases, then using the cocine similarities, uh, along with the prompt template, we were extracting the data. 

Speaker 2  (13:42)
Okay, we call it as a retrieval. Um, so retrieval, and then we were doing the reranking before retrieval, so that we can get the accurate results without the hallucination. Also, we were exposing some mattresses there. 

Speaker 2  (13:58)
In the For the users also for the monitoring. Also, we were using the isolation hallucination rate. We were using the cost involved on computational literacy time. 

Speaker 2  (14:16)
Recall procession, all these values. We were exposing to the in the monitoring for the reports in the reports and I did the Fine-tuning also in the racks like I can talk about that. 

Speaker 1  (14:30)
And for your data opposition, you know, what are you country with similar? 

Speaker 2  (14:36)
Yeah, I work with air flows. Then I work with the uh, step functions okay for a question on the answer. 

Speaker 1  (14:48)
And have you been involved in any migration activity from a non-prime data platform to observe topic club? 

Speaker 2  (14:55)
Yes, yes, I've done that when I was in Mom of China, so immigrant compromise through the database. 

Speaker 1  (15:01)
Okay, what was the on prime ticket platform most includ 

Speaker 2  (15:04)
Clouder, run. 

Speaker 1  (15:05)
Okay, familiar with cloud era and cloud era manager as well for monitoring of your health and right now you are working on Azure. 

Speaker 2  (15:17)
Yeah 

Speaker 1  (15:19)
And what kind of monitoring tools do you use for manageing for monitoring pipeline? 

Speaker 2  (15:26)
For monitoring the pipeline Okay. So we have sorry. We have the ads or monitoring the pipeline so there we can see. 

Speaker 2  (15:36)
Dashmalav, can you 

Speaker 1  (15:41)
And you have experience on, you know, be high. Mental 

Speaker 2  (15:45)
Yeah, yeah, but why won't you 

Speaker 1  (15:49)
How can I turn up my questions here for I hope, are recording has given you a brief about this opportunity? Yeah, do you have any specific questions regarding again? Not to file wrong. 

Speaker 2  (16:08)
We assume can tell me what the project and the technical stuff plays. 

Speaker 1  (16:12)
Yeah, sure, the project is for a banking client called embrids. &. It's for a senior data engineer position. 

Speaker 1  (16:19)
We are looking to expand the existing data engineering team for this point, this would primarily involve, you know, retail pipeline development. And yeah, so majority of the yeah, the bank works on cloud era. Majority of the data is on prime and yeah, so a high cloudera. 

Speaker 1  (16:42)
Manager bdfs yeah, so that would be more or less. The second year you could programming language would be in price part. Yeah, and yeah. 

Speaker 1  (16:56)
So and yeah, so rule. Although it's a lot of experience on eml pipeline development, there could be a lot of more than eating pipeline development. There will be a lot of ML pipeline development 

Speaker 2  (17:09)
Ok, understood. 

Speaker 1  (17:13)
Yeah, and again we there are multiple rupees, specifically for a daytime during department of the bank. You know, as a senior resource, you will, you know, require even be required to collabourate within multiple stakeholders. It may be analytic leads. 

Speaker 1  (17:30)
You know, data leads data scientists, you know, data, arteches, data, msmes, to understand their data requirements, you know, and translate them into typical solutions, design development. You know, monitor. Yeah, so, but predominantly, the requirements would be more on ML pipeline and development. 

Speaker 1  (17:49)
Along with, you know, other data pipeline. 

Speaker 2  (17:52)
How can I? 

Speaker 1  (17:54)
The social as part of your mogest value you work with ado. Yeah, so you treat me more of the text tax that you know that your normal family is going to be seen, you know, a morely on prime, right? And if required, you know, you will also be involved in the migration activities from all pride to a public. 

Speaker 1  (18:14)
So there is transition going on. But is it's not completely done for now? Everything is on Prime Minister. 

Speaker 1  (18:24)
And so do you have friends or family? This is hiberty team, as mentioned that this opportunity will require you to travel. This is a long-term opportunity, so we have many friends or family. 

Speaker 2  (18:34)
You say a family, but I'll move first and then I'll 

Speaker 1  (18:40)
So you basically from Bangalore. 

Speaker 2  (18:43)
None from now. 

Speaker 1  (18:44)
No, you quickly talk, okay. And are you have no constraints travelling? Once we have a confirmation 

Speaker 2  (18:55)
Ok. 

Speaker 1  (18:56)
And what's your current notice period 

Speaker 2  (19:00)
Currently, I'm serving, so my last number 

Speaker 1  (19:06)
Do you last working deal? 

Speaker 2  (19:07)
Right 15th of June. 

Speaker 1  (19:10)
Into June okay, I mean, June, okay, a month and a 1. I would say, okay. 

Speaker 2  (19:15)
But I can't negotiate. 

Speaker 1  (19:17)
You can do it negotiate. It's okay, correct, okay. So it's nice talking to you. 

Speaker 1  (19:23)
Do you have any specific questions? Anything else that you wanted to clarify? 

Speaker 2  (19:27)
Hello, no, I'm good. 

Speaker 1  (19:29)
Ok, ok, ok, thanks for your time today. It was nice talking to you see. 

Speaker 2  (19:34)
Yeah, thank you again. You have to thank you. You have a good deaf. 
