
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Answer myself a preferred around 14 years of experience working with Working with the efficiency from last 3 years and before that, I was working on a Maharashtra. So we are really starting with the data engineering, and then I switched to the NI side on the nls that I have worked with the pipelines. The pipelines racks operators, rack pipeline display and then I worked on the occasion which is evaluating the agent. 

Speaker 1  (00:30)
So we are generating a feedback out of the link. So these are two things that I've got on the alarm sides. Apart from that, I've good exposure to the data which snowflake majorly. 

Speaker 1  (00:43)
Along with that exposure to the LLM's chatbots, along with that Google exposure to the data which site, which is high Pala Oracle databases vector db is also created the pipeline during the dlts pipelines adf Azure pipeline that I have used for the full load and the internet load. We are we have used the job overflows also in the database for the I mean client data. So for the we are using the multiple architecture, the multiple architecture we are using the bronze silver golden layer, a user data along with that, we have used the ADF items also there, creating the bronze and the silver tables in the D and Delta tables. 

Speaker 1  (01:36)
So these are the things that I have worked on. Currently. My application is more into the educational domain which is the diagnostic stress given by the students, and then they evaluated used that teachers Also, we have the chatbots for using the questions so that pipeline we have built-in. 

Speaker 1  (01:56)
I've worked on the Child. I worked as an individual contributor but I worked as a lead before. On the outside, also Along with that, yeah, so we are in days of spring to 3 months of psi. 

Speaker 1  (02:12)
And my role is responsible is to get the requirement and then kidneys documentation around it and then walk accordingly, based on the GST stories. Yeah, that's pretty much for my Son. 

Speaker 2  (02:28)
Um, so can you explain a bit more about your recent project in a workout? 

Speaker 1  (02:34)
Yes, sure. So my recent project is, as I told you it's about the Educational domain, where? It's start with the kafkal ear, okay with all the diagnostic data that's comes in and we are the CDC layer. 

Speaker 1  (02:49)
Then, we've the bad jobs running from 1NS2 to S3G nightly running jobs, we're transforming it from railway. The radio in the multi operate architecture, some of the jobs are running in the ADF and some of the jobs are running as if workflow in the database. Okay, so we're getting all these data in the Delta tables. 

Speaker 1  (03:11)
And then from that also, we have the files there in the system. We are chunking it chunking our data and for chunking, we are grieving. I am embedding and embedding with the better degrees that typeline is there? 

Speaker 1  (03:27)
Uh, so also we are making sure that our data should be not. I mean the training other position data should be aligned, so we have the drift matrix. Also there we are exposing for the monitoring also, we are sending the Alert system, if the threshold changes Along with that, we have the chatbots, which again, the user query embedding somebody promptly, we have provided. 

Speaker 1  (03:57)
Then, we are sending the way to the LLM and then we get the response in between, we have implemented the cache memory. 

Speaker 1  (04:18)
But they do not So sorry. Yeah, so I was talking about the batting layer and then the vector dbs into chatbots. We are getting very responsive. 

Speaker 1  (04:32)
So we're the language we use the lunch in year for the orchestration. Also, I've worked with the air flows. I work with the step function, lambdas everything so I've designed that thing in the In the pipeline. 

Speaker 1  (04:49)
We have used the S3 is we have used the Azure we have the adms, all those things we have used. But that's pretty much formal AR. 

Speaker 2  (04:57)
To issue what is what was the objective of this application? Like what was the final outcome? 

Speaker 1  (05:03)
Yeah, final outcome was first the Chatbot, so they can ask any question related to the organisational data. That's the first thing, the main problem. I mean What you say. 

Speaker 1  (05:19)
The success matters that we are talking about. It should give their relevant answer to the user. So that was the first time I have walked on the tuning as well on the right side. 

Speaker 1  (05:28)
Second, talk about what we are doing. 

Speaker 2  (05:32)
CAC world? Did you use a RAG approach instead of Fine-tuning the morning? 

Speaker 1  (05:39)
I live in a moment that we have used. Because we don't have the we have this SIM. I mean, we have not the huge Datasets okay of data and what the cost of optimism, all those things we have preferred are pipelines. 

Speaker 1  (05:53)
And that's very easy to use. 

Speaker 2  (05:59)
And how about like how you evaluated your drag model? 

Speaker 1  (06:02)
Yeah, I mean. Ok, so based on the mattresses that we've received, whether I was a hero station date, how was a precision recall? Ok. 

Speaker 1  (06:12)
Um, if there is any drift in the feature distribution. Also that we were checking as a mattress. So based on that, although the written literacy and the cost also keeping all this in mind, so we have to check on each layer, whether could be a problem in the chunking layer, it could be a problem in the prompt layer, or in the embedding layer. 

Speaker 1  (06:33)
So on the chunking layer or all are the problem in the retrieval layer. So And we have to make sure that the Chatbot should be fast. Okay, so where we were focusing more on the latency than the accuracy that was a trade-off that we have fixed. 

Speaker 1  (06:53)
So on the chunking side we have recursive character, taxes, splitter and where we're providing the chunk size and the overlap size we were tuning the to make sure that we can have the correct context context on the chunking side, then on the embedding layer we are using the bg model where it converts the embedding and the embedding to the vector dvs, the vector device were using pine cone earlier in which we showed quadrant for the cost purpose. So that we did it once we have that data there along with the matrices calculated, now on the user side when he is asking the question. 

Speaker 1  (07:37)
So there we've added the cashew air with the semantics. So that even if it is asking the same question with a different text, he will be able to recognise. That on the cashew side and then once we have received that, then we are the prompting layer in between in the prompting, we are restricting with the guardians and everything keeping it short contextualise the bronze away, giving the role there we are giving the task. 

Speaker 1  (08:10)
Don't forget and with some context, we are doing basically the data in the bullet points bullet format, so we are giving some examples here as a few Few-Shot Learning. So once all these changed. 

Speaker 2  (08:27)
Can you tell me like how you neither the vaccination? And if the hallucination is high, then what steps you took to like fix that issue. 

Speaker 1  (08:38)
Yeah, for the first time thinking we're checking the relevance score. Okay, how relevant we are getting the data? Also, there is a human being feedback involved. 

Speaker 1  (08:46)
So how many times the user asked the same if it didn't get the answer, how many times he has asked the contextal question based on the same that rate, we were populating it. So yeah, these are 

Speaker 2  (09:04)
The context on that context. So basically when I mean you have a Chatbot so how you manage the memory of the Chatbot, and if the chat is going too long, then how you handle that scenario. 

Speaker 1  (09:19)
Yeah, we were using the summarised memory buffer because what it do is it will okay we were storing the chats in the mongo dbi. Also, so what happened is, in the summary buffer we have. Let's say if you want to retrieve top 5 chats and the earlier chat it will summarise those chats. 

Speaker 1  (09:40)
So let's say if they are 2015 will be summarised. 10 will be retained as it is. So that's how we will we will be doing that. 

Speaker 1  (09:50)
Per user. 

Speaker 2  (09:51)
How you deploy the supplication, and what was the audience size that? Can you simultaneously in this application? 

Speaker 1  (09:59)
I'm in the whole organisation can use that that was the user size and how we deployed 

Speaker 2  (10:05)
Well, approximately, can you tell some numbers like around how winning audience can be there? Or what is the target audience that you have like expected when you are deploying the application? 

Speaker 1  (10:19)
Yeah, it was our internal users only lekin, who knows who want to know about the architecture, organisational architecture and everything they get to know all through the chamber. 

Speaker 3  (10:34)
So 

Speaker 1  (10:35)
What time is if they want to ask about that seasonal export or any any data specific to the organisation? I can ask him so this size could be around 5K26K users. 

Speaker 2  (10:50)
And what was the deployment step to be here? 

Speaker 1  (10:53)
Yes, so we have used the data bricks. We have used the data edf pipelines. So basically we were there was a pipeline for the embedding layer that was one of the pipeline in using the adf pipeline we have created that, so initially we are 

Speaker 2  (11:14)
Really click the background. Sorry back and I understood. But I want to understand like the application where it was like how it was hosted and how user used that application. 

Speaker 1  (11:26)
Katezeta hosted in the In the production environment of the data breaks And we have used the streamlit there for the UI for the user. So also, we have deployed the steamed cloud for the UI and for the other things we have. The adf pipelines. 

Speaker 2  (11:50)
Do you do you think I mean, what do you think about the security aspect of streamlining, stimulate application, or you want to like if you get a chance to enhance the application or you will analyse this? Yeah. 

Speaker 1  (12:02)
So we have the ARB board. Also, we have the GAR defacts, so artificial Artefact from so there we have the we only keep the repository which are safe to use analysis by the AIR B board and then we can use them so 

Speaker 2  (12:22)
But this is jeffroins used for saving the architects right? But when you post the application, it's like the builds So you are keeping the films also in the article. 

Speaker 1  (12:39)
In the difficult versions in the database plunging. Given the versions in the database were streamed out secure. See library wise. 

Speaker 1  (12:50)
We are using keeping it from the data gifts. I'm not sure about the cloud then how they're sickens. 

Speaker 2  (13:05)
Can you tell me like what was your day-to-day role in this whole application? 

Speaker 1  (13:11)
Yeah, so we get the record from the product owner we I create the documentation around it and the documentation I have to specify the class names and the things that needs to be changed. Basically we get the epic and then I Created documentation around, so once oil, everything is done. What are the things that we need to change and I work out accordingly. 

Speaker 1  (13:36)
On the YouTube stories, we have 

Speaker 2  (13:40)
Okay, so any platform here is link for tracking the task. 

Speaker 1  (13:44)
Yeah, yeah, you're using the 0. 

Speaker 2  (13:48)
How much you're comfortable working in a working with AI tools and ids. 

Speaker 1  (13:57)
Sorry. Which tools? 

Speaker 2  (13:59)
AI tools, and ID 

Speaker 1  (14:02)
Hi, can you specific that AI tools? 

Speaker 2  (14:06)
For example, cloudy cursor or vs in vs code. If you use a copilot 

Speaker 1  (14:12)
Oh, okay. I am comfortable with it. We are using the copilot. 

Speaker 1  (14:17)
Also, the Jennifer Jenny grew used with a database 

Speaker 2  (14:24)
And have you worked on any traditional AI ML application? Yeah, I did that. Can you explain me about the projects? 

Speaker 1  (14:37)
Ok. Ok, let me recall that because we're using the Great and boosting methods, sampling random forest method. That was there in be one of the applications that we were using it. 

Speaker 1  (14:54)
Ko diver analysis, the I completely forget. I mean, I can tell you what I have used there. I forgot the name problem that you are solving. 

Speaker 2  (15:14)
The project name or when you have worked on this project. 

Speaker 1  (15:16)
We are working on the boss and we think that was led to the msme where we were. Ok, sorry. Reverse, we were failing the I forgot a town sorry. 

Speaker 1  (15:37)
Kind of classification thing. We would do so whether the things are matter or not matter. Okay, those things we were doing it. 

Speaker 1  (15:48)
So based on that, we have what I have used is the random forest there for the initially steps. So initially we are checking the missing values. Then, the kind of shape that we data that we are processing the relationship, then the feature engineering that we have done out of the columns okay, poor extracting the data, and keeping only the relevant columns there, then we did it using the random forest for checking the accuracy prevention required value. 

Speaker 1  (16:28)
Everything. Okay, and then we tried the other approaches also using the boosting methods also just to check whether they're increasing through or not. So once all these things think that I done done 

Speaker 2  (16:43)
It's a boosting for gradient hoisting, and how it works. 

Speaker 1  (16:48)
Yeah, so gradient boosting is worked on the sequential method where it treats the trees and with one tree checking the Errors from the previous 3. And then it evolved Over time, so let's say if one tree is having some error the next thing to live is and the next other treat relief is so that's how the boosting method works. 

Speaker 2  (17:18)
Have you gotten excited? 

Speaker 1  (17:22)
Yes, I have used that exhibit exhibit LG boost cat boost on this. 

Speaker 2  (17:29)
Continue, tell me simple difference between Hg boost and light BGM and random forest. 

Speaker 1  (17:38)
Our random forest is kind of different thing. It worked on the bagging. So first it will first, it will check whether the Yeah, first, it works on the ensembling methods in the banking methods. 

Speaker 1  (17:55)
It will create the parallel trees, right? So and once it generate the output, it will combine an apple and give it to the give that a particular output to the user. From Pita boosting method as a told you right. 

Speaker 1  (18:10)
Check the previous error first and then evolve. And what's the difference between LG rose and the cat hosting method like GB basically take only few parameters. Xiaomi recall, but Sorry, I'm completely forward. 

Speaker 1  (18:27)
The difference. 

Speaker 2  (18:45)
I'm so earn, you walked on the auel cloud, right, so have you worked on pleasure? Understood you 

Speaker 1  (18:55)
Azure ML studio. Mobile match using I want to know the your data factory end Database. 

Speaker 2  (19:14)
Can you tell me how you are deploying the models and using it for inference and how you are maintaining the model versions of the model. 

Speaker 1  (19:25)
So for the deployment, we are using the database only. We have created the unity catalogue of defrod, and the unity So that's how we were keeping the versions also maintaining the version models there in the database itself. So We're not using anything other than the database. 

Speaker 2  (19:51)
So when you deploy a model, what are the stages of the model can be done in database? 

Speaker 1  (19:59)
The stages in the sense 

Speaker 2  (20:04)
When you first Put the model in the database, there are some labels or stages. You can say Which function? Which model is currently using which version of the model you are currently using or you deleted the model or 

Speaker 1  (20:20)
I'll talk about the ambulance. 

Speaker 2  (20:23)
Knots in the database itself. So in the database, you go to the model Models model screen, you see the model, right? Then, you see the version of model beside the version of the model. 

Speaker 2  (20:36)
There is some labels are written here. So those labels like basically, there are 3 levels. Which determines which model you are using in production? 

Speaker 2  (20:47)
Which model you are staged? Which model is deleted or are chived? 

Speaker 1  (20:53)
Yeah, I've used. I've seen advertisements. 

Speaker 2  (20:59)
How these models are related to the experiments 

Speaker 1  (21:04)
Oh, yes, so models are basically for the experiments we have the ML flow that is, we are tuned hypertuning the model basically is some parametres. Let's say example for the random forest, we can change the depth sample size leaf size all those things. And we can. 

Speaker 1  (21:30)
With a multiple model version, we can specify the different parameters here, and we can log that in the middle flows So something like that, you can 

Speaker 2  (21:43)
If and what are information about an experiment we can store in the experiment. 

Speaker 1  (21:51)
Yeah, there are multiple like. I mean, the R square value usually take things into months region for the regulation. Then, we have the accuracy decisions. 

Speaker 2  (22:08)
To these are metrics, apart from metrics, envisaged information. 

Speaker 4  (22:16)
Jaise, aapko. 

Speaker 1  (22:18)
Vishka Bhai meeting Chal Rahi. What are the other parameters that we can keep in the database? I'm not sure about it. 

Speaker 1  (22:32)
We're sending the mattresses. And showing them contract dashboard, but Apart from that, I do for the experiment. 

Speaker 2  (22:52)
No question on the lack of the Agentic AI school. How you enable monitoring in the agents 

Speaker 1  (23:04)
Sorry, how do I enable monitoring? 

Speaker 2  (23:07)
Monitoring. 

Speaker 1  (23:08)
Wow, okay, so that's the thing that we what we really do is we Apart from the basic parameters, we keep the PSI okay, and then we keep the KL divergence ratio, we keep the gas ratio. 

Speaker 2  (23:28)
Monitoring, how? 

Speaker 1  (23:34)
How do I make a message? 

Speaker 2  (23:36)
Yeah, where this KPI is, our matrices are like visualised or stored. 

Speaker 1  (23:43)
That is there in the that is getting populated in the in one of the table we are populating from there all this thing using the end notebook so notebook that we have scheduled it on the everyday basis using the workflow. And although mattresses are coming inside the delatable, only Yes, story. 

Speaker 2  (24:12)
How about the matrices of the LLM that you use for the Chatbot? Like what is the usage? The token usage only token consumption and Honest thing saw you keep in monitored on that 

Speaker 1  (24:27)
Yeah, so we're calculating all those things on the notebook. Only from the notebook, it is going to the database. Okay, always think that we're again calculating it. 

Speaker 1  (24:39)
I mean that's a change of calculation that we are doing through the notebook. 

Speaker 2  (24:49)
Monitoring tools like lanks, may land fuels. 

Speaker 1  (24:53)
How can I use a landscape? 

Speaker 2  (25:00)
Okay. Yeah, I'm pretty good with the interview. Abhishek. 

Speaker 2  (25:07)
You have any questions from your side. 

Speaker 5  (25:12)
Voting I think you're open to work with result. You don't have any constraint as shifts in the movie. 

Speaker 1  (25:18)
Yeah, I can tell me the shift time, please. 

Speaker 5  (25:22)
The dustbin is went to the US, but hopefully this shift. I mean, as per if Indian, it would end by 998. 

Speaker 1  (25:31)
9 PM to. 

Speaker 5  (25:34)
It starts at 10 9P. 

Speaker 1  (25:36)
Ok, stop. Ok, fine? Yeah, good. 

Speaker 5  (25:41)
Ok, you can well share the feedback. So then we'll see. Thanks again, thank you. 

Speaker 5  (25:47)
Thank you. 
