aishwarya.k@genpact.com
yukti.malhotra@qmail.quesscorp.com
Speaker 1  (01:24)
China Veen Hyderabad. Hello, hello, everyone. 

Speaker 2  (01:31)
A hi screen. 

Speaker 2  (01:50)
Raveen Kapoor please camera. Let me take the screenshot. Is me and I'm done with a screenshot? 

Speaker 2  (02:02)
You can get it Thank you. Thank you. I could just give you 1 minute just 1 minute. 

Speaker 2  (03:03)
Aha. 

Speaker 1  (03:08)
Yeah 

Speaker 2  (03:12)
So far, guess how are you doing today? 

Speaker 1  (03:14)
Yeah, I'm doing good. 

Speaker 2  (03:15)
Thanks to thank you so we can here. We think today, sir. Nice to meet you and we'll be spending this next 1 hour understanding. 

Speaker 2  (03:24)
What exactly you are doing? Okay and puts your take to activities are into your project and if you again if you have any questions related to the project or 20 thing you won't ask him. We can be discussed at all and then passed last 510 minutes, okay. 

Speaker 2  (03:43)
Sure. So just if you can provide me a digital intro about your correct day-to-day activities, what exactly you want to be there? Doors means that I more interested in what you are doing to the entire team. 

Speaker 2  (04:01)
Not about we are the entity is doing what is your government. What is your contribution into the project into the team? What type of problems you are solving there. 

Speaker 2  (04:10)
Okay about it and I will use it further. 

Speaker 1  (04:15)
Yeah, so currently I'm working with emphasis, which is the project that I'm working on is into the educational domain. Okay. So I have total years of experience around 14 okay, before that I was working with a gene packed as well close to 9 years. 

Speaker 1  (04:34)
I was working there as mogass 10 years, but currently if I talk about my day-to-day activity. So currently I'm working as an individual contributor here, but my team sits in all in London and we are working on agile. Basically, so we have the scram master peers, so I get we get the required from the pos only and then we use to have that. 

Speaker 1  (05:02)
Agel ceremony is all so I have worked as a data engineer before, but switch to a data. Science, where I have worked with, mostly with eds, okay, mostly with the performing the LLM's build on the LLM's models. Done some modelling also in so created some of the models out of the classification models I have created. 

Speaker 1  (05:29)
Apart from that, we have created the pipelines idea of pipelines. Currently, we are working with data bricks, emblem. All these things deployment, I'm not doing it, but if I get chance I will, I will, but availflows, we are using it. 

Speaker 1  (05:44)
And apart from that, the application is more into the Yeah, agentic. Based. Basically, we get the we have to evaluate the performance of the customer service agent. 

Speaker 1  (05:59)
So we have multiple parameters, we have the so we have the review board also ARB board where we have to present them. They can like they are the smmes of our they will going to evaluate the exactly what our model is, perhaps and how they will evaluate. So we will just compare both the models, and then we re treatune. 

Speaker 1  (06:23)
That then we have the G artefacts, where we are G frogs, where we are keeping all our repositories there for the security purpose, and all the models that we built has been audited by them ARB team. So that the information credentials could not be leaked. Also, we are adding some branches on their model side so that it cannot leave this sensitive information we are doing the feature from feature engineering extraction to THE building the model, creating the pipeline. 

Speaker 1  (07:00)
So all these things I am doing. 

Speaker 2  (07:05)
Okay, this is good to know. I was just going through your resume just for you to understand few things here. So you did be our education into 11 till 13, yeah Was at a pcm? 

Speaker 2  (07:23)
Is it 

Speaker 1  (07:24)
No, no, it was B.Tech. 

Speaker 2  (07:28)
Beta, how come Beta completed in 2 us and 11 to 13? 

Speaker 1  (07:32)
No, it was Sorry, 9 2 13. 

Speaker 2  (07:39)
The inventory 11 to 30. So I was thinking, like, how will be I completed it? Okay, it was my input for me, right? 

Speaker 2  (07:50)
Yeah And then you have you started working in 

Speaker 1  (07:55)
Yeah, fa is as young. It was a finance company. Okay, so there I was working as a data engineer. 

Speaker 2  (08:06)
So you were doing me the 9 to 13, and you started job into June 11. 

Speaker 1  (08:10)
Yeah 

Speaker 2  (08:12)
So in between of your recent, you were working full-time job. There is it 

Speaker 1  (08:20)
No, I started with them on 2014 around. Okay? 

Speaker 2  (08:25)
Mentioned again, here, 11. There are so many discrimines here, prakhani. 

Speaker 1  (08:30)
I need to check 

Speaker 2  (08:32)
Yeah, please please check because ICI management is now showing 11. You are saying 9 240 so it is around like second year you started walking into accomplish so it's presenting that one okay and then it was serious you started to pay 50 like babies check back, you are mentioning you both get to check okay, check back more stillly used work from one7 till. 23 till 21. 

Speaker 2  (09:04)
Again, this is a disco procedure into seniors speciality. You worked till December 2017. 

Speaker 1  (09:09)
No, that was a project of the 

Speaker 2  (09:11)
Impact on 7th January 

Speaker 1  (09:12)
Your jacket to death was the project of the gene pact CS was the project of the gene bank. 

Speaker 2  (09:17)
India's speciality, yeah, sebs. Was the project object objects? Okay? 

Speaker 2  (09:22)
Because, okay? Alright, and you're some murder, right? You are working into the right advocation. 

Speaker 2  (09:47)
So right now you are working into emphasis. 

Speaker 1  (09:50)
Yes, into offices. 

Speaker 2  (09:52)
Internships. Okay, and you make sure what if the tools and technologies taken all those things you are working right now there and this is this is good. So are you aware, about the tools and responsibilities, particularly, if you have any questions on that one within I can tell you about this and then we can proceed further. 

Speaker 2  (10:09)
If you have anything else, I can. 

Speaker 1  (10:12)
J you can please tell us this also. Yeah, you can tell me about it. The roles and responsibility. 

Speaker 2  (10:22)
So this story is actually a senior or particularly so, you will be expected to communicate with the clients. To understand the requirements, what exactly needs to be solved. And then the delivery aspect of it like what needs to be kind of people we need into the team. 

Speaker 2  (10:38)
How we are going to take the solution and do end and day to decommication with the client. What is the you know, with the assign format or an HDFC format? We are ready to use this. 

Speaker 2  (10:50)
So are we going to achieve those particular stages to make the solution act, multiply the solution? So entire delivery, you will be Absolutely. Along with this, there will be things where you would be required to do the, you know, some sort of level of development and to guide the Child members to perform the developments. 

Speaker 2  (11:13)
Okay, no, can sure I know you are okay with the definition. 

Speaker 1  (11:19)
No no, I'm good and things just like you're okay this yeah I'm okay with us. Yeah 

Speaker 2  (11:27)
Alright, so just coming to this first part of which you are you have mentioned about it? You work with the cloud technology stuff as end up was in which only true services you mentioned. S and Landa. 

Speaker 2  (11:38)
So are these 2 only work or some other services below two-year-old? 

Speaker 1  (11:43)
So I work with the their multiple, like lambdas. As 3 lambda, step functions ecmrs, the glue also that you are using it, but we switch to these pathside. Okay, our data bricks, so we're not using it. 

Speaker 1  (12:01)
Yeah, these are the few that I've worked in. 

Speaker 2  (12:05)
So What you were contributing these services, or it is like you were maintaining those services. What exactly the work was done to these services? 

Speaker 1  (12:13)
I support it, not configuring it but we are using it apart from that. We are using the SNS quiz. Also all the things that I mentioned, but sometimes there is a need to create it so we will have to create it as part of the cli and everything. 

Speaker 2  (12:32)
So it's okay. I need a new version of it. We can provide what exactly you are to me to that area so it will sends or anything any service to mention. 

Speaker 2  (12:45)
What exactly is your you know? I'll be contribution. That is I am more interested because that is what you will be doing here also, right as you what you are trying out doing that is more and you are working as a manager there or you are working as a Ic role potentially, you are performing. 

Speaker 1  (13:02)
My destination is manager, but I'm working as a Ic rule. Only. 

Speaker 2  (13:06)
MI0 right then, when we saw always you right? It's only one person which is working. Okay, so what I can be like into SNS or into laptop functions, what I think we were solving there if we can keep it. 

Speaker 2  (13:20)
IDM O. 

Speaker 1  (13:22)
So I mean, I need to talk about my application then so it's an application. It's at 2 part. Okay. 

Speaker 1  (13:29)
First is the that it is consumed by the teachers and the students, and there they have less different sets of. Question air where they need to answer it? And then so basically we have the system like the Kafka built-in ok, then the pipelines built-in basically the SG pipelines, not the ST pipeline but the night running job and the data we are dumping into the S3 is only as a file and then they are keep on moving. 

Speaker 1  (13:57)
We have the multi hop architecture there. And those architecture based, then we are transferring the data from raw to the golden layer. And then we are, as a team, the ML side, we are consuming it. 

Speaker 1  (14:13)
And then in some parts we are using snowflakes or parts we are using red shift. And then we are sending a gear to the endline, and then some parts we are sending the gear to the sftp for the to the stakeholders for reporting and so we have different debium for the cdcs, everything we are doing it if I talk about the other things which is there is their Delta pipelines built-in okay, I in data bricks or I am talking about the data bricks site. Some data bricks side, we have the um, multiple notebooks. 

Speaker 1  (14:46)
Okay, the idf pipelines also consuming those notebook and breaking the pipelines. That's other thing, and if I talk about the lambdas there, then we have different services, like Java services which are consuming the APIs of the models. Okay? 

Speaker 1  (15:03)
And those things we have greater than multi or multi-service architecture. There so basically we are using the higher external architecture there and in the micro services with multiple ports and adopters. And then we are using that using that micro services, we are consuming the APIs and listed down the all the all the requirements that we are doing sets angular API, which I talked about REI RB team, which uses that UI so all the question that we have consumed consumed by the listed down by the auditors we just showed them, and then they give the ranking on what the model predicts. 

Speaker 1  (15:47)
And once everything finalised then comes into the ML team what they are doing is they are doing the eds on top of it so on the Ed side we are sorry on the Ed side we are creating some feature extraction feature building. Okay and then once those are fine lines the data is cleaned. Then we are creating multiple models. 

Speaker 1  (16:09)
Okay on those models Then, we have the flow comes in where we are. Last week, last year's listing down the best performance performing model using some parameters like accuracy, precision recall and F1 scores. So these are the few parameter that we are doing it funds. 

Speaker 1  (16:28)
The best model gets predicted. Then, we are retuning it on the second part where we have the agentic model where the sales comes in and where we are. Garh interest, giving the feedback to the client. 

Speaker 1  (16:43)
Ok. So on the client, whether um, there are multiple parameters like amathetic services. And those parameters that we checked in, we have created a prom templates there than embedding Pop templates, and then we have the vector dB that we are scaling it pine dB. 

Speaker 1  (17:00)
So once all the data is there with a prom temples, we are listed on multiple models in the prompts, and those prompts. Are comes in into picture and based on that, we just give the ranking to the agent. So this is mostly the overview of my application is what we are doing it right now. 

Speaker 2  (17:20)
Ok, so you're using the model onto the which platform currently, and which model you are using mentioned about? 

Speaker 1  (17:27)
Um, which model means AI mean you talk about the llms? PM yeah, we're using 

Speaker 2  (17:32)
In generally I remember more any foundational model or anything you paid by yourself? 

Speaker 1  (17:37)
We were using the group one earlier but we switched to the OpenAI one because of the tokenisation and the costing issues. That's we're using that. So where 

Speaker 2  (17:50)
Where is this model currently deployed? 

Speaker 1  (17:53)
Yeah, it is deployed in production. The data breaks itself. So using the 

Speaker 2  (17:59)
Through the data of database environment 

Speaker 1  (18:01)
Yeah, and the database, environmental and 

Speaker 2  (18:03)
How this Kebab, being and all those things are currently managed into republics. 

Speaker 1  (18:07)
That's that I'm not taking a I'm looking at it. That's a different team, which is doing the deployment. Okay, it's in that detail. 

Speaker 1  (18:14)
Remember not a part of it. 

Speaker 2  (18:17)
Not part of the deploying the modern system. 

Speaker 1  (18:18)
Correction, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (18:21)
Do you have any experiences to that area? By the way. 

Speaker 1  (18:25)
There's an no I'm learning it. It's a part of the data engineering thing, but I'm learning it. I have no exposure on that. 

Speaker 2  (18:35)
And who is doing the more monitoring right now? 

Speaker 1  (18:38)
We are we are creating the pipelines. 

Speaker 2  (18:42)
Okay? And what type of poetry you are doing there? 

Speaker 1  (18:45)
We were doing it like we were evaluating the matrices that we have told you right so we were creating the models classification matrix, so we are mostly focusing on the recall values there. We don't want to miss the, uh, false negative. So that's the overall thing 

Speaker 2  (19:10)
So only the recalls you are looking forward. Just 2 minutes back, we were talking about the apple score and this pencil. And also like, are you looking at those values also? 

Speaker 1  (19:21)
Yeah, we are looking for the processions. Have funny score? Ok, we were looking for the trade-off between the precision and the recall. 

Speaker 1  (19:31)
So those things will 

Speaker 2  (19:34)
A kind of between The president can be equivalent. Then what refers to us. 

Speaker 1  (19:40)
FM score is just a just create a balance between the precision and the recall value. Okay? So let's say, if our model is giving high accuracy and the low recall value, then we need to check for the affine score. 

Speaker 1  (19:58)
TuneIn. 

Speaker 2  (20:04)
Score is a mean of both precision and ticotile. Yeah, correct, isn't it? Have you worked with any service like camel flow, saysmaker or cube flow? 

Speaker 2  (20:19)
Any of 

Speaker 1  (20:21)
Message yeah, we are using the ML flows. We have done the sagemaker before long time ago. But we are using the mil flows 

Speaker 2  (20:31)
And what exactly we are doing in trouble? 

Speaker 1  (20:33)
Yeah, he is an excellent flowers. We are it's for the hyperlapse parameter tuning that comes up with a best model. So just the model versions we have listed down. 

Speaker 1  (20:42)
It will automatically generate the report for the best performing model. That's overall. 

Speaker 2  (20:53)
I wrote it those scripting of tending the modules and magnifying the best model who created our scripts. 

Speaker 1  (20:59)
We are going to walk, we're I mean I mean, it's it's already we've been treated, but we are refining it enhancing it. That's calculating the model. Financing, the model rates already greater 

Speaker 2  (21:15)
So what is the enhancement you are doing there and to improve this work into private? 

Speaker 1  (21:19)
Yeah, not in the able flow, but in the models. Okay, so how we can tune it better. So in the model side, we are doing it to automatically reflect in the ammuse. 

Speaker 2  (21:28)
Report, so just give me an example. I don't for the So it's not due to 

Speaker 1  (21:37)
So in the models we have listed down the problems. Okay, one prompt for the empathetic one from the Self services, one for the relevant question era, I mean, there are multiple parameter. So those versions we have created and those prompts if we are not accurately answer that answer that exactly the exact exact question answer. 

Speaker 1  (22:02)
Then, we have to make that promise better. Okay, that's the first thing. And the 

Speaker 2  (22:09)
Often is something you pass at the time of Question Answering, right? Correct. It is not related to model monetary. 

Speaker 1  (22:17)
Not exactly. Yeah, it's just a prompt. We are listened down there. 

Speaker 2  (22:21)
So prompt is something when you pass the question to you to the already trained what to deploy more at times not setting the problem right, and getting the answer generated out of it. Then, you find there is an issue. The answer is not right. 

Speaker 2  (22:35)
And then you do something with your model. 

Speaker 1  (22:41)
Yeah, so judges. We're tuning the throms only. So here we are, we are tuning, the watch promise, something difficult. 

Speaker 2  (22:50)
Work for the lml model. We are just studying the prompts of saying that 

Speaker 1  (22:54)
Nothing else we are doing. 

Speaker 2  (22:56)
And the nlm model, which is being used, is it a foundational model train on your raw data, or it is 

Speaker 1  (23:01)
It's a classification. 

Speaker 2  (23:03)
Models set. 

Speaker 1  (23:04)
Yeah, it's an LLM model only, but gives the classification on the matter, not parameters parameters. So if it is, as I told you one parameter is empathetic, so it will be met or not. Based on that we check that just a classification. 

Speaker 2  (23:21)
30 classification, thank you. Doing it to pass the prompt and how this thing like when you are passing the prompt to your lung model, how you are integrating your prompt in between you have multiple words of procurement, right, how you are ensuring that this prompt needs to be sent along with the user query to the lm, to get the answer. 

Speaker 1  (23:42)
Ok, so the architecture is like we have the question here then we have the chunking. Word embedding vector database comes in in the detectivated database. We are sending the on the chain on the chain we are sending the Question along with the prom, ok. 

Speaker 1  (24:02)
And then gives the output okay, that's that's the sorry I missed your question. What was that? 

Speaker 2  (24:09)
So a question shows that you have multiple purchases of props available, right? I sector query, let's say I'm asking some question to the model about a classification, whether this image is a door or a cat, right? It's an animal. 

Speaker 2  (24:25)
Or it's a bird or it's a human or what it is right. So I just Put an image or some information about it? I sent it now. 

Speaker 2  (24:36)
You have multiple versions of your prompt coming able to write, which is needs to be captured along with your context inside it, to be important to answer the question. So how that probably being selected there 

Speaker 1  (24:48)
That's the logic we've Put in in the notebook. Ok, so based on the so in between the Leh m's and the prompts we have the embeddings also that is summarising the context basically and based on that we have created a lanchan also in between so that is giving the flow flow lie I mean, give us the flow whether it need to pick that cat or a dog. Okay. 

Speaker 1  (25:14)
So that thing we are doing once you have the summarising context, then we send it to the album, not that directly promising. 

Speaker 2  (25:23)
So you are getting the context out of vector right? You have 

Speaker 1  (25:27)
On yeah, I mean from the similarity check. We did it, but we are using the burden between then encoder model for summaris. 

Speaker 2  (25:38)
So it's encountered department, so it's just the tip. Exactly. 

Speaker 1  (25:45)
We are choosing choosing the encoder and decoder model which is bird, but LLM is mostly into the decoder model on So it basically predict the next word, ok, that LM do, but for summarising thing. Okay, we are using the bottom there before the 

Speaker 2  (26:06)
For a bidding saying you are using blood 

Speaker 1  (26:08)
No, not for the embedding embedding, we have the other model, which is OpenAI model only once the embedding is done. Then, we are sending D embeddings to the vector dv. For a storage then prompts, we are sending it there when we are comparing their similarity. 

Speaker 2  (26:23)
Vispect, TV's. 

Speaker 1  (26:25)
We are using the pine db spine condition. 

Speaker 2  (26:30)
And where is it deployed? 

Speaker 1  (26:33)
It is deployed in the That's not sure. 

Speaker 2  (26:42)
And the context and the data is stored into the electro database. Currently, if subbie cities are categories, targeted and how these storage is being used. You know, make sure that it is persistent and you are not losing any, you know, data already stored it to be a bit sound, it is that being handled right now. 

Speaker 1  (27:00)
Right now, we have the indexes right in the In the vector Devi's so first we greet the index, it will go into less down all the queries, all the vectors. Okay into that indexes. So we have the replications. 

Speaker 1  (27:14)
Also, we have done the replications, and all those things had been done employment in India. 

Speaker 2  (27:23)
What's the answer is now sent question is sent to the lm model and your model answered your question. Then, use it. We are checking whether this answer is provided rightly or not right fair then you are doing the ensments who is doing that part of checking the course answers. 

Speaker 1  (27:39)
Yeah, so there is a AI TV team. So there's checking it. They are the smashes which will they will provide the correct list whether the whatever the model predicted and whatever they have predicted that then it's come to us. 

Speaker 1  (27:54)
And then we verify it. 

Speaker 2  (27:57)
Can you verify it? And 

Speaker 1  (27:58)
Read further train mode. 

Speaker 2  (28:02)
We crop change the prompt, not the model you change the prompt which you actually and then you do it tune the prompt and then you ask back again to the border and then you see whether the results are getting popular to properly or not. And how you are ensuring here in between that the model is not able to 

Speaker 1  (28:21)
Yeah, so we have the rax pipeline wax are nothing but we're giving the all the context to the uh encoders encoder model. Okay if it needs some text file or something that we are providing you. 

Speaker 2  (28:39)
And once the queries being sent by the user to the model, and everything being done in between something happened. Let's say some network issues happened or something like that has happened there. So the process didn't complete. 

Speaker 2  (28:57)
So how we are ensuring that you will not start from the beginning back again and it will only start from very failed. 

Speaker 1  (29:07)
Ok, so you're talking about if we get the response and it's not able to provide the response again. 

Speaker 2  (29:12)
Good question. A query started doing the semantic search into respective B fighting the context, and here we failed. Somehow I'm at the at my side, I'll waiting for the response so it needs to retrain. 

Speaker 2  (29:25)
I don't want the user to do it back again to Put the quality back again right to get the answer. Because then it will go back again to my entrance to it, right? And it will duplicate the tokens to my model also planning the model. 

Speaker 2  (29:41)
Also, how can you 

Speaker 1  (29:43)
So we are, yeah, for that one. We are using the cache. We are putting down all the questions and the responses also That's the thing we're doing. 

Speaker 2  (29:55)
Which casualties are using 

Speaker 1  (29:56)
We were using it at all. I mean, I don't remember it. Sorry. 

Speaker 2  (30:04)
It's a threat but cash here only also only can solve the problem of similar questions. You are asking every single time, right? So you can keep cash and give you the answer of it. 

Speaker 2  (30:15)
I ask some questions. Similarly, questions you are asking, then can get you the answer type of public cash and it is not going to end a limit saying my question here is that when you ask the question in between finding the context at all, we just take It never reached to the lm at all, so it's a new Queen, sir. 

Speaker 1  (30:34)
Yeah, I mean, I'm not sure it's it may be the synchronous call. We are making it not sure about it. Tia alcheta. 

Speaker 2  (30:48)
Okay? And How you are heading right now? The security aspect of it like associate requirements, GDPR requirements. 

Speaker 2  (30:58)
Pig prompt injections. How is being entered right now? 

Speaker 1  (31:02)
F AF prom prediction, we have listed on the guardils. Okay, in the prompt and on the security side, we have the JSJ frog artefacts, which is audited by the auditors for the application, so we cannot download it anything on the fly from the cloud. So they verify it, then we will use it. 

Speaker 1  (31:24)
So that's how we are doing it. 

Speaker 2  (31:28)
And any pbi, information and apc. 

Speaker 1  (31:32)
No, yeah, these are filled. Then, these are women. These are done by the auditors only we are not doing it. 

Speaker 1  (31:42)
So we will get the requirement that we have to use that model because they have already done the auditing online. 

Speaker 2  (31:51)
So, and this application, which we are using right now. Is it a real-time based solution or it's a batch processing? You are doing there. 

Speaker 1  (32:00)
It's a bad processing. So we have the transcripts, we have already have the transcripts. After the call we received it. 

Speaker 2  (32:10)
Audio task task. 

Speaker 1  (32:13)
Textile text answer, but there is a curiosity. Software, which translate into the text Of the viewer view, reports 

Speaker 2  (32:23)
Again then you are using a text to do the met knowment kind of thing. So the health voters, what is the size of that match? You can tell me 

Speaker 1  (32:34)
Size is huge because Based on one ids, we have multiple calls. Ok, so we need to stitch down the data, removing all the unnecessary things. And then we create the fine-tuned data to our model. 

Speaker 1  (32:51)
It's going to be a couple of it comes in GBS okay. 

Speaker 2  (32:59)
Give an idea how many 

Speaker 1  (33:00)
Because we get the data into the database, we get the data into the database and the database. How can I tell that I'm not sure about it. 

Speaker 2  (33:12)
It's a series of time. We're thinking the data bank before the database yesterday. Yeah, for doing the 

Speaker 1  (33:18)
For the work correctly. 

Speaker 2  (33:20)
Okay? And how you have a number of tokens are being consumed right now. 

Speaker 1  (33:27)
We have the capping of like in the LLM. We have 1 million token, okay, but 1 million is being you consume by all our team. So So let's consume by all our team. 

Speaker 2  (33:43)
How is it happening at home? The topologic standpointing, climatic how it is happening. 

Speaker 1  (33:49)
We are doing it in our model. So chunkings, splitting all these things we are doing it, but on the tokenization side, we have the capping of I don't remember 

Speaker 2  (34:01)
But would you you need to reduce the talkers before passing into the motor society? Simply Put the entire 

Speaker 1  (34:08)
Then, across it to Indian, that's what we use. 

Speaker 2  (34:11)
Doctors say, so, how do you step in order those capitalizations? 

Speaker 1  (34:16)
Yes, so in the model we have used the encoder model also before sending it to the era. So that's what the this model is doing. Summarising the context Okay, producing the 2 countries. 

Speaker 2  (34:32)
To summarising the document is something will reduce the documents using what you are saying. 

Speaker 1  (34:36)
Yeah, it will not give the it will just give the let's say if we are putting 1000 token, it will reduce to the 100 tokens and send it to the lm. 

Speaker 2  (34:50)
Again, the one you are using is the bottombike yeah, but If you can just give me some idea about this part and GPT open open I GPT are using right? 

Speaker 1  (35:03)
Yeah, open ye. 

Speaker 2  (35:04)
What's the difference between these 2? 

Speaker 1  (35:06)
Yeah, bird model comes in. Okay, so bird model is basically encoder and decoder. And if I talk about the OpenAI, which is built on the self attention Concept, so that's the decoder only so it's task is to protect the next word. 

Speaker 1  (35:26)
But in the back before we were using bird distil bird, Robert bird. So all those things, we were first encoding it, then decoding it. And then we're predicting the next word on the next sentence, or maybe we are translating the thing if we talk about the Yeah, that's what time is calling me right now. 

Speaker 1  (35:50)
But there are a huge differences in the Open browser and search AI model and the board model. 

Speaker 2  (35:57)
But don't you think at the number of top concerns the huge data you are getting, but is not the right fit to do that particular task. It has an additional tokens, right? 

Speaker 1  (36:08)
Possible? Yes, sir. There is a context window basically. 

Speaker 1  (36:12)
For example, for our requirement, it is working that's why we are using it but maybe there are some challenges with it which I'm not aware of. I'm confused. 

Speaker 2  (36:26)
This is like right now. You are getting a gbs of data into your pipeline which you are doing through the best transformation. Let's say tomorrow the customer example to send you the terrabytes of data. 

Speaker 2  (36:37)
How will you handle it? 

Speaker 1  (36:39)
Yeah, so that's a part of the Data engineering thing, right? So first we'll create it to the chunks, open the chunks, we will have the um. We will come. 

Speaker 1  (36:53)
We will use the spark in between For parallelisation, of the data And petal distribution of the data, basically, and then we'll tune, that is park okay to basically at the end. We will need the contextual data. Ok, summarise conceptual data. 

Speaker 1  (37:14)
So if you're getting multiple regard, then we will distribute it to the multiple nodes that's a part of the spark, and then we will work accordingly, we will transform the data then. 

Speaker 2  (37:31)
Okay. And I think you had near the time. Also Got to see the description. 

Speaker 2  (37:39)
Here is Ok, have you worked with any information? Retrieve a lot. Text extraction kind of techniques. 

Speaker 1  (37:51)
Text retrieval, yeah, I mean 

Speaker 2  (37:54)
Information and trivial, let 

Speaker 1  (37:56)
Chandigarh, retrieval, yeah, I've used that. 

Speaker 2  (38:01)
In individual application, what exactly was the problem we solved there using the information. If we can give an idea? 

Speaker 1  (38:07)
Information retrieval is nothing but the there's a class right chain retrieval so that use the LLM S and the all the prompts. Um challenges I didn't, because that's a role of the umbilical cord. The ChatGPT, okay. 

Speaker 1  (38:24)
To bring that data from that context The challenges first thing is the cost of the tokenisation. That's the first challenge. Then, the then the type of cluster that we have to use. 

Speaker 1  (38:38)
Okay That can do the computation also one thing we faced it. Long time back was the because there is one API right? And the one API, if multiple people are hitting that that thing, we need to orchestrate or maybe we have different models right on the those model we are using the rays. 

Speaker 1  (39:02)
So on the raise, it is doing the multiple concurrency. Okay, I'm talking about a concurrent thing, so there we have used it. But there are a lot of challenges using the array. 

Speaker 1  (39:12)
Yeah, I mean, we have used the executive threats and everything so we have tried them. Dozens of challenges faster 

Speaker 2  (39:25)
Okay, I think I'm behaving one more question here onto the project. So I do side of it. So let's say you have a situation of to design a solution to start the delivery of a solution. 

Speaker 2  (39:42)
Let's say the problem statement is that the client is trying to solve something like they have instant punishment tools. Now they are getting incidents generated to it. Someone is checked in those incidents, taking some action to it, and then they are fixing the action. 

Speaker 2  (40:01)
Okay, right now it is taking a lot of time to do it. They have already created the runbooks as Sophies and all those stuff till the time. Yeah, good. 

Speaker 2  (40:12)
I'm saying Then, the client wanting you is to make an AI solution for this problem to Provide the Incident voice. It will go to my all the SOPs and unbooks to my past tickets. I will be the formation. 

Speaker 2  (40:44)
Technique, this looks like to this problem. That is how it was solved last time. These are the steps can be used to solve this particular issue. 

Speaker 2  (40:52)
I want to solve this problem now. The question comes here is techniques and solution we are going to use here to make this particular entire solution. Work second but I would be Do you need to solve this problem 3? 

Speaker 2  (41:06)
How much time do you need to deliver this particular project and the fourth is the project ban? How we are going to execute the entire 

Speaker 1  (41:16)
You got it? Yeah, got it. And basically you are automating the servicing ServiceNow tool, basically right where we list on all the incidents, and then it will automate without the human intervention you want that to be at least get the root card. 

Speaker 2  (41:35)
I don't want it to fix. I don't want it to be fixed. I want it to be mapped and Acknowledge identifying that this may be because of this by roots on this, the recommendation you should follow to get the issue. 

Speaker 1  (41:50)
Yeah, so there are multiple parts of it. First thing is that yeah, we can build that using the agent land frameworks for the orchestration. So, but the thing is like we have the documentation. 

Speaker 1  (42:06)
Okay, where we have previously solved those issues, or maybe if the new comes in, that will go to train that from the previous errors. Um, ok, so what we're gonna do is we will go to first list down the problems so okay. So classify classify those problems basically and based on the previous error that we have received. 

Speaker 1  (42:29)
Okay, so we will create the maybe the trainer test data, and then on that training data, we will Put down all the previous records. Okay, and then we will create a framework of the Lang chain on the Lang chain. We will decide okay if it is layered to the upcluster issue if it is led to the coding issues. 

Speaker 1  (42:48)
Okay, so all those things we will create. Basically, we will create trying to create the pipeline on those pipeline. We will dump down everything, then the all those things embedding vector databases that comes in. 

Speaker 1  (43:00)
Then, at the end, we will try to check the parameter whether it's hallucination, hallucinating it or maybe the vague answer. So all those things we'll gonna train it. But majorly we'll be going to use the if we can use the agenda with some tools with the tools we can list COK just go on, go to that document and find a whether they have received that uh solution from there or not so we will adjust a mix of the rack concepts. 

Speaker 1  (43:30)
Is just a mix of the agentic. It's just a mix of the llms, so all these things we will gonna combine with it. So then we can tune down all those things prompts. 

Speaker 1  (43:41)
Okay, I mean there are multiple things. 

Speaker 2  (43:50)
And about the project and deliberates estimations. 

Speaker 1  (43:54)
Yeah, I mean, um, so why I'll start with the data. How big is the data is? Then, we'll select the architecture thing. 

Speaker 1  (44:03)
Okay, I'll Put into the categories in the bins and on the based on A 

Speaker 2  (44:09)
So it is precisely 100. Let's say 100 tickets a month. We are getting 

Speaker 1  (44:15)
Under tickets, we have 300 tickets. 

Speaker 2  (44:18)
Under tickets per month. 

Speaker 1  (44:19)
100 tickets per month. Um, ok, so you want the what do you need? I mean, the timeline, we need to 

Speaker 2  (44:31)
Built-in a project plan available to create a project plan. How's the time do you leave to multiply this solution? But be the method you will be using to do the deliveries. 

Speaker 1  (44:43)
Um, ok, so first of all, we have to have the architecture of the project first that will going to take us about. 

Speaker 2  (44:52)
And we discussed already, you already mentioned power architecture, let's move forward to the project panel, the deliveries, please. 

Speaker 1  (45:00)
Um. Ok on the timeline, it will be. I mean, needs a month to build the framework and then 100 tickets if you're doing it. 

Speaker 1  (45:12)
Sorry I didn't get you question exactly. Or maybe I'm not expertise into it. 

Speaker 2  (45:17)
This is given, I'll give you an example. You need to go to a shock, buy a podless biscuit, okay so there is a planning required for fight. You need ₹10 first in hand then what you need. 

Speaker 2  (45:29)
It needs a clothes to bear. Then you need to go out and then there you need to look at some shops, go there. You buy the skill you come back. 

Speaker 2  (45:37)
But this entire Then, what you need, 15 minutes. Ethiro, entire timeline, 50 minutes to me. What is the estimation technology? 

Speaker 2  (45:46)
You need to get thinked for you, right? And how are you going to plan these are going to plan? Are you going by working by these days by this area? 

Speaker 2  (45:55)
And at this level? With whom I'll be doing this. Hello, that's how I'm going to do it. 

Speaker 2  (46:01)
That's a miss a plan, right, so a project is given to you, you need to plan it. You need to have some members to afford it. Right? 

Speaker 2  (46:09)
Someone is going to do some parts, someone is going to do some part. Someone is going to do some part right, and then I'll be designing the delivery I need a month 2 months 3 months one year, 6 months 2 years to deliver this particular project I will be doing it into a design session, I'll be doing some sprint by spread by spread by spread feature by feature. I am delivering it or I will be delivering a lot solution right? 

Speaker 2  (46:29)
That is what I am looking for. 

Speaker 1  (46:32)
Ok. Okay, so let's say, if my system has to Do 100 tickets ok at it? They are taking at around a week to fix it. 

Speaker 1  (46:43)
Now with that model with the agentic model, we'll gonna try to run down to the Maybe we can't do this. We need to do that, okay. So that's our ideal. 

Speaker 1  (46:57)
That will be the ideal goal, and then we will create a team of the detail engineering team than the we have. The ML teams. Those 2 teams that we're gonna work out so infrastructure site That's right. 

Speaker 1  (47:14)
Sorry, I lost you. Ah, are you able to hear me? 

Speaker 2  (47:22)
Hello, Bluetooth internet looks big broken, so yeah? 

Speaker 1  (47:29)
Ok, I was talking about, yeah, I am saying that. 

Speaker 2  (47:32)
If there's just completed in next 122 minutes. 

Speaker 1  (47:35)
Yeah, ok, let's say we have already tickets completed in the 1 week, then I'll try to run down it to 2 or 2 or 3 days. So we need a detangment team. We need the ML team and detinging team will go into look into the all the data sites ok. 

Speaker 1  (47:52)
The pipelines and all those things ML side will go into Create a Cricket story, all the tools that they are needed. So within a month or within we'll plan it. Accordingly, the sprint and everything on the data engineering side in the amulside. 

Speaker 2  (48:14)
I think I think we touching the time here now so I'm good to hear For Now. If you have any questions for me, I will give you the forum now please say for now. 

Speaker 1  (48:25)
Yeah, I mean, get tilted. Tell me about the project please. 

Speaker 2  (48:31)
So it's sort of one specific project. There are multiple projects of people. One of them which I just talk about. 

Speaker 2  (48:36)
You problem, we are going to solve. This is one of the problem we are planning to solve for some of the customers either some multiple other problem statements we have where we are going to do some document comparisons. And doing the agenda solutions for the, you know, clients and they are multiple agent AI solutions. 

Speaker 2  (48:56)
We are, you know, building right now. So The multiple projects it's not one single project available there around 1718 projects. Now in progress. 

Speaker 2  (49:07)
We have no kind of problems we are right now struggling. So Oh, I'm excited. 

Speaker 1  (49:14)
Sweetsen, to the M. L. 

Speaker 2  (49:19)
Yeah, it's included completely. 

Speaker 1  (49:22)
No, yeah, I'm good. 

Speaker 2  (49:25)
Yeah, that's all? 

Speaker 1  (49:26)
Yeah, thanks for your time. 

Speaker 2  (49:28)
Thank you, okay. Yeah, thank you. Thank you for having 
