jaskaran.singh10@infosys.com

Speaker 1  (00:02)
How will you go about designing this floor? 

Speaker 2  (00:06)
Okay, so with the air flow, you want to design a system which will automatically create the ticket out of the issue that they have resolved. Okay. Yeah, the flow will be the same. 

Speaker 2  (00:21)
Instead of the documents, I'll receive the logs. Look in the Chunky there with the ear flows. We have to create the tax correct? 

Speaker 2  (00:32)
So in the track Dax itself That's basically sending us the logs of the actual A. R uh where we have the alert system configured. I worked on that long-term bargain. 

Speaker 2  (00:47)
So where we're receiving the multiple logs, the log, so we're extracting, we were actually refined the data so that our LLM can get the context out of that instead of sending the whole log to the LM we were doing the fine-tuning of the um. Contactal data with the corresponding ID And then we are sending it to the we are creating the embeddings, and then we are sending it to the llms, to reprocess it to process it so once our LM is able to understand okay, what is the issue? What is basically we have created the agents in a workflow or in the approach at menu using the land rough, so where we have to define the state workflow, the starting Starting note locate than the conditional notes. 

Speaker 2  (01:40)
Also, we need to specify we have to specify the edges. Also, and we have to specify their roles. Also there then we call the run method graph that is steam as a method that we can call, which will tell us the step-by-step of what the actual illum is doing. 

Speaker 2  (01:58)
And then once it will know what the context is, what the error is, what the solution is, then we can create the Gera tickets from there on the application. Through the apers, okay. 

Speaker 1  (02:17)
So This model check. Would you allow an llim agent to generate an escal against productions near flake or a database? 

Speaker 2  (02:29)
Sorry. 

Speaker 1  (02:31)
Would you allow an LLM? Agent to generate an execute escal against production snowflake or a data breaks. 

Speaker 2  (02:40)
No, we went alive. 

Speaker 1  (02:42)
Okay, if let's say if you want to do that, what all controls you think must exist before you can approve this design or architecture? 

Speaker 2  (02:51)
Yeah, we have to design like we have to Add the Admin road, okay to some to some particular group, or maybe we have to be the RBA. C of some Delta tours on the category where user can only view the data. Okay for the Aren't you moving viewer? 

Speaker 2  (03:12)
Data on the administration has the right to execute those comments? It will I delete our job, so these are the things which will be taken care by the administration. 

Speaker 1  (03:28)
So what kind of access will you provide to that agent? 

Speaker 2  (03:34)
Yeah, U. So we, what kind of Okay, we have to restrict it with. If we find those delete, ok, or some drop keywords while taking a secret or something executing those. 

Speaker 2  (03:50)
For those, we need to guarantee the prompt in such a way that it should not execute them. Drop on the delete, all the tables, and also you need to check. For the actual portion is the user corresponding user has or not. 

Speaker 2  (04:09)
Which will be able to guarantee the port 

Speaker 1  (04:12)
Bye, bye, so let's say there's an agent, and it keeps calling the same tools repeatedly never completes the task. What technical safeguards would you build around this? 

Speaker 2  (04:25)
Yeah, we can try for the retry. So that I can think of if it is not, then it has to Okay, in the conditional edges, we need conditional loads. We need to specify the retrieve, and if it is more than 3 or 5, then it has to come out on the loop. 

Speaker 2  (04:45)
Something like that, we need to provide the logic. There This. I can think of right, but there might be a better solution. 

Speaker 1  (04:55)
And let's say, how will the operations know why the agent got stopped in case it stops. 

Speaker 2  (05:02)
Legent isn't found. Sorry sorry I didn't get you. 

Speaker 1  (05:09)
Amine amine lachem, previously agent, was keen, kept calling the tools repeatedly and never complete the task. Right? So in case if you Put some safeguards, and you know, you want to now the opportunity wants to know if at all, it gets stopped. 

Speaker 1  (05:27)
What was the reason for that agent to get stopped? So how will you check that? Or what do things will you do 

Speaker 2  (05:32)
So that's why we have the graph at a stream method which will go into give the actual logs of what agent is actually doing. And we have to design the module. Let's say it is, keep on calling the dependent to provinitives at the supervisor there or maybe the yeah, supervisor will find the supervisor we will left and we go to supervisor checking so there we can write that logic and the supervisor. 

Speaker 2  (06:05)
Something like that, we need to desire 

Speaker 1  (06:13)
Let's say again another example of just a scenario agent automatically restarted a failed ET and pipeline, and it has reprocessed the old files. 

Speaker 2  (06:23)
It is 

Speaker 1  (06:25)
Old states right? So some of the cold layer records got duplicated. So what would have gone wrong in the design? 

Speaker 2  (06:36)
Yeah, I mean, we have not crossed the incremental load correctly. Also, we have not handled the duplicates. These are the basic checks we usually perform, sending a data cross to the earlier layers. 

Speaker 2  (06:50)
Because we know that any in any time the if the job executes from the start, it will go into push the data to the tables and the data will be duplicated. Okay, so there are 2 ways to handle it, which we usually do first. Is we delete the current data from the actual terror and then we use the data. 

Speaker 2  (07:12)
Every time that's the one rate, or whether we have to use the water mark, to check the last processing date, and then we have to load the data from there. So through that way 

Speaker 1  (07:28)
Okay, let's say you want to, you know? Put down some task that the agent has to do, can you? Can you give me any 5 actions than an agent can do autonomously, and any 5 other actions, which would require a human approval. 

Speaker 1  (07:44)
Based on your experience of understanding 

Speaker 2  (07:48)
So 5 actions, which silically repeated 

Speaker 1  (07:53)
The fire, I mean, we are just listing on the actions that the agent can do right, so let's say if you can give me the 5 actions for a you know, data platform agent to do autonomously. And then similarly, another set of 5 actions which the agent can do but with human approval. 

Speaker 2  (08:12)
Yeah, as I told you right executing the comments something User cannot day agent cannot execute those Commands, that's the first thing, and where the user is calling the okay. The The LLM should know which tools to call. So based on that, we have to provide the context to the context of the LLM. 

Speaker 2  (08:41)
In the prompt, we have to mention it. So that's so that you can Call those tools okay, in a synchronous or a synchronous way. But 5 items you want to do Human, the loop vehicle added for our labelling. 

Speaker 2  (09:04)
Whether we are getting the correct data or not. I mean, for any validation, we usually do Did the agent can automatically call it? It can check the correct data data type if they are not matching or something. 

Speaker 2  (09:25)
I mean, I can recall it those things up. 

Speaker 1  (09:29)
Okay, that's fine. Okay, let's say you have 2. Have you used spark? 

Speaker 1  (09:41)
You have 2 sparked jobs, right? So one is processing 2 TV of data and finishing in 25 minutes. And there's another, you know. 

Speaker 1  (09:54)
Process, which another task which processes 100 GB of data and edit, takes 3 hours. So can you just walk me through? How will you investigate this and find out or going to be the cost? 

Speaker 2  (10:08)
So there are two things First I need to check whether it's a cluster issue or a data issue trial logging. I will check that hour. The clusters, a number of executors memory sports, relevant to the particular job. 

Speaker 2  (10:25)
Also I can see the, uh, that's the one I mean. If the cluster is fine and it has a sufficient memory, the jobs are not waiting in the waiting stage. I'm sorry the task. 

Speaker 2  (10:38)
Then, I'll check for the data issue and the data issue. I'll check the issue and the data. If it is stewed then obviously the other The executives take time to execute. 

Speaker 2  (10:50)
Uh, so we have to the solution would be the salting and the other Aq approach that we can mention it to the parameters, the number of partitions and everything. Who gives web data is finishing? That means it has the sufficient memories of everything. 

Speaker 2  (11:08)
Also, what kind of operations we are doing in najwal? So are using group Pi or some other exchanged, or the shuffling operations, are we performing extensively for these things we need to take care of. 

Speaker 1  (11:34)
Another one, like let's say your database pipeline ran for 8 months and Saturday. It is 5 times slower. 

Speaker 2  (11:42)
Uh, sorry, does not change. 

Speaker 1  (11:45)
There's a database pipeline, which ran for 8 months. Okay, and suddenly, it is now 5 times slower. Ok, there's no custom configuration change or even code. 

Speaker 1  (11:56)
They did not change, so how will you debug this or trouble choose? 

Speaker 2  (12:01)
Okay, there is a data bricks pipeline, which is running from last 8 months, but suddenly what happened? 

Speaker 1  (12:11)
I mean, it has just gone slow, suddenly, 5 times slower. 

Speaker 2  (12:19)
Okay, nothing else I mean, there is no data change, right? Yeah. 

Speaker 1  (12:26)
No code, no quote, change. No cluster configuration change I will not say data change. But you can, you can just see what all can be the possible cause 

Speaker 2  (12:38)
Yeah, I mean The volume of the data is increased or something, okay That would be one of the reason because if nothing has been changed. That means the data has seen If it is processing large volume of data, which is not handled in the code. 

Speaker 1  (13:03)
Any other? 

Speaker 2  (13:08)
Yeah, stunis, we have to check whether it's student or not. Date, I mean with, we have to focus on you on the data. What kind of data we are receiving of the actual spike of the data. 

Speaker 2  (13:22)
Are you in the region? 

Speaker 1  (13:25)
Okay, let me, let's see, let's say. You want to look at it the other level? What dashboards or metric should have been there or where you will see the alerts before he actually the user start complaining. 

Speaker 1  (13:41)
To whatever causes you mentioned right, let's say. How will you proactively identify this before user actually complete? 

Speaker 2  (13:50)
Thank you, yeah. Yeah, these actually issues actually come in. I was written on the application Basically, we were taking the spikes and just recall Through goods and the data area It actually takes to complete Okay, actually, we're checking these 5 time. 

Speaker 1  (14:42)
That is okay, that's okay, let's say, yeah, that's okay. Based on your experience, let's say. Have you seen any spark or victabics jog that completed successfully, but Tata produce the wrong output. 

Speaker 1  (14:57)
Have you seen that 

Speaker 2  (14:58)
Come out to emissions in the email or Generic 

Speaker 1  (15:03)
Keeping in general, also, you can see 

Speaker 2  (15:05)
It is producing the wrong driving in the table. Here's in the wrong data. Okay. 

Speaker 1  (15:15)
I mean, if you've seen it already, you can tell me them, because if you have not seen it, what can be the cause? 

Speaker 2  (15:23)
No, we have seen that sometime. The data Is wrong in the table team? Get through the pipeline or the any other changes. 

Speaker 2  (15:33)
But sorry, what is the question 

Speaker 1  (15:37)
True question is something like, you know, the job has completed successfully, but it has produced the wrong output. Now, job can do a lot of lot of thing, right? Done, yeah, so what can be the cause, you know, it shows its complete success. 

Speaker 1  (15:54)
Basically, it is it has done something wrong, but it is saying it has completed successful, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (15:59)
Yeah, upstream downstream, you need to see what has changed and something, so we need to dig up the issue. 

Speaker 1  (16:09)
So I mean, what all steps will you? What all things will you check-in your debuber process? 

Speaker 2  (16:15)
What are things I'll check? Let's say my quantity is, I'm just taking a simple example. Onvi, I'll take over 1ID I'm getting multiple records. 

Speaker 2  (16:28)
Okay, I'm just taking conceiving once in ivory, so that means I need to check the joints. What kind of joints it happened? Are we joining with the correct data or not? 

Speaker 2  (16:39)
Because it used to be having 2 rose now. It is giving me 3 rows. Is there a data issue? 

Speaker 2  (16:45)
Okay, what is the there in the epistem? And how what joints it has performed all those things we need to verify based on the logics. There are other several cases also, and this is calling this. 

Speaker 1  (17:02)
That is fine. And so let's say, okay, have you used Kakka by any chance? 

Speaker 2  (17:12)
Yes, I have broken up. But from last 23 years, I have 

Speaker 1  (17:17)
Okay, we'll just check just based on understanding and exactly times okay? So let's say Business is saying that there is no message which got lost. Okay, and the order is strictly to what as per the customer, which is required and patroport. 

Speaker 1  (17:44)
Anyways, let me just I mean you mentioned. You are not that you let me you know. Okay. 

Speaker 1  (17:59)
Okay, let's say you, I'll give you another. Let's say defect in the streaming transformation logic, let's say you are consuming only right, so defect and streaming transformation logic was found, and what you have to do is you have to replay the last 7 days events. So, you know, in your architecture, what should be there to make this, replace safe? 

Speaker 2  (18:25)
Okay, so last 7 days, data I need to replace 

Speaker 1  (18:32)
Yeah 

Speaker 2  (18:37)
Rock it so. We are maintaining the Messages, we have to maintain the messages. Okay, I'm just thinking of the snas. 

Speaker 2  (18:57)
I'm just considering data. Is the data flow to the downstream or not still there in the queue. 

Speaker 1  (19:04)
Let's say it didn't go to downstream. If it goes downstream, then investigation and other things will increase. So let's not go that way. 

Speaker 2  (19:11)
Yeah, we can imagine. We can replay the data to the This To the there is a URL for it in that afternoon, which we have to configure it so that we can see the 

Speaker 1  (19:29)
That is fair. That is fine. What I'm saying is, so your system should have some kind of design which will allow this replay to be a safe, yeah, so how will you? 

Speaker 1  (19:38)
What are things will you see? I mean, in case if you have to design it? Let's say tomorrow, if not the issue has not happened today, but tomorrow. 

Speaker 1  (19:47)
If this thing can happen, how will you make your system more resilient to it? Which will allow you to replay the messages without actually affecting the downstream system or other systems. Adopta, getta, getting corrupted and how you can avoid that. 

Speaker 2  (20:06)
No, I'm seeing this is a retention period the check that we need to add send the messages. I think that can take care of storing the messages there. For the number of days clinic Can you give me the offsets to the offset weekend? 

Speaker 2  (20:31)
Check what the number of messages from the last 7 days. Edit long time by convert. 

Speaker 1  (20:43)
That's okay. That is fine. Have you worked in banking only right? 

Speaker 1  (20:51)
Most of the time banking Okay, let's say, you know right, there's this sector there's having a lot of regulation compliance and controls, right? So let's say there is an auditor you know, and he asked, if you could show how, you know, markets risk score was calculated 14 months ago, not now. So and understand which all source fills were contributing to that score, and if at all, there was a change who changed it. 

Speaker 1  (21:24)
And which all reports are consuming that so what all things you feel and for this, too, for you to produce this kind of investigating data for the auditor. What all things should be there in your platform for you to, you know, support this kind of questions or auditing. 

Speaker 2  (21:44)
Yeah, I'm in the database. Usually logs. All the sorry I didn't get your question. 

Speaker 2  (21:51)
So you ask me to verify how the Leh M 

Speaker 1  (21:57)
No, no, see, let's say this is today. I'm an auditor. 

Speaker 2  (22:02)
Okay. 

Speaker 1  (22:03)
And I come to you, I ask you, okay, tell me, how was your risk score calculated 14 months ago? 

Speaker 2  (22:09)
Only 4 got country water score. 

Speaker 1  (22:12)
Come mortgage, risk code. Let's say mortgage risk core you. Your Sister is calculating that and how it was calculated. 

Speaker 1  (22:20)
14 years 14 years, 14 months ago, not now. So, and then when I say how it was calculated, you need to understand what all feels, it was consuming, how you, what was the logic behind that handling behind, calculating that score? So What are things you feel can be there or should be there in a platform for you to support this kind of auditing, usually auditing, can happen 6 months, one year, instead of 14 months, let's say, even 10 months ago if they wanted to know. 

Speaker 2  (22:52)
I'm in risk if we're calculating on the through the logic, or we're talking about specific to the LM only. 

Speaker 1  (22:59)
No, not, this is not related to lnm. This is specific to log 

Speaker 2  (23:04)
Drive into the logs, we usually check. Ok, in the splunk for everything. There wish we have to I mean, we have to strong. 

Speaker 2  (23:14)
We have to make the division strong with the law. And the logic changes yet to the volume also 

Speaker 1  (23:28)
Okay, have you have done any kind of masking of Pi? Okay, so let's say some customer information accidentally got embedded and indexed into a you know, vector database. So what you should do, let's say, in first few hours, you know, to overcome from that. 

Speaker 1  (23:51)
And what they design changes can prevent this from happening or re happening again. 

Speaker 2  (23:58)
Yeah, I mean, in the multiple steps, we need to perform the massing first is a reliable filter or a column masking in a database itself within the Delta team, also on the layers, with the prompting, we have to specify that. If there's any API information, just mask it. That's the order change, also in the evolution itself. 

Speaker 2  (24:23)
We have to encrypt that that data first Through multiple layers, we can add the marketing depending on whether we need 

Speaker 1  (24:41)
Okay. So okay, based on your experience, can you tell me any architecture design decision that you have taken, which let's say initially looked right? But then, after a year again and a 1 you felt that no, that was not right. 

Speaker 1  (25:03)
And with example, if you could tell me, maybe I'll have another follow question on that. 

Speaker 2  (25:10)
Yes, I can talk about one of the pipeline. Here we are having the their 2, where we have the origin data, okay, for one of the pipeline. There are BMT changes for the other pipeline and they both are not in sing, sink. 

Speaker 2  (25:30)
In the sense they were not. The timings were not same for both of the pipeline. But the user complained that I and MGF. 

Speaker 2  (25:40)
We are loading the data into the original data in the incremental way. Okay, so what after few months? The user complained that they're not receiving the correct data because we're joining the BMD table with the original data, so they're seeing the values for the new data only because every time the data comes in, we're not triggering the B mts ok BMT was trigger only. 

Speaker 2  (26:10)
When the BMT files arrived Which will be usually in a month? Or maybe in A Wave, 1 or 2 months? And that's how the BMT was loading and the other table, which is the original table, is we're loading it daily, okay with the incremental data. 

Speaker 2  (26:28)
So now also at the end in the combined one, we are aggregating or joining the BMT data equity, original data. So what happens that for some of the ids, which are processed 1 day before? Okay. 

Speaker 2  (26:43)
Here the BMT did not trigger but for the other one, which is the original data for few of the record, which is let's say trigger today, they were getting updated with the dnt. So the user updated that user said that I other AID were not matching with the data, so we analysed it, and we found out that the Timings of the bow, the beauty were not insane. That's how we solve that ugh. 

Speaker 2  (27:10)
That's the recent issue I worked on the LM issue, also like, I can talk about that as well. 

Speaker 1  (27:19)
Done that. It's fine. I have one last question from my side. 

Speaker 1  (27:27)
Say. You have, you know, in the current project. You see that there is a heavy cloud, which are clouds. 

Speaker 1  (27:37)
Have you used by the way? 

Speaker 2  (27:38)
Azure. 

Speaker 1  (27:42)
Votra, ok, let's say we talk about Azure itself, right? So, your portfolio manager comes and says that, you know, there is a very high cloud spending, you know, multiple cloud spending. There are multiple Genia pilots going on. 

Speaker 1  (28:01)
Some inconsistent KPI definitions have been provided, and this poor data quality, right? So and they say that we need to, we have 9090 days before you want to actually scale the current solution. So what all 5 steps will you take? 

Speaker 1  (28:22)
In priority. 

Speaker 2  (28:24)
Continue repeated, please. 

Speaker 1  (28:26)
Let's say you're hopeful, your manager comes and tell you there is a very high cloud spent, right? Yeah, you're the current cloud spent is very high, okay? And there are multiple geniots, there are inconsistent KPI definitions, data qualities, poor you know, you and you have 90 days before you want to scale your AI solution, right? 

Speaker 1  (28:52)
So what all will be your first 5 actions that you will take? 

Speaker 2  (29:01)
Okay, see you talking about the cost. First thing Today, we have limited, we have the deadline for production. What are the other concerns apart from the cost? 

Speaker 1  (29:19)
I mean, the data qualities did not good And the KPI definitions are not correct. 

Speaker 2  (29:26)
Yah, there are multiple things, right. So I'll go step-by-step. To the 0.75 I asked to create the spikes, okay? 

Speaker 2  (29:38)
Because in the spikes, we can do some experiment of Come with approach where we can reduce the cost of the LLM first time. Where we have to send only the required data to be available That's the one thing. Also the data quality issue. 

Speaker 2  (30:01)
I have to on the data quality. Obviously we are if using prompts we have to restrict or guardial with the data quality. I have to specify the how well the we are cleaning the data and what checks additional checks, let we're performing, while senior reared to the L. 

Speaker 2  (30:22)
M. Checking the context and everything Okay, data quality, we need to fix it so that incomes in the First, we'll fix the data quality issue. Okay, the last step would be the costing, and we have to reflect the code. 

Speaker 2  (30:42)
Everything competing, the dotted quality should be correct, and at least the happy part should go. Okay, then we can think about the costing of reducing the LLM cost to the required sentence of user, changing everything. That will take into consideration. 

Speaker 2  (31:04)
Apart from that For the jobs we will see the cluster, if we can, how well the cluster is, and if we can Tune some of the jobs through that cluster through the code code optimisation. I'm talking about Authority should be taken cost. These are a few things I will take the consideration. 

Speaker 1  (31:38)
Okay, yeah, that's it from Nice side. Do you have any questions for me? 

Speaker 2  (31:43)
Can you tell me about the project and the role 

Speaker 1  (31:47)
There are multiple projects for which we are hiding. Currently, so exactly which project and what might be Omar current profile details. I don't have that with me. 

Speaker 1  (31:59)
Another multiple, it's said banking only. So yeah. Any other questions? 

Speaker 1  (32:07)
Okay, great, thanks Pratap. Thank you for your time. Have a nice evening, thank you. 
