ddineshbabu@kaartech.com, k4korganizer@kaartech.com, nianjula@kaartech.com, recruitteam@kaartech.com

Speaker 1  (00:04)
So I run 14 years of experience. I'm currently working with the emphasis from last 3 and a 1 years, and before that, I was working with longest time. Several credit working on the January Project, but frojana was with t Eds, Muslims presently done the idiots, influence. 

Speaker 1  (00:30)
The projects applies some models. 

Speaker 2  (00:34)
And what if that idius, idias, what is that Eda. The data analysis exploration part okay 

Speaker 1  (00:49)
And so currently my application going into the education domain. But I have On the banking domain also majority on banking domain close to 90 plus years. And so my application is led to the Test test actors I will diagnostic test which is done by the student. 

Speaker 1  (01:13)
The older reports and get it Send it across to the multiple users that we have. And then we have basically the calf by multip architecture batching streaming, and then we have the data breaks majority, where we are having all the Delta tables stored with GVT catalogue configure. For accessing and We have the RBAC control access control And we have greater one of the chatbots, which is Yes, the project, which is later, where we are having the Chunky layer embedded layer through the adio pipeline that we have created, and then we have this fine-tuning of the chat box. 

Speaker 1  (02:11)
There's some parametric that we are exposing where to the ragas, and Gains, another risk, total rank, called this recall accuracy. All this A metric that we are exposing to So Yeah, I mean, currently I'm working against a lead before. And it's more into a where we are going to 15 years old sprint, at 3 months of BSI That's 

Speaker 2  (02:45)
Okay, can you explain a project or an assignment that you have done wherein you have used a foundation model? If you can walk me through the entire cycle of like the foundation model, how are you accessing it? And then how have you deployed, or how have you built the application around it, and how have you deployed the application? 

Speaker 2  (03:15)
I want to understand what sort of data goes in what sort of processing prompt engineering. Everything that revolves around if you have to develop an enterprise level application that majorly uses the foundation model. 

Speaker 1  (03:34)
I told you got my current project, so let's start with the all the documentations with different formats like PDF. Xmls, headox that are done that are coming through the calf car to the data bricks, and between the idea pipeline where we are 

Speaker 2  (03:54)
How is Kafka collecting them right from? Where is where this dropped? Or where do this documents present? 

Speaker 2  (04:03)
And how document? 

Speaker 1  (04:07)
Yeah, there's a separate application for it for dumping the data and from that application. It is doing the Kafka streaming to our this adless. Storage storage, so that's how we're getting the files from their E Tl S files. 

Speaker 1  (04:27)
We're receiving it and from IDL S we have the python building, which is collecting those data to the data breaks Delta tables. So this is how it is linked. Also, in some case, we are using the Hg also in S. 

Speaker 1  (04:46)
T. Yes. We have also triggered base whenever we have the file comes in into lot. 

Speaker 1  (04:50)
Now we have trigger the lambdas and through lambdas, we are dumping it again into the adls, same location, and then we have the pible built-in for the database to collect those files, and in what our application is doing, we have the chunking layer where we are retrieving those documents. And we are creating a sentence based this sentence aware Chunking method that we have used And that is basically creating the context for the LLM, and then we are embedding. 

Speaker 2  (05:28)
Which LLM are you using? 

Speaker 1  (05:30)
Yeah, we are using the open GPT model 45 minutes. So once we have that data with a chunking, then we are embedding those documents, and we are storing them into the data bricks provided vector vector DV. And so these are already these are all scheduled, and every day we are receiving those based on trigger, we are receiving those files and by weekly, we are triggering it to make sure the data is in sync, okay with the actual data. 

Speaker 1  (06:11)
With a correct data, and then we have the Okay, for the retrievals, we are 

Speaker 2  (06:23)
What is your chunking strategy? 

Speaker 1  (06:26)
Yeah, chunking, as I told you a sentence. Aware context aware class is there that we are using? Polluting the deliberators, or the separators, basically of how the sentence will break and from that it will go into break the next new lines out of it on next chunks, basic And then we have the in between. 

Speaker 1  (06:53)
Also, we have the chunking compressions that we are using. The high approach in some cases we are using the high approach. In some cases, we are using the embeddings of the queries that we have retrieved. 

Speaker 1  (07:10)
Are the documents we are using the okay? From the query, we are generating the Relevant chunks, and relevant chunks, how we're deciding it based on the hide approach where we're creating the through the Leh M small model, we're generating the prom from the for the L. M to generate the answer, and then it will matches with the embeddings document that we have. 

Speaker 1  (07:46)
That's the one compression that we are doing other one. We are doing is with simple embeddings. Just to make sure that our Chunks got compressed, and the context remained the same. 

Speaker 1  (07:59)
So that is one of the approach, and then we have for the retrieval we are using the land chain. I mean, the whole thing is in lanchain, only and for the retrieval QA class, we are retrieving it and then we are again doing the For the ranking, we were doing the pie encoders for the large documentation and then combined it with the cross encoder for the rank and for the searching we are using the dense approach in the dense one. We are using the BM25 for the sparse. 

Speaker 1  (08:33)
Keyboards, search and then your for the dense on. We are using bad weddings, then we are combining it with the ratio of 70 or 30% and then once we receive that data, we are doing the reranking and from the tree ranking, we are taking the top 3 and from so and then we are providing the output to the user. Apart from that, we are exposing the other matrices. 

Speaker 1  (08:58)
Metrics like we have the record value, which is actually checking the data from the groundt, the label data basically and the document and the response that we have received. Okay. And apart from that, we're exposing the accuracy, whereasing the reciprocal rank in what rank the correct data is coming into and we are exposing the answer relevance faithfulness, these are the houses I guess metrics that I am talking about apart from that, we are exposing the cumulative gains NDCG values latency value. 

Speaker 1  (09:40)
As 99 and 95 value error rate hallucination rate Yeah, these are the few that we are exposing. 

Speaker 2  (09:51)
Right? So you're using GPT models, right? What is the basic difference between GPT's OpenAI models and non OpenAI like lamas or something of that sort, right? 

Speaker 2  (10:05)
What is the basic difference and how would your approach? If you're using GPT or a Lama, how would what would change when if we have to Use Lama models, instead of GPT for the same application. 

Speaker 1  (10:27)
Okay. Talking about the difference from the actual opening GPT model and the other model, I learn. For navy metro. 

Speaker 2  (10:40)
Meta models. Yeah, let's say Meta models. 

Speaker 1  (10:45)
Basically, ChatGPT. I mean GBT models that we use for the creating multiple It has the excellent reasoning and the What you say, the coding And that's the one thing other thing is that for the agents, we basically prefer the GPT models. But. 

Speaker 1  (11:11)
For the lamas, uh, we usually prefer for the local, okay. Their self-hosted I'm just recalling it. I Further lemons, we can basically Okay, call 

Speaker 2  (11:31)
How do you access a glamour model on GPT model? I mean, you can talk about the comparison from these terms right access deployment. What would be the cost for each of the models that if we have to deploy what are the cost aspects? 

Speaker 1  (11:53)
Yeah, I mean to chat it GPT models are less costly compared to the other models based on the token size they provide and the costing. That's the one thing I told you they are easy to use. Excellent reasoning. 

Speaker 1  (12:11)
Agents congratulated using but for the lock. Local local proposals we usually prefer de LA to under the reason. 

Speaker 2  (12:22)
When you say the local purpose, would you mean 

Speaker 1  (12:25)
I mean, when we set up the locally, when we set up the application locally tested application locally for that purpose, we can use the land. That comes with because we don't have to pay for the suscription. For the learner model, they can easily be Configure and can be used I either determine. 

Speaker 2  (12:52)
And how about this journey? 

Speaker 1  (12:56)
For the deployment. So it comes with a different I think ChatGPT are easier than grammar. That's not sure about sure. 

Speaker 1  (13:24)
The Lano models with Laura and kept we can do that. I'm not sure if we can leave it with the GPT opening. 

Speaker 2  (13:37)
Okay. Where have you used data? I mean, in this rand application, you said you have used what on is in data bricks within the database environment. 

Speaker 2  (13:51)
What components are within, and why have you chosen? Databks, and how is this application access by the user? 

Speaker 1  (14:03)
Yeah, so why we choose the databrise? Because it's a pay as ego service. Based on the cluster that we are, we don't have to reinvent the wheel by Managing the clusters, the database you already doing it. 

Speaker 1  (14:21)
And for the computational purpose, it's fast. And because on the compromise face, if we do all those things we have to like cloud error we have to do it, manually all those management clusters, everything, okay, number of executors, course, all those things we have to do it manually. Let's sum with all those features guiding. 

Speaker 1  (14:43)
Apart from that, they are easy to use, they can, we can create the multiple mode. It can be easily configured with the Azure. Also I mean, it's a part of the Azure only with idiots pipeline. 

Speaker 1  (14:53)
That's why we have used the data breaks Also, it's it is handy with the park format. Okay, park fight format. So what was your other question? 

Speaker 2  (15:11)
How is the application used or how are users accessing your brand application? 

Speaker 1  (15:18)
Yeah, I mean, we have exposed the end points to the user and from those endpoints, there's just separate application, which is They're using it on the downstream, they're using that API or through that, they're communicating it. But based on it, we have created a separate UI forever. 

Speaker 2  (15:45)
Have you used any foundation models apart from GPT 

Speaker 1  (15:49)
I have used the ashure 1 km back. For the same drive application, also for the general family Where recently, using the open air network 

Speaker 2  (16:11)
Okay? And the reason being is Const or the ease of use, or what exactly 

Speaker 1  (16:19)
He is a fuse and the cost of 

Speaker 2  (16:22)
Okay, now that you have used both right? I and when you were using Lama, I want to understand the deployment aspects, and how have you fine-tuned? And How did you docrie? 

Speaker 2  (16:40)
It? Okay, can we doctorize a tips of what components go into the Docker right? The foundation Lama model 

Speaker 1  (16:56)
Okay. Yeah, I mean, in the doctor we have to the component that we have to Configurate, basically, we have the end points, right? So through end points, we can configure the So if I'm talking about the Docker, one I in our application, we are using the swagger for exposing the end points of those. 

Speaker 1  (17:28)
But of those models in the Docker, we have created the doctor. Compose file wide and file where we have considered all the configurations there, where to the environment, the basically the targets or the images that we need. Yeah, I mean, we're exposing all the entrance centre, the operation we're doing it point, running it in production or maybe in the tap. 

Speaker 1  (17:59)
So for that purpose, we have created, you have confuse that doctor let's Put in the interviews 

Speaker 2  (18:08)
What is your day-to-day water? What are your day-to-day responsibilities in and right now, you are, I guess, working on this, educational assistant kind of thing, right? What exactly is your responsibility of day-to-day basis? 

Speaker 1  (18:28)
Yes, it's to be currently working as NDG contributor so I get that account and then at the Zira specific, so we have the refinement meeting, and based on that, we pick the Zeus, and if the time I mean story points, we specify story points that how many time will take to complete. The And then Yeah, I mean we are just from master. Which we actually report every day, we have 50 I mean we have restrint or status making Yeah, that's a nice day, we get the geras we get the appics, basically, and from that active, we have the germs or the user stories. 

Speaker 2  (19:19)
Okay, can you explain me the architecture like what happens from an user request or a user input? If a if the If I'm talking about the RAG application, when the user sends an input or asks a question, what happens from that point at the back end? The user gets the response 

Speaker 1  (19:46)
Change the user okay from the user's point of view. Okay. 

Speaker 2  (19:53)
From user is only just passing an input arume, an input is question is passed or user. Drops in a question or asks something like what happens. For example, if it is a student is like, can you give me the percentage of my subject wise comparison, or my current marks to the previous test marks? 

Speaker 2  (20:21)
Something of the sort of question is what a student inputs? What happens? How is that person processed? 

Speaker 2  (20:30)
And how is the response generated retrieved generated and sent I am looking for the technical details, not the functional aspects 

Speaker 1  (20:42)
Yeah, so the user query gets embedded. And then we search the similar embeddings in the actual embedding model, maybe the through the vector store, we usually search it. Tom, with that as I told you, it will search in 2 ways, dance and the spark and the sparks, it will be comparing the keywords searching, the keywords and in the dense dense part, it will go into check the embaddings, okay, similar imbalance using the co science similarity, and then Once it retrieved the documents we have to rank it. 

Speaker 1  (21:26)
Using the cost and Put on Bind. And then it will, we will get the relevant document, and then we choose top 3 out of photo and top 5, and then we return the response to the user. 

Speaker 2  (21:45)
Alright. And During during developing a RAG application or some sort of LLM application. What is the actual pre processing or the data analysis we do? 

Speaker 2  (21:59)
And what is the Post example LLM LM generates, or the land generates response. What is the post processing that happens? What is the pre processing that happens? 

Speaker 1  (22:12)
Yeah, I mean, in the pre processing. Usually check If we're for the PI8 data, we have to check whether arunautics are we exposing those credential details of the user details, so we have to restrict the restricted to the prompt family. We have to guartell the prompt. 

Speaker 1  (22:31)
Basically. And also, we have to manually search for the python library that are we getting all those What is the context? And if the user input some hated or some irrelevant for some abusive languages, so do all those things, we usually filter it out apart from that. 

Speaker 1  (22:58)
Is the user has been proper? I mean chudi, because there can be prompt injection, so those things also. We are checking, uh, in the file also and the database. 

Speaker 1  (23:10)
Also, he can. There can be an option that he can add something like. Ignore all this previous I went something like malicious data. 

Speaker 1  (23:21)
You can do And all those things we are filtering it out. And after the post one also, we are doing the same thing. We are checking the relevant response that we are receiving from the we are doing the same check. 

Speaker 1  (23:35)
Okay, if it is if it is asking for some customer details, we have to measure that it should be masked. We are doing the markets of the rural level filter Sorry, the column column based filter which acquired by the database for the PID There could be analogies. That we have to list it apart. 

Speaker 1  (24:04)
Yeah, I mean, we have to make sure that the LLM should not generate the vague answer. So we have to make sure the hallucination also should not be benefit does not know the answer issue. Offering, you say, I don't know, okay. 

Speaker 1  (24:18)
Because you have to design the complex such a way that it can answer. It should not answer the irrelevant question for the user. Access controls. 

Speaker 1  (24:38)
These are the things few things we usually take care 

Speaker 2  (24:44)
What is your experience around traditional Machine Learning models used? You have done a lot of Eda, right? You would have And this before lining your Machine Learning model or right? 

Speaker 2  (25:02)
What is one Machine Learning model that you have? Train deployed. 

Speaker 1  (25:09)
Yeah, I've used the vision leaf for the classification. I've used the random forest. So that I can talk about 

Speaker 2  (25:20)
Random forest for classification How does it make any assumptions? 

Speaker 1  (25:27)
Sorry, does it make any assumptions? Assumptions in the sun, sorry, I didn't get yourself. 

Speaker 2  (25:38)
The variable should be in should be so whether there shouldn't be much variance between the between the data points. I mean, if we know about logar regression, there are certain way certain assumptions that a regression model makes right. So do classification models make any such, and can you explain the relation between A classification and regression model model 

Speaker 1  (26:16)
Okay, so classification basically tells us it could be by variant, it could be either binary, or either it could be multiple classification that you can do If I talk about the binary, it could be logistic regulation, where we are predicting the data. Panabi. For them, numerical, sorry for the numbers for the discrete data. 

Speaker 1  (26:46)
We usually prefer the regression model and for the categorical type, we usually prefer the classification model. It could be logistic logistic regression, or it could be random forest or any gradient model or The distance base gradient learning model could be the regression model. Other than that, it would be classification model. 

Speaker 1  (27:15)
But I can talk about their regression more. Because either told me, what are the assumptions? Be it usually In the random forest, get the multiple trees in parallel. 

Speaker 1  (27:33)
Also, it has the feature of the random random feature. It will pick, okay, or then it will create the trees out of it. And they'll be an estimator which will tell that the number of trees that we want, so how it works? 

Speaker 1  (27:49)
Is it actually pick the Guinea impurity value, which is the probabilistic value of the of all the trees that it has created out of it? And then it will check the information gain. Okay, and then it will check the random variance, because in the formula, there are 2 parts I'm just recalling it. 

Speaker 1  (28:15)
There are 2 parts, one is the reducible. Other one is irreducible, which has the the number of trees, got. If we increase the number of trees, the variance could be decreased. 

Speaker 1  (28:28)
So that's why it is recommended to have the number of large number of trees. But making sure the trade of overfitting and underfitting should be matched. Okay? 

Speaker 1  (28:41)
And Yeah Also, they are, if there is a chances of based on the data, right? If the data is having imbalanced data, it will easily prefer to use the random forest. Because it will automatically take care of that. 

Speaker 1  (29:02)
And if we have the balance data, we can choose any other model Yeah, I mean, did I answer question or 

Speaker 2  (29:15)
Yeah, may I understand why are you looking for this change? 

Speaker 1  (29:24)
Yes, actually, my company is asking me to relocate. 

Speaker 2  (29:29)
Base based on both sides of the current current currently 

Speaker 1  (29:31)
Yeah, Noida. I will get simply relocate to some other location which is Chandigarh, which I am not comfortable below. 

Speaker 2  (29:46)
Okay, alright, got it. I don't have any further questions. You have any questions for me. 

Speaker 1  (29:54)
A no, I'm good. 

Speaker 2  (29:56)
Alright. Prakash, thanks, waiting good day bye. Bye. 
