shemonti.rakshit@lumen.com
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Thank you for your endocrine project. What you have developed so far in the Agentic AI in the landgraph and all so yeah, you can start. If any recent curious project which you have worked and then we'll go more into deeper on that side. 

Speaker 2  (00:18)
Yeah, sure, so. Currently, working on the genius application, which is more into the chatbots that we have created and expose the end points within the data breaks. So I've around 3 years working experience with GenAI. 

Speaker 2  (00:37)
From last year, on the same company, it is more into the Chatbots used by the teachers and the students And for different for different modules, basically We have the different Datasets of unstructured data coming up in the chunking layer through the bedding layer, and then we have filed tune the This application, this Chatbot application and The generation layer we have used a land chain measurely. For the queues, user embeddings tworry embedding is a high approach. Also in some cases. 

Speaker 2  (01:21)
And then we have the So We are using the LLM also in between Meta columns also First for the fallbacks. Also, we are using the smaller models We're exposing multiple regulas metrics, like answer relevance. Your contact decision recall MM R&D CG values There are a few things we are exposing. 

Speaker 2  (01:52)
Yeah, that's that side. Actually, in the current situation 

Speaker 1  (02:00)
Okay. Alright, alright. So can you explain me the rear architecture at higher level? 

Speaker 2  (02:10)
Yeah, architecture, okay, so it has the chunking layer first. The chunking layer there are 2 types fixed chunking or sentence based awares, chunking, and then you have the embeddings in the weddings, you have different models, okay, we are just in data, fix provided vector store, you have the iron coal TV. They are doing just basically converting the text to the vectors. 

Speaker 2  (02:40)
Then, you have this searching algorithm and the searching overcome, you have two different approaches, dance and spars. In the dense layer, you will going to have the Definite similarity. On the sport side, you can as the keyword matching, which is BM25. 

Speaker 2  (02:57)
Apart from that, you can have the T. F ID F also, which is, I mean The basic on top of it, we have to be in 25. Then, we can combine both the approaches with the percentage Right now, we're using 70% of the tense and 30% of the scars, then they then they have there This reranking pink, the reranking. 

Speaker 2  (03:22)
You can have the winepover of the top. Rosen, today on the blind, could you side? You can as if you have the multiple millions of data that you want to rank it. 

Speaker 2  (03:32)
So in that case, you will want to Asser, buy encober from the buyencoder. We can have the Pop 3 using the cross encoder. So 

Speaker 1  (03:42)
Prakhar, if you don't mind, can you please while answering your question again? You please look at the camera. It will be good for me fit on mine. 

Speaker 2  (03:59)
Okay, so, uh, these ranking reranking is basically done through the as I told you by corrupt and the cross importer, and once we have the reranking our top 5 okay. We can have the, we can check the latency also, so there's a call that we need to take, whether we want the accuracy, latency or the accuracy. So we have to maintain these 2 approaches the trade of kind of thing, and then if it is lagging with the answer, there are some matrices that we need to check, like recall value. 

Speaker 2  (04:34)
So there are few four things, basically question answer context relevance and the ground. And based on all these 4, there are multiple pattern matrix that we have explored, we have basically So if we are, let me give an example of one only have This recall value in the recall. If we talk about if it is coming low, that means your ground value on that answer that is that it generated is not correct. 

Speaker 2  (05:01)
So in that matter, we need to check these two things, and there's some way other matrices. Also, this is This is actually happening. 

Speaker 1  (05:11)
Okay, so how does the embedding work basically? 

Speaker 2  (05:16)
Yeah, beddings worth. Hi beneath it. It's what to act where we are converting the tokens into the vectors, so I mean, that's what the embedding needs and through the searching, it uses the conscience similarity. 

Speaker 1  (05:36)
So so like, how the cocaine similarity works 

Speaker 2  (05:40)
Cussain, similarly, basically checked the direction, not the magnitude. It checks what all direction the vector is in and similarly, if the user queries in the same direction it will go to match with that. 

Speaker 1  (05:57)
Ok. And Alright, so what are the vector databases you have worked on? 

Speaker 2  (06:06)
Majority. 

Speaker 1  (06:10)
Only the vector store ok? Have you ever get a chance for concroma DV caughter and pine cone? 

Speaker 2  (06:17)
I did POC on that message. 

Speaker 1  (06:21)
Okay, alright, so Prakhar, suppose you have your rack pipeline. Okay? You have built an application on rack and as of now you local and then you have to plot on plot, and currently it is handling 100 request. 

Speaker 1  (06:38)
Okay, per minute, or you can consider the application is not that much scale level. Now certainly, and your rack pipeline has, you know, can handle the 100 PD of 100 pages PDF at a time, and suddenly there's a spike, you know, 1000 PDF the client is want to trigger that, and then you know, there is also the spike in the. Request side, so there will be suddenly one billion requests are happening over there, and then what happens due to this, there is too much latency in the I know the application and the hallucination is coming and the response which the user is expecting. 

Speaker 1  (07:20)
That is not up to the mark. Okay, that is, that is deviating from the expected response. So for this scenario, what are the what are The Matrix which you're gonna use to I mean, understand like, there is a deviation in the pipeline. 

Speaker 1  (07:35)
And what are the key measures you will follow-up so that you're going to make the entire pipeline stable? Okay, so that the one billion request can manageable, along with the latency issues, legislation, issues and the response issues 

Speaker 2  (07:52)
I think you're asking 2 questions. One is the if the application is not scalable. 

Speaker 1  (08:01)
There's a new app yeah, so due to the application is not stable due to that, these issues has been caused. The allucination, the latency earlier it was 100 request is suddenly request increases. The latency is going to be supposed. 

Speaker 1  (08:17)
10 seconds was a usual time average time now. It is going to be 10 minute if a 1000 requests are there, so what that is the reason due to the spike in the request user requests, these things has been caused. What is your implementer? 

Speaker 2  (08:35)
Yeah, for the scaring thing, right? Um, if the multiple requests are coming, I'll think of one approach which is the we can kind of distribute the loads among the servers using a load balancer, but exposing the API gateway before the user can query. Before the request So that way we can distribute the load among the servers, multiple instances we can create for the same Of the same application or the same drag application That's the one way I can think of and the other one is, if there is a latent northern latency, but your Anthury not getting generated correctly, in that case, if the answer is not getting generated correctly, I need to check the value of the Recall value. 

Speaker 2  (09:31)
Okay, what's the actual value? It is generating first. I'll see whether it's a generational issue or a retrieval issue. 

Speaker 2  (09:36)
So on the generational issue, I'll check, I'll pass the chunks directly to the element CD actual value. If that is coming correct, that means it's a retrieval problem. 

Speaker 1  (09:48)
How you can pass so how you can pass the chunks, directly to the LLM without the embeddings. 

Speaker 2  (09:56)
The vidouti without the embody so that I'll check with a metrics without the embeddings. No, but. 

Speaker 1  (10:08)
Hello, you think LLM can do you think Leh M can understand the direct? The prompt also itself goes to the embedding. First, so behind the scene of Leh M call, you know, the trans LM is built on top of the transformer model. 

Speaker 1  (10:23)
So the Transformers model, they are the encoder decoder model. So if you just pass any information to the LLM that has been converted to the to the numerical value, that numerical value LLM understand and then it will generate a numerical value that numerical value will convert Y the converter to the text value that is how the flow is going to happen. So, as you mentioned, like you gonna pass chunks, direct to the LLM and See the Response. 

Speaker 1  (10:51)
How much response is deviative? So I am just curious to know, like how you will do that. 

Speaker 2  (10:56)
Even in the context that I'll retrieve through the chunks. Okay, um, I'll pass those chunks in the prompts the prompts will understand I mean, I have to For generating the answer right? So the prompt will going to have the context, it will pass to the L. 

Speaker 2  (11:14)
M. It will generate the answer Okay, that way, we can check what actually the value it is coming through the LM because we are removing the other layers. We are directly passing the input data to the lm. 

Speaker 2  (11:30)
The actual content ok. 

Speaker 1  (11:31)
Okay? So Prakar, so if you have to suppose your documents has lot of Pi information. And you want, you do not want to pass those information to the LLM so what are the key measures you do? 

Speaker 1  (11:46)
Follow? To protect that information that the information will not pass to the LLM, and it will also regenerate in the output whenever the user is asking that query. 

Speaker 2  (11:56)
Yeah, through the cartels, we usually do along with that, we have to write the python code audit script in the notebook itself, whether, uh, if it is, we're passing any email ID okay from the presentated output to the post generator output. From the LLM so that we need to pars, it also in the database. We have applied the this level row level. 

Speaker 2  (12:26)
Notificable, rural masking and column masking just to be verified that the user should have the appropriate role to see those values. These are the gardening that we have done Do not expose API data, but I was talking about the It is already there, right? We have to just pass the actual context. 

Speaker 2  (12:49)
With the security layer in between thodi album, we can get the response back. 

Speaker 1  (12:54)
So suppose, if you have, if you do not have the cloud based guardrail system, you mentioned, you will write the python script. So how you're going to write that python script, like, what are the methods, the techniques you're going to use? 

Speaker 2  (13:06)
Wow, I can use the rejects pattern only. In the contact in the text, we can verify that if it is 

Speaker 1  (13:15)
They have a tragic rejex, is a very traditional approach, so sometimes rajex has also, you know, is not much confidence score in terms of the mapping the patterns. So what you will do in that case 

Speaker 2  (13:31)
Yeah, I mean, I'm passing through the multiple layer of security, right? That's the first security, otherwise. 

Speaker 1  (13:37)
Okay, the first security is RAG X rax. Then the second one 

Speaker 2  (13:41)
The second one is the roof column asking thing okay from the feature is so wrong because we are searching right, then send the sparse thing. So there, we're checking whether it should not expose the data directly to the user from the vector store. There should be some security layer, like the role level masking or column level masking should be there. 

Speaker 2  (14:06)
After the LLM send the output before that, before the response, we have to check whether it should, it is actually exposing the P? I? Value or not. 

Speaker 2  (14:16)
If it is done, we have to guarantee So 311 coffee, high level 

Speaker 1  (14:25)
Alright. Do you think if we pull any, you know again this model for the period detection? And if you train it in a way so that it will also help to your, I mean customised data. 

Speaker 1  (14:43)
So that can also be a good approach, but yes, that is okay, so okay, so prakkar, if you have something like, you know Ah, like if you have a agentic multi agentic application and yoga, you have to maintain the R BSc security, and you know that layer, you have to maintain and R0 and all accessology, so how you want to plan in a way so that it will be scalable at a enterprise level and so how you will do that 

Speaker 2  (15:18)
Okay, so these are different layers basically So see agents, we can use any agents left. We can orchestrate for the specific purpose. We can use their language wear the auto gener, many different other crew AI. 

Speaker 2  (15:37)
So this is the one layer so start with the first one, which is the user layer. Then, you have the login layer, which is also login, which is which we can scale it separately. Okay, through the through the walk or your There are several others, right? 

Speaker 1  (15:55)
Yeah, the odds authentication, and you know, the RBA CRB C layer. So like, have you ever worked on the RBC security and Yes, how you have implemented 

Speaker 2  (16:08)
Filters and roll level filters in the database itself. So they have the commands to do that. 

Speaker 1  (16:15)
Ok, okay, alright, alright, and how are you gonna build the CAC pipeline? 

Speaker 2  (16:21)
Yeah, CRC Tc pipelines, we will go to use it. Okay, so once we deploy our code okay in the gate hub, so the CI will come this into Comes into picture it would go into verify the test cases. Okay, it will do kind of vulnerability check of the code. 

Speaker 2  (16:45)
Generator does text test and then it will go into create the Docker image of the model. Okay, so once we have that model, then the CD will come into picture, which is the controller. Deployment into the Dev UT or other broad environment. 

Speaker 2  (17:06)
And once this is done, then we have this deployment, either we can do it in the WS or Azure, we are doing it in the WS using the ECS. So not the easiest, AK sorry. That way we can deploy. 

Speaker 1  (17:27)
Okay, okay, Prakar, I'm done with your interview. If you have any questions for me, you can ask Annu, I'm good. Okay, okay, thank you, thank you prakrit thank you so much for your time. 

Speaker 1  (17:39)
Have a great day. 
