shemonti.rakshit@lumen.com
Speaker 1  (00:04)
How are you preferred? 

Speaker 2  (00:15)
Yes, sure, your voice is breaking. Hello? 

Speaker 1  (00:23)
My internet pakist. Can you check your internet ones? 

Speaker 2  (00:36)
Hello, is it fine now? 

Speaker 1  (00:45)
Hello, yes, my debt is working fine praker, I think it's problem from your side. 

Speaker 2  (00:52)
Okay. Is it fine now? 

Speaker 1  (01:00)
Okay, let me try if the problem still persists, then I'll tell it. Okay so prayer, can you just introduce yourself? 

Speaker 2  (01:12)
Yeah, so myself tuck her. I were around 40 minutes of experience working with Starting with the data engineering, then I switched to the aim from last year. And currently are working with the emphasis from last 3 years. 

Speaker 2  (01:31)
We are working as a empathy, educational domain and working with geni stuffs before that, I am working with Mogan, where I have performed the E. D. Yes. 

Speaker 2  (01:45)
And then it's a models for the banking domain and majorly my overall expertise in the banking domain in the healthcare as well. Our previously, I worked with serious and SCL Show my text taxes like I'm working majorly on the database where I'm the sure also the side as well. On the Azure, I'm working with E. 

Speaker 2  (02:13)
DF pipelines measurement and the data groups on the data big side we have higher. I had worked with a dlt's workflows, and ML flows models. We have created genetic catalogues, we have deployed it across multiple environments. 

Speaker 2  (02:37)
And Sorry. Across the multiple environments and on the area side I worked more immediately with S London's step function, ok, ECR clusters, and we are eater. This grew as well long time back. 

Speaker 2  (03:01)
Apart from that, I've worked with kafra as well. So currently, my application is moving to the educational domain where the application is used as the teachers and the students for the diagnostic tests, so we are getting multiple data formats and entire data with different fight formats, and then we have created the 3 layers which is chrunking and blooding. And I work on one chat applications where the user can ask it's a private organisation with Chatbot, which leaders can ask a question. 

Speaker 2  (03:34)
This student can ask the questions and didn't get the appropriate response. And for that one, we have exposed the regular matrices, we have fined the Layers are embedding layer changing layer. Also, we have several parametrices that we have experienced like MMR and ND c's community games. 

Speaker 2  (04:00)
Apart from that, add a good exposure to the radian pipeline. Also, I've worked on incremental data also. So yeah, that's pretty much from myself. 

Speaker 1  (04:11)
Okay. So Prakar, I want you to tell me about any of your recent project that you worked on, like from end-to-end right from the straight from the requirement gathering to the production deployment, or maybe with the hyper care on monitoring and what is your role into that specific project? And third thing which I want is how distant project has benefited to client, and what is the KPI Put that, so please explain me in our very detailed 

Speaker 2  (04:43)
Yeah, we talk about the chatbots, which I have worked on. So as I told you that we are getting the organisational data in different formats, which were in jsm, xmls, okay, some conference documents? 

Speaker 1  (04:57)
This is for which one is it the same educational one that you were talking about? What was the name of the 

Speaker 2  (05:04)
It was ID. 

Speaker 1  (05:06)
Hi Bixby 

Speaker 2  (05:08)
So there we have all the documents that are getting stored. Also, some CD CS that were coming up from the carfall. Also, through the streaming there, we have the batch and the streaming pipeline and all the data comes into the history from S3 clear um. 

Speaker 2  (05:27)
Some jobs are running that are pushing that data from SC to the a DLS and from a DLS vakes the pipeline to send those data or the transits of the data to the database Delta table, so that was our source of data. There were some adocric to transform. The unstructured due to the unstructured data, and once we have that data comes up in our database table. 

Speaker 2  (05:55)
So from there, we were getting the chunkings, okay? Chunks, in the sense we have the kind of tax skater sentence skater sentence against skater. Where it will check what that sentence is long enough to junk it or not so that the we can have the contextual information intact. 

Speaker 2  (06:19)
For all those For all, for all the documents basically, and then we have the bedding layer and bedding layer was, you have tried multiple models, but recently we are using it with the bg, we have tried the other approaches chat compression, or what you can say, the context compression basically, so there are multiple classes where we have used the element. Extractor and also the embedding, so we were just combining both approaches I'm using that BC model. We have checked the embedding, we are checking the embeddings. 

Speaker 2  (06:58)
Majorly, and once we have those embeddings reading in the database database, we were using the veteran store and for the searching. We are also using the features too as well for the keyword search along with the bm 25, so we were combining again. The both approaches for searching Then, the user queries and basically the prompts comes into picture. 

Speaker 2  (07:24)
We have written the Meta prompts for the for this small queries. Also, we are using, in some cases, we are using the hide approach also for regenerating the queries, along with the answer, and then we are sending it to the lm, because sometimes the semantics got mismatched. So in that case, we were having that approach. 

Speaker 2  (07:46)
Also once we have the retrieval layer, once we have done the generation layer, then we went to the. Retrieval layer and the retrieval side. We were again doing the dense approach and the sparse approach of searching, combining both with some percentages, 70% lens and 30% was the sparse approach. 

Speaker 2  (08:10)
Then, we are the ranking incomes, and we are doing the buying coder, ranking Because the documents were huge and taking the top, they send it to the cross encoders for the query and your document mapping so that you get ran properly. Getting the relevance is very busy. And once we have those ground truth, along with the corresponding data that we have received for through the llms, Leh M we were using the OpenAI earlier, we were using the azo open, but recently we had used a we are using the As he said, open, yes, GPT-4 mini item. 

Speaker 2  (08:51)
So once we have the data, then what you are doing is we were Exposing some matrices matrices in the sense, we were checking the Regas parametres is like, answer relevance, okay, and the effectfulness, taking I mean, we were checking the 4 parameter parameters, question, answer context permission on the ground fit based on that, we have created multiple equation of multiple matrices. So one is the answer relevance, painfulness, recall value, and then we have the lmr. And decisions value capability, green value, reciprocal rate value. 

Speaker 2  (09:34)
So once we have those values. In fact, because these values are we are exposing on the by decay. Making sure that our data isn't synced and whatever the user is quarring. 

Speaker 2  (09:47)
He will, he should get the proper spons out of it. Along with that, we were checking the latency L95 value. The key showed that the the answer should be relevant, along with the less little litre. 

Speaker 2  (10:06)
Apart from that I've worked on the other tuning sites as well. Maybe the chunkings and the embedding layer when we're really reinding, the index also once in a month. And this is the basic leader of my project. 

Speaker 1  (10:29)
What was your contribution to that like? Aha, your individual contributor to this project or you think the project or what was the 

Speaker 2  (10:40)
Unstructured, but let's see we have around eight people in the team. Sure, I was in the development only so I have pull it all these things. 

Speaker 1  (10:52)
Okay, perfect, and what was the K? P? I for that project like how it was before, and after a view Did this everything? 

Speaker 1  (11:02)
So what was the case? 

Speaker 2  (11:06)
See a we are supposing the matches is right. So based on that is a continuously check-in. If there is a data trip okay. 

Speaker 2  (11:14)
If there is a conceptual drift, or it's The data should not be stayed okay if you're getting the CDC's, are we? Are we taking the incremental data or not through all those things? We were making sure and checking it every time based on the matrices that we are exposing. 

Speaker 1  (11:34)
Okay, so your platform operates in. How many countries is this only for like, a specific country? 

Speaker 2  (11:42)
Particularly states for different states, they have different youth for the US only as For different schools for different school, they are different. 

Speaker 1  (11:56)
Okay, now just imagine or maybe just think about that. The same platform operates in 15 countries. So the content that is appropriate in the US may be restricted in some other country like this, how they will be or any other country. 

Speaker 1  (12:13)
So your single safety model was trained on like puer centric content standards, right? So a school of Germany complains your AI refused to discuss like whatever the history like World War to history or something with a like maybe a 16-year-old or something like that they have just like a restrictions in the Germany so and which is a mandatory curriculum in other countries. So how are you designing your safety architecture in the like local awareness, and maybe it is very similar to the state wise as well. 

Speaker 1  (12:44)
So how do you resign that Okay. You gotta G. 

Speaker 2  (12:52)
Yeah, I got a question. Basically, I need to scale it to the different region, the same application, and making sure that the answer should be relevant specific to the continent over the country. Wow, so we can Okay, we can have the multiple Set up around the multiple available zone okay? 

Speaker 2  (13:22)
Of the same application and the restriction that we can do based on that. Policies that we can configure I'm just recording, I'm just thinking a loud Okay? So Security wild. 

Speaker 2  (13:40)
If I talk about, I'll measure that via information should be should not be exposed. Is there somebody I think, let me backtrack it. If the user is searching for the world world history for the for the Germany, you should be getting the Germany data. 

Speaker 2  (13:57)
So there we need to restrict On the WS side or the Azure side, maybe on the table. Tables, weekend catalogues, basic, basically we can distinguish between along the regions so if the One data or the tables are there. In the German region should not be exposed to the other region. 

Speaker 2  (14:23)
If I'm talking about the data break site or the table side, so there we can configure it using the uniticra. 

Speaker 1  (14:32)
Might be, I mean, I have just given an example of one such thing, which is restricted in one of the country. But maybe a mandatory curriculum for the other country. So there might be N number of feature or N number of things like that, so how will you like configure such things, then how will you decide which country I mean, this is the safety like content safety that we have to apply for this country and not for this country. 

Speaker 1  (14:57)
And and there are like a 15 countries, right. Now it's not like a 1 or 2 countries or not, something like that. So 

Speaker 2  (15:04)
I mean, I 

Speaker 1  (15:06)
What is that one thing in the architecture that you will think about it like? Maybe this might be a very practical question right in this platform they might use in other countries as well. If this is serving in one country if it's performing, they are, might be, it's a phase to have the project I guess if they want to so. 

Speaker 1  (15:28)
I mean, what is that one thing that You will take care of it. 

Speaker 2  (15:34)
Yeah, I mean, just like deploying the appetition, the multiple regions. Okay, so for that one, we have, the, let's say database is deployed to multiple regions. There we need to add the privacy policies. 

Speaker 2  (15:45)
Okay, or maybe we have to restrict it based on the roles. Organisation rules, or maybe you can apply the pro filters and the column filters. There we can't make it in on the wild. 

Speaker 2  (16:03)
Deploying it to a different digit, we can specify the policies that's what I can think of I've not done that, but 

Speaker 1  (16:11)
No problem, again, one more thing. For example, like I reduced it right? Your platform right? 

Speaker 1  (16:22)
So you're that platform source student from first grid to 12 grid, just for example, I don't know if it's actually selling up which grade are Okay, okay. So imagine that it is serving from grid, one to grid, 12 okay, and then grade one student and a grid, 12 student like they are using the same platform. But they asked the same question, what is what okay? 

Speaker 1  (16:52)
So the safe answer for a six-year-old is very different from a safe and educationally appropriate answer for a 17-year-old, maybe It's a house in this case. It is a content safety thing as well. But then how do you architect the age other response generation, as well in your current system? 

Speaker 2  (17:13)
In the current system, I have to add the prompts, the prompts I'll add. First. I'll get the information of the user, okay. 

Speaker 2  (17:22)
What user and what rating is belonging based on the database from the database? I can get that, and then I'll check to restrict the promptly late with sub basic. I can add like if radio less than I can add that threshold, whether it is less than that. 

Speaker 2  (17:41)
Then, specify, don't specify the more more information just give the basics as the rate 6 or grade less than rate 5 can understand is something like that I can think of. I would like to give the guards 

Speaker 1  (18:04)
Okay. Okay. Okay, one more thing. 

Speaker 1  (18:10)
For example, I mean, in those lines are only so in your platform student is asking my teacher kits me at home. Okay, what should I do? Okay, so this is like inappropriate content, right? 

Speaker 1  (18:30)
So it's childhood, potentially disclosing the abuse in that particular platform. So your safety pipeline was built for inappropriate output, right? So how do you handle sensitive input that requires real world attention? 

Speaker 1  (18:47)
So how do you manage that? 

Speaker 2  (18:49)
So I told you, right? We have to guarantee it prompt should not be hallucinated with the other information, it should be stated to the document that we have provided the input that we have provided, so we have to guarantee the problem basically. And for the security purpose for the P information, we have to make sure that krishnanshu revealed all those informations. 

Speaker 2  (19:12)
The LMS. 

Speaker 1  (19:13)
If you're not seeing, will your will your system or not? Pay any appropriate. Oh, action on that. 

Speaker 2  (19:27)
What kind of action I mean 

Speaker 1  (19:29)
So for example, Child is giving some input over there, right? That He is getting abused, so do not use like human in a loop for like, you know, like, or maybe teacher or A 

Speaker 2  (19:45)
Anybody like having here that depends on the. Requirement, if I want, if some words that needs to be tracked by the by the prompt. So I can store them okay? 

Speaker 2  (19:59)
Linked it with the user or the students, and I can, because individuals, we can see what kind of question the user have asked So again, the Leh M comes into picture and I'll Make sure that what kind of Features, we want. Okay, let's say the user is asking that I got abused by the comptecher. Because my lm won't give the answer. 

Speaker 2  (20:26)
I don't want my LM to give the answer because which he might be elucidating, but I can track those questions in the separate. Separate database or separate query. I can fetch and can inform the The parents or navy academics and headoff. 

Speaker 2  (20:47)
Steps will form the parents of meeting something I can do, but not especially to the application. I will modify it. 

Speaker 1  (21:01)
So for example, you said we are using the data breakfred. So for example, your data break database workflow is running lightly at like a 2 AM or something, and it injects from st 3 bucket transform via like data link and loads to a snowflake at 3 AM. It fails at a staged, I mean, there are different stage, right? 

Speaker 1  (21:27)
It fails in a stage too by morning. The cold layer has yesterday still data. So in this case walked me through the incident response. 

Speaker 1  (21:35)
And how do you really designed to prevent this kind of a thing? 

Speaker 2  (21:40)
Basically, we check the SLS Please check out 69 specific. So he just informed the stakeholders that sometimes the data can be stayed okay. But the time limit would be like 1 hour or 2 hour that can happen. 

Speaker 2  (22:00)
But yes, it is fair. We have to specify to the users and users that they might be getting the data need. We have to inform them, but to fix those issues, what you usually do is we reiterate all the steps.com failed. 

Speaker 2  (22:19)
Okay, and maybe sure that there should not be any duplicate data. So all those things, duplicate data, missing data, all those checks. We have already there in the notebook. 

Speaker 2  (22:29)
All the jobs That's how we ratify it. 

Speaker 1  (22:35)
Okay, okay, so this is a RAG based system? I believe right? Or Okay? 

Speaker 1  (22:45)
So, in, uh, and I mean, in your ratway system. For example, you just retrieve like a 5 jumps for every Queen. Okay, so and the user is complaining answers are irrelevant and then you check. 

Speaker 1  (22:58)
For example, the chunks retrieval technically related to the query keywords, but miss the actual intent. So what do you change first second? And third, what do you change? 

Speaker 2  (23:11)
We'll check your refund value. Because in that case, the required value would be low. Because it's not matching with a ground truth values, so it's a I'll pass the Input data to the lm and see what output I am getting, if I'm getting the correct output, that means the issues with the retrieval. 

Speaker 2  (23:38)
So increase the retrieval, we need to fix that and we need to find Tribute retrieval site. We should have the character value among our values and decisions value through all the stuff. 

Speaker 1  (23:56)
You have any idea about the context window prakhan. Then, so, for example, if the user uploads maybe a 300 page financial report, okay and ask what are like top 3 risks mentioned in this document? Okay? 

Speaker 1  (24:16)
And then your LLM has like 32K context window. The document is 150k tokens. So how does your system handle this kind of a scenario? 

Speaker 2  (24:29)
Yeah, that's what the other layers come into picture chunking and embedding. Northern wedding, basically the Child. And we should not Send all the data to the L. 

Speaker 2  (24:42)
Lms, because of the contact window overflow, so we can summarise it through the LLM, or maybe we can use it cheap models, like for summarization, like birth or something, or maybe the chicken model less than that, so we have to summarise the data first and then we have to send it to the level that approach 

Speaker 1  (25:11)
Have you worked on multi agent architecture or anything prakrit? 

Speaker 2  (25:16)
Yes, I do. 

Speaker 1  (25:17)
Which kind which framework have we used it? 

Speaker 2  (25:20)
I have worked with majorly on the land chain, but I have worked with a land graph also. 

Speaker 1  (25:29)
Okay, I mean, when do we use landcraft? And when do we use language chair? 

Speaker 2  (25:45)
So landroffic, basically the flow chart structure In the flowchat, we can specify the tools. Also, you have to Bind those tools, so the agent will automatically check. What kind of tools they need to Theatre, that requests that the user has asked for. 

Speaker 2  (26:08)
So what, you know, in my application, there was a requirement for the We were getting the emails. Also, so from that email, we need to extract the intent and from that intent, we need to call the other multiple agents, so let's say it is a address change or an ID request something, so my LLM used to check the intent of the email and from that email we have to call the corresponding Agents, so agent will automatically call that so for that workflow, we have user right now. Change interview for the chat room. 

Speaker 1  (26:55)
Okay? So I mean, I saw your resume, so you are seeing you built like a landcraft comparable architecture, so what does that mean? Trigger alike, is it very similar to landrock that you have built-in Okay, so can you can you tell me like, how do you what is? 

Speaker 1  (27:17)
What is the difference between the land graph and what is the need of building this new framework? Or is it better? 

Speaker 2  (27:26)
Yeah, I mean earlier, we were So we have to separate the multiple agents, so we have the planner earlier. We have only one agent, and in the one agent. We were doing the all the tasks like this idea. 

Speaker 2  (27:43)
Everything, then we come up with the other approach of the planner agent and planner agent will go into cause the other agents through the at that end, we were sending it to the queues, basically to some queues, if it is ID Q or ID so that approach we, I mean, just to Separate out some agents. So one agent is a time agent having a landgraph. Another agent between the other agent with a land just combining and interacting with those 2 agents. 

Speaker 2  (28:15)
So that approach, we have tried 

Speaker 1  (28:24)
Oh? I mean, for example, you have a landgraph on flow where, like 3 notes run in a pattern. I mean, I'll just take an example of your ID project only okay so node a fetches, the student data node B maybe like fetches the curriculum. 

Speaker 1  (28:46)
To see features something like assessment history. Okay, so currently, they run sequentially like taking, maybe the time not in and second student, so how did you paralleze them in a landup? And what specific landcrap construct do you use? 

Speaker 2  (29:03)
I have not used the other thing I were using. The recent majorly for the or some threat goals, executive threat tools. In the python So to make it paralyse, we tried with t I don't know if it is for the same approach. 

Speaker 2  (29:25)
We tried their ray also. For the for the parallelisation, but that didn't work out So I went a long time back, but I've used the executive framework measure for the Prime Minister. 

Speaker 1  (29:48)
I mean, in a similar way, like, for example, in your landgraph cycle itself. There is like a planner, executor and evaluator okay and the planner the evaluator keeps seeing, for example, not good enough late. Maybe I'll retrieve that's what they are saying in testing. 

Speaker 1  (30:12)
I mean, whenever you are testing it, it works fine, but in a production, the query has been cycling for like a 200 iterations and consumes. Maybe a $50 in API call. So what went wrong? 

Speaker 1  (30:25)
And what are the 3 layers of defensive add in this case? 

Speaker 2  (30:30)
Okay, in the landcraft itself, the agent is not able to 

Speaker 1  (30:38)
There are like a you have a cycle planner, executive, evaluator and a plan. Okay, so the evaluator is keep saying this not good enough or he try, or maybe it's not working. Okay, so in a testing when you tested, it worked fine. 

Speaker 1  (30:56)
But in the production query, it has been cycling in a 200 iterations and consume almost like a 50 good dollar in API call. So in this case. What might have been wrong? 

Speaker 1  (31:07)
And what are the 3 layers of defensive add if you come across in such situation? 

Speaker 2  (31:12)
Yeah, I mean we have to restrict the number of tries first. One way, and if it is not working, we need to send it to the queue, maybe a DL Q not the DL Q. Retrieve, squeeze. 

Speaker 2  (31:32)
We can send it to the retry. Skills, and later we can pick that messages again, and then we can refer 

Speaker 2  (31:55)
Yeah, I mean, I have to fine-tune the jobs also, right? What kind of task it is time to come? Ati and Finding the final finding the job first. 

Speaker 2  (32:09)
I'll see what the error is basically. And then, based on the time taken decision Fine, tinting. 

Speaker 1  (32:17)
Okay, supra, have you? Do you have any experiences working on mcp? 

Speaker 2  (32:24)
Mcp, I have used it, but not majorly. I know about it. 

Speaker 1  (32:29)
Have you used A2A? It were on the archive. So what is observability, prakad? 

Speaker 1  (32:40)
Can you explain what is observability in AI? Now 

Speaker 2  (32:44)
The observability is the Year to the authority monitoring, observability, is the matrices that we have exposed like that. To verify what the how the model is performing. Okay? 

Speaker 2  (33:01)
And Through some matrices, that regha's parameters, or maybe some other exposed matrices that we can see I think that's absolutely 

Speaker 1  (33:14)
Okay, in Ivan Evans, do you know what is eval? 

Speaker 2  (33:18)
Yeah, events are majorly for the notification. Evaluating the let's select star from something. Okay? 

Speaker 2  (33:30)
And it will evaluate or it will evaluate your Sums matter, multiplication algorithm. And what kind of operation do you want to perform? Go to specific that in the event I've used it, but I'm not able to recall it nearly. 

Speaker 1  (33:53)
What is the difference between live rank? Advanced RAG and modular RAG and have you used any of it? 

Speaker 2  (34:01)
Sorry. 

Speaker 1  (34:03)
Night track advanced track and a model. 

Speaker 2  (34:06)
Are you Siri? 

Speaker 1  (34:07)
There are so many types right now. Okay, no, so what is semantic chunking Vs fixed size chunking? 

Speaker 2  (34:26)
Giving the, let's say if I want to chunk around 100 100 character and we have to specify the overlap size. We don't know the numbers we have to do hit and drive. But the problem with that is, you're not able to capture the correct context out of the channel mauta the other thing starts sentence aware, changing, which is, it will automatically check. 

Speaker 2  (34:53)
We have to specify the separators, basically, if it is a sentence or a paragraph or a long paragraph, it will try to reduce, I mean not reduce, but basically it will cut long sentences into the short sentences, or maybe the paragraph, and sentences, 2 words and words are two things. So that's how it works sentences. Something 

Speaker 1  (35:23)
What is the difference between the agent that uses the tool and Vs the agent that artisted other agents? 

Speaker 2  (35:31)
Yeah, I mean we have different libraries like new AI authentic. So these are the model that we need to we can use for the Noticles, master or slave, or maybe Jas, supervisor or the agents. So for that one, we have to, we can use those libraries through clear also. 

Speaker 1  (36:00)
Orchestrate the other agent. 

Speaker 2  (36:01)
Yeah, this is what the orchestration we can do through them, and the other is like land draft, or maybe either Landroff, you can use it so you have to cover Bind them tools there across the agents and we can work accordingly. 

Speaker 1  (36:24)
So I'm good prakaniya, do you have any questions for me? 

Speaker 2  (36:28)
Recently, about the project and the role you have 

Speaker 1  (36:32)
Yeah, so here the projects are mostly like I would say, the 80% of the projects are based on the agentic agentic engine project right now. That would be working on there might be like a lower code engine or low code agents as well. It depends entirely on the business and the cost that is involved with that, so if they don't have much of a budget, so we are here post. 

Speaker 1  (36:57)
History using couponent studio Microsoft, so Azure is the R code provider, so we do have like all the 3 providers over here, like AGC P AWS and a sure, but mostly like, at least in my team, we are deploying our deploying partner or provider is the assure, and we are using all the things related to thosehore at the 20% of the work might depend, so sometimes it might be a like a core AI N will thing kind of a thing. Maybe 1 day you will tell if somebody will tell just use the try to create a forecasting model. 

Speaker 1  (37:37)
So yeah, I mean that is the combination that is the like 1820 I would say, I'm a part of AI team. Here we are the only AI team in the wind right now we are a team of 2025 people over here so yeah, that is pretty much all about it. 

Speaker 2  (37:54)
And it's for the individual contributor or 

Speaker 1  (37:58)
All interpends, it mostly individual contributor here, but it depends. So if the project is big, so maybe the 3 or four people will be deployed to that one project. So it actually, and one person is only not attending just one project. 

Speaker 1  (38:15)
It is like right now I'm at least 5 project at the same time. So that is the Kind of crazy reason me to do here. So yeah, sometimes might be the individual contributor or sometimes, might be in a team. 

Speaker 2  (38:29)
Okay. Thank you. 

Speaker 1  (38:34)
Okay, thank you. Thank you so good difficult. I changed it back to you. 
