agangadharan@navaera.com, ppadhiar@navaera.com, prakhar@fizerv.com, skachwala@navaera.com
Speaker 1  (00:10)
Can you just read about a print profile and the grand company you are working with at mortality tech? Thank you very much. 

Speaker 2  (00:18)
Call, yes, sir. I'm working with I'm emphasis from last 3 years on total life around 14 years of experience with Big DATA. And along with that, I work with LLM, as well. 

Speaker 2  (00:34)
So majority, I have worked with data in snowflake, okay, spark spala, on the apple side, I've worked mostly with the classic models, along with that, I have worked with ryas, making the chatbots. Also I have worked on the realm side only, but on the different application, which is led to the within the feedback to the agents. So currently my application is or into the education domain which is used by the teacher and the students. 

Speaker 2  (01:08)
Immediately, I worked with the banking domain. The firm last year. I'm working with education government emphasises so we are they have the architecture like On the date engineering side, they have the nightly jobs running gets the uterus pipelines, so those are our Data basically getting informed as a transcripts. 

Speaker 2  (01:32)
And therefore we're generating the feedback system of the clients ok of the agent that is talking to the customer that the first thing that I have worked on the other model that I've worked on was a Chatbot. It was the provided by the it was internal. Basically so they have internal documentation documents all those things. 

Speaker 2  (01:54)
And then we have greater Chatbot using the um rats, including the embeddings and the vector databases. For those things we have used. Apart from that, I have a good exposure to Delta tables also in the database. 

Speaker 2  (02:10)
I've done the certification also. Yeah 

Speaker 1  (02:19)
So from the AI side you have mostly worked on the agenda. Use cases right? 

Speaker 2  (02:25)
Yeah, come not the agenda. But getting the feedback of the agents. So that was our problem statement problem. 

Speaker 2  (02:35)
So whatever they call that we receive, we have to rate the agent accordingly. 

Speaker 1  (02:41)
So, have you also been on the data stuff? I mean, what the maximum size of the data you have worked on? 

Speaker 2  (02:48)
It was there in the table. Because the size is Not sure. But it was huge basically because we have to do the lot of cleaning lot of processing before using that data. 

Speaker 1  (03:03)
So the use case was what, for this particular case. 

Speaker 2  (03:09)
Let's say if we have a transfer it off the image and we've basically getting a transfer from the qfinity software. So which is converting the voice data to the tax on. So there are a lot of things like unwanted. 

Speaker 1  (03:27)
That's noise noise, good. Okay, fine. Just sound just looking through your profile. 

Speaker 1  (03:38)
Just giving me a moment. So can you just explain any architecture you have designed all any kind of risk which you have created from branch and mostly related to any platform development explosion? You have 

Speaker 2  (04:01)
On the architect side, I was involved with t Data ingestion, particularly And then using a multi of architecture, we have cleaned the data, and then we've used the then we have trained that data. So from the scratch is I have not done that. But I was in the middle of the project management. 

Speaker 1  (04:26)
Ok. So thank you. Welcome. 

Speaker 1  (04:37)
The We're having the knowledge of these parks, python, also as well. 

Speaker 2  (04:43)
Yeah, I think call Mahabalipuram in Samsun. 

Speaker 1  (04:47)
And what about the cloud technologies? 

Speaker 2  (04:50)
Yeah, mostly work with AWS and measure. 

Speaker 1  (04:59)
Websitm, you can start with what should I think? 

Speaker 3  (05:05)
You're on me, okay. 

Speaker 1  (05:11)
That is going through the 

Speaker 3  (05:15)
So Let's say you have to Apply platform data engineering platform. Where data will be coming from multiple sources, then you have to do an ethic. Then, there are some processes that will run, and then the data will be stored somewhere or exposed Y IPS to some other customers or other platforms. 

Speaker 3  (05:42)
Now I want you to give me an overview architecture, overview, how will you design the process? What are the things that you will keep in mind? So that We can cater any developments that let's say we have some initial requirements. 

Speaker 3  (06:04)
But that may change in future. So how will you design so that this scope, when the scope changes, you can ingest all the changes that are coming in while you are designing the architecture? 

Speaker 2  (06:21)
So what? 

Speaker 1  (06:22)
Maybe you can use any whiteboard kind of a stuff if you have access to or any kind of diagram or any very basic box diagram you can make use of. 

Speaker 2  (06:34)
Ok. Let me open the stop. 

Speaker 2  (06:50)
I am sharing mask. 

Speaker 2  (07:08)
Nowadays, take your time. Yeah, everybody is chemistry. Yeah. 

Speaker 2  (07:21)
Ok, so you said how we will go into the architecture wise of the application. So initially we have, ok, can I describe my application, and then we can Start with the Kafka where we have and let's say Cannot draw the boxes, but I'm 

Speaker 1  (07:46)
No night's okay, completely fine, just sir. 

Speaker 2  (07:49)
So from the Kafka, we have the deplesium comes into picture, which is sending us the cdcs, basically, from those cdcs, we're getting the data into the S3 ok in the streets we have so this is the one part now we have the multi hazards concept which is the jobs that are running taking the data from the SG and then we have the multi hop architecture. We have the basically the raw layer. Okay, I mean talking about the transformation. 

Speaker 2  (08:29)
Raw air canonical layer. True, sorry. There is a reel there. 

Speaker 2  (08:40)
So we are doing the transformation on that side on the ETL side and again we're sending it to the SP only. So in between we have multiple processes like we have the step functions. Of the association function are talking to the lamdas. 

Speaker 2  (09:01)
Solanda's Just for each functions, we have a step function. Those step function called the lambda, and those lambdas are again redefining it sending the data to the SMS. Basically the request whatever we are so this has 2 parts basically. 

Speaker 2  (09:26)
One part is if we are uploading the file into the STS that is invoking the lander and then give the pipeline, which is also invoking the lander. They are doing the same thing. They are sending the data after transformation to the SG again. 

Speaker 2  (09:43)
So this basically we are getting the data into the skies. Okay, after this canonical layer, we are sending our data to the in 3 parts S3 somewhere in the snowflake. And somewhere some part in the Earlier, we were using the stretch shift, but we were using the shift You can now wear using a snowflake. 

Speaker 2  (10:15)
So okay after the refrigerators is done, we have the basically we have built-in the using the data breaks. Okay, they are too. 

Speaker 1  (10:26)
Shots and how this is a layer above this Yeah, which is consuming A 

Speaker 2  (10:32)
Consume body. 

Speaker 1  (10:32)
Modified S3 data, right? 

Speaker 2  (10:35)
So from those stories we have again, some jobs are running, okay, badly and sequentially, this is kind of a workflow. Ok, so workflows has been triggered as per the request based on the scheduled time that we have provided. Then again, there are creating the storing it as a Delta table. 

Speaker 2  (11:00)
I'm just recalling whatever my system is. Then, I'll connect each year. Then, we have the Delta table store there. 

Speaker 2  (11:07)
We have the transcripts. Translate and there some tables which I talk about the chatbots. Also, those were getting injected through this clear only and then we have separate data table. 

Speaker 2  (11:23)
Okay, for the chat worker. Consume, I mean, we have the There is another layer for storing the queries. Also of the user where we are using the Momo TV. 

Speaker 2  (11:44)
Okay. Yeah, I mean, you're just thinking once again. Yeah, then we have the on the ML side. 

Speaker 2  (11:54)
We are using the OpenAI model OpenAI model, open aiim, writings. Ok, and then we were using the quadrant. Cotton cotton currents vector database for the rack track chain. 

Speaker 2  (12:17)
Yes, yeah, that's it. So initial part is the Kafka. We are getting all our data through the streets. 

Speaker 2  (12:25)
And from 

Speaker 1  (12:28)
What kind of data is it? 

Speaker 2  (12:31)
This is the multiple applications of these students basically diagnostic data. So whatever the test the student has given that will comes up into this iron test. 

Speaker 3  (12:55)
So When you say that the data is being read to S3 And then that role data is being ingested into Titanium breaks or snuff like horrid shift. Whatever club platform that you have Hello, let's say, so. Have you designed this or your part? 

Speaker 2  (13:22)
Part of I was a part of it. 

Speaker 3  (13:25)
Ok, so what contributions did you did in this? What was the role that you played in this 

Speaker 2  (13:32)
Yes, I mean, we were checking lot of things. I mean Show trying to do basically what I have done is was the at that time is optimising the job because jobs were taking lot of time. So they have some different architecture before this is the refined one which we were using currently. 

Speaker 2  (13:58)
But earlier, they have different one with different Technology also, we have used the micro services at some point there. Ok, conserve it, different different architecture ways. That was one of the part which I met House. 

Speaker 2  (14:18)
If we are exposing, the APIs basically 

Speaker 3  (14:22)
Ok. So so when you are saying that the from kamka, the data is being stored in S3 Did you did you have any checks on that? 

Speaker 2  (14:43)
Anything checks in the sense. I mean, we are 

Speaker 3  (14:46)
Sits, raw data. 

Speaker 1  (14:48)
It's an early structured data, right? 

Speaker 2  (14:50)
Yeah, it's an honest function, no, no, no I mean, we are just Dumping all the data with no check. Basically. Okay That was a requirement that I forgot while we were keeping the Why we are keeping all the all the data 

Speaker 3  (15:11)
So when you say the ETL process is running, so you are taking the raw raw data, and then then you are defining something so you must be having. Some rules, and then you are putting it back to S3 or some flag or red ship. 

Speaker 2  (15:27)
Correctly, this is a refined layer. I mean, so this is the source of information then we have refined it. And then after that, we are sending to the state. 

Speaker 3  (15:35)
So what were the repirations like? What did you require? 

Speaker 2  (15:39)
Yeah, so this is the part where we are doing the transformation, basically of the data, keeping the null checks and everything. This layer is doing it because we don't want to miss any data of the student just to check whether maybe for different purposes, we don't want to reject the unwanted data. That's why we are keeping it. 

Speaker 2  (16:03)
There is a deplesium which is storing. Basically the we're not sending all the air to the streets, but what we are doing is we are sending all the cds part which is changed over time. 

Speaker 1  (16:15)
And what is the intention period which you are making which you are using for this particular use case? How many days of data is captured. 

Speaker 2  (16:23)
Aaj, yes, so Yeah, on the retention part, we have Ok, save 7 days. Basically, 7 days of data we are keeping it, and then we're caring. 

Speaker 1  (16:39)
Ok. So our timing is also done in the S3 

Speaker 2  (16:44)
Sorry, come again. 

Speaker 1  (16:45)
Hi kyun is also done using the Sthree different different tiers or is there any other technology or using? 

Speaker 2  (16:54)
Our carving, I think, is also done in the SD card because Yes, yeah, because we are getting multiple data on the streets each day every day. So yeah, we are doing their carving. 

Speaker 1  (17:05)
Any specific year you know, in which this architect data is kept 

Speaker 2  (17:10)
Sorry, I forgot that in history. We are not archiving the data. We are just simply removing, because we already have the data there in the data break side. 

Speaker 2  (17:20)
And that's not flexible. SHOW. Sorry, yes, using something. 

Speaker 1  (17:29)
Boy was just asking that if you're arriving data in SD then what was the tourist year you use or the storage class you used there? 

Speaker 2  (17:38)
Okay, that was the confirmation side. I have was not a part of it, but there are 3 types basically. Based on the cost of 

Speaker 1  (17:47)
And the data which you were consuming or ingesting that was a streaming data, or the batch. 

Speaker 2  (17:53)
It was a badge, this mostly, but we have the stepping data coming up in the in one of the layer where we where we were using the data breaks. Okay, let me recall it as dreams you do Haya, using the piece dream piece for me. Spark stream, spark streams, we are doing it. 

Speaker 2  (18:20)
This is the power spark question. We have the Ok, we're sorry we were making the DL T pipeline. When the DL T pipelines, we were having the same data Still. 

Speaker 2  (18:39)
Yeah This is basically handle the steaming data. They have multiple layers for it. Xiaomi, we have the this bronze silver end of the golden rule. 

Speaker 2  (18:52)
What we are defined. 

Speaker 1  (18:54)
Store so can you just tell me the difference between these different different layers? 

Speaker 2  (18:59)
Yeah, bronze data is basically keeping all the data. And the silver years defined redefinite data removing the unwanted data means dull values in sufficient values. And then on the golden side, we are again aggregating the ring. 

Speaker 1  (19:18)
So if I come to the bronze layer, then how this is different from the your line number of first in which you have written calf card divers, 3 

Speaker 2  (19:29)
Yeah, so this is these are 2 running. Sequentially, okay because one of four one of the pipeline for one of the job recommend was that we are using the these are two different two different applications. So here it is okay once again, so this one is mostly to our R part which is used by the students and the student the teachers and this cause were the logics. 

Speaker 2  (19:59)
Okay, the rules that we have defined based on the states, so it's a different application. I think I have not worked on this one but I have mostly worked on these areas. These are different application altogether. 

Speaker 2  (20:17)
Open industries. Yeah, this is this is basically connected. This is 3 and another database sides. 

Speaker 2  (20:23)
All this connected. After this holding? 

Speaker 1  (20:28)
Any particular reason that why you shifted from snowflake to Lord Shiva or reach shift to snowflake? What was the reason behind that? 

Speaker 2  (20:36)
Yeah, I mean, we shift. It was already been done I was not a part of it but the reason was that Snowflake was fast because it's stored the data in a different way. The micro participation. 

Speaker 2  (20:52)
Uh, there were a lot of other challenges right? Uh, redship, we have to heaven, it's pay to go service snowflake, but red shift is not Also, there were some other challenges where we were sorry. 

Speaker 1  (21:13)
Blood shift is also on demand nobody 

Speaker 2  (21:16)
Hi Bixby 

Speaker 1  (21:18)
Hello, is So can you just now draw any diagram which Aslam has talked about about the requirement or the use case, which we have asked that there are multiple sets of data from different different kinds of data types? Are there then consuming that data? And the data science is, say Ntv's, it's not an mbsv, that's in TVS, you'll use chunk of data as well. 

Speaker 2  (21:50)
They're just to add-on this one. We have used the adf python, uh, long time back. So if we have the different data type, okay, different data type. 

Speaker 2  (22:04)
Let's say. Ok, so that part Adm basically handles it very well. Let's say the bronze layer we have Data like it. 

Speaker 2  (22:21)
Jessica date is taking it as a string. But on our silver. And then Golden layer, we need it as a timestamp. 

Speaker 2  (22:37)
So how we do it is. We Convert the data. So we have a job written in the notebook where we are exposed to converting our data to our matching table, which is our Delta table. 

Speaker 2  (22:53)
Um, so that way we do it. But I don't know any other way we can perform it or the AD side idea that 

Speaker 1  (23:02)
You talked about the Delta table, so what are the Delta tables? What are is there any chance we can implement this in AWS, and what are the Delta lakes or Can you just give some brief about what is Delta lake Delta table? And how do we maintain this if we want to maintain this and S3 or in any or data breaks or any other technology. 

Speaker 2  (23:26)
Yeah, data lakes are nothing. But the SG only so we are keeping the data there just as storage, but how it is different from the Delta table. Because Delta T provide the acid, a functionality On top of the on top of the data, and it's a frame, it's an open source. 

Speaker 2  (23:46)
This Delta TI mean, just have the acid functionality and comes up with a table. Okay. Yeah, that's a good thing to do. 

Speaker 2  (23:57)
That's the only two things I know about it. 

Speaker 1  (24:24)
So and what formats did you work on the different different Datasets? Sorry, storing these while restoring these Delta lakes or data Delta tables, watch what format or data or was used, right? 

Speaker 2  (24:42)
Remove. What was it holiday data? Fine? 

Speaker 2  (24:45)
Okay, there is another part where we have used the there are 2 ways we are using the ORC park so ORC. We are doing it when we are simply dumping the data to the storage location of the Azure, and then moving that data to the database. Okay, so in that part we have to read the data as a urc format and then again dumping to the database. 

Speaker 2  (25:10)
The other way is the parking format, which is directly injecting the data to the Delta TV, there. It is automatically converted data into the park in the form. 

Speaker 1  (25:23)
And so, any reason, any differences which you can highlight about the using different pik formats and aver any differences? 

Speaker 2  (25:34)
Yes, I know about it, but I need to reckon C URC is majorly. Used for transactions, okay, acid transaction data for the park, one, its having the columnar data. Okay, which is fast for the retrieval and This has the Better data also that we have, I mean, I'm just forgotting the difference. 

Speaker 1  (26:10)
That's okay, nobody's okay, obslm. You can also ask if Do you have anything to please? 

Speaker 3  (26:25)
Ok, Prakar, how comfortable are you with smoke like? 

Speaker 2  (26:30)
I am going to go quite comfortable because I have worked with these. No pipe creation not in the same project, but on the other project, also what we just know, sorry, snow pipe and streams on that TV streaming also. 

Speaker 3  (26:47)
Hotel hotels, streams. 

Speaker 2  (26:49)
Yeah, streams in the snowflake is basically creating these stream on top of the table. And then we have okay, so let's say the data comes in again in the steaming, then it will go into check for 3 parameters, 3 column. Basically, is it an update for insert one I mean, I'm talking about the action that 3 column provide so something if it is an insert, then we come to know. 

Speaker 2  (27:19)
Okay, this is an insert data if it is upgraded. Okay, but there are kind of booling fact that itself for these 3 columns. Industrial office, okay. 

Speaker 3  (27:31)
Ok. I give you a scenario okay, let's say you have a table, hence not like which was earlier coming. Let's say monthly nar. 

Speaker 3  (27:47)
That data will be coming weekly and you have a change log file. Okay, the product team is giving a change log file. Now what you do is what the task is to update the existing table with the new Change lock file. 

Speaker 3  (28:07)
So what will be your approach? 

Speaker 2  (28:12)
Okay, initially, it was a monthly data. So if it is monthly, I am consuming that we have partition the data as well. On the month basis. 

Speaker 3  (28:22)
No noise is a single table where we are updating the table. 

Speaker 2  (28:27)
Yeah, so there could be multiple ways we can do it if it is weekly. Then I'm just thinking whether to use I. I'll assume no. 

Speaker 2  (28:40)
I'll i'll make sure that between the partition between the clustering. I'll take a call between the partition or the cluster. So because the data is weekly. 

Speaker 2  (28:52)
Now, then it will go into create a lot of I'm just thinking whether it's going to create a small small file has per month or if there's a sufficient data to have the data inside the month month twice date month, twice partitions. 

Speaker 3  (29:13)
No, no, let me clear the question you have an existing table. That is a table earlier what we did like. Let's say that data was coming January February March, so there is one table, and every time we get an update from the product team. 

Speaker 3  (29:30)
What we do is we refresh that table. Refreshing means like we trunked the table and instead of the new data there. Now what the new scenario is here, we will be getting a weekly update value that is a change logic. 

Speaker 3  (29:57)
How will you do that? 

Speaker 2  (30:00)
Calculate the partition again from monthly to weekly Again? But that will going to create a lot of partitions. Hey, weekly means. 

Speaker 2  (30:15)
HHV on. A 1 week, 2 week. Let's say if It will go on to create Okay, perm, 1 week. 

Speaker 2  (30:33)
We have one file only right. So within the month, we have 4 files. 

Speaker 3  (30:38)
No, you have to update it weekly, not monthly enough. 

Speaker 2  (30:44)
No, I'm just thinking, how many parties are going to create? Yeah, if not, then okay? Yeah, I'll do the partition. 

Speaker 2  (30:58)
Only that will work for me. 

Speaker 1  (31:03)
Dish, a cat and can you create partition of the existing table? 

Speaker 2  (31:09)
Yes, we can create it. 

Speaker 1  (31:12)
And what is the command of creating that simply if you have to Data partition of the existing table 

Speaker 2  (31:21)
Yeah, insert into okay. Okay? Mahavihati data in the form of weekly. 

Speaker 2  (31:32)
Okay so insert into I need to override that table. And now, because already we have the month data now wear, because we have to keep that data somewhere. Sorry, I'm not able to understand the exact problem. 

Speaker 1  (31:53)
No, no I was just asking the solution. Which that you will be partitioning the table. So I am just asking whether you can simply create a partition of the existing table, or is there any command which you can use any create alternate, delete those commands or how would you create partition in the existing table? 

Speaker 2  (32:16)
Hey I'll use the insert to command where I'll pass the partition. Ok, with slate staff on that table that I think should work. Because it will go into create a new table with the same data. 

Speaker 2  (32:31)
But with a different partition. Show that should work in 

Speaker 3  (32:40)
Ok, nut, the next question will be like you have the data in S3 and you are trying to ingest the data in Scrompflake. What is what will be your approach? Give me the process steps. 

Speaker 2  (32:57)
Yeah, I mean, in between, we can use the depend on the data we can use the snow pipe. I'm so we can create the Okay so we can either go with the lamdas, because if we Put some file into the okay, the snowflake will automatically take care, we have to configure the queues, okay, so in the S three's, when we upload the file if you going to be There's a way right, so in the snow price. We have to provide the notification integration, so notification integration. 

Speaker 2  (33:35)
We have to pass the parameters of the quiz, ok, sir, and Q will going to Get back the data into the stages and stage to the table in the snowflake. 

Speaker 3  (33:53)
What are the different type of stages that we have in snowflake? 

Speaker 2  (33:56)
Yeah, we have 31 is the user. What is the external external if the internal and the external in the internal it has the use with the ad the rate with the external we have? We can provide the name of the stage. 

Speaker 2  (34:17)
And then we have the external location also that we can provide like castri or storage location. 

Speaker 3  (34:26)
Ok. 

Speaker 1  (34:30)
One more thing related to this only as I just want to ask how would you if there is a huge amount of data so How would you what would be the best approach of loading that from S3 into the Stockland? It is not a small it's around TVS of data. So it's no pipe would be good enough for any other any other way which we can use to copy data into the snof table. 

Speaker 2  (35:02)
The other way. So basically we're doing the migration We have to created the chunks. This is what I can think of right now. 

Speaker 2  (35:13)
We can create the chunks. And then we can upload those chunks. Okay? 

Speaker 2  (35:18)
If the data is huge. What is the other way? 

Speaker 3  (35:28)
How much data can be handled with 

Speaker 1  (35:30)
Sooner Bhai snow 5. 

Speaker 2  (35:33)
Yes, I mean. 

Speaker 3  (35:34)
What is the greeneration that you can run 

Speaker 2  (35:38)
500 MB I'll make sure that he will have. 

Speaker 3  (35:47)
No, I'm asking it, the snow pipe is having a limitation. Are you aware of it? What is the limitation? 

Speaker 2  (35:55)
Just say I'm happy, no I mean it has the same limited size limited, it can hold the limited size only. Maybe I'm not sure I'm not sure when 2008 MB to 500 MB C. 

Speaker 3  (36:12)
Let's say if so one have asked like it's in a TBS, and then you have you have divided or split it the file into different chunks, then also to load this data. You need a time frame. Okay, do you think that Snow pipe will be able to handle this data. 

Speaker 2  (36:42)
See. This type of scenario is no type is used only for the small data. Yeah, but we can go with the other way. 

Speaker 2  (36:54)
We can use the We can use the Dax also, air flows. We have Or we can use the I'm just thinking. 

Speaker 1  (37:06)
Also, how will tag fix this problem? Responding, how will tag help in this particular scenario? 

Speaker 2  (37:17)
So we can have their scripts, right? That's all for the end of the pipeline. 

Speaker 1  (37:23)
Maybe, okay, so 

Speaker 2  (37:25)
Pipeline radio pipeline on 

Speaker 1  (37:26)
So although those scripts will be making use of data, which is divided into smaller chunks, and then again, it will iterate a small pipe through all divorce data, and then it's a good okay. So that's the approach which you are suggesting, right? 

Speaker 2  (37:43)
Ok, yes, I was thinking of the other way, but Who is the party pipeline? We can create it that pipeline will be running the eastern 

Speaker 3  (37:56)
Okay, broker praker, what is the latest technology that we have worked upon? And there isn't projects. 

Speaker 2  (38:01)
What is the 

Speaker 3  (38:03)
Technology, technology that AI is 

Speaker 2  (38:07)
We are using the data breaks majorly. 

Speaker 3  (38:10)
Data breaks, okay. 

Speaker 2  (38:11)
Database is known as parking sparkling Siddhartha's pair of carbon 

Speaker 1  (38:16)
And data bricks are you aware about the white spaces? What are the virus spaces? 

Speaker 2  (38:22)
What are the widespread 

Speaker 1  (38:24)
Work is space. 

Speaker 2  (38:26)
What is space? Is it correct? What is 

Speaker 1  (38:32)
Yeah, work WO work. 

Speaker 2  (38:36)
What is the specifics, especially 

Speaker 3  (38:37)
Work work. 

Speaker 2  (38:40)
Ok, work space. Yeah, yesterday's yeah, I know about it. Workplace basically. 

Speaker 2  (38:48)
With different multiple teams, they have the different worlds. So if one teams were working on the one workspace, then the other team is so we have the concept of the unity catalogue, that is managed that vanishes the all the workspaces. 

Speaker 1  (39:01)
Advantage unity catalogue. 

Speaker 2  (39:04)
University at Leh is nothing but your giving. The unit at law will provide all the accesses can necessarily access that the other team needs. Let's say we've delivered Q&A production environment and all those will have the different tables. 

Speaker 2  (39:20)
So if I need to access the key one. So I need to ask for the access and that tax will be going to provide Pocket, there were different commands. 

Speaker 1  (39:45)
And yell, have you also wait on the database? Marketplace kind of stuff, those things 

Speaker 2  (39:52)
Our database sorry. 

Speaker 1  (39:54)
Like snowflake, marketplace and low Marketplace, you have data breaks. Also, there is some data sharing which, you everyone know, data sharing concept here. 

Speaker 2  (40:04)
So we normally Delta shared Production table to QA ok. 

Speaker 3  (40:18)
Can you share this with external customers? 

Speaker 2  (40:21)
Yeah, can we can share it with the other Extraction on database. 

Speaker 3  (40:27)
How do we do it in snowflake? If I want to share a data with you, what is the process 

Speaker 2  (40:34)
I mean, I'm not sure of it, but I know that we can share that tables so we have the commands for it, create Delta share table table link and we have to provide the recipe and also 

Speaker 3  (40:47)
Ok. 

Speaker 2  (40:48)
And maybe the external location we can provide. We have done it to using the database only not to the other source. 

Speaker 3  (40:59)
So Coming back to architecture. This is the initially I asked you something, this is what the process that he worked upon. Now. 

Speaker 3  (41:12)
Let's say you have to create a platform for Captureing data, so this will be a platform where we will be processing multiple Datasets, which will be which we will be receiving from. Let's say vendors, multiple vendors API anything. It may be anything, and then you need to do an ETL. 

Speaker 3  (41:39)
Then, there are certain rules that we apply on this data. And then we will be exposing it to external resources. Why are you allocation? 

Speaker 3  (41:55)
Now you're Give me an architecture overview. I don't want what text tech you will use. How will you handle this Datasets that are coming from different sources? 

Speaker 3  (42:09)
What will be the processes that you will be using to? Let's say I user capture. You have to build a platform where the user captures the data or user does the process, and then you have to do a series of steps where you will make sure that the data has to be corrected when it goes out from this platform to the customer or a platform or some storage layers. 

Speaker 3  (42:41)
Okay 

Speaker 2  (42:47)
Ok, so as you said Multiple vendors, okay, then we perform the ETL, and then expose the data to the other sources. So I'll make sure that I'll decide if it is a batch data or a stream data. The data is a batch data. 

Speaker 2  (43:05)
Then Okay, then we can do simple. Ok, we can. So they are multiple ways down, we can have the Using the piece park or maybe creating the notebooks Multiple moves, I'll try to create the pipeline first pipeline in the first week in the bronze layer. 

Speaker 2  (43:30)
We have, we'll consume all the data. Can store it into the On a table or I can go with a file file also. Ok, and then in the silver year I'll perform the transformation and the check validation. 

Speaker 2  (43:57)
Check basically. Alternatives. In the transformation. 

Speaker 2  (44:05)
Okay? And on the golden game. I'll perform the aggregation. 

Speaker 2  (44:13)
So this will my overview, and if I go inside the bronze layer. Just a simple table, I can use the Delta table over here. Okay. 

Speaker 2  (44:28)
Table or the okay. I can use the Delta table here. 

Speaker 1  (44:32)
So before before just this blonde's were, what do you think? There must be something like ingestion kind of there that how the multiple Datasets. We are receiving them. 

Speaker 1  (44:44)
They are coming from different data sources, data suppliers. They all have different different data data formats. So Those things we need to take care of yeah. 

Speaker 2  (44:58)
That we need to take care of all these things before sending the details to the in the bronze beer itself. We can do that right? So in the bronze layer, even if it is getting the data from Kafka or into some story location. 

Speaker 1  (45:14)
See it bronze her law data, right? Yeah? But raw data, in order to be a part of your system, it should be ingested from different different sources. 

Speaker 2  (45:24)
Right correctly. 

Speaker 1  (45:25)
But in hand they all have but different different frequency of the data suppliers would be having. Yeah, so before this particular layer there must be some layer which does all this kind of work which in just all the different different Datasets make use of some technology tech stack which maybe you can recommend here we will be using what technology for this particular purpose. And then we has told the data into the belong there. 

Speaker 1  (45:52)
Right? So before branch layer, what we will be doing. 

Speaker 2  (45:55)
Yeah, we can use the STS okay, what the IDS storage location, where we can keep all the data. Ok, and then we can create maybe the use of adf pipeline we can Inject our data. Show the notebook we can transform it. 

Speaker 2  (46:22)
Into the Delta table because in between, we have 

Speaker 1  (46:25)
Adf is assured, data facilitate 

Speaker 2  (46:27)
Yeah, something it's correct. Show through the idea we can Weakness can inject our data into the idls story location, and from that location, it will pick that data. And on the transformation side, we can never know where we're going to do the transformation, depending on the what kind of data that we have, we can filter out, we can write the notebook based on the Datasets. 

Speaker 2  (46:54)
We have received so let's say if parking one we have different notebook for the tax one. We have different number is something like that. We will 

Speaker 1  (47:04)
Ok, you have also had on the chatbots, right? So so just go. How can we achieve this particular any of this phase of this particular architecture with your AI agent? 

Speaker 1  (47:19)
Or any those thing 

Speaker 2  (47:21)
See. Ok, so in what you know, these things we cannot do that because we need the refined data, refined data in the sense we should have something to train the data on. Correct, show advanced these things are built. 

Speaker 2  (47:41)
Then, only we can do the we can do the processing of that data. 

Speaker 3  (47:53)
Okay. 

Speaker 1  (47:54)
Aslam I am done with the questions. So if you have any, then you can question 

Speaker 3  (48:00)
A praker continue with the growth layer, please 

Speaker 2  (48:04)
Continue with t 

Speaker 3  (48:06)
Broz, lek attel transformation. What will you do in the platform? Let's say I'm capturing something on the platform or doing an ET on the platform. 

Speaker 3  (48:18)
But before sending it to the final delivery platform, whatever I have, what will be the steps that I will be doing with the data. 

Speaker 2  (48:32)
Um, ok. I talk about the in the bronze here itself, right? You're talking about. 

Speaker 2  (48:37)
So in the bronze, there is nothing but storing the raw data. 

Speaker 3  (48:41)
Not in the bronze layer, the initial layer silver layer 

Speaker 2  (48:45)
Yes, silver layer. I'll do the validation check. Okay so something like quantity should not be great less than 0 but I'm just taking an example. 

Speaker 2  (48:56)
Some mild check investing values. Okay? Ok, all those things we can do. 

Speaker 2  (49:04)
Then, on the validation, then we are again transformed the data. Maybe we can do the we can create multiple features feature in the some multiple columns out of the existing column. Okay, we can create the flagging. 

Speaker 2  (49:18)
We can create the okay, I'm just talking about the depending on the business need, we can create the multiple columns out of it. And then on the golden layer, we will do the aggregations like average or something. So those things and that can depend on the business. 

Speaker 3  (49:35)
Probably remove replicates in silver layer. 

Speaker 2  (49:38)
Yeah, remember duplicates, we will gonna check. If okay. We have to write the using the pice bar. 

Speaker 2  (49:49)
We have to write the coding that if the account is greater than one based on the all the columns, then we have to keep on the room number one, something Using a window function, basically 

Speaker 3  (50:07)
How comfortable are you with writing queries? 

Speaker 2  (50:11)
Yeah, I mean I used to do that daily. 

Speaker 3  (50:15)
Ok. But in what gave me the query for getting the top 7 salary from an employee table? Top 7 salary from unemployed unemployed table. 

Speaker 2  (50:47)
77 salary from the employee. 

Speaker 2  (51:36)
Something like that early Timmy night know with there are other ways also using the correlated queries or something. This is the one I can think of right now. 

Speaker 1  (51:50)
Okay, this is the one any other solution to this particular. 

Speaker 2  (51:55)
Here is Korea related query at weekend, right? 

Speaker 1  (52:01)
Ok, maybe we can leave. Can you Tell me a way of deleting the duplicates from a table. Which has all the columns, which are having same values, and maybe there is no primary key in them. 

Speaker 2  (52:17)
Ok, you are talking about the sequel or 

Speaker 1  (52:20)
Chequel. Persequel, then we can come to spar. 

Speaker 2  (52:24)
Priya's selection. Ok, so first we will gaurack on the All the columns that you buy Goodbye account. Okay. 

Speaker 2  (53:02)
Grukhai. Mumbai. Call. 

Speaker 2  (53:10)
I just wrote it last time. Occupies a column. We were keeping all the columns here, which is If a form tablet, what starred? 

Speaker 2  (53:41)
To unstar, a typical cover holding edit with a withcology Sir. We were checking the counts. Basically, count is greater than one. 

Speaker 2  (53:57)
Then we can do it here. We need to provide all the columns that is needed. Let's say the family idea or something. 

Speaker 2  (54:14)
All the columns. That way, you can 

Speaker 1  (54:19)
Ok, we have only 2 minutes left. So maybe we can wrap up. So anything else, assalam, maybe you want to Thank you. 

Speaker 3  (54:32)
Ratan, nice talking with you will get back to you. 

Speaker 1  (54:38)
Thank you, prakr, have a good day like all 

Speaker 3  (54:41)
When? 
