leesa.wandele@nextgeninvent.com, "Talent (SMB)" <talent@nextgeninvent.com>, talent_list@nextgeninvent.com

Speaker 1  (00:00)
Yeh, hello, so here we are working on Predicting the irrigation needs So it is more of the GU stacked ensemble ensemble means that's mostly it gives us the average rating average voting. Actually, so if there are multiple trees, then we'll get the we will get the average voting out of all the trees that we have created. And we are using the LGB. 

Speaker 1  (00:36)
LGB X GB and the cat boost. Ok, so we have the playground series. H6E4. 

Speaker 1  (00:44)
So what we are trying to do here is we have the blend original source data with a competition data. So we have blend the original data with the competition data. And we've done the feature engineering U domain driven interaction and aggregation. 

Speaker 1  (01:04)
Also, the GP oxalated light GB. M. We have used GP accelerated light GBM Hg boot boost CAD boost, and we've used the 5 fold stacking with logistic regression metallonic. 

Speaker 1  (01:21)
So threshold optimisation for the balanced accuracy on minority classes. So we have a list on all the imports that we are using. So initially we are starting with the numbi pandas, Mat, clot lip dot pipelot, sea born warning, ok, and then we have the model selection like straight. 

Speaker 1  (01:45)
Is stratified keyford? Ok statified K4 and then we have the label encoder. Liver encoder is for the categorical mapping. 

Speaker 1  (01:55)
Then, we're using some mattresses. Here we are using the balanced accuracy score transification report and the confusion matrix. Another thing that we are doing is the linear model. 

Speaker 1  (02:06)
We have the logistics regression. Then, we have the class weight which import the compute sample weight. We are using the lights gbm, which we have discussed as G boost and the cat boost. 

Speaker 1  (02:23)
All this parameter, now we are loading the data. And here what we're trying to do is we're reading the train data test data and the irrigation data. And when we are capable of shapes of all this data, we have the trained DF test DF and the original data. 

Speaker 1  (02:41)
Now we're adding column. To the original ok, so this is our trade data with the maximum + 1. Ok, and we have the trained df ID maximum plus OnePlus length of the original DF right, so we are going to greet the ID and ID would be maximum of the maximum ID getting it from the train DF + 1. 

Speaker 1  (03:11)
Ok, range, starting from the maximum + 1 to The length of the original DF right, and now we're contaginating the original data with the competition data. So we're using the period concature, and we're concatting the train DF along with the original DF ok blended train, then we are finding the shape and everything. Okay? 

Speaker 1  (03:36)
And We're getting the value count for the irrigation need. Okay, is it all? Let me run it entire thing. 

Speaker 1  (03:49)
Ok, so meanwhile, it is running then we're doing the feature extract feature engineering. Okay, so we are extracting the details out of the feature so we have in the category column. We have soil type crop type. 

Speaker 1  (04:06)
Ok, so all type of first soils, all type of crops we have And then we have the growth stage of the crop. Okay, seasons, we have irrigation type. We have canal or reservoir river. 

Speaker 1  (04:26)
Soar then we have the water sources mulching used. Mulching means kind of we are trying to understand the water level. Every munching means they have to cover the crops. 

Speaker 1  (04:43)
Okay, so that the moisture will be remained in the soil. Or the munching means the water should not be evaporate. So for that reason, we have to do the mulching region. 

Speaker 1  (04:57)
Also, what is the so these are the numerical column which is the page of the soil moisture from the soil organic carbon. Connectivity, electrical connectivity in the soil temperature, humidity, rainfall, the sunlight hour. Wind speed, field area actor ke the area of the field. 

Speaker 1  (05:25)
And then the previous irrigation, so what if we've used the previous irrigation, then we have to list on it here? Now, after the balance feature that we have, then we're creating one method which is the engineering feature. And in that one we have the data frame, ok, so now we're coping the that data frame, and then we are trying to find the water balance. 

Speaker 1  (05:51)
So water balance means how much water it will be remained. Let's say if the rain fall has happened along with the previous irrigation, then we have a total water. Input, so what is the total water input we have received from the rainfall? 

Speaker 1  (06:11)
And whatever we left it with the previous aggregation, then we have the evaporation evaporation. Evaporative stress that tells us that the sunlight and temperature, ok? And the wind speed. 

Speaker 1  (06:29)
All the soil is having divided by the humidity. Okay, humidity + 1, we are doing it as to remove the 0. We don't want to divide it by 0. 

Speaker 1  (06:43)
That's why we are putting it + 1. So it is giving up the index. Okay, so the temperature sunlight and the wind speed is hitting on the soil. 

Speaker 1  (06:58)
And the humidity in the air okay? So, because if the temperature will increase, all those getting increased sunlight will going to increase, or maybe the Window is going to increase. This is going to increase the irrigation need because it needs it will take out a lot of water from the soil correct. 

Speaker 1  (07:21)
Due to the evaporation, but as we have humidity in the air right so water is there in the rain in the air so it won't allow them to. Evocate the water because we have the layer of water human humidity. So that's what we call it as a habitation index. 

Speaker 1  (07:43)
So more of the temperature and everything and less humidity. So the evaporation would be high. Otherwise, it will be low. 

Speaker 1  (07:52)
Then, we have the moisture deficit based on the humidity, minus a soil moisture. So humidity in the air minus water in the soil. Ok. 

Speaker 1  (08:06)
Then, we have the water balance, which is total water input, which we have calculated from the rainfall in the previous elegation, minus. Evaporation evaporative stress because how much it is allowing to water to move evaporation to go up, multiply by the field, correct. So That's how the biggest field, the more the evaporation. 

Speaker 1  (08:36)
Okay, so that's how we're receiving or we are. Having the water going up, ok Evaporation is stress multiplied by the field actor so the size of the arms, the longer the field size, the larger the evaporation. Okay? 

Speaker 1  (08:59)
So if anything goes up-and-down, it will go into have the Water, okay, water will be going to be lost from here. Right? The total input minus the water loss will be the water balance. 

Speaker 1  (09:12)
Motor water will be there or not in the soil or not. So crop relative moisture, which is target encoding proxy, minus, no leakage. Ok, let's understand this one. 

Speaker 1  (09:25)
So we have the moisture map is equal to, so we'll try to group by the cross crop type. So if I can show you here, if you look at the original data set, which is 1000, 20 And the irrigation need is approximately Solo is more. And high is very less So we have a data imbalance here, as we can see. 

Speaker 1  (09:54)
We're low is almost 50%. And the rest is Total issue. Rus', totalist. 

Speaker 1  (10:06)
It's almost 60% And the high middle are the rest. 40% are high in medium, so there is a kind of imbalance, but not that much. Um, now we're So we have this soil moisture meaning based on the cross type crop type. 

Speaker 1  (10:28)
And we have the soil moisture Divided by the crop type. So we're trying to calculate the relative crop moisture relative crop moisture. So relationship crop moisture, which is coming up from the end of Soil moisture divided by the crop type. 

Speaker 1  (10:55)
Ok. So more the Divided by the crop type Film one, not 0. Carovaran, what it is doing. 

Speaker 1  (11:10)
Let me check what it is doing. 

Speaker 1  (11:25)
So here it is. Taking all the moisture map items And it is creating the lid example moisture map. Having the wheat is 0.8% and rises, what's going to so with column relative moisture. 

Speaker 1  (11:46)
We are calculating the soil moisture divided by the Expression is the crop type Show all the items that is at right in this corner. Ok, so we have the map of moisture map, and we have convert map to spark column map column. So we have Moisture map dot map. 

Speaker 1  (12:27)
Okay, we eat and 08 will come here, so the wheat will go to create List of. Then, we're Collasing with the cross tide crop type 1 or 0. Can you give me some example? 

Speaker 1  (13:00)
Let's say we have a sample data of wheat rice in cone, which is crop type and sweat moisture. And wheat is heavy. A moisture map is point 8 risks. 

Speaker 1  (13:11)
The 1.2. The relative crop moisture would be 06, which is a soil moisture divided by the 0.8. Crop type crop type is weight. 

Speaker 1  (13:31)
And then from the moisture of wear, picking the Ok, got it. Show relative rock moisturiser. So here in the moisture, my fee will be having crop type and the mean of the soil moisture. 

Speaker 1  (13:51)
Okay? Now we're dividing the soil moisture divided by the Crop type. Of coming up from the map, okay? 

Speaker 1  (14:03)
So if we have the wheat Swiss motion is 06 then relative would be soil moisture, which is 0.6 divided by the Reserve from the map. Moisture mode of that particular value. Then, we have the mulch interaction, which is Soil moisture into mulching used ok. 

Speaker 1  (14:32)
So I'll moisture multiply. If there is a mulching used, if yes, then 1.5 will go into multiply it by 1.5 otherwise, no Ok, now we have the soil health. The soil health is the organic carbon that we have used multiply by this soil moisture divided by the electoral connectivity that we have soil serenity risk is electrical connectivity multiplied by temperature divided by the rainfall. 

Speaker 1  (15:07)
Ph, a deviation is while PH −6.5 okay, climate stress, heat, stress, dryness index and the wind evaporation. So heat stress would be The death, if we multiply the temperature with the humidity. And we take the percentage Temperature and humidity. 

Speaker 1  (15:34)
Then, we're a dryness index dryness, come from the sunlight. Divided by the rainfall. Wind depopation is Wind is Blowing and the Temperature divided by the humidity. 

Speaker 1  (15:51)
Okay, so irrigation per factor is equal to previous irrigation. That has been happened divided by the Field field previous aggression that has happened divided by the field is the irrigation per Hector ok, rainfall per Hector rainfall divided by the area. Now we have the moisture retention moisture retention is soil moisture multiplied by the organic carbon. 

Speaker 1  (16:20)
Mohammed machine Maharashtra temple temperature ratio is slow. Moisturised by the weather temperature. Temperature ratio. 

Speaker 1  (16:28)
So we have the cross soil season interaction and code. It has the group estate. So for group column in soil type season, crop growth stage. 

Speaker 1  (16:41)
We have the moisture mean ok, soil type moisture mean season moistureme and crop growth moistureme. If we've found That we have the soil type moisturemen. In the map, then we'll group by that and we will use the Soil moisture. 

Speaker 1  (17:07)
Transform with a mean Ok. Now we have the engineering feature. We're calling it from the train full. 

Speaker 1  (17:19)
Engineering feature calling tum DF comada moisture map. Ok. Now we're the feature column, which is The column, not in the ID irrigation needs ok. 

Speaker 1  (17:37)
Feature column except ID and irrigation need. That's we're popular, so we're getting all these values. Okay. 

Speaker 1  (17:54)
Now so we have to do some calculation around it. So we can do that. Let me let me know if I can print the third one. 

Speaker 1  (18:08)
Train full ride. Vocabulary do that, it targets and categorical encoding. So target mapping is low as 0 medium as one Irrigation Mein aapke apne, if we have calculated the value, then we have categorical column. 

Speaker 1  (18:30)
And in that we have the We're concatting the training full stop Categorial. Kategorical, okay. Tanvi is a miracle. 

Speaker 1  (18:45)
I draw a closet. So what we're trying to do here is target and categorical categorical encoding. Now we've GPU accelerated model training, so we're using the light GBM 3 models that we've used LGB. 

Speaker 1  (19:09)
LGB params led GBM ok led GBM. Because we're using the GPU's estimators learning rate. Number of leaves 31 Max up. 

Speaker 1  (19:23)
6 class weight balance were possible to management ex boost were using cat boost. We using model configurations, okay. Now we're using a 5 fold CV training with all models. 

Speaker 1  (19:38)
Ok, so we have All the models here. Split it. If we are doing it, then we have the extra ok, confix models model dot fit. 

Speaker 1  (19:55)
If we do, then if we're going to run for all the models and based on that, we'll get the balanced accuracy score. Ok, now for 5 foot 4 every foot we're receiving the our values. Okay, overall, the balance accuracies. 

Speaker 1  (20:15)
This one have been the maximum. Now we're stacking it with the logistic regression. Ok, using the H tech method and the simple average baseline. 

Speaker 1  (20:28)
Also, is there Steck metal learner with CV? So better feature, if you look at these 3 probably into 3 model simple average Out of force, balance equities,0.98 steak metal out of frequencies,0.79. Now we're the threshold documentation for balance accuracy. 

Speaker 1  (20:55)
So best class sweet, we have received is low 1 medium 0.8 high is 1.4. Now we're doing the analysis analysis and visualisation. So here if you see that for the Unpredicted, and the actual Calculation matrix confusion matrix basically is 97%. 

Speaker 1  (21:21)
Show the majorly we have With low? And hi Vikas. So what the model has predicted low, but there was high, it's 0.0% medium. 

Speaker 1  (21:40)
The model predicted high, but it was medium, very less. Yeah, that's how it is now. We have 3 classes. 

Speaker 1  (21:55)
Purchase recall. Which is low, medium and high? So we can see low is very high. 

Speaker 1  (22:01)
Irrigation need low is very high. Recall is recall is very high recall per class for the low class. The recall is very high. 

Speaker 1  (22:16)
Now the classification report, we have the precision recalled afnescore, so precision is 99%. 99 is a good one recall for low is very good. One, for the 96% F1 score is 9788. 

Speaker 1  (22:35)
Now the accuracy we have is like this one93%. Ah, feature importance, if we get going to calculate we're getting it. Swile moisture is one of the features that is the most important crop growth. 

Speaker 1  (22:50)
Growth temperature, multiplying used wind rainfall and total water rainfall. Ok, so that's how it is and let me know if you have any questions. 
