fernan.dedios@optum.com, p_anjitha198@optum.com
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Ok, so starting for the Chatbot, can 

Speaker 2  (00:03)
Can you look look into cameras? Why need to take a story? Yeah, thank you. 

Speaker 1  (00:17)
Also for the pipeline thing we have used our lantian, majorly, and how the data comes up in the pipeline is that we have the ADF pipeline and in the AD pipeline we are our retrieving, the I mean, we are retrieving the data from the ads and from ideals to the Delta late. So, and using the idiot pipeline, so this is the one pipeline for the for the for the documentation. Also, that's the one way, and somewhere we are uploading the files like PDF gsn and some conference pages. 

Speaker 1  (00:53)
Some policies, data SOS policy data, those also comes from 50 to the ideas only, and then we have this chunking layer in the Chunky. We are using the This is recursive splitter taxes splitter, and then we have the embedding layer in the bedding layer. We are using the B eg a model and then from the embedding. 

Speaker 1  (01:17)
It goes to the vector database for storing the embedding and from the probe from the UI side, the UI is built-in the this angular and then we are exposing the this layer through the fast API and then we have the prompts we have written the prompts over there that is summarising the context. Of the user as mass also we have added the cache token wear for the semantic text and again once the data. Once the user reports of sentences it goes to the embedding, it goes to the sprout, clear and time it goes to the lm and he get the response back so the retrieval side we have used the We have tuned at retrievals, okay, we have rewranking their retrievals as well. 

Speaker 1  (02:16)
Just to make sure we are getting the relevance. Diversified data from the probes, along with that, we have tuned. The vector databases also with the embeddings also And we have added some memory also supported buffer memory. 

Speaker 1  (02:31)
We have used for the chats so chats. We are storing in the mongo duty for the particular session of the user and from where we are retrieving it. We are storing only top 5 and then previous chats. 

Speaker 1  (02:44)
We are having it and summarising that chat and sending away to the uh from Also, we are exposing the reports also, so we have. We are checking the precisions recall value. We are checking the Mr. 

Speaker 1  (03:02)
Mean reciprocal rank for the ranking and then we are exposing the Hallucination rate error rate fallback rate the costing the token usages. Everything so we are displaying that in a dashboard kind of thing also design talking about the retrieval site and on the generation side we have checked. We have walked on the latency also just to reduce the latency because our main focus was to give the accurate result. 

Speaker 1  (03:34)
Uh, give the accurate result and religion can be tuned later so that was our approach we have implemented the chain types. Also, we were using the map reduced chain type type Further further documentation, it will go into it will go into create the embeddings for each of the documentation and again. Once we have the summarised data, we will send it to the LLM, so that's however, we have designed them. 

Speaker 2  (04:05)
So which retrieval method you have used 

Speaker 1  (04:08)
We have used a chain retrieval method from the vector store, which is our vector DV. 

Speaker 2  (04:14)
So how you comes up with that that we need to use this. Not the 

Speaker 1  (04:21)
I've been written, we have tuned the parameters in the chair retrieval. Like we've taken the top 20 okay, and from those top 20, we are taking the top 5 documentation, which can be ranked. And then 15 can be diversified. 

Speaker 1  (04:39)
So that's that way, we were doing it for that one. We are using the I think the NMR we were using. 

Speaker 2  (04:50)
So how you maybe what about the cost optimisation while maybe using your Leh M right? So anything you thought upon or you optimise so that you can maybe reduce some cost. Yeah 

Speaker 1  (05:06)
So we have reduced a tokens first, so the output because we have just regulation matrix token costs. Okay, so we have to make sure that only let's say 1000 tokens can be input and out of the 1000 tokens. The 500 tokens can be our output. 

Speaker 1  (05:25)
Okay, but that will be displayed on the UI for the user. So and also for the for the cost of commission, right token that we have decreased a token using the summarization of the before sending to the element, we are sunrise in the data. And also I talk about the MMR and the chain type was the map reduce. 

Speaker 1  (05:51)
Okay. So instead of putting everything on the query message for the prompt, we were summarised each of the each of the documentation on the retrieval side each of the documentation. And after summarization, then we are putting into the area so that we can get the data based on the diversified and based on the relevance. 

Speaker 1  (06:13)
Something like that on YouTube. 

Speaker 2  (06:16)
So you have mentioned that you also worked on the spark architecture 

Speaker 1  (06:21)
Yeah, that's why. 

Speaker 2  (06:22)
Yeah, can you explain sparkling architecture? 

Speaker 1  (06:27)
Yes, you should, so park architecture works like they have the driver memory then the executive memory on the driver side. They have so basically, driver role is to sync synchronise with the worker notes schedule the jobs and everything. And So whenever we submit our job, some portion, we need to some memory or some course, we need to specify for the driver and rest to the workers. 

Speaker 1  (06:56)
And once you submit our job, they will convert it to the jobs stages and everything and the Dag is basically created. And so it is the role of the driver to make sure that how many stages will going to create how many jobs it will go to create and based on that we get the result back to the driver and then we see that out. 

Speaker 2  (07:21)
How you handle data scheme in spark joints? 

Speaker 1  (07:25)
Yeah, I mean stunners is how do I handle? There are several methods okay it will show us if we dab only whether there is a shuffling or not or in the Or in the Dax only we can see which executives taking long time to run so the best way to reduce seaness is you can use the salting methods or if you have the spark for or something are which is which has the AQ in by default or in the 3 also you need to. Turn on the AQ in the AQ. 

Speaker 1  (07:59)
E we have to specify the qins, Q and some other parameters like colas fractions and the number of coalest partition also united specific specify to make sure that the sooners will work I have worked on one of the job so not recently but 2 years back I did that. 

Speaker 2  (08:22)
So what's the difference between cache and persist? 

Speaker 1  (08:26)
Yeah, kaise, by default is the case only there are 3 parameters in the pursuit, so if we putting all as true with the memory, then it will be a cashew, but with the persistent method we conserve, we have several other uh parameters, also like memory and dis memory reputation memories inflation. So all these parameters we have if we pass them so the meaning of all this is like, we are not putting everything on the memory we. If memories full, they can leverage the artisans for the story. 

Speaker 1  (09:00)
Apart from that, they have, the replication. Also, say sorry synchronisation. Also, the synchronisation means it will summarise and compress the data before reading or after reading. 

Speaker 2  (09:15)
Is there any scenario where cache works better than if you 

Speaker 1  (09:21)
Yeah, cashew is always preferred. When you have the small data at the small data. That means the memory Aadhaar. 

Speaker 1  (09:28)
That file will be there in the memory. So from memory, it will be easy to use the latency will be reduced, but effect keeping it in the disc side. Then the literacy will be more So if you have a small data that will work. 

Speaker 1  (09:41)
Otherwise it will Give me a few errors out of memories. 

Speaker 2  (09:47)
So if I'll say, if you can design a real-time pipeline using Kafka plus spark streaming 

Speaker 1  (09:57)
Yeah, I mean. If you're talking about the steaming jobs through the Kafka or we can do that with the bad job as well, I have more work. Most of all, mostly on the bad job, I can tell you about that. 

Speaker 1  (10:09)
But do you want me to tell me about the streaming Jobs? 

Speaker 2  (10:16)
You can give me a little bit of overview of that. 

Speaker 1  (10:19)
Okay, for the steaming thing, right? So we have the calfus team also, and then we have the this world piice power question. So they have the concept of auto cloud in the pice park. 

Speaker 1  (10:35)
So with the picepark.is stream, you can read that file. So basically we are using number if we are using the multiple architecture which is bronze layer silver layer and the golden layer. So we have to make sure that our bronze layer bronze table should be steeped table and then your silver table having some validations, um. 

Speaker 1  (10:55)
The constraint, everything then it should be your uh. It should also be your steaming table and with a golden layer. It should not be the, but it should not be the steaming table. 

Speaker 1  (11:05)
It should be the normal table, normal dead material. So on the bronze layer, the data comes up stored using the Kafka with a Kafka stream and we are using the debtism also for the CDC so that data comes up with all the file formats we stored into our brass layer, keeping all the file format or everything alive as the first source tooth. Of data, and then we have the silver layer. 

Speaker 1  (11:32)
We're Adding more validation there, like validation percent, they should not be null values in the primary key. If there is any null values with the some percentage with less some percent with less percentage we can impute that data. Also there are some other validation. 

Speaker 1  (11:50)
And after that, we are keeping the data into the border layer, which is the aggregated data coming from the silver data. So this is the I am talking about the dlt pipeline that we can create for the student. 

Speaker 2  (12:05)
How do you ensure the data quality and reliability? In this case. 

Speaker 1  (12:12)
Yeah, data quality see in the bronze layer. We have all data. Now, when we come up with the silver data, either we can extract some of the features ok, future me, from one column of we can create the multiple columns like that. 

Speaker 1  (12:28)
We can do that and reliable data. We can make sure that it should not be duplicate. It should not be duplicate data. 

Speaker 1  (12:37)
The let's say for some columns like quantity. They should not have the wrong values like negative values. So these things we need to consider, based on the reason we make sure that our columns are Probably a lie along with that. 

Speaker 1  (12:55)
What are what are data type that we need to expose? So those things should be taken care in the silver day? Also, because if the data is coming up as a string in from the bronze layer should be converted to the date timestamp in the silver layer itself. 

Speaker 1  (13:09)
So those few things we usually take. 

Speaker 2  (13:16)
So if we talk about the LLM, then I can say, so, how do you prevent hallucinations? 

Speaker 1  (13:30)
Ok, how do you prevent the hallucination? Their subveral ways? First, we have to Give the relevant data excitation to the rack model. 

Speaker 1  (13:43)
That's the one way the other way is. So there are several factors if these user is asking the same career again and again because he is not getting the relevant answer. So also we have a several matrix there, which tells us that for particular question, how many times the user ask the same question. 

Speaker 1  (14:02)
Ok? So that means if he is asking multiple same questions, he is not getting the multiple correct response. That's the that's the other way. 

Speaker 1  (14:10)
Third way is the human interaction where we check. Okay, the relevance is score basically the MMR uh, rate that tells us what range the actual data was there, in what rank the actual data was there. And the whatever we check, we check. 

Speaker 1  (14:29)
Basically, it should be greater than point 5. The range should be greater than point 5A may point 6 ok, so that rate we check hallucination rate we check. So what's the precession recall everything? 

Speaker 1  (14:43)
The environment of metric, we take it to consideration to check for the allocation. 

Speaker 2  (14:49)
That is, for checking, so I'm just looking for prevention. 

Speaker 1  (14:55)
Prevention, let's say user is asking for the 7 days of return policy. Okay if in an answer you are getting 24 hours or something. So that's a human interaction, human loop. 

Speaker 1  (15:11)
Basically, we need to Put in to check whether we are getting the relevant answer or not. Also, we need to give the relevant data to the RAG. Ok, where sounds joke? 

Speaker 2  (15:24)
So what is the difference between diagine? Tuning. 

Speaker 1  (15:28)
Ok, 5 tuning is basically There are several ways to do the I mean, war. Ok, Fine-tuning means the Pre-trained model. We have to use the Pre-trained model and then we have to increase the accuracy within putting more of the data in the model. 

Speaker 1  (15:53)
But with our data, why we didn't use the Fine-tuning because we have a small set of data and we don't want, we have the cost consideration because cost will be high in few Fine-tuning than the RAG. Yeah, I have created lot of doors and don't with the Fine-tuning and the extraditional approach that we are using for the ramp for just recalling that so first thing we have the cost consideration because with the cost Fine-tuning will be more and with the normal RAG it will be less tokenization also uh, there was another consideration for the token captain. 

Speaker 1  (16:37)
Yeah, these are the things that I can. I can recall it. 

Speaker 2  (16:44)
So you have also worked on mlos. 

Speaker 1  (16:48)
Yeah, I'm a lot. 

Speaker 2  (16:51)
Keso, can you explain me ML life cycle? 

Speaker 1  (16:56)
You're talking about the urban flow or 

Speaker 2  (17:00)
Yeah, flu life cycle. Just if you work on some ML application, so what would be the steps right? 

Speaker 1  (17:11)
No, actually, for the longing thing we are using the Americans, but not. And I didn't get your question in life cycle notice. 

Speaker 2  (17:21)
Like, say, you mean how you work on some machine learning application, right? You get some data. Then you need to work on some machine learning application right? 

Speaker 2  (17:30)
Or you need to build maybe some model, right? 

Speaker 1  (17:33)
We talk about the ingestion layer. I already talk about that ingestion layer with the bronze one silver. Please clean data. 

Speaker 1  (17:41)
So I mean, if you're talking about the that thing I can explain. But you know 

Speaker 2  (17:47)
I'm just trying to get it like how your life cycle means a training development monitoring. 

Speaker 1  (17:57)
Ok, so there are multiple paths. Okay, one way is we are getting lot of data into the Delta table. And for that one, we have a separate pipeline once separate pipeline in the sense we are getting the data from the calf car called to the so we have multiple layers. 

Speaker 1  (18:13)
Okay, batch processing is window from S3 to S3, so we have the read layer. Refined layer and the canonical layer through that one. 

Speaker 2  (18:21)
That I did you already explain yes? 

Speaker 1  (18:24)
I 

Speaker 2  (18:25)
Motivation is to just check about the model life cycle. You can say right how you build models. 

Speaker 1  (18:35)
I work on the rack pipeline and these things only. ML flow is using juicy, but I'm not here the more exposure on that Kesuck, text. 

Speaker 2  (18:50)
How do you use ML flow for tracking of Virgin and help in your workdone? 

Speaker 1  (18:55)
It's been where it's been there in my projects. We're using naval phones for registering the for multiple models. They are keeping all the parametres there in the America but I didn't get much chance to work on it. 

Speaker 1  (19:11)
To be honest. 

Speaker 2  (19:12)
Thank you. So did you get anything else to work on the deployment of models production? Or 

Speaker 1  (19:30)
Yeah, I mean, these are all in the production, only these pipelines, everything, but we've done the container of the APL using. 

Speaker 2  (19:39)
Wah aahuri bhaage bhaag, he will goard in those steps or you are just building something and just providing to somebody else. 

Speaker 1  (19:47)
Yes, some team is there because we're not doing it. 

Speaker 2  (19:51)
Are you aware of what they are doing? 

Speaker 1  (19:53)
Yeah, I'm aware of what they're doing. But 

Speaker 2  (19:56)
So can you explain a little bit so once you build something from how it goes. 

Speaker 1  (20:03)
Ok, I can talk about the adf pipeline first, the data factor so that way, that's in the That's that we have the particular stage. Like def and the broad, so in the broad, we have to replicate the same thing on the broad from the Q from the uit to the broad so that's one of the piping that I already talked about the other way is the unity catalogue in the data bricks, so where we are exposing, the workspace. Clear to the QA Dev and the plot, so there we need to make the changes in the production for multiple so we have to create a cluster and everything. 

Speaker 1  (20:46)
And then for the APIs, we have the talker continuation, where we are executing everything on the emray, or sir, they easy to ec, to instance, in the ews, AWS, those things we have those scripts. 

Speaker 2  (21:03)
You are using both ews and resolve. 

Speaker 1  (21:05)
Yes, we're talking about yeah. So for the exposing, the database, sorry, exposing the Indians, we are using the There are several other steps available in the lambda. As a step function also 

Speaker 2  (21:21)
So for E Tl you are using it. 

Speaker 1  (21:23)
Yeah, for the 

Speaker 2  (21:26)
And for executing your code, you are using database 

Speaker 1  (21:31)
Yeah, for example, please no no. Not on the adible bus on the assure itself. 

Speaker 2  (21:36)
Vajah June. So where do you are using AWS? 

Speaker 1  (21:42)
We're going to stop using adws for the APIs. I mean, where we are pushing the apricots. 

Speaker 2  (21:52)
Square, so web services you are using. So, can you compare your ws will versus S your ecosystem? If you you have an idea on because you've worked on both yeah, adf. 

Speaker 1  (22:11)
Yeah, sure. Okay, so if I talk about the Edwards PF 3 on the azo side, we have adls ok storage location, only then you have the Similar to lambda's We have okay. Once we Put the file in the adls, we have the trigger. 

Speaker 1  (22:31)
Sorry, we have the triggers in mezure, and in the ads we have the lands. And for the pipeline thing we, for the orchestration, we have this step function in ws, and in the sure we have the Step function orchestration, we don't have anything in the maybe the I can. It's the idf I can or the No, no sorry, adf, we have in the Azure. 

Speaker 1  (22:57)
We have the mwa in the adws air flow basically in AWS. Also, we have for the OpenAI. Also, we have the Azure OpenAI money, money in this country is not sure so. 

Speaker 1  (23:14)
Yeah, these are the few things common in a younger 

Speaker 2  (23:18)
To what is the difference between your shared cluster and job clusters? 

Speaker 1  (23:27)
A shared cluster and the job cluster are basically the interactive clusters where we can cover them job cluster. Basically where we run out of workflows, a workforce in the sense we can create the workflows like we can create the task, we can create a team. Organised the flow there in the database line Sequentially of parliamentary, let's say, if I if let's say if I have for idd one services export service, which I want to send a data to the one of the Delta table, so that one, we can run that notebook so behind the scene. 

Speaker 1  (24:13)
It is running the notebook only, but we have the table as a task. It will create a one task in the task. We have the notebook. 

Speaker 1  (24:21)
So that's a one task. The other task can be dependent on the the first task. Or you can be run pandemic, right? 

Speaker 1  (24:28)
So that's how we define it. And those things will run on the job job cluster. Correct job custom. 

Speaker 1  (24:34)
We can schedule those things on everything. 

Speaker 2  (24:38)
To which one is better and in which scenario 

Speaker 1  (24:42)
For the E Tl pipelines for the incremental load, adf is better and for like daily run. Scheduling thing, we can use the workforce. Because at the end, we are refreshing the data on the Delta table. 

Speaker 1  (24:59)
So for that reason, we are using the workflows, but if we are getting multiple files on the idol side. 

Speaker 2  (25:06)
I'm digital confused, so we were talking about the share clusters and job clusters. 

Speaker 1  (25:12)
The stop stops already for the workforce. And the shared cluster, we can Where we can I mean, I'm just guessing whether it's it can be used for the multiple work spaces or Multiple applications I have not used that maybe I've used that. At I am not able to recollect. 

Speaker 2  (25:35)
Thank you. Your baby on the right track. But yeah. 

Speaker 2  (25:38)
That's fine. So you have some exposure on doctors, humanities. 

Speaker 1  (25:46)
Yeah, doctor. 

Speaker 2  (25:48)
CIC D Pi. 

Speaker 1  (25:49)
Yes, Jack can serve yes. 

Speaker 2  (25:52)
You have used a Jenkins, so you created a jenkin pipeline or using support to do that. 

Speaker 1  (26:00)
Yeah, we're going to exposing the stages in the jungle. It was already there, but I have tuned some of these stages. 

Speaker 2  (26:10)
Tuke. So how we can enable some plug in Jenkins. 

Speaker 1  (26:20)
Plug in in the sense 

Speaker 2  (26:28)
Plugging means evil if we need some new functionality, which is there in jenkies, but is not unable right now. So how we can enable that 

Speaker 1  (26:40)
The thing I'm not about on that. She basically were the version of fear. Actually, what time should I sir? 

Speaker 2  (26:50)
Is how do you deploy your models using? Dockers and communities. Yeah, problems and communities. 

Speaker 1  (26:56)
Yeah, and that we have to specify everything on the Docker. So whatever the images that we need, the run command. So that's why we are going to execute on the locker container. 

Speaker 1  (27:06)
Everything that patient will be abusing talker. Compose comments those things will be updated. Then we can. 

Speaker 1  (27:15)
I mean that gives the advice? 

Speaker 2  (27:20)
So have you ever encounter any vulnerabilities? Any other images? 

Speaker 1  (27:28)
Not sure, but we are using the snorer. Sooner cube for the vulnerability in the court, not in the documents. 

Speaker 2  (27:35)
Not in the packages, so you are not scanning your packages. 

Speaker 1  (27:41)
I'm not sure about we will be doing it, but I'm not sure. 

Speaker 2  (27:47)
Infra team is handling that 

Speaker 1  (27:49)
Kya navish, ya andesh agreed. 

Speaker 2  (27:56)
So so what I understood like you are involved in deployment or production deployment, but not in that extent. 

Speaker 1  (28:05)
Right? Yeah, not in that extra income. Assam fixed some enhancement, I can do not majorly focus on the 

Speaker 2  (28:20)
So, how do you integrate machine learning models into spark pipelines? 

Speaker 1  (28:29)
How do I add the machine learning model? 

Speaker 2  (28:34)
Machine learning models, park pipelines. 

Speaker 1  (28:39)
Ok, uh, I'll greet the I've been using a note to only weekend. Right, I mean what they use this, sir. 

Speaker 2  (28:48)
So okay, leave it so for air flow, so you are doing it using it for scheduling, right? 

Speaker 1  (28:55)
Long time back ever using it, but right now, we are the idiot. 

Speaker 2  (29:00)
No, you're using. 

Speaker 1  (29:02)
Now we're going to have using the ADF pipeline agent. 

Speaker 2  (29:05)
Are the NDA pipeline you are using as a scheduler? 

Speaker 1  (29:09)
Yes, as I scheduled. Some jokes are scheduled in the database also. But majorly, the we are using the triggers for the schedule. 

Speaker 2  (29:27)
What are the different type of triggers in India? 

Speaker 1  (29:30)
Yeah, that different type is one of the file based trigger. Another one is the you can schedule the time using a time based schedule. Block. 

Speaker 1  (29:47)
Block triggers webinated specify the blocked volume. The path that need 

Speaker 2  (29:54)
That's a even trigger. 

Speaker 1  (29:56)
Sorry, that's a that's even 

Speaker 2  (30:05)
Alright. And thank you worked on the database workflows just like for adf, you are using forest schedules, so you also work on the database workflows. 

Speaker 1  (30:19)
Yes, I 

Speaker 2  (30:21)
So which one you feel is better? 

Speaker 1  (30:25)
Majorly, we're working on the ADF thing that I think, because from the ADF we are some of the job, we are triggering from the ADF to the database to the Web, I don't realise exactly web monitor something so the clinical 

Speaker 2  (30:48)
So when you use a adf or scheduling through adf, so are you using Python, God. Or you are using your pipe this notebook notebook. So which one you 

Speaker 1  (31:07)
Notebook extensively using the notebook only Yesterday. 

Speaker 2  (31:17)
So how you so let's say you are just scheduling some job, right? And what packages is required to run your notebook? So how you? 

Speaker 2  (31:30)
How you define that. How you add that then? Yeah, this is the some specific package that I need to install with while running my job. 

Speaker 1  (31:46)
Packages, we're going to have Again? 

Speaker 2  (31:55)
That your notebook or your python would require right? Yes, so how you define that, or how clear you add that? 

Speaker 1  (32:07)
In the notebook itself, using the paper command If we require some ok Let's I don't remember actually. We already have the everything installed. the.com and you have the library heavy at the end of Maybe at the other computer side, we are 

Speaker 2  (32:34)
You are you are creating a image right? Yeah, so how look how you are calling your image from ads? 

Speaker 1  (32:42)
No, no, that's a great thing. Sorry, tattoo, submit thin. I'm just thinking where they have different all the library. 

Speaker 1  (32:50)
Maybe at a compute side, they have data time, not sure crush. That's yeah, it executing my name. I'd never thought about it. 

Speaker 2  (33:04)
So because when you try to heavy schedule from adf, when you are calling any notebook right deficit and also you need to provide some cluster right on which you need to run that right so packages, what packages are you trying to use so you can't use? I think talker directly through adf. 

Speaker 1  (33:24)
I think we are using a GT facts awesome repository. There will be calling. 

Speaker 2  (33:38)
Alright. Great. Suresh, do you want to ask something? 

Speaker 3  (33:54)
So, have you ever faced performance issues? 

Speaker 1  (33:58)
Yeah, most of the time we face the conversation while the job is Tak. 

Speaker 3  (34:02)
The major problem he faced on. What's the resolution? 

Speaker 1  (34:06)
Okay, majorly, the job is taking long time to run, so we need to check whether it's a cluster issue or a data issue from the cluster side. We check. We increase the event, not increase. 

Speaker 1  (34:17)
We check the auto auto scaling. Even if we have scale, the clusters. Why's not perform so those tuning? 

Speaker 1  (34:25)
We usually do with increasing their memory or something. On the data side, which we check, I mean what type of code we have written like is there any students coming up in the weekend? See in the UI Sparky, for those things we generally check apart from that, we check the polling standards. 

Speaker 3  (34:50)
Tell me not generic. So what is the real problem you faced in your applications? 

Speaker 1  (34:58)
The real problem that we have faced is Ok, so we were using that distinct keyword every time okay in the pipeline so that is causing a lot of because we have a huge data that is causing a lot of latency or notified it is consuming lot of Time to execute the process. Okay? So we define that. 

Speaker 1  (35:25)
Also, we've seen in multiple duplicates, data that is coming up. So the one challenge that we have faced is that we have. Not clear to the performance issue, but we are getting the duplicate data in the in the in the notebook in the world so that I have resolved resolved recently. 

Speaker 1  (35:47)
So those things I have done I mean, do I want to do I talk about that or Are you looking for something else? 

Speaker 3  (36:03)
I have built data like In your project. 

Speaker 1  (36:09)
How do I meet Delta lay so we are? I mean, we are 

Speaker 3  (36:14)
By streaming applications right Kafka use right kavka. 

Speaker 1  (36:19)
Dear. 

Speaker 3  (36:23)
So if the application is fail in between, how do you make sure that the data is copied or stored? In our target. 

Speaker 1  (36:35)
Okay, let's say if we are reading from the adls. And let's say the data is not Copy properly ok into the saver layers. 

Speaker 3  (36:45)
So for European, what is what is the source in your 

Speaker 1  (36:50)
Source is high. Sources of. 

Speaker 3  (36:55)
Sources, ideal list ok where you would copying the data. 

Speaker 1  (37:02)
From from gdls to the notebooks are sorry to the data bricks. We are talking about. 

Speaker 3  (37:09)
Data breaks iconic story data, right? So where you are storing? 

Speaker 1  (37:15)
The data, the Delta table from inside the digital space to 

Speaker 3  (37:18)
So where is the data type? What is your cloud provider? Azure. 

Speaker 3  (37:24)
Azul, okay, so I mean Delta very well. What kind of service you are using for storing that data. 

Speaker 1  (37:35)
I mean, we're just writing the command. 

Speaker 3  (37:37)
Service or using? 

Speaker 1  (37:39)
EDF pipelines, we are using 

Speaker 3  (37:42)
You are using admirable. But pipeline is just crossing the data, right? You're not storing the data in a dm pipeline somewhere you are storing it. 

Speaker 1  (37:49)
Right? So we have the notebook defined in the pipeline. Okay, so that is those who are getting executed in the notebook. 

Speaker 1  (37:56)
Itself, we have writing the data to the data game. Do the next sense 

Speaker 3  (38:07)
The databases are ideal or pipelines are just the jobs, right? You are air somewhere you need to pass the data where you are persisting. 

Speaker 1  (38:18)
See. We are getting the data in the adls. Ok, a DLS then that's a file based data. 

Speaker 1  (38:25)
They will trigger our jobs job in the sense is the pipeline jobs inside the jobs via the data bricks notebooks. Ok, so there are a couple of notebooks that are running so 1 for 1 of the notebooks we are storing some data into the Delta table. Ok. 

Speaker 1  (38:40)
So on the other notebook, we are storing the network table at the end we are storing it to the golden layer. I'm talking about the Silver and the golden layer. Do you want? 

Speaker 1  (38:50)
I mean, is it fine? Or may I missing? I'm missing something. 

Speaker 3  (38:54)
Where is that Kafka here? 

Speaker 1  (38:58)
Scarfi is a separate player where we're getting the data from the carka to the a DL. 

Speaker 3  (39:05)
Tell me the application where you worked that steamy. 

Speaker 1  (39:10)
Yeah, I mean. 

Speaker 3  (39:11)
Vocab, what is your target? How you are using that cup file between 

Speaker 1  (39:17)
Ok, so we have a calf calm, then we have a debassium, then we have this S trees, ok, we are the Reed canonical, and they're ready economically ordihazal der sari, and then these are the night learning jobs that are to join. So That we have the kafar connector also, right, so that is taking care of incrementing the data to all these refined data, to the S3, that's the 11 part of the job the other way is through the Kafka. Um, we're getting the jobs. 

Speaker 1  (39:56)
The files in the a DLS ad LS to ADF ADF notebook. Zodiac, we're doing 

Speaker 3  (40:05)
So in your scenario, so if the job is fail in between so how do you make sure that data is not having not duplicated? And also, how do you ensure that COVID into target 

Speaker 1  (40:20)
Yeah, so basically we are getting the incremental data, right? So we know what are the maximum time stem that we have received the data? And at the end, we are overwriting that data, if because earlier we don't have that data. 

Speaker 1  (40:33)
Right? So again and again, if we are overwriting it. It overwriting on the maximum timestamp data right? 

Speaker 1  (40:41)
Even if it is fail, it will go to override the new data only. Answer questions. 

Speaker 3  (40:51)
Did you did you use even her? 

Speaker 1  (40:56)
Event hub in place of car yeah, yesterday's another floor which is using that event. And then with a smooth flake snow pipe is there that way? I've confirmed that not in this application but on the other application I did. 

Speaker 1  (41:19)
What I know about work. 

Speaker 3  (41:22)
Okay. What format the message? Will be stored in event up. 

Speaker 3  (41:32)
What is the best format? 

Speaker 1  (41:35)
The formatwale is the party 5 million. 

Speaker 3  (41:41)
Information, the message you are sending through. Iran. 

Speaker 1  (41:45)
No, no, no, just the Gs and forward we're using for the messages and for storing the data we are using the in the database where using the Pakistani. It's a by default, busy. 

Speaker 3  (42:02)
I can't do banry. 

Speaker 1  (42:06)
I'm not sure why not paying because my application we are using JN omega. Not sure about 

Speaker 3  (42:16)
Is it required to convert Jason to bioner? While writing up, you can directly write into Jason format on message. 

Speaker 1  (42:24)
I have not worked with a winery or more. 

Speaker 3  (42:34)
Ok? And 

Speaker 2  (42:38)
Olive India. I think lucky want to ask those 

Speaker 1  (42:42)
Yeah, can you tell me about the project and role that you are hiding? 

Speaker 2  (42:49)
Roll is for AIM L engineer. And project right now, I too, don't have much information on that. But yeah, this is for AI ML engineer where you need to maybe work majorly on deploying model through production right? 

Speaker 2  (43:08)
Some performance enhancements, right? And there are a lot of other things like Vulnerabilities fixed right and whatever we discussed with you, I think everywhere, whatever you work for told that yeah, every everything is going to be used in that room. And Yeah, these are the major things that we are looking for this role. 

Speaker 2  (43:38)
This is basically for the engineered AIM L English, okay. 

Speaker 1  (43:43)
Okay, understand. Yeah 

Speaker 2  (43:49)
So, alright? Yeah, thanks for your time. 

Speaker 1  (43:51)
Yeah, thanks for doing. Thank you. 

Speaker 2  (43:53)
Yeah, thanks. Suresh thank you here. Bye. 
