p_anjitha198@optum.com

Speaker 1  (00:02)
Just tell me something about like yourself like where you are currently and You know how's going? What are the key things you handle right now? Or the electrons and what kind of projects do you work on it? 

Speaker 2  (00:16)
Yes, sure so myself a prakhai I around 14 years of experience walking with the emphasis right now from last 3 and a 1 years before that, I was working with August tenley, and for close to 9 years, and before that I was working with NIT, same on the backing profile. Thank you too much. And I work with the genact, also with seves account. 

Speaker 2  (00:44)
But for Indian, I am working with the education domain which is I read So on that one, I'm working with data breaks working with t I worked on the unpromised sides also worked with cloud and everything Kafka streaming Kafka. And then we switched to the database side on the data which side I work with t Mostly the DL pipeline, the notebooks we have created right and idiot pipeline assured data measure pipeline. Also, we are using it here in application. 

Speaker 2  (01:21)
Apart from that, I have a good exposure to the snowflix side as well. Working with a spark. Bixby majorly, with python, I have a good experience on the python and is Kala as well. 

Speaker 2  (01:36)
Also, I'm working as a mil engineer here working look at a rap pipeline we have created. 

Speaker 1  (01:44)
When did he started to work? Thank you for measure me like like we kind of measure you in data engineering side, we do have exposure to data science. But we right now have major major work, you know, kind of a data engineering side and going moving for like in every every other company. 

Speaker 1  (02:03)
Right. So when did you started to contribute in ML side? That's what I have. 

Speaker 2  (02:10)
Yeah 

Speaker 1  (02:10)
Everyone has learned that strength, but not everyone has got that part of water. 

Speaker 2  (02:16)
Yeah, actually, when I was working with Mogan standard, also here as well. So I started work exploring the rat side. So for one of the clients we have done, we've created the pipeline for them for the rack. 

Speaker 1  (02:30)
Like me a visit tomorrow. Deployment kind of stuff we do as a data engineer for RAG, or is it like from idea stage for where like, you know, or data science work is completely different than I intelligent. So that's what So you have we have contributed, you understand how to work on right side, from genetic engineering side, right? 

Speaker 1  (02:53)
There is that, from 

Speaker 2  (02:53)
The British engineering side I know because we have adf pipelines built-in lt pipeline scheduled everything we have done that. Also, these pipeline for the chunking and beddings. Okay? 

Speaker 2  (03:04)
Vector said because basically merely we are using the database only so I've got exposure to walk on those side as well with the yummy floor also okay all these things I know and worked on that, but majorly my focused memorial into the our data engineering side okay with us parking. 

Speaker 1  (03:24)
Because you're seeing kind of confused, right? Mostly all around L and M. Ragi. 

Speaker 2  (03:32)
Important post. 

Speaker 1  (03:34)
That's right, that's an exposure. Okay, got an God to understand you. Thank you so much, and you have heard into ajushen and need a loose side. 

Speaker 1  (03:43)
Both That's going to go. Thank you for watching that. And so I will be assessing on technical side of Di think the hiring manager for this pulsion is different, and he would be coming in after me. 

Speaker 1  (04:01)
I am kind of working in autumn from over like far 5 year, almost 6 years now and been to it formatic, art, deloyed, TCS R and being different. Was it started in Hong Kong ended up in Bangalore? So I'll just assist you for data. 

Speaker 1  (04:28)
Science Yeah, so in byathon we'll start with python, a SM Bye, we have price one with that. So we'll start with python first two weeks, so I've been sent you a small, a list in python, right chat 20. So yeah, so this is our list, for example, and it is having a times tank on around it. 

Speaker 1  (04:58)
Okay? Okay. So So there is a problems right? 

Speaker 1  (05:05)
For example, when we make IP call together at a right so there are thousands of API call we do right so kind of four example I've taken a time stem of this and for error there is there could be a time stem after B.P hit a certain window. Right? For example, the rate limit is 600 right. 

Speaker 1  (05:23)
We might hit the Out of you know, context and we hit the divorce, right? So we have locked his for example, I want you to plot this to understand. For every minute, for every window minute, how would you plot it on a chart? 

Speaker 1  (05:43)
Using a metal layer or seawarn, how would you identify what will be your approach for this? This is a list of time? For example, we can continue in India and just to be comfortably happy. 

Speaker 1  (05:59)
So gather that I am Gogi her a minute every in 1 second is a call for life. You know, 3 times a call, there is a call for like, you know. So on, it continues for 10 minutes. 

Speaker 1  (06:13)
And we get this time in milli, right? For example, right? Let me edit this list. 

Speaker 1  (06:18)
I think it's confusing a little bit. So this is long time milli seconds. So we have this thousands and thousands of countries like this, the uppan ko windows Mein, aapko, use karke, you'll have to log in every 60 seconds Mein how many calls are going so basically I want you to 

Speaker 2  (06:46)
Thank you, everyone. 

Speaker 1  (06:48)
Windowing functionar in banking. 

Speaker 2  (06:51)
Ok. Mono function for 4:10 minutes, right? 

Speaker 1  (06:57)
Yeah, for a minute, you know, just like, in naturally, we have that dashboards right? Which keeps on coming up right now, right? Now, how would you create your own deshpute, if you have to 

Speaker 2  (07:11)
Okay? So these are the timestamps for every second for evidence. 

Speaker 1  (07:16)
For every second, so for example, if you see 5665, then 66 extension, there are 2 calls 7070, there are 2 calls. So it number of calls for that particular seconds are more right in the same way. It can go like, you know till any time is 10 in seconds. 

Speaker 2  (07:34)
Join the passport, we have the window function, right? So that we can use the window function for 

Speaker 1  (07:41)
So this is a list, so I want you to make use of this list, you know, convert to data framework. Whatever you have to do. So how would you write a code around this 

Speaker 2  (07:54)
For 10 minutes, right for 10 minutes. 

Speaker 1  (07:57)
For every minute, just like a tasual type road would be, if we don't have access to that as an Inter engineer, maybe there is some other team owning that dashboard. We might not get that dashboard, so we'll have to greet our own dashboard. How will you figure that out? 

Speaker 2  (08:14)
Okay, I mean. Will group by we will divide it by Let's say 10 minute of window. We've need right? 

Speaker 2  (08:26)
1 minute of window we need so if we divide it, let me, let me let me recall. Think it loud. We will get the If you divide it By minute. 

Speaker 2  (08:42)
Except for 1 minute, we will get the aggregated window. And that aggregated window, we can use Yeah, let's say we're dividing it by 101 minute for each of The Times 10, so let's say we're getting some same values. Let's say 67, right? 

Speaker 2  (09:02)
So if divided by 1 minute. Okay, so we have 

Speaker 1  (09:08)
What happens is so what will happen is like you will have output of every second separately. I want you to do is what I want you to do is and that particular second. You know how many calls happened in last 1 minute then in next second, how many calls happened in last one? 

Speaker 1  (09:27)
So it's going to be a rolling window and giving a so there is a python operator called as a rolling rolling user. 

Speaker 2  (09:36)
Ok yeah, we can use the rolling window. Also, I've been rolling. Okay for so let's say, if my data frame is having these values. 

Speaker 2  (09:53)
And then if we're dividing this by Always thank you. By 60 didn't see for each of the values. So for dividing, let's say, I'll get one okay for this one2. 

Speaker 2  (10:13)
Sorry. What was your ask here not going to do for 1 minute? Meet to see how many calls we have received right home last week. 

Speaker 2  (10:21)
Okay, so we need for the last 10 minutes, right last 10 minutes. Yeah, we can find it. 

Speaker 1  (10:30)
Can I show you the converts this to a data frame? Let's convert to a pandas, data frame. 

Speaker 2  (10:36)
Yeah, can I share my screen? 

Speaker 1  (10:39)
Yeah, I rush are good. Let's convert this list to a data frame first. 

Speaker 2  (10:54)
Okay. Then we'll book the list here. This is the list I will be getting Let's say this is the list. 

Speaker 2  (11:10)
Right? And once you'll get the data frame, or maybe we can convert to 2 pounds. I'm an either way, would you fine now? 

Speaker 2  (11:23)
Whatever thinking is if we divide each number by 60 because we need a window of 1 minute show. Okay, drive 69, so it will give me some number which is maybe 3 or 4. Now I'll Ok, you said the rolling windows because you want to have the from last 10 minutes. 

Speaker 2  (11:50)
I'm just thinking 2 ways. First way is, let's say, if we get the number as 4 okay, 1234. So I'll do the number. 

Speaker 2  (11:59)
I will have to receive all the values less than 10 minutes. Because these are 1 minute. 

Speaker 1  (12:07)
In this approach, for example, say at 62 seconds. You will be considering all the you know, partitions having one, so it will take the old time step also. 

Speaker 2  (12:18)
Okay, the previous one also. 

Speaker 1  (12:21)
It will take. We just want in last 60 seconds. 

Speaker 2  (12:25)
Yeah, okay. Last week, last week, 60 seconds. Sorry, I have just 

Speaker 1  (12:33)
Anyway, anyway. Look at can you convert this to our data frame using pandas? 

Speaker 2  (12:39)
About finders yeah, this is 

Speaker 1  (12:41)
Instead of using 5 year, how would you convert a list? No, not using 2 punders that's a data engineering. Just using fundle, how would you use APD say import pandas as pd, and then say pd dot what Creativity dot et dot 

Speaker 2  (13:00)
Mumbai mumbai.com. 

Speaker 1  (13:11)
Okay, send it across to me. 

Speaker 2  (13:16)
Ok, so this will be giving me the list. 

Speaker 1  (13:23)
You have so many things written in your regime for data science side, right? That's where it is going to cause a confusion. Because I'm just telling you that data science is banana samphai, you know, conversion up down right and just just think of it if you are not able to convert to a data frame, a list to a data frame. 

Speaker 1  (13:48)
How would you you know, anticipate a science of visions that I understand but even with vice park, we kind of scale using price? What are the basic data science code of learn, for example, like machine learning is in Pand python? Okay, cool, cool, that's okay, okay. 

Speaker 1  (14:18)
Ah, what how do you write an constructor in python? How would you initial constructor in python? 

Speaker 2  (14:28)
Ok. Severe classes. Send unpanny parameter few contacts number 

Speaker 1  (14:48)
Okay. 

Speaker 2  (14:56)
Get this baby. 

Speaker 1  (14:59)
And how would you initialise the values within it? Let's say I want to have a class which say 2 hours 2 which takes, you know, initialises 2 venues. 

Speaker 1  (15:20)
How would you declare it? 

Speaker 2  (15:24)
How would I declare it? Yeah. 

Speaker 1  (15:28)
Do you know what_underscore in it? 

Speaker 2  (15:33)
Ok me, yeah. Underscoming for me also 

Speaker 1  (15:42)
So how do you know how to initiise within in it? 

Speaker 2  (15:51)
Ok yeah, I mean Something like that, we will do. Ok. Disable. 

Speaker 1  (16:08)
Ok. Wow, yes, so I'll do okay. Okay, yeah, so you'd kind of take theself, and then you define and then you initialise the values. 

Speaker 1  (16:21)
Okay, okay. Annie sended across to me on the chat for both all 3 thousands 

Speaker 1  (16:43)
So how do you send emails in your say price park jobs? How do you send emails across? 

Speaker 2  (16:50)
Close javisatta de alerts in database. Night song that way we do it. I mean, we set the threshold okay of the variable or anything. 

Speaker 2  (17:01)
You can set it there. 

Speaker 1  (17:06)
Okay? And then which appeared in python, or in python, do you used to? How do you send like when there's the code? 

Speaker 1  (17:13)
How does that code look like when you send an email across 

Speaker 2  (17:17)
Yesterday's ACT P email we have. I don't remember the exactly 

Speaker 1  (17:22)
Fast text, that's so 

Speaker 2  (17:23)
Send an email to send body used to at long time backwards. That's a script. We usually use for notification services. 

Speaker 1  (17:34)
Ok yeah, Tod, send sending me or maybe, have you used? Do you know how do you configure male male services in Azure? 

Speaker 2  (17:44)
Mail services I didn't do that, but I know about the data breaks now. 

Speaker 1  (17:52)
Ok. Okay, let's go into data data website. So what are the different kind of computes which are available in databases? 

Speaker 2  (18:08)
Ok, so we have 2XX ok, small, large medium. So these are the computers we have 

Speaker 1  (18:20)
If you have to optimise to a say, a low cost cluster in database, what kind of compute would you use? 

Speaker 2  (18:27)
Yeah, I mean, we have 2 type of clusters, job cluster and the interactive cluster. So for scheduling the job, we can use a job cluster, which will take less computes. We start with, the less compute. 

Speaker 2  (18:37)
Uh, we can auto scale that also with minimum maximum that we can do. And if you want to increase the performance, we can go for the photo on everything. Well, these things we can do. 

Speaker 2  (18:50)
But we started with 

Speaker 1  (18:51)
Photon profile. 

Speaker 2  (18:52)
Photo is a story to pull up the pulled in the engine which is used by the tongue. In the park, basically projects boost the performance of the uh of the cluster for executing the query. 

Speaker 1  (19:08)
Okay, so how is it different from the old trunkstran? You know We we are having tons of since the beginning of supervised because you and me, both are experienced guys. So we have you might have used spark one dot X6 also at some point right now we have 3.2. 

Speaker 1  (19:25)
So how is the project tension, you know, changed in database and how photon gives an additional advantage? 

Speaker 2  (19:33)
Hey read it or read about it. How the photos? It's just an option that we need to enable in the database. 

Speaker 2  (19:44)
Sorry, I'm not able to recall it. I read it about that. 

Speaker 1  (19:50)
What does the changes in sorry, new advantages in spark? You know, 3 dot X versus spark 2 dot X. 

Speaker 2  (20:00)
There are several changes like a qi was worth hard to manage AQU that was the first thing. What does that mean is because even if we turn on the aqi, we do not. We cannot have the proper performance of these tuna in the data that also cannot be solved. 

Speaker 2  (20:19)
So for that, also, we are going to do parallel tuning of with some adding some parameters, there parameters in the sense like skinness, joint true Okay, broadcast also sometimes doesn't work. Sometimes. The analysis of the table is not even we have specified. 

Speaker 2  (20:37)
We have to refresh the table sometimes for getting the better analytics of statistics of the table. I have done the performance during so I can talk about that how I tune some of the jobs. Okay, auto broadcast join eczember of executed. 

Speaker 2  (20:55)
Those things were hard to because it was hit and dry majorly. That is partly comes up with major performance. 

Speaker 1  (21:06)
So in Delta tables, right? How do we optimise the Delta tables? 

Speaker 2  (21:11)
How do we optimise the Delta table? 

Speaker 1  (21:13)
Common optimisation techniques we have for data stolen data type. 

Speaker 2  (21:20)
For Delhi table itself, it's using the compressions. Okay, parking files inside it. We can optimise. 

Speaker 2  (21:28)
We have the optimise keyword there. We can vacuum that also, I've been removing the old files because that also give a huge jump on the on the performance. If we are trunkating or removing the older files within a vacuum commands, optimise or optimise we have 

Speaker 2  (22:05)
Adasra tantric question or You are asking something else, hello. Hello? 

Speaker 2  (22:57)
Hello? 

Speaker 2  (23:28)
Hello, can you hear me? 

Speaker 2  (23:44)
Hello? Hello? 

Speaker 1  (24:08)
Hello? 

Speaker 2  (24:13)
I'm sorry. Those are not issued from myself. I'm so sorry. 

Speaker 1  (24:19)
So I have been all the time. Ok, sorry for that. Yes, whatever was asking like, I think, in expertise in bail data website. 

Speaker 1  (24:30)
So how do you optimise a data intellect tables in The normal optimism. 

Speaker 2  (24:37)
Yes, I told you right. So it already have the compression, okay, snapping compression it use parki file, it use which is a column format. Show that also storage and the retrieval is high. 

Speaker 2  (24:51)
Apart from that, we can Set the retention time also. Ok, retention time means we can. It will automatically cleanup the older file and if we want to do it explicitly, we can use a vacuum commands. 

Speaker 2  (25:06)
Okay, we can optimise. We can use optimise keyword. We can use the we can create the table in such a way that we can create the clusters. 

Speaker 2  (25:16)
Also, we can do the liquor cluster, so all these way, we can optimise the Delta tables. 

Speaker 1  (25:25)
Okay. Yeah, at ships. Good to be able, how are you using database in your current projects? 

Speaker 1  (25:35)
How do you design your applications? How do you act the application sort of toughest situation you have seen in your project and have you solved it? 

Speaker 2  (25:44)
Yeah, actually, we are creating the pipelines pipeline. We are used in the AD of pipeline. Also, we are using the D lts workflows, so the challenge that we faces sometimes because some jobs are file based and some are reading the data from the S ts or some other location ideals or radls location. 

Speaker 2  (26:04)
So what challenges that you face is. Sometimes the triggers does not work okay on. The file base sometime the files arrive late. 

Speaker 2  (26:11)
Okay, so we have to make sure the class. The running job window should be appropriate to run the next job. Okay. 

Speaker 2  (26:19)
So that challenges we usually face, because it will lead to the job failure. Also, we need to restrigger the jobs we need to monitor it thoroughly. These are the challenges we usually face in day-to-day work. 

Speaker 2  (26:37)
Apart from that. So this is basically the workflow, right? So starting with the adf pipeline and triggered the notebooks in the notebook we have the transformation logic. 

Speaker 2  (26:47)
Then, again, in the migration side, we have these wrong. We are using the multi operature here. So in the bronze layer. 

Speaker 2  (26:56)
Sometimes we see the duplicate data in the silver layer. So we need to make sure that it should not be duplicate, because we are getting the implemental trait daily. So all these challenges we usually face even day-to-day life. 

Speaker 1  (27:11)
Okay. For example, there is a table. Okay, which does not have a say. 

Speaker 1  (27:16)
It has the same, for example, a timestamp fellow. So how do you identify a duplicate data? 

Speaker 2  (27:21)
It doesn't happen. 

Speaker 1  (27:23)
How to ensure that? 

Speaker 2  (27:24)
Ok. Diwali, if it doesn't every time stem, then it will be hard to track because usually check the maximum time stem filter and from there it will pick the next incremental data. Safeguard, if we don't have it, we have to Ask the business team to provide some other tables. 

Speaker 2  (27:43)
Maybe the ideas if we can have we can store that ID what are the latest ID we have received? 

Speaker 1  (27:51)
From foreign if you have, if you have sever million records, okay, and you have say our primary key there, okay or a composite key there. So how do you identify an incremental difference? Yesterday. 

Speaker 2  (28:05)
Please, yeah, because we have the if the ids are in primary key. They already sorted, so we can keep the latest ID. I'm from that idea. 

Speaker 2  (28:14)
We can select the maximum records from that particular idea. Let's say. Till now, we've received 10 ids in the next call, it will get the more than 10 records. 

Speaker 2  (28:27)
Okay, because we already have that. We already have that ID is equal to 10 already there in the silver table, so from that table, the maximum ID will retrieve and query that 

Speaker 1  (28:47)
If you have The Times the next time stand then what you would do. 

Speaker 2  (28:51)
Same same thing. I'll do while check the maximum time stand and the primary key associated with it. Then, I'll receive the data. 

Speaker 2  (28:59)
That is 

Speaker 1  (29:04)
Do you have experience calling LLM Pi is like any kind of issues you have faced like tryout issues. Have we faced time out issues? 

Speaker 2  (29:12)
Yeah, we've faced a lot of challenges with the LLM because there was only 1AP. I and the multiplier teams over using it. So it'll be creating a bottle nap, and it was also creating the tokenization issue. 

Speaker 2  (29:27)
Because we are creating, we are using money tokens. So what we did is we have created ex. We have used the executive framework. 

Speaker 2  (29:35)
Sorry. 

Speaker 1  (29:42)
Yeah, yeah, I can hear you. 

Speaker 2  (29:43)
Ok, so we have implemented the executive framework there to paralyse the multiple AI calls. Everything also there is a feature in the data breaks for the end points where we can configure the fallback methods so let's say one model is getting all the traffic we can ask. So we can set up the fallback method to the older version of the model. 

Speaker 2  (30:08)
Yeah, so that we have done that. Yeah, we have worked with the ray. But they have several problems. 

Speaker 2  (30:21)
So we switch to the executive, a CIO simple library executive fund. 

Speaker 1  (30:30)
Do you I think have you worked in Java like any year initial days like when you started? 

Speaker 2  (30:34)
Yeah, I have explained exposure to this services. 

Speaker 1  (30:40)
Like, do you think? Do you know what's the difference between a multi threading and a multi processing system? 

Speaker 2  (30:46)
Yeah, multi. Thriving is basically the tasks are running on the simple course, okay, so let's say, if we have 4 course, 4 thread will be there. And they will be processing those tasks, but in the multilateral Multiprocessing, we have one application which is doing all the task. 

Speaker 2  (31:10)
Okay, without any things. 

Speaker 1  (31:17)
Do you remember the sentence for how do you implement a threading in python? 

Speaker 2  (31:24)
Um yeah, I mean, AC guy awaited. Ok, so we have to create the threads in AC. Gaayo with fixed thread, pools say they're going to specify the threat pool numbers, everything and then we can start the thread and we have to pass the task there. 

Speaker 2  (31:45)
I'm going to wait a wait. Termination method, we have to use so all those things we need to use. 

Speaker 1  (31:58)
Or in Aju wattol grander things. Do you use like near day to date like? Do you use A Area of and what all what are the all the things he used to use? 

Speaker 1  (32:10)
Have you used event ups? 

Speaker 2  (32:12)
Sorry, come again. 

Speaker 1  (32:14)
If he went ups, ajure, he went ups. 

Speaker 2  (32:17)
Eventually went away. 

Speaker 1  (32:19)
Event hubs. 

Speaker 2  (32:20)
Event obviously yes, I have used the same thing. Event? 

Speaker 1  (32:26)
Let me use it again. 

Speaker 2  (32:28)
So let's see if the file so we are we have the trigger based system right in the adf. So let's say if one file is arriving at what location we have to set up the event in the event. We have to pass a subscription resource all the details there. 

Speaker 2  (32:44)
We have to specify the what kind of blog we're storing. It's output, create delete or anything blog. Also, we need to give the permission to all these blogs blogs. 

Speaker 2  (32:55)
So these things kind of setups we usually do because that will trigger the let me treat the trigger event for our pipeline which is already there in the evening. 

Speaker 1  (33:08)
Hindi is causing as well. 

Speaker 2  (33:11)
Now I've noticed the government. It's a separate. So apart from 

Speaker 1  (33:15)
The year confused so I went up with a car for solution in a Europe. That's you're talking about something else. I think so. 

Speaker 1  (33:24)
How do you implement streaming in Raju's event up here? That's a different thing. Already sorry. 

Speaker 1  (33:32)
Do you know about how do you configure dental dentonic tables? How do you restrict a different team and how do you share the data using your data leak? 

Speaker 2  (33:42)
So we have the Delta share option. Also, we can create the multiple web work workspaces. We have better store. 

Speaker 2  (33:50)
Also, we have unity catalogue. Basically, so in the unit atlope, we have to define the cluster instances, then on that log. Sorry, you was your breaking. 

Speaker 1  (34:03)
Can you turn off your video? Your internet is stunning. You can turn off the videos of maybe the quality will improve yeah, sure. 

Speaker 1  (34:13)
I think it is just a spring. How do you configure the unity care plugging? 

Speaker 2  (34:19)
Unity catalogates like we have. We have to create the workspaces there multiple workspaces with each specific to the basically the accounts. We will say like Dev account product account and the Q account those were the instances then in those instances, we'll create the this workspaces. 

Speaker 2  (34:41)
In the workspace, we will specify the Meta stores there because Meta stores are associated with the storage location. And those things will be configured. So let's say, and then we have to create the catalogue inside the catalogue. 

Speaker 2  (34:56)
We have to create the schemas, and then inside the scheme, we will add the table. So for all these workspaces, we need to create separate catalogues and everything and then if we want to use the one table of the def, ah, and if I want to use the one table from the pot to the definition. 

Speaker 1  (35:24)
Ok. Do you like heavy used data vections before GitHub or Jenkins and GitHub actions or Jenkins. Do you have exposure to gatubactions? 

Speaker 2  (35:39)
Are you talking about the gate of workflows or So different thing. 

Speaker 1  (35:45)
Yeah, kind of get up workflows, red, you see, a get up actions or not. And the builds the projects right? 

Speaker 2  (35:51)
We have used that for one of the K use case. But maybe I'll mix because majorly I'm working on the database site. The might be I will know, but I have used that all one of the users. 

Speaker 1  (36:05)
So how do you build your projects currently? 

Speaker 2  (36:09)
How do we use in the Jenkins? We builder. So once we 

Speaker 1  (36:15)
Power so, for example, your code is in gencis. And how do you do it? How do you run it? 

Speaker 2  (36:24)
My coat isn't Git up. How will I run it? 

Speaker 1  (36:29)
How will you? How are you pushing it to your venture report? 

Speaker 2  (36:36)
How will I push-up to the Azure account? 

Speaker 1  (36:39)
Yeah, how are you deploying it on your day-to-day? So, for example, you're developing it, and then how do you deploy it? How does a production deployment happens? 

Speaker 2  (36:48)
Basically, we deploy the ad of pipelines. We already have the different URL set up for the broad UN the deaf, so let's say for one pipeline. We have to export. 

Speaker 2  (37:05)
Let's say if I want to migrate from debt to crod, we have to extract the template adf template, and then we have to deploy there in the probe so manually, we are doing it right now. Doesn't it ok? 

Speaker 1  (37:21)
So where are you using Jenkins currently in your production deployment? How do you use Jenkins? 

Speaker 2  (37:29)
Jenkins, for the builders, so once we deploy the code, it will create the PH and everything. Once it reviewed, then it will go, it will trigger the Jenkins pipeline, basically. 

Speaker 1  (37:42)
RM. You can't you have breaking a breaking a lot? Unfortunately with I can't understand you much. 

Speaker 1  (37:55)
Let me ask the issue I'm having. Let me are you able to hear me clearly? 

Speaker 2  (37:59)
Yeah, I can hear. Let me switch the different network. Once you Is it fine now? 

Speaker 2  (38:14)
Is it fine now? Is it fine now? Hello. 

Speaker 2  (38:33)
Hello, hello oh, hello, hello. AI is positioned at work. It doesn't work. 

Speaker 1  (39:10)
Yeah, so whatever I just wanted to understand you know, for example, here every board in later. So how do you how do you use it? And how do you deploy to development? 

Speaker 1  (39:19)
And then how do you the testing is done? How do you move it to motivation? Yeah. 

Speaker 2  (39:27)
Yeah, so we've ever get her right. So once you require changes, it will trigger the champions job and basically test our changes test pieces. So once it's done then we have to ask for the review. 

Speaker 2  (39:43)
It approved posed once it months, we create the it deployed into the master branch, basically, and then on the production side. We have to create the release section. Everything and then we have to set the correct version of the master. 

Speaker 1  (40:01)
Still, I think there's some issue with that. If you want to watch I just want to hear 

Speaker 2  (40:16)
Is it fine now? 

Speaker 1  (40:18)
Yeah, yeah, can you 

Speaker 2  (40:19)
I think this is the schedule I switched to their network of life. Ok, so I was talking about that thing, get her right. So once we deploy changes into the GitHub, it will trigger our Jenkins shop, which usually tests our changes unit test, basically, and then once it deployed, it will be asked for the review margin. 

Speaker 2  (40:42)
Everything then we merge the changes. 

Speaker 1  (40:45)
How does it test the changes? How does it run the job you hold on cluster? 

Speaker 2  (40:51)
Yes, what I want to do. So we have to write the stages in the Jenkins file. So those file automatically trigger our test cases which are written in the test folder, total automatically run those tests that configuration we have done in the general factor. 

Speaker 1  (41:12)
Have you implemented this for the changes of this? Someone else? Someone else implemented 

Speaker 2  (41:18)
It's all already implemented, but I have wrote some of the code on that on her jumpkin stages. 

Speaker 1  (41:28)
So if you have to do a testing up or talk of file on your local computer right? So how do you do? How do you do that, right? 

Speaker 2  (41:36)
Testing in the sense we have the Docker composed on all these commands done. Will it be automatically turn on our server application? Basically, Hindi continued risk application. 

Speaker 2  (41:50)
We will we can run it in the doctor so doctor file we have right? So the doctor composed and all the commands. 

Speaker 1  (42:03)
Also, you haven't experienced a lot of carbohydrates, and I'm sure stuff and python, right? Tender on history. Also, you have some exposure, right if that is 

Speaker 2  (42:15)
Dead Bixby 

Speaker 1  (42:21)
Stuffling, okay, this is another database. Do you have anything for me? Any questions for me today? 

Speaker 2  (42:34)
You can tell me about the project and the position that you hire it here. 

Speaker 1  (42:40)
Yeah, this is so optimism product based company right? You know, right in Austin, in Noida optimum, and there are only few companies which are On its own product based company. So we have our own data. 

Speaker 1  (42:56)
So lifestyle companies, and we kind of you know, our customer centric. And so what are this project encompasses? Is it has a lot of machine learning and a lot of led GPT based or You know, Papa Azure endpoint, agent EI based projects which come comes to us from data science teams. 

Speaker 1  (43:23)
So we have to have good understanding of those as our data engineer, we have to scale those understand them and set up all the systems that are and data science. Yeah, so data science don't have experience on data engineering side at all. So the kind of Make help from take help from us, because they just cold from us. 

Speaker 1  (43:49)
In simple files and they share the code with us. Those are very small code, but the actual production is very huge. You might have to do all kind of solution from token issues and all what you are doing right? 

Speaker 1  (44:06)
And then it's an individual contributor 

Speaker 1  (44:22)
and then the project would you or the product is usually deployed then you switch to a new product and you take care of the production and production monitoring and everything on your own there is now no one else who's going to come and take care of your own projects. And you will keep on getting you projects every now and then we usually have one done in the last 5 years, so I have handled a lot of projects right now. But yeah, but that's that's all? 

Speaker 1  (44:58)
I am just so French engineing role here in us. I was a Western manager in India. But I have switched off engineering role more here, client centric, but if it's good for we get new problems every day, mostly from data. 

Speaker 1  (45:15)
Science City, we are working mostly on ldm right now and I genuinely applications correctly. So vector TV. So from your application, I think that you have exposure to AI what you are majorly into detent engineering to 

Speaker 2  (45:39)
Yes, yeah, I felt that I have the exposure. Okay because we also transitioning few things to the genuine. 

Speaker 1  (45:48)
Yeah, but your resume, but it can confuse will confuse anything. Okay? Because it has all the stuffs in tough top 5 lines. 

Speaker 1  (45:58)
Yeah, so that's where you have been interviewed by my seniors already. So I it's just a us based guy. They needed me to interview that since a community, how long would it take if we select you to join to optimum? 

Speaker 2  (46:18)
Yesterday can join early within a month. 

Speaker 1  (46:22)
Are you already your notice period 

Speaker 2  (46:24)
Jam on Mumbai notifications. 

Speaker 1  (46:27)
And okay, I'll let my seniors know. On how druppo ok, and I'll let you know okay, we'll have to discuss first within our teams because this position is highly technical and We have to gauge you on all to that. Okay definite. 

Speaker 1  (46:50)
But yeah, it seems very nice to talk to you. Thank you so much. I all I always you know. 

Speaker 1  (46:58)
Support more, because I am also succena. Only so I support people from Google communities, but yeah, let's let's hope for the best. 

Speaker 2  (47:08)
Yeah, pleasant. Thank you. Thanks a lot, yeah. 

Speaker 1  (47:10)
Yeah, take care bye. 
