venkatesh.m@srushtitechsolutions.com
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Yoga yojana is a looking for jockey. Because my company is asking me to relocate. 2 Tuppoo, which I'm not comfortable with. 

Speaker 2  (00:15)
Ok, but. A year, okay to relocate to vodrah, Gujarat. 

Speaker 1  (00:21)
Yeah, that is fine. 

Speaker 2  (00:26)
So what about Pune? 

Speaker 1  (00:29)
Pune have been there before I didn't like the I don't know. I didn't like the Whether or something that's right, I'm not competing, but I'm ok to Bangalore or Samsung city. 

Speaker 2  (00:44)
Okay, got it. So you're currently working from Noida. 

Speaker 1  (00:49)
Jaya 2. 

Speaker 2  (00:56)
So he mentioned like you are currently working in scripts, right? So how are you? Like most of the time savaiya task car research-oriented, puppy have to do supocis, you have to do subsearchy, and then you have to fund whether it works or not. 

Speaker 2  (01:11)
So how do you plan that in a sprint? 

Speaker 1  (01:16)
Ok, so within a sprintway, before that, we have A Basically we have an epic. Okay, basically, we create a diet, design documentation first, so with the initial things that is required. And then we comes up with a user stories, which used to be we can pick on the current sprint and in those stories, we have to create task. 

Speaker 1  (01:40)
Okay, so let's say want to change something. Which is, let's say we want to try some different pipelines offer other cleaning, so we can try that in the 11 sprint if it works, if it doesn't create the backlog of the same story, okay. And then we can pick that from there whenever the time needs. 

Speaker 1  (02:02)
So we create the so take it as a tag that item 

Speaker 2  (02:07)
Okay, so how do you actually figure out the ended up of a project there? 

Speaker 1  (02:14)
How do you figure out the 

Speaker 2  (02:17)
A date of a project like whether pinny get a new requirement a new project. So how do you go about? Creating WbS, and then how do you get the end of the project in that case? 

Speaker 1  (02:29)
Yes, I told you right. So initially, we when we have the epic, we will go to we do some receiving the research part, creating the documentation there, at least we can have the high level diagram design document, and then we go to the go into the lower level design. Accordingly, specifying all those things needed like what classes need to be changed. 

Speaker 1  (02:53)
And let's say, if we have a thing that needs to be changed in the current sprint, current documentation, we can do that right, basically before creating the story. We have those things ready. So we have the overview of what needs to be done in this psi. 

Speaker 2  (03:15)
Okay. So no, but that that will be Yes, so then how are you deriving the ended? Like how many months will be required in order to finish the project? 

Speaker 1  (03:25)
At least we come up with a basic things, at least if you want to make some Fine-tuning that we can take it on the other sprint or other PSI For those things, we define it. But initially, we come up with the things, the components that needs to be built those things. We first focus on and then enhancement, we take it on the other story. 

Speaker 2  (03:55)
So how do you normally like Alok task to your team members? You mentioned that you have worked effectively. It also said. 

Speaker 2  (04:02)
So what do you consider and how do you assent us to those teams? 

Speaker 1  (04:06)
Yeah, so might ask hostel create the documentation around the epic. So I work with a team itself, creating that and then once it's ready, then we know what are changes, we need to do, and we can pick any any be money from it. I need the member they can deliver. 

Speaker 2  (04:28)
The capabilities repeat. 

Speaker 1  (04:30)
Yeah, so initially, my task is to create the design documentation first high level and will low level also. So once it is ready then. So we give the I mean it goes on with the within The Strain only. 

Speaker 1  (04:46)
So everybody knows what things are getting being developed. And then if this is ready, then we can ask anyone anyone from the team to implement that. 

Speaker 2  (05:02)
Ok. So can you explain Bias-Variance, freedom 

Speaker 1  (05:15)
Buys weren't trade-off, okay? So there are two things Challenges with the model was that it is underfitting and overfitting. So if it is underfitting, then we call it as a biasiness, because it is more toward more dominating value, it is. 

Speaker 1  (05:37)
It will predict the data based on the dominating value. If it is overfitting, then it learn the data from the test and the train data. Both maybe from the feature future date. 

Speaker 1  (05:51)
Also, it has learned the data. So that's come as a part of the overfitting, where our train is trained, data is giving the good accuracy, but our test data is not So we need to find a way where we can support both biases and the variance. 

Speaker 2  (06:10)
Okay, so when will you choose between like Random forest Vs grade in boosting 

Speaker 1  (06:20)
Sorry, great and boosting. And 

Speaker 2  (06:23)
End up forest. 

Speaker 1  (06:25)
Random forest, okay? So gradient. That's that I'll be able to based on the linearity of the data. 

Speaker 1  (06:33)
So if my data is linear, or maybe it is more in the polynomial feature than in that case, I'll go with the gradient boosting from the random forest. We will pick majorly, the Data where the relationships are not not known before. In that sense, we have the thresholds, we can give other thresholds and also random forest good for the future extraction. 

Speaker 1  (07:07)
So the feature importance, basically. So in those cases I will go with the random forest. 

Speaker 2  (07:16)
Ok. So When will you decide between using a deep learning or Vs tradition level? 

Speaker 1  (07:31)
West start with the traditional learning. Only then if my mattresses are not strong enough to support my model, then I'll go for the deep learning. Basically, we there, we're adding more layers. 

Speaker 1  (07:47)
Okay, hidden layers, basically, just to tune our data and that will go consume a lot of CPU GPU's, which eventually increase the cost of the model. So that's how we have several parameters. Also checking the matrices like For the leader data, we check for the R square. 

Speaker 1  (08:09)
We check for the Rmse, emses, okay, all these matrices for the classification thing. We check for the accuracy, recall value forest score. All those feature So based on that, we decide 

Speaker 2  (08:28)
Ok. 

Speaker 2  (08:47)
Show border common causes of model drift, and how do you detect it? 

Speaker 1  (08:51)
A common causes. 

Speaker 2  (08:54)
Model drift. 

Speaker 1  (08:57)
Ok Como cause of the modern drift, ok First thing could be the features feature data. Imbalance and the feature what you call if we have lot of features in the date in the model, it will go into cause the overfitting. So other thing is the data imbalance, if 101 particle is dominating the story. 

Speaker 1  (09:22)
Okay? So that way there is a drift. In the Model electricity show the way we solve it using the regulators. 

Speaker 1  (09:34)
That way we did 

Speaker 2  (09:36)
Can you please repeat that? 

Speaker 1  (09:39)
Yeah, I mean, using the regularisation like we can use the for the linear models we can use the laser ridge, okay and their elastic modes. These way we can do that. For the nonlinear data, we can Use the Azerbaijan, sorry we can use the PC O also for the classification thing. 

Speaker 1  (10:02)
So that's how we just trimmed down the features that is important to train the data. 

Speaker 2  (10:11)
So what is actually model drift? 

Speaker 1  (10:17)
Okay, modern drift is not getting the accuracy on the model is what the model drift is. Sorry, I'm not sure up. 

Speaker 2  (10:30)
Okay. 

Speaker 2  (11:22)
So normally like, how do you handle tight deadlines? 

Speaker 1  (11:29)
Type deadline sites basically. We'll haven't we tell them of friendly? Okay, this based on the poker sessions we have right. 

Speaker 1  (11:40)
So if it is strict. Timeline. What we say is, we will going to cover this part of the story first okay, we will not take the because we need to do the development as well as the QA also. 

Speaker 1  (11:58)
So we take the small portion of the whole story and then we do, we develop that first If it is feasible. So that's where we do it. 

Speaker 2  (12:12)
Ok. What is CNN Vs Vijayan Transformers? 

Speaker 1  (12:19)
Ok, you're talking about the conversational neural network right? And the vision. Yeah 

Speaker 2  (12:25)
Convolutional. 

Speaker 1  (12:26)
Convulations workspace on the Okay, so they have the They have different layers. One is the conversation layer than they have the polling, okay, masking, and then the flattening of the data. And then they have the output layer, then the output we have to again go on with t Provide the hidden layers. 

Speaker 1  (12:51)
Basically, we can train them using the Geo R railway layer. And then we have the output in between we can augment the data. Also, if the performance is not good on the other side, which is sorry, what was at the other one? 

Speaker 2  (13:10)
Vision Transformers. 

Speaker 1  (13:13)
Sara, not worked on the vision. 

Speaker 2  (13:17)
Ok. So what is attention mechanism? 

Speaker 1  (13:26)
What is attention mechanism? So that part of the transformer and basically your these Transformers are built on the concept of self attention, which means that they have to predict the next sentences. Predict the next sentence and Yeah, so in between they have different. 

Speaker 1  (13:59)
So there's a mapping of each word, and then we have the probability store so you have the Q kV, also their matric. Also where we have to define with how one word is linked to the other and that gives you their probability score again, we have to Put them into the soft match layer. And where do we do I mean then we get the output So there lot of things are there attention forward field. 

Speaker 1  (14:34)
Okay? And Yeah, this is the thing I can record. 

Speaker 2  (14:42)
What is Fanta, versus prompting? 

Speaker 1  (14:45)
What is Fine-tuning Vs prompting? Yeah, promptly, we have. We have the role. 

Speaker 1  (14:55)
I mean, if we talk about the prompting, we can have context roles. We can have the tone format booking and the context as well. So these are the parameters that we have for defining the prompts, and we can train them also using the different roles. 

Speaker 1  (15:12)
We have, like system user, other human. These are the multiple roles we have. And if I talk about the Fine-tuning, then we can fine-tune. 

Speaker 1  (15:23)
If I talk about the rack pattern, we can fine-tune the chunks, we can find tune the embeddings. Okay, we can have different evolution parameters of the rags like the the accuracy trust. Okay, they are many. 

Speaker 1  (15:44)
I am just not able to recall it right now. These are the few parameters that we have for tuning them. Basically, we are fixing the context to sending it before to the L. 

Speaker 1  (15:54)
M. 

Speaker 2  (15:57)
Okay. A So how do you reduce salucinations in llms? 

Speaker 1  (16:06)
Yeah, using giving the context to the to the LM like. We can give the document documents which is the concept of the rank with prompts plus giving that exact documentation document and then giving the data to the L. In between, we have the embedding zone. 

Speaker 2  (16:30)
So what is accuracy? 

Speaker 1  (16:33)
Yeah, accuracy is so we have the confusion matrix where we have 2 positive, 2 negative false, negative false positive. So accuracy is the TP upon TP plus FP which is 2 positive divided by 240 + 1 positive ring. That tells us the number for the accuracy. 

Speaker 2  (16:57)
Is that a gracious reset precision good event? 

Speaker 1  (17:01)
Sorry, that is the procession so accuracy is same thing. I think If I'm not wrong. 

Speaker 2  (17:09)
Effect, it's self precision are the same. Don't have been different things. 

Speaker 1  (17:17)
When is for the Sir, I am getting that face. 

Speaker 2  (17:23)
Okay, so what is recall? 

Speaker 1  (17:24)
Yeah, recall is tpo one tp plus FM, giving the This is the formula, and that's how we calculate the recall. So our model focused on the recall value, give them importance on the recall value. Because we don't want to miss the false negative cases. 

Speaker 2  (17:54)
And what is hephone school? 

Speaker 1  (17:56)
It's a harmonic meet between the Precession and recall. 

Speaker 2  (18:06)
So what is that used to actually check? Like 

Speaker 1  (18:12)
Sorry, what it is used. 

Speaker 2  (18:15)
What is the purpose of using like FN and recall? 

Speaker 1  (18:20)
Ok. I can give you the example if we want to credit the patient having the cancer or not. So how model is giving 95% accuracy? 

Speaker 1  (18:34)
What is recall value is less so 95 means it is fitting the patient who are having the And who are having The WHO are having the cancer but 5%, it is not able to detect them. Now if I talk about the recall value, where it is saying that the Where the person has the cancer, but our model saying that the person the patient does not have the cancer. So, that matters that number If we increase it, let's say if we make it 200, that means that we are not giving the importance to the false negative cases. 

Speaker 1  (19:22)
And we are We will not be able to detect those patients for the dialysis. Because we have the large value of the recall. So we need to decrease that value recall value. 

Speaker 1  (19:38)
So that if even if our model is saying he is not is not having the cancer we can take take those patients also. Thank you. 

Speaker 2  (19:52)
Yeah, do you have any questions or question the company? I think I don't have any good questions from myself. 

Speaker 1  (19:57)
Yeah, can you tell me about the project and the company, please? 

Speaker 2  (20:02)
Yeah, so it won't be exactly a project. So Way, we are. A product biscuit company and we are into not exactly core front tech but Appear into compliance for creating a central banks and part of like regulatory tech. 

Speaker 2  (20:24)
So we have overlown products which are based around anti-money laundering and production. So we normally create solutions based on that most of the like client interaction with the front and application that's using Java applications, but there are different fruit detections that we have. We have already created, or we are creating that actually lesser AI ML like we have a check for detection that is based on that uses deep learning or check for detection. 

Speaker 2  (21:03)
And there are couple of more areas that we have planned, that is related to NLP for creating chatbots. So like I mentioned it's not for a specific project. We are into software product development. 

Speaker 2  (21:19)
So The Domain will be antibiotic and for detection, so there will be different rules based around that. 

Speaker 1  (21:29)
Okay. 

Speaker 2  (21:35)
Thank you. Yes, thank you. Thank you. 

Speaker 2  (21:38)
To s***** again, you have a good day. Thank you. 

Speaker 1  (22:58)
Ashok. How hi Bixby 
