h.tyagi@sunlife.com, rajesh.kumar.sharma@sunlife.com

Speaker 1  (00:00)
Rajesh, and I'm a part of the digital team, internal audit and life, and I have been with sunlight from last 18 more than a couple of years. And Yeah, I have. I majorly my expertise lies in advanced analytics, predominantly. 

Speaker 1  (00:24)
In order domain pharmacy, full healthcare, all of those things, what we do here is you basically support our auditors with dated data-driven decision-making in terms of the audit help them with various tools and technologies, build them assets projects and all of those things for them to be able to use it right. So that just because they are not very good in coding, right? This is where we come into picture. 

Speaker 1  (00:53)
We will assist from there. So coding solutions, so that's what I do. So Any question before you started with your introduction. 

Speaker 2  (01:08)
Yes, sure. So myself, praker, I want 14 years of experience currently working work you with emphasis. And before that I work with Mohan, standly and severes, which is a healthcare domain, and then I was associated with the NIT. 

Speaker 2  (01:27)
Also immediately, I've worked on the 

Speaker 1  (01:29)
Sorry, nip. 

Speaker 2  (01:30)
An idol technology. Ok, we just go forge now. So majorly, I worked on the banking area, then my expertise on the healthcare domain. 

Speaker 2  (01:42)
And currently I'm working with the education domain which is an activity used by the teacher student for their diagnostic tests. And we accumulate all the data. Using the aiml, we have the chat chat boots. 

Speaker 2  (02:03)
We have created in the data which itself. So Yes, sir, and we have the E Tl jobs running in with the Azure radio pipelines we've created We've created the multiple architecture And land chain on the AIM L side and you have come the other application which is the feedback system of the agent evaluation. So that also gives in the land graph and everything. 

Speaker 2  (02:34)
And I started with a certain engineering, and then I switched to the aimling, so I have worked on the eds, also on the August January. Ah, walked on the NLP when we don't have the llms, so worked on those NL p's and extraction using the comprehend extracts, and everything so. Yes, majorly, I've worked on the data bricks right now. 

Speaker 1  (03:02)
Okay, so and any experience you have in risk and order domain risk compliance, not in domain. 

Speaker 2  (03:11)
Yes, I say I have. I mean I worked on the backed office front and backed office both. But there I have analysis some 

Speaker 1  (03:22)
Scenario is company Vs it. 

Speaker 2  (03:24)
Mogan's strategy companies. 

Speaker 1  (03:26)
Global standards, strength and back and doesn't sorry. 

Speaker 2  (03:30)
Yeah, I backed office, and I kept office in the sense they have The confirmation, basically, the market wire confirmations that we're usually received at R and then we have to validate that data. So there are multiple matrices. And then if there is some error or something or if there is any fraud detection kind of thing, not the fraud but just using that term. 

Speaker 2  (03:55)
So that we need to evaluate using the NLP with a matter or not cut condition. Similarly, that I've worked data application. 

Speaker 1  (04:11)
What was the busiest problem? 

Speaker 2  (04:14)
Where on the mosquitoes standing? The business problem was that once we have the documents confirmed from the market wire. Okay, uh, was the trade has been confirmed. 

Speaker 2  (04:25)
Then, we get the acknowledgement data, okay, and then we have to verify that particular data. So with that data, there are multiple parameters that we have to evaluate with some different conditions, basically, and that we have trained our model on that work that give us the classification thing like, is it compliant ready or not on something like that is it? 

Speaker 1  (04:52)
So what were the tests that you do that? You would do over there. 

Speaker 2  (04:58)
Test means. 

Speaker 1  (05:00)
Soup. You said the data that you have you check whether it is compliance ready or not right? You check the accuracy of the data. 

Speaker 1  (05:08)
Yeah, but in terms of accuracy, what are the checks that your model would do to confirm that? Yes, it is accurate. Yes, it is complained. 

Speaker 2  (05:17)
Yeah, I was a classification model. Okay, so there we usually check the accuracy. Precision recall values, those were the parameters that we 

Speaker 1  (05:29)
No, no, no. So I know, precision recalls sensitivity, specific sensitivity, euc, right? But before that, what are we checking? 

Speaker 1  (05:39)
So for example, let's say if I'm predicting my sales, my accuracy will check that in terms of what has happened Vs in terms of what is predicted. What is the percentage of correct prediction, correct? And that is my accuracy, which is fine. 

Speaker 1  (05:53)
But here we are trying to predict sales, right? In your case, what will be trying to predict like what should the text in each of these cells should be same or mean water? Put the parameters be same column value should be same. 

Speaker 2  (06:10)
What exactly yeah, values would be same templates over there? Okay, it's been a long time and 5 years back, so templates were there. Okay, the structure they used to check whether the structure of the data is correct. 

Speaker 2  (06:28)
Samjhargans usually Put in the data that it usually check those when corresponding value values for them, and some small checks were there even Ok, so what the business problem that we're trying to solve. So we have the valid scenarios that we have in one of the location STP location usually get all the documents. Okay, corrected documents by the ARB team and those we need to validate whether it is falling under which category. 

Speaker 2  (07:06)
Okay if it is calling him falling under the Norm, they were some name, were there norms or something, so we usually get that template. Okay, verify that with the one that we have received. Okay with all those steps we usually, I mean I'm not able to recall it right now but those things I have done 

Speaker 1  (07:33)
Ah, okay, help me understand this. Do you understand? Employee expense process. 

Speaker 2  (07:41)
Employee, exactly. 

Speaker 1  (07:43)
For claimed proper employee expense. So for example, odm, or let's say if you stay back in office you claim for the dinner or you go out for a tea mounting. And then you come back and claim for the bill, have you ever done that? 

Speaker 2  (07:58)
Yeah, I'm that. 

Speaker 1  (08:00)
Ok, so my question is What on the 10 I am just tapping a doubt. So that you can see it can 

Speaker 1  (08:31)
What are the tests that you would do to identify fraud activities in employee expense process? 

Speaker 2  (08:39)
What are the tests do to identify the fraud activities? 

Speaker 1  (08:44)
So let's say, hi, let's say your you're the person who approves all the employee expenses you're from financing. But I'm sure you would know that a lot of employees who perform fraudulent activities, correct that let's say the bill is ₹100. They came in for ₹200. 

Speaker 1  (09:02)
Let's say there will be one attendee. He would came it for 5 attendees, right? So all of these Checks has to be in place to prevent employee to claim something that is not eligible for overcome easily right to prevent any overcame. 

Speaker 1  (09:18)
Yes, so what are the tests that you can think of? 

Speaker 2  (09:26)
Okay, first check would be the approval limit? Okay? That we need to Specify F. 

Speaker 2  (09:37)
Let's say, if we're going for the outing for the some dinner so we can have the average cost of the person. And then, based on that, how many person went and just an estimation, what the will bill bill would be? And if the gap is, the difference is huge, then we will See that the MMNS find to try to find the outlier. 

Speaker 2  (10:03)
Ok, there in the data or in the set Iven't okay. Yeah, these Hotels, I can check. Google limited on. 

Speaker 2  (10:27)
The system Not sure. 

Speaker 1  (10:33)
Choose to get no problem. So basically, where is this? There is just one audit project that you have done, and that was all about data reconciliation. 

Speaker 1  (10:44)
Then in 

Speaker 2  (10:46)
Plot wrong, correct. So why did 

Speaker 1  (10:47)
If you choose advanced analytics, given that advanced analytics accuracy can never be 100% right? So instead of advanced analytics, why did not you choose rule-based analytics that you have to take data? People or rather, let's say you have a template or and you have the natural data. 

Speaker 1  (11:11)
And why do you did not compare Columbia? Column? The data content for both the data set. 

Speaker 2  (11:19)
First, the data can be correct, but the underlying structure or the data should be should be matched. Right? Those were the checks. 

Speaker 2  (11:29)
We have we're saying why we didn't validate the actual data Vs why we are go with the this ML approach, correct? 

Speaker 1  (11:41)
Yeah, I mean simple rule-based approach would have also please worked and probably with better actual. So any reason why you went with male approach. 

Speaker 2  (11:52)
Um, yes, for the signatures and everything we used to have. That textile extract thing which will verify the signature and the In the document. Apart from that, we used to summarise that what the actual document is all about all the claws. 

Speaker 2  (12:14)
Clauses that they have added. Maybe that's why? Because of the text, we have lot of texts than the numbers. 

Speaker 2  (12:23)
That's why 

Speaker 1  (12:26)
Ok, and what are the various steps that you had used to cleanse that text? 

Speaker 2  (12:33)
Yeah, I mean, for cleaning the text what we have done that using the NLP only we have first tokenized that data. And if there's some irrelevant stock. 

Speaker 1  (12:50)
So what is stopping this token? What is stopping this? 

Speaker 2  (12:53)
Yeah, I mean, if there is some just splitting the words, okay, inform the sentences. Correct? And then we have the stopwords, remover. 

Speaker 2  (13:05)
Okay, and then we have the lemonisation, which is converting the Remove the. Safix, words like play playing from play. Ok, these all things we've converted. 

Speaker 2  (13:24)
And then yeah, these are the these are things I can recall right now. 

Speaker 1  (13:30)
So you said you remove stock words. What did you remove stock words? 

Speaker 2  (13:35)
Yeah, because that is not needed. I mean, that's said no. 

Speaker 1  (13:40)
Why not? Why? How did you remove stockbirds? 

Speaker 2  (13:44)
Yeah, when there's a library, there's a method in the NLP. Okay, stop for functioning today, so through that, when we have to look at 

Speaker 1  (13:53)
So these libraries, these are all pretty defined, right? So for example, I mean, the libraries that I have used will have a pre defined set of words right now, did you find any word that was not a part of those that stop word library, but you still need to remove that? So let's say my name is Rajesh Sharma and I am a sunlight employee. 

Speaker 1  (14:21)
Now let's say when you apply stockward. Mike will be gone is will be gone and all of those things. But what if I also want to remove Kumar Sharma? 

Speaker 1  (14:31)
Rajesh's full name is not necessary. I want to summarise. So people will understand with Rajesh, right? 

Speaker 1  (14:38)
So how would you remove Kumar and Sharda? That is not even part of that stock forgetting. But did you encounter any such situation that you had expressed? 

Speaker 1  (14:55)
Stopped. 

Speaker 2  (14:55)
We have used like rejects. Okay, we have specific specified. What let's say for example, tax right? 

Speaker 2  (15:03)
So from the title, we can split the middle name, first name and last name. And from that one, we'll pick only the first name. So those things we have done 

Speaker 1  (15:14)
Will you be able to write a pikey code? So that Ok, sure. We believe you can share your screen. 

Speaker 1  (15:26)
Open a notebook. 

Speaker 2  (15:28)
Yeah, I'm sorry, screenshot, you disabled. 

Speaker 1  (15:34)
Once you 

Speaker 1  (15:49)
See if you're able to do now, yes. 

Speaker 2  (15:54)
Yes He are able to see my stream. Please open. 

Speaker 1  (16:08)
So what I'll do is I will give you a text from your resume. Okay because I cannot give you a real text because of For Tata confidentiality issues, but I think this you are resuming in both of us apps or you can share that. So let's say this is the text, okay? 

Speaker 1  (16:30)
This is the text, and I want you to clean this text. So how how would you do it? Or rather, let me, so let's say we have candidate ID. 

Speaker 1  (16:46)
I'll look at a realistic one for you. Okay, let's say I'm interviewing. And I want to summarise I have 5 candidates. 

Speaker 1  (16:53)
I want to summarise their interview content so that I spend less time in identifying which is the right candidate. Okay? Okay. 

Speaker 1  (17:08)
Unvi. So let's say there is a data frame like this candidate. ID text resume and the desired skill that I am looking for today. 

Speaker 1  (17:22)
So what you are supposed to do is number one. Summarise the tricks and number two. Identify the Penetrate. 

Speaker 1  (17:39)
Who is most authentic Uber? Isoli tea? Ok. 

Speaker 1  (17:50)
So number one, you'll have to summarise the text for each of these candidate, and number two, you will have to identify candidate who's most identical to the desired space. 

Speaker 2  (18:01)
Okay, using the LLM or 

Speaker 1  (18:05)
Not no NLP. NLP. So maybe you will start with importing the data Incalling in TS yeah. 

Speaker 2  (18:33)
Perfect. So this is my text, at a time on the thing about beautiful. You can. 

Speaker 2  (18:58)
Number of this text what we can do is I'm saying on each of the split. 

Speaker 2  (19:34)
Is Krishna? 

Speaker 2  (19:47)
The simple test chocolate America. So what we want to change is the skills Let's say from this text at my scale. And the years of experience 

Speaker 2  (20:20)
Kya, hello, I'll have Threshold. Abhivitha. Parallel specifically, okay if you're going to see fronditions vary specific. 

Speaker 2  (20:52)
Specifically, logic logic, okay? 

Speaker 2  (21:08)
Oh, ABM LB so Subsidy. It was when the end of people, all those things it is matches, and then Ok, and let's say for the data engineering Naya general ke liye ke liye, addressing skills and yet Copy 88 366. And once I'll check with the logic. 

Speaker 2  (21:44)
Okay. And first of all, I have to Clean the data text from a text. He removed the decision on Siddharth details at the weather. 

Speaker 2  (22:11)
Play xia, let's say if you're we are removing the umbrella. Sorry. Specifically, the texture 

Speaker 2  (22:46)
activate 2 guns. Excluded the photographs figurines network exclude, and that into the multilateral release. Turn on. 

Speaker 2  (23:01)
I have due so distant. TV minus Saturday, which is more of the I gives a hang grammar technique. Okay for a specific idea. 

Speaker 2  (23:20)
Which is usually committing the two things of 14 years or smoking? Then, if she have any That's a 14 years. Show 14th February plus years to cook, become a trendy We drink 30 plus things. 

Speaker 2  (23:55)
The first Kantham, if there is any panchati. 

Speaker 2  (24:26)
Ok, so at that I'll get the 

Speaker 2  (24:45)
See, my main aim would be that. I'll have this The let's say 2 words okay in each of the rows. And then I'll Absolutely. 

Speaker 2  (25:07)
It was 25 days come. I'm just thinking. Data certify. 

Speaker 2  (25:16)
I'll create a at the end. What my data will look like is Skills to be specified at the path. Ok, and a year seat. 

Speaker 2  (25:32)
Tech bills would be like 15, turn on lube. 

Speaker 2  (25:54)
Trinamools. Category of festivals of democratic, it falls into the aim. Software, that is not abdomen, piliri, specified overs. 

Speaker 2  (26:24)
This data, vegetarian speed. The what are the skills that is that he has an experience? Tofu federers is preferable to the AM and not. 

Speaker 2  (26:42)
Yes. So converting those things into skills. What text? 

Speaker 2  (26:54)
Put the X effect, the entrance. The entrance of the specific species 5 The taxi sending. Scientists, 2017's teacher continents are specified. 

Speaker 2  (27:27)
Orange languages are specific include narer Did you do not write the screenshots? Northeast, then great district will come out. In October. 

Speaker 2  (27:52)
Skills, similarly, similarly, for the Experience also, I'll do the same. A my main goal would be that from out of this text, I'll try to create the structured text understructure would be similar to the I just give him. 

Speaker 2  (28:31)
Yeah, I'm sorry, ok, so experience and category would be. I'll specify ok based on the We have used the Anuv, Anuva we have done that one second I am restricted Ahmedabad. We did the we can do the hypothesis testing also there. 

Speaker 2  (29:05)
For predicting weather, the For predicting the category basically I mean, this is a things I can recall it right now. 

Speaker 1  (29:21)
It's been a long time. Okay, what is your code doing? What is your food doing? 

Speaker 1  (29:25)
If you can start from beginning? Yeah, because we are reporting the data set. Let's say yeah, go on, please. 

Speaker 2  (29:31)
Yeah, it is first converting to a data frame. Okay, data frame, actually. Let's say and I don't need that data frame right now. 

Speaker 2  (29:42)
Ok? So RL Twill remove the Stopwatch from this text on the list of the text. Once I get this text, I'll spread. 

Speaker 2  (29:51)
The data explode into the multiple array K having the distinct count. And first I'll convert that into the n-gram and Grammy's kind of 2 texts. Ok, in I'm sure correct, correct. 

Speaker 2  (30:13)
So then I'll stop. Then I'll Remove the snow first. I'll have to remove the stove for Sunday. 

Speaker 2  (30:21)
I have to create, and then using this split excluded distinct. I'll have those um listed in the rows. Okay. 

Speaker 2  (30:35)
It should be distinct. And similar to that right, so if it has Python or mibijava. I'm the film is having python or E Tl. 

Speaker 2  (30:52)
So, similar to that, if it is skilled, then I'll again explore those things. Okay. So once I have that data, then I'll check if my tax content in the Java python. 

Speaker 2  (31:08)
If it is then I'll add that in the list. And then similar to that, I'll add some more validation like if it is containing the plus I have to convert it in the 14 years. If there is a -, I will concentrate the string. 

Speaker 2  (31:26)
Okay. And I don't remember it. Actually, we've used the hanova for uh Categories category only. 

Speaker 2  (31:37)
Get an auto run link that sorry. Also, we will have the logic where I will specify if risk and python effects candidates having experienced greater than 5 okay and some other skills set, he will fall into the AIM L category, otherwise it will fall into the data engineering category similar to that. 

Speaker 1  (32:01)
APH. Okay. So Ukraine currently working for emphasis right. 

Speaker 1  (32:12)
Yes. Up short of 

Speaker 2  (32:14)
Pizza pizzas. 

Speaker 1  (32:18)
Episode of Noida, so any reason why you are leaving this company. 

Speaker 2  (32:25)
Yeah, actually, my company is asking to relocate to Bangalore. That's why. 

Speaker 1  (32:33)
And what is your current CTC here? 

Speaker 2  (32:37)
MI currently is around 30LP. 

Speaker 1  (32:42)
And expected would be 

Speaker 2  (32:44)
Yeah, I mean, as per the market standard. 

Speaker 1  (32:49)
I mean, still if you have gone to percentage in your mind. 

Speaker 2  (32:55)
There are 25 around. 

Speaker 1  (33:02)
Do you have any questions for me? 

Speaker 2  (33:07)
They can tell me about the project. Wow, hi, I mean what you're hiring for. 

Speaker 1  (33:14)
Opposition, so let it basically we are a team of right now 5, we were previously 61 of us left us couple of months back. And this is this position is just to fill that person's position. Now we are looking at your role over here would be to work. 

Speaker 1  (33:39)
And in hand independently with the audience. So this is a role of 90%. You know, helping your juniors like other team members who are less experienced than you helping them with basic problems that they are facing. 

Speaker 1  (33:58)
So be technically logical. So now we work at the auditors and we help them perform data-driven analysis audit analytics. So that means Just because they don't have the expertise and they don't know python, and they don't know data analytics, right? 

Speaker 1  (34:22)
What we do is we kind of help them, because if the data is small, they should be able to do it manually right sample testing and all of those films. But to cover the entire population, they don't, we are not equipped. They are not skilled and they are not equipped with appropriate tools and technologies. 

Speaker 1  (34:37)
So this is where we come into picture we build for them, projects or assets that they can readily use. Just as AGU Y graphical user interface, they can upload the data. They can check the box that I want to do data quality comparison. 

Speaker 1  (34:54)
I want to assist the data quality of the data that are just imported right? Or maybe I want to see whether there are any anti-money laundering happening as per this data, right? And they will check the requirement, and they will say, submit, and the algorithm should be able to identify the outliers right? 

Speaker 1  (35:15)
We also build various projects like we extracted data from the data source, like sequel database and all of those things. We do some advanced analytics on it. We do some prediction, we do some text extraction processes. 

Speaker 1  (35:28)
And then the final output output the final output data will be then fed to tab. You dashboard and disabl dashput will be the product that they'll be using right so then they'll be kind of it will be easier for them to look at this dashboard and identify the outliers and for future similar audits. Also, they should be able to see, you know, that in the past, this is the solution that are already available. 

Speaker 1  (35:59)
And maybe we can let me miss this. So in a nutshell, what we do is We greeted assets for them so that they can use them and perform their work in any even better and efficient way. Ok, was I able to 

Speaker 2  (36:16)
Question, I yes, you 

Speaker 1  (36:20)
I see. We still have 15 minutes. If at all, you have no more questions, I would like to ask one more question. 

Speaker 1  (36:26)
Sure, so can you tell me your Agentic AI journey use, said in your interview in your resume that you were able to build an On data data bricks, I believe we were able to build AGI solution right then, Agentic AI using L ML M drag, and all of those things know, so just start from the beginning. Okay, this is where the data resided. We imported into our data bricks and algorithm next week. 

Speaker 1  (36:58)
I don't want coding. I just want step-by-step. Up you perform to achieve the nptel product and that was the agenda and we probably has just 5 minutes. 

Speaker 1  (37:08)
So 

Speaker 2  (37:10)
From last year I'm working on the same thing, so creating the RAG pipelines. We started with the AD basically so we have the data comes in the size okay, or maybe in the ST we have multiple data files that is going to be injected into the From the adls, it comes to the Delta table. Ok, and from the Delta tables, we have those 

Speaker 1  (37:35)
Is Delta tables? 

Speaker 2  (37:37)
In the Delta tables, we have the matter data of the files. Basically. And the text that it contains, and those texts that we Put down into the chunking layer in the chunking layer. 

Speaker 2  (37:50)
We have created the structured data out from the unstructured data, and then we have them. We create the embeddings, and then we store them to the vector store, which is there in the database. And then we have the user query. 

Speaker 2  (38:07)
Okay, little bit of metaprompts, we have written after that from before the after the wedding. Sorry and then those metaphors comes into picture. Which summarise the text from the sorry, not summarization, but basically, we are putting the context under the query in the LM prompts in the prompt, and then we are sending it to the L. 

Speaker 2  (38:32)
M. And in between, we have the memory also. So basically we are using the summarised buffer. 

Speaker 2  (38:40)
Memory, which is Kindly kind of taking the top K elements and then summarising the previous chats. And then we have the retrieval there where the retrieval layer we are having the diversified and the um semantical data that we are capturing from the uh embedding spectrum weddings, we have implemented the dense and the this keyword vector search, which is bm 25, we've implemented that so through all those things. We come up with the context and the user query, and then we will pass it to the element to get the response, making sure that the latency should be high. 

Speaker 2  (39:21)
Okay. And the cost should be low. 

Speaker 1  (39:27)
Ok. And the whose end user for this 

Speaker 2  (39:33)
Yeah, it's an internal chatbots that we've created an application. So anybody from the organisation can use those 

Speaker 1  (39:47)
Alright, I don't have any further question. If you have anything, maybe we have another two minutes or 

Speaker 2  (39:55)
No, no, we are good. Yeah, I'm good. 

Speaker 1  (40:01)
So Thanks to you, thanks for your time proper. It's really nice coming to you and maybe you'll hear about the next steps from the HR thanks a lot so all the best for your Future loans. Hope to see you. 

Speaker 1  (40:19)
Thanks for you. By the way, sorry, what is what is your notice period sorry? Are you in my past? 

Speaker 2  (40:24)
Yeah, it's very crazy. So my dog 

Speaker 1  (40:28)
Thank you, serving a notification. Yeah. 

Speaker 2  (40:30)
So, it's on 27th of July. 

Speaker 1  (40:36)
May June and July. So, do you have any already? You have an optimal hand. 

Speaker 2  (40:42)
No, I don't have 

Speaker 1  (40:45)
Then, why did you resign without any offer? 

Speaker 2  (40:48)
No, if I don't resign, I have to move back to the Bangalore, right? So which I don't want, I'm not asked to also exploring some other opportunities. 

Speaker 1  (41:02)
I mean, because this is very risky without a job in hand just because we don't want to go to Bangalore, you've just resigned and how long have you been working in this organisation? 

Speaker 2  (41:12)
It's been 3 years with them. 

Speaker 1  (41:16)
B is the nearest possibly sending you the not even hearing from me. 

Speaker 2  (41:20)
No when I joined it was work from home. Uh, completely now. They are switching to the Bangalore office. 

Speaker 2  (41:30)
So yeah, what was the holidays? 

Speaker 1  (41:34)
And you notice period here is 3 months ago. Yes 

Speaker 2  (41:37)
3 months. 

Speaker 1  (41:38)
We need to June june, July means you have already resigned a month back, correct? But I mean, what is just wanted to understand? Why do you so do you hate Bangalore more than you love your job? 

Speaker 1  (41:54)
Which is why he resigned just not to love it to Bangalore. 

Speaker 2  (42:00)
No, there were several other conditions different opportunities among story. Otherwise, I would be working on the same thing, right? That's one of the reason relocation was another challenge. 

Speaker 1  (42:19)
Ok, I think we are talking. So I'll see you soon. Thank you for time. 

Speaker 1  (42:23)
Thank you. 


Summarize the text
Identify the candidate who is most identical to the desired skill 
Nlp


text= “
Databricks Certified Data & ML Engineer with 14+ years of experience designing and delivering large-scale data platforms, ML systems, and production-grade Generative AI solutions.
Expert in Lakehouse architectures, distributed computing, and AI system design, with strong hands-on experience building RAG pipelines, multi-agent AI systems, and LLM-powered microservices for real-time enterprise use cases.
Deep expertise in modern data platforms including Databricks, Delta Lake, Snowflake, Spark (PySpark / Scala), AWS EMR clusters, ECR, S3, Snowpipe, SnowSQL, and Azure Data Factory pipelines with incremental load strategies, CDC, orchestration, and large-scale data transformation.
Strong hands-on experience designing medallion/lakehouse architectures for analytics and AI workloads.
Experienced in distributed data engineering and ETL/ELT pipelines using PySpark, Databricks Workflows, Azure Data Factory, AWS Step Functions, Airflow, Lambda, SNS, SQS, and CloudWatch, supporting both batch and near real-time enterprise workloads.
Proven ability to optimize cluster performance, partitioning, file sizing, job parallelism, and cost efficiency across cloud environments.
Proven ability to translate business problems into scalable AI systems, combining data engineering, ML, and modern GenAI frameworks.
Core Expertise in GenAI Systems: RAG, multi-agent architectures, LLM orchestration, embeddings , Data Platforms: Databricks, Delta Lake, Snowflake, Spark (Scala/Python),ML Engineering: NLP, deep learning, model deployment, MLflow, Cloud & MLOps: AWS, CI/CD, Docker, Kubernetes,Backend Systems: Java (Spring Boot), REST APIs, microservices,Evaluation & Observability: MLflow, prompt evaluation, system monitoring
Strong background in machine learning and NLP, applying classification, regression, clustering, embeddings, and statistical techniques to real world business problems and GenAI driven use cases.
Designed and developed scalable AI-powered microservices using Java 17 and Spring Boot, exposing LLM and RAG-based capabilities via REST APIs for real-time inference.
build scalable data and AI systems. Expertise in distributed data processing, MLOps, and Generative AI including Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG), LLMs, and Agentic AI systems.
Experience in MLOps and deploying models in production.
Proven experience building end to end ML and data pipelines, seamlessly integrating data engineering layers with ML consumption, APIs, and analytics. 
 
 
Canditate ID, Resume Text, Desired Skills”
t1=nltk.stopwords([text])
refined_text=//n gram

t1.split().explode().distinct()

if(refined_text.contains([“Java”,”pyhton”....]))
	skills.append(refined_skills)
Exp

// 14+ years to 14 yrs, - concat,
//skills,yrs,
# threshold p-value >0.5 
#logic{
python> 5, ai -ml:{nlp …..}
Data eng{pthon , elt…}
}

Skills 		exp   category   pred
Python	java	14	AI ML	  yes/no
			
Java	etl	10 	app dev
`


 
