ananyaananth.n@tcs.com
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Now how he started your career. You can start like just within 23 lines. Tell me the start of your career, just can set you possess and how you move to the transition to the next steps. 

Speaker 2  (00:12)
Yes, so I started with the hadur with a data engineering things. I work her, I worked on hardu all those things. And then parade. 

Speaker 2  (00:22)
I moved to other projects which is on Java there. I learned the Java microsovic on all those things I work for around one and a 1 year and then nice fish back to the data brick site. Uh, not the database, but the spark site majorly another spark side. 

Speaker 2  (00:37)
I have built some application on top of that. Then, um I switched to the E I'm L part. Okay. 

Speaker 2  (00:45)
AIM L part means I was doing the eds for the Mogan stammer, and there I have used a traditional models in everything then I switched back to the uh. Then, I move to the data break site where I was using all those all the same thing. But with a different application, so I have got a chance to work with Azure adf pipelines and some modules from the adws also so it's some big enterprise application there. 

Speaker 2  (01:18)
I have built multiple pipelines on the data engineering side as well as on the Gen. This GenAI side you can make in the chat box. There was another application which I worked on using the BERT, which is evaluating the agent feedback system. 

Speaker 3  (01:36)
Yes 

Speaker 2  (01:37)
Yeah, those are the things that I have currently working on. 

Speaker 1  (01:50)
Ok. And what are the different organisations you transition? 

Speaker 2  (01:57)
I started with This is algox, and then I move to an IIT then why work which impact jam-packed with Morgan Stanley? Uh, I became the FT for the Morgan, Stanley and then I move to this emphasis from last 3 years from working there. 

Speaker 1  (02:21)
And location? Noida. And fine? 

Speaker 1  (02:26)
Ok, you can share your screen and give you one python coding question so that you can write the coding part using lunching filmbook. 

Speaker 2  (02:36)
Ok, just give me what Can I open the notebook? 

Speaker 1  (02:42)
Yes, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (02:50)
I'm sharing my screen. 

Speaker 1  (03:06)
Okay, so I've sent across the use case. 

Speaker 2  (03:17)
Load the PDF file split the document create embedding create vector store colonial model. Create the Bronte temperature and: epiercers. 

Speaker 3  (03:32)
Ok. 

Speaker 4  (03:34)
Kashi hi, I'm just checking if Prachi is available. Okay, so sorry because I'll have to. We have back to my calls. 

Speaker 4  (03:41)
So actually, most of the parallels are also not available. Aprachi also looks out of office. I'll check if she can join if she does. 

Speaker 4  (03:51)
Then, we'll take the screenshot, if not, then I'll just complete the screenshot with you. Okay, then we can arrange a call for Mrs. Tr C. 

Speaker 4  (03:59)
Select okay, prakha, you'll have to remove the background filter as I told you earlier and stop sharing your screen for a moment. 

Speaker 3  (04:09)
Ok. Yeah 

Speaker 4  (04:34)
No, I don't think sushi, is there ha? 

Speaker 1  (04:36)
Ok sure, yeah, we can have a stretched at the moment with 3 of us, and later. 

Speaker 2  (04:42)
Yeah 

Speaker 4  (04:46)
Ah, Shikhar, what could be your preferable location? Are Noida? Okay, we'll have to get that check. 

Speaker 4  (04:55)
Okay, do you have any idea Kashmir? Just that of okay, Noida yeah. 

Speaker 1  (04:59)
This would be Noida, good governance. 

Speaker 4  (05:01)
Oh, okay, and what could be your notice period 

Speaker 2  (05:07)
The current limit serving 

Speaker 4  (05:11)
How many days? 

Speaker 2  (05:13)
So my last working day is 20th of July. 

Speaker 4  (05:19)
20, right? So we almost have what 

Speaker 1  (05:23)
50 days, 2 days. 

Speaker 4  (05:24)
Yeah, yeah, 52 days we have so Alright, uh, Prakash show you're right. Keep it in the centre of the frame and please your hiding your signature, so just hold it from the edge. A yeah, get a little closer to the camera. 

Speaker 4  (05:48)
In the centre. Yeah, just what's there? Now you can hold your ID Card right next to your face where I can see your face and your ID Card. 

Speaker 4  (05:59)
Put together. Please ensure that your face is your ID Card is not riding face. Okay, now you stay like that. 

Speaker 4  (06:05)
Only get your hair closed with the camera. 

Speaker 2  (06:08)
Getting rid of my hand okay? 

Speaker 4  (06:13)
So that side of your frame is not clear. So you do one thing you shift towards right and show your ID Card of left side. Yeah, just of perfect. 

Speaker 4  (06:29)
Look at it. A Pragat justu reiterated in the C. Work 5 days a week from office and we do not provide work from home option alright. 

Speaker 4  (06:40)
Okay, sure Ok, no problem, thank you so much. I'm all the best. Thank you. 

Speaker 1  (06:48)
Thanks, Kavita yes, Prakash so you can write the python code using lunch chicken framework. 

Speaker 3  (06:54)
Yeah, sure. 

Speaker 2  (07:04)
Hey, M Sharma screen. 

Speaker 1  (07:07)
Yes 

Speaker 3  (09:00)
Open the model views in the sentenced transformer. It does not store we created from. Let's say It'll going to have the If we do the embedding Ok. 

Speaker 3  (09:40)
The sentiment management, I'm still at PD. A new call. Turn on Hotstar. 

Speaker 3  (09:55)
Pasta is concerned easily. I'm batting. So we N getro store coming up from the endpoint raglova.com, serve and Get handbon ok there, I'll get the endpoint from Quarter victory story of the attached open the newspaper with the call. 

Speaker 3  (10:31)
The maximum data. The data get going to this one. Sync butter store. 

Speaker 3  (10:45)
It will be sync. What time is do something like that going to create the website store? Okay, man's heart, this actress store and Chunky. 

Speaker 3  (10:58)
The Congress user has given the 1212% Axis Xiaomi. We can witness to colonial L. M. 

Speaker 3  (11:09)
What's the weather? Can you Lisber. So you have the you, sir. 

Speaker 3  (11:32)
Okay, are you the user? So are you the victors cure? Everything is done. 

Speaker 3  (11:37)
Let's say I am using open AI. Ok. No, with that letter store. 

Speaker 3  (11:52)
Okay, with that hot rescue. I've been going to Have the similarities search Of that, use a query. Let's say the context. 

Speaker 3  (12:15)
And then I will go to Haiti. I'll pass this That's a prompt. Her elders and the role. 

Speaker 3  (12:33)
Narrow sangi. Context is Contacts again. Oh, I'll assign the Our context on the query. 

Speaker 3  (12:52)
Let's see if I like this one ok, hello, all you have to use the law. Delete the alumni alpha was the OpenAI, front ok. 

Speaker 3  (13:33)
Okay, watch already 100. Open aif calendar. Empty 0 time. 

Speaker 3  (13:52)
In the crowd. 

Speaker 2  (13:53)
Yes, something like that. I'll do. I'll have this PDF loaded using Pi PDF library Tanu. 

Speaker 3  (14:03)
Use 

Speaker 1  (14:06)
Ok. 

Speaker 2  (14:07)
I'll trigger the challenges for chunking layer using the recursive taxpayer. Then, they're embarrassing model and going to use a sentence transformer Hugging Face one, then I'll create a new column of that chunk. Okay. 

Speaker 2  (14:22)
From the text basically, I'll get the columns text. Ok, and then I'll create this workspace vector store there. I'll pass that column, okay. 

Speaker 2  (14:35)
With the PDF embedded there, I'll get the vector store from data collector store. I'll find a similar similarity search of the user query. Okay, and I'll pass that in the prompt with a context and the user query and then in the LM I'll use the inbox function. 

Speaker 2  (14:52)
Something like that. I'm going to do 

Speaker 1  (15:01)
Ok. Despite this code in the chat window Ok. Ok. 

Speaker 1  (15:19)
Now the next huge cases like the UR fund with machine learning. 

Speaker 3  (15:24)
Yeah, fine with it. 

Speaker 1  (15:27)
Ok, the next use case is to write a programme for random forest and decision tree. 

Speaker 2  (15:35)
Rhino forest. 

Speaker 1  (15:37)
Endamforest and decidentary. 

Speaker 2  (15:40)
In decision tree. 

Speaker 1  (15:42)
No, no random forest and decision. 

Speaker 2  (15:52)
So I'll leave the right hand S. 

Speaker 1  (15:53)
Issue current city expected CTC. 

Speaker 2  (15:58)
Currently, I am drawing around 30. Ok, I'm looking for roundures in that. Ok. 

Speaker 2  (16:13)
So, is it under budget over 

Speaker 1  (16:17)
Yeah, that will be taken care by H. R. 

Speaker 2  (16:39)
Ok, I'll use the runner and describe 

Speaker 3  (16:41)
Patient tree classifiers. Tree. I'm going to use this to glass classes. 

Speaker 2  (16:48)
Look for the time. 

Speaker 3  (16:51)
Train contest. I use the let's see the Korean. And here are pasta. 

Speaker 3  (17:12)
Let's say the input, I'm passing, okay. Add them the Or instead of that, I'll use the Texas Twitter. This is true. 

Speaker 3  (17:26)
Printer splitter. Can you ask input headpass? They I want to find I'll point 85. 

Speaker 3  (17:41)
Ok, hey? Here I'll perform the skills. Scan scalar. 

Speaker 3  (17:51)
In the run of the category of needle, actually Whether you want to go home, something generally, we can do. 

Speaker 2  (18:05)
Simply, if you pass that 

Speaker 3  (18:07)
Testosterone. 

Speaker 3  (18:19)
Something I'm blue for the Turn off the list. 

Speaker 2  (18:22)
Something I'll do I mean, I'll split the input, 20% to test and 80% to train. And then pass the train data to the decision tree classifier or the random forest classifier. From there, I'll get the uh prediction output, which is then I can compare this prediction output against my test data. 

Speaker 2  (18:47)
Ok, sure. 

Speaker 1  (18:52)
Saying machine learning how much years of experience you are 

Speaker 2  (18:56)
Machine learning, I have around 5 years 5 to 6 years ahead. 

Speaker 1  (19:03)
Ok, once again, let me capture your details. So, machine learning, 5 years, I'm mentioning genius to us agency, a 2 years and lunch in framework. Also 2 years. 

Speaker 2  (19:15)
223 years ago. 

Speaker 1  (19:21)
P data engineering, how much 

Speaker 3  (19:24)
Around 12. 

Speaker 2  (19:25)
10 plus I have 

Speaker 1  (19:37)
Ok. So now a one program LGP for python, so you have to write the program. 

Speaker 1  (19:56)
Just give an example of acing programming using AC and await function. 

Speaker 2  (20:04)
Ok, you sing programmeming, what do you want to achieve here? 

Speaker 1  (20:10)
Any sample Put? 

Speaker 3  (20:14)
Ok. 

Speaker 2  (20:17)
Also, if we are, I'm within 356. 

Speaker 3  (20:42)
List of wine I want to have. 

Speaker 2  (20:49)
Can you listen right? 

Speaker 3  (21:10)
But we can call me A Can't that file? 

Speaker 2  (21:21)
Insecured, Syrian forgetting that issue. I've used the executor framework majorly. I've worked on dharmata. 

Speaker 1  (21:37)
Ok, I'll not C file a few file in the data frame. 

Speaker 2  (21:41)
Lodza C square in the data frame. 

Speaker 1  (21:44)
Yes 

Speaker 2  (21:52)
Using the piceberg, or using the pondas or anything will define 

Speaker 1  (21:56)
Fundas. 

Speaker 3  (21:59)
What will? 

Speaker 2  (22:02)
That we have already read, right? 

Speaker 1  (22:24)
Again, can you write a program? How the lunching will handle the E semantics search how you can enable that. 

Speaker 2  (22:31)
Change into the cement semantic search. 

Speaker 1  (22:34)
Yes 

Speaker 3  (22:37)
Ok. 

Speaker 2  (22:38)
So semantic search similarity search. You're talking about right similarity search or the Semantic kiss is the semantics only we'll understand the so that way only similarity such, it will figure out the semantics. 

Speaker 1  (22:59)
What is kosign similarity? 

Speaker 2  (23:02)
A cuisine similarity is a dot product of the 2 documents which are having the similar angle. Basically, if they are similar, the angle will be less otherwise, it will be huge. So there are 2 vectors majorly. 

Speaker 2  (23:17)
Uh, irrespective of the magnitude they vary, they differentiate based on the angle. 

Speaker 1  (23:29)
How do you integrate the luncheon with the vector database? 

Speaker 2  (23:35)
Lancheon fury launched with a vector database. Okay, yes, we can use the pine cone chroma db. Ok So they have this FIS library. 

Speaker 2  (23:46)
Uh, those we can use it, we have to pass the um. Bijli, you have to predict the index, and that index we need to pass as a parametre. Then, the directory location, so there it will go to grade the embedding for us. 

Speaker 2  (24:03)
It can be pine condition. 

Speaker 1  (24:16)
Can you explain nude orchestration in the multi agent system, certain node Note orchestration. Intern AMA S multi agent system 

Speaker 2  (24:29)
Ok, multi agent system. Yes No orchestration. 

Speaker 3  (24:38)
Yes 

Speaker 2  (24:39)
Are you talking about the mcp or completely different? 

Speaker 1  (24:45)
For the example, let's, I'll give you an example. You have created 5 agents now. Those 5 agents needs to synchronise like they need to interact with each other feet. 

Speaker 1  (24:54)
The response and give the output from the final digit. How you will accomplish this through python programme? 

Speaker 2  (25:01)
Yes, I mean, land rough will go into help us on this one. So we can create 5 agents. Okay, name, let's say supervisor manager or master or sleep, and then we can assign them by tools. 

Speaker 2  (25:15)
Okay, so we have to grade the agent in the agent itself very to pass the tools. Okay? The agents that we have created agent 1 agent 2 agent 3, anything, and with agent one, we going to have. 

Speaker 2  (25:30)
The tools is specified, so we need to Bind the Tools, there tools can be sequen, tool, search tool or any inbuilt tool that we can use. That's how you're gonna do Set automatically. 

Speaker 1  (25:49)
Are you secure like okay? How do you secure the ramchain framework against prompt injection attacks and you have created one workflow how you have to secure it? Let's say you are like the productionising that workflow. 

Speaker 1  (26:03)
For banking domains, each and every data is secure. Do that hopely secure the whole year. 

Speaker 2  (26:18)
Yes, there are many ways to do it. Okay, each of the layer we need to first is the, if I using the prompt they should be guaranteed with the strict prompt. If they don't know then they can if they are going to be hallucinated, then they can say, I don't know the answer. 

Speaker 2  (26:35)
Okay, so that's the easiest. Way if our model is fine-tuned, okay? Using the tulor Lora concepts basically specific domain. 

Speaker 2  (26:46)
They have been trained on then there. We can add the security layer also with the uh correct, I mean, using the vector search. And the embedding layer searching, ok, that also can be restricted with whether we want the diversified data, or whether we want the uh exact data. 

Speaker 2  (27:08)
Okay, also, we can fine-tune the temperature control. Also there that we can specify apart from that. Yeah, these are the few things that I can recall it right now but there are other things as well. 

Speaker 1  (27:28)
What is the difference between synchronous and a synchronous execution in Lanja? 

Speaker 2  (27:34)
A synchronous would be that With the executive frameworks, ok, where the event has been happened and it is not waiting for the other event to execute. So through that way, we can have that workflow specified everything and that can execute it without any sequential manner. And sequential is like synchronous is a sequential execution fashion. 

Speaker 2  (28:08)
Night, so that's how we can do that. 

Speaker 1  (28:19)
Please tell all the core components of plank chain framework in sequence manner like for an example. Firstly, you note a PDF file, then you split the PDF file in that manner I want like the 10 key components along with a short 2 to 3 words. 

Speaker 2  (28:38)
Yeah, sure. So we have the first that taxes is splitter than we have the chunks chunk with overseas and the overlap that we need to specify once we have that we can create the embeddings in the Abbey, ok, and there it will going to greet the words out of the numbers in between we have to, we can add the positionally positional tokenization, or maybe the token layer that we can add-on in between the Chunky and the embedding. That's an option. 

Speaker 2  (29:14)
But once we have done that, then from the abandoning, we can store that upbending into the vector dv vector store or any other store, we can store it. Then, we have the memory layer comes into picture where we can use any memory classes. Like if, for the for the coast for the concern of the cost, we can use the semantic memory semantics buffer. 

Speaker 2  (29:42)
Sorry, some summary buffer memory something is there so what it will do? Is it will take the first stop K records maybe from the database or from the session and then it will go into a summarise the rest of the chats if the text if the chats is huge. Okay so that we can use in the memory layer. 

Speaker 2  (30:02)
And then we have the user query, and with the embeddings, and with the similarity search um, then comes into the picture of the retrieval on the retrieval size. We can add the chain type. Also, chain type can be its mm R or it can be map produce. 

Speaker 2  (30:19)
Okay refine, so there are several others also. So once we have the retrieval layer comes into picture, then we can have the retrieval types also, whether we want the dense or the sparks search. So with t With the keyword to keyboard match, we use the BM25 with the dense one we use the similarity, such maybe with the cosine, uh majorly, and then once we have those things ready searching is layer retrieval is rare, then based on the hallucination rate we can do the reranking, and when the reranking is done. 

Speaker 2  (30:59)
Then, we send the reader to the LM okay in between, we can at the fall back Leh m's also or some metaprompts, we can write. This is the 

Speaker 1  (31:11)
Way ok, what are the books in lancheon? What are the Pebbs. 

Speaker 2  (31:19)
What are the Web hooks? Can you can you specify that, please? 

Speaker 1  (31:25)
It is weybook, yes. 

Speaker 2  (31:29)
Yeah, I hoardo, that me, I'm not able to recall. Can you Elaborately. 

Speaker 1  (31:39)
Okay, these are like the components which allows you to connect to the external system. So for an event trigger through XCT page fall, if you want to extract something trigger something, then my books are 

Speaker 2  (31:50)
Yeah, I've been here talking about the tools right? Where we specify the It's just a tool in the agentic way. We can have the search tool, the sequel search tool, all those things I think that comes with. 

Speaker 1  (32:05)
The event trigger mechanism. 

Speaker 2  (32:08)
Similar to that, I mean 

Speaker 1  (32:15)
What are different types of picture database? And what's an advantage? What are the different vector database you have worked upon? 

Speaker 2  (32:23)
Yeah, I've used multiple like I started with the quadrant. Then I moved to the chroma pindab. Now everything we are making it in the vector store. 

Speaker 2  (32:36)
Which is in database. Yeah, the advantages are if we're using the Facebook writer Fai SS then it's simple for local use. Ok, we can use that it will create the indexing everything on the local settle, but with a pine cone and the chroma deviates. 

Speaker 2  (32:55)
The UI is emin, more enriched where we can see the score basically of the rankings and everything but they are comes with the cost. Okay. And similar to the vector store where everything in one place. 

Speaker 2  (33:12)
Okay. So there is no it will reduce the network time out right latency. Basically, so that's why we use the vector store here. 

Speaker 1  (33:25)
Ok, regarding the 3 cloud systems, you have fine with which cloud system WSGP or is here. 

Speaker 2  (33:32)
Yeah, he ws and razor jicbi are not home. 

Speaker 1  (33:38)
Ok. Are you aware of coconut, etc. 

Speaker 2  (33:50)
Telugu. 

Speaker 1  (33:51)
Tk Google AD ki. Agent development ki. 

Speaker 2  (33:57)
Are you not going to do not following that? 

Speaker 1  (34:01)
What are the main components of agentic system? 

Speaker 2  (34:05)
Main core component of the agentic system. Yes, yeah, it can have the This, sir, ok, the tools, okay, the model, the agents okay, how we are structuring those agents. We can their different types, right? 

Speaker 2  (34:25)
One can be supervisor or we can add it in a sequential manner, pedal manner. So all those things we can do Apart from that. Yeah, these are the few components saying On the agenda, okay, happy 

Speaker 1  (34:39)
We've created a multi agents. 

Speaker 2  (34:42)
Yes, I did. 

Speaker 1  (34:45)
Any external certification done? 

Speaker 2  (34:47)
Yes, I have done this database. GenAI, and This statement engineering certification. 

Speaker 1  (35:00)
Gift. A guy didn't mention that you have worked in Mumbai. Singhly for a how much time duration. 

Speaker 3  (35:12)
Close schools. 

Speaker 2  (35:14)
1826, as 67 years ago. 

Speaker 1  (35:19)
6 cm, okay. Fine? What's the reason of change? 

Speaker 2  (35:27)
The reason was that I was in on-site, ok, and I want to move back to India. That's why. 

Speaker 1  (35:36)
Yeah, so that was on its location. 

Speaker 2  (35:39)
The biodiversity Canada, I was there in Canada, with mauka standard. 

Speaker 1  (35:45)
You know, for how many years 

Speaker 2  (35:48)
Close to 5 years ago an hour. 

Speaker 1  (35:55)
Intent, you have to some reasons like you want you to come back quickly. Ok. And what's the reason of transition from the current organisation to this one? 

Speaker 2  (36:10)
This one is basically they ask me to relocate to Bangalore. That's the reason on 

Speaker 1  (36:20)
Ok. How do multigencies communicate with each other? 

Speaker 2  (36:27)
They have the process of think and act. Okay. So first they think, okay, gathering all the information, which is the user is passing and then they act upon it using the tools provided, and then they come up with the file output. 

Speaker 1  (36:46)
K. Honour the memory types in Argentine. 

Speaker 2  (36:52)
Memory types are basically we have buffer memory. We have the semantic memory summer buffer buffer memory. Ok, then there is another word. 

Speaker 2  (37:05)
I forgot. 

Speaker 3  (37:11)
Even paste, not only 

Speaker 2  (37:12)
These are the types 

Speaker 1  (37:15)
What are the challenges in Argentina? 

Speaker 2  (37:19)
What are the challenges in AI? Agents. 

Speaker 3  (37:23)
Yes 

Speaker 2  (37:26)
First, if the cost ok, because we don't know the boundary of the Leh m's and they basically work on the tools right? So also they we need to pass the Recent information to the LLM's ok, because otherwise they will work on the previous world version of the data. That are the also, the latest is very high. 

Speaker 2  (37:55)
Sometimes Sometimes the allucination rates also. So basically we have to ground. We have to measure citration similar to the ground truth of the data, to make sure that we are getting the relevant answer. 

Speaker 1  (38:15)
What is the supervisor agent? 

Speaker 2  (38:18)
Supervisor agent ok. So it's an agent. It's one of the agent, okay. 

Speaker 2  (38:25)
Which the other agent will report to basically and give the output to the supervisor and supervisor is the first point of contact. Similar to the gallery that we are going to follow Yari. 

Speaker 1  (38:46)
Haji worked on landscape. 

Speaker 2  (38:49)
Landscape of method I have not probably used that but I know for the monitoring purposes. We are using something with the basic traditional approaches using the mill floors and everything we do it. But landsmith, I've worked on 

Speaker 1  (39:07)
How do you handle the imbalance data set in the classification problem in machine learning? 

Speaker 2  (39:13)
Yadyapia, multiple ways to handle the uh. Imbalanced data. So first thing is that we can use the K full model ok K full threshold model based on the ratios. 

Speaker 2  (39:29)
If you want to maintain, we can use the K for the there are other group fold. Also I am not able to recall, but based on the requirement that we want to Follow the padburger ratio, let's say 50% is data. Time is balanced and 20% is not balanced. 

Speaker 2  (39:52)
In that case, the key food will work right, but If the model is more biassed toward the negative case, or the positive case, based on that, we need to take the call. 

Speaker 1  (40:10)
Ok, coming towards python, how do you handle or implement the dependency injection in python? 

Speaker 2  (40:18)
Dependency injection, python. Yes Okay, so you want it to be maintained by the all the objects creation, and everything world will be. Maintained in the fly or Dependency injection. 

Speaker 2  (40:40)
I am not Done that. 

Speaker 1  (40:44)
Okay, explained about python's memory management and garbage collection. 

Speaker 2  (40:49)
Day I got it. But Ok no, I'm not worked on those things. 

Speaker 1  (41:01)
Okay. Now some short descriptions in terms of like your nose and responsibilities. So in agent, you have built 

Speaker 2  (41:14)
How many agents we have so like Go to go to 5 agents, ok, they are in one of the applications which I told you about the agent feedback evaluation. So they're there was one of the use case where we've paid 45 agents. 

Speaker 1  (41:33)
Okay, all those 45 agents were like standalone once or like, they were interacting with each other. 

Speaker 2  (41:40)
So yet they are interested similar to the supervisor and the agents warflow. 

Speaker 1  (41:50)
Ok. And in terms of launching, what are the work you have done? So to come again, any workflows created in terms of plan, chain and GenAI, any workflows created any Chatbot? 

Speaker 2  (42:05)
Yeah, I've worked on the rats morning, majorly using the language. 

Speaker 1  (42:10)
Ok, what was the work done in Frank using brand chain? 

Speaker 2  (42:13)
We will try to freeze it in the middle of the chat bottles of the internet organisation. 

Speaker 1  (42:18)
How many? 

Speaker 2  (42:19)
It was only. It was only one that I have walked on. But Only one is there depending on their regions that we have. 

Speaker 2  (42:32)
Eventually evaluated. 

Speaker 1  (42:36)
Again, machine learning. What's the work you have done? 

Speaker 2  (42:39)
In the machine learning Yes, yeah, I have told you about the eds, right? So I have done multiple eds on the August sandalwood data, so I am aware of the features in engineering, ok? The traditional model that we've used boasting models. 

Speaker 2  (42:57)
Ok Solids, all those things we have used. Is smart learning ok? 

Speaker 1  (43:05)
Yeah, the argentica work. You have done right now. In which organisation? 

Speaker 2  (43:12)
In my previous project, I have worked on the agents. In emphasis on. 

Speaker 1  (43:18)
Ok, and then the current project you are working on, which 

Speaker 2  (43:20)
Technology with the rags launched in 

Speaker 1  (43:25)
Ok. How much years of experience you have in financial and banking domain? 

Speaker 2  (43:31)
Close 29 years 96. 

Speaker 1  (43:37)
So are you aware of all the banking domain, non and creature and the other things? 

Speaker 2  (43:41)
Yeah, I know about them. Front as front of his gap office, I've worked on many areas away. What's the banking? 

Speaker 1  (43:51)
Ok. Punks, I'm can from my side. Anything you'd like to ask. 

Speaker 2  (43:58)
Yeah, come to me about the project. And the position that you're hiring for 

Speaker 1  (44:03)
Budhia, I'm yeah, the project is for a banking domain, and for the position is that it depends. We have got multiple positions like AI solution. Architecture developer, EA developer, EA lead engineer, and like you would be positioned based on your experience. 

Speaker 1  (44:23)
So, resource with the 14 plus years of experience will be aired where if not only you would be designing the solutions you would be leading a team as well. You would be guiding a ship towards the final destination in terms of AI. We are also using exploring AI, which is the latest technology, evolving in the AI ecosystem. 

Speaker 2  (44:55)
Okay? Yes, so. 

Speaker 1  (44:57)
Yeah, it's all about AI. We have got like the proximity multiple distinctions so a set of people working on the agenda and then along with the land chain and Chennai stuff, is there there are footprints of machine learning in data sciences. 

Speaker 2  (45:13)
Ok, thanks. Yeah, I'm good. 

Speaker 1  (45:20)
Ok, sure, thank you. It was nice talking to you. Have a good rest of the day. 

Speaker 2  (45:24)
Yeah, thank you, see my bye. 

Speaker 1  (45:26)
Thanks. Bye. 

Speaker 3  (45:49)
Zaraa, see some of the rehab. 
