pratibha.singh63@techmahindra.com
Speaker 1  (00:01)
Yeh, hai. 

Speaker 2  (00:10)
A prakran can you please win it? Your video. 

Speaker 1  (00:14)
Yeah, sure. 

Speaker 1  (00:28)
Oven. 

Speaker 2  (00:45)
A precautionary shoot your ID pooj your Aadhaar card or PAN card. 

Speaker 1  (00:49)
Ok, rescue me a moment. 

Speaker 1  (01:25)
Yes 

Speaker 2  (01:32)
I'm not able to hear properly. So always coming very unique. Can you please be loud? 

Speaker 1  (01:36)
Yeah, sure. So. This is my 

Speaker 2  (01:39)
You can just yes. Dangerous so long for it, I think that is Ok, you can Put it down taxpicker so prakher. From panel C instanist, they will be taking decision. 

Speaker 2  (02:00)
Yes, are you ok, so you can record the session? Yeah, sure. 

Speaker 1  (02:09)
ISU can record sorry. 

Speaker 2  (02:12)
Gir video should be enabled for the entire session. Actually, yeah, I can't see on YouTube. Thanks. 

Speaker 3  (02:27)
Hey hi, faker. This is Neha. I work as a solution designer. 

Speaker 3  (02:32)
I also have I am who is a solution. Architect and solution designer so praker will start with Brief about usl and your experience, especially in Agentic AI area. 

Speaker 1  (02:53)
Yeah, sure. So I around 14 years of experience working with emphasis for last 3 years. 

Speaker 4  (02:59)
And 

Speaker 3  (03:00)
Which company scorers emphasis? Ok, sorry, sorry, carry on 

Speaker 1  (03:06)
Before the river was working with the mogul standa for close to 9 years and then before that, I was working with sci, which is also a banking domain order wealth management. Basically so got continuous working on the education domain which is the application used by the teacher and the student for the diagnostic test. So here we are, using a data break snowboard for the chatbots. 

Speaker 1  (03:42)
Also, we have one application where we are evaluating the agents. Ok, feedback So for that one, we have configured the pipelines also, llms, land chain, all those things we have configured. So apart from that, I have done the certification on data brick side as well and Oracle as well. 

Speaker 1  (04:07)
So working as a user contributor now, but I have worked as a deal before. So we are working with the agile here, 15 labels, days of his print and 3 months of Psy. Yeah, that's it for myself. 

Speaker 3  (04:23)
A superker how did you handle E Tl part of data? So obviously you must have done the data processing. 

Speaker 1  (04:31)
Hi, yes. 

Speaker 3  (04:33)
So how did you handle that? I mean, what sort of Cardrails that you have Put in place to ensure that the data that you have received. Is accurately? 

Speaker 3  (04:49)
Stored. Yeah, alternatively, and also qualitatively. 

Speaker 1  (04:55)
Yeah, so we have. I mean, we have this trick prompted. Also for the pipeline, we are using the sure radio pipe 

Speaker 3  (05:02)
Technology, you have used sorry. 

Speaker 1  (05:05)
Sorry, comment technology. So for the pipeline for the pipeline, we are using the your AD of pipelines and for the prompt LLM, here we are using the OpenAI. Lm. 

Speaker 1  (05:18)
And then sorry, the database provided lms there and yeah, I mean, for the other thing, sorry or the other part from guarati or 

Speaker 3  (05:32)
So the atl part so obviously you must be processing good amount of data. So watch strategy you have followed because as a data engineer, obviously your key responsibilities also to ensure that the pipelines are in place. I'll ensure that it is stored safety correct. 

Speaker 3  (05:53)
So obviously the quantitatively and qualitatively. What needs to be, you know, manage or handle? So how did you manage 

Speaker 1  (06:04)
So if I talk about my architecture is like, we have the Kafka system Kafka, built-in which is our first source of information that Downs ADS N the CDC part incremental data into the S3, and from there we are reading the data through the ADF pipelines. Okay, from S3, so once the job once the file comes in, then we have the trigger based file system in the ADF where the a DLS also so from S3 to we are dumping it to the um. We are we are extracting the data from H32 our some EAP tables from EAP to our database table at the end. 

Speaker 1  (06:49)
Okay. So that's how we are doing it a file based system. Once its trigger, it will automatically run the pipeline for us and do the transformation, everything in this park and store the data into the Delta table. 

Speaker 1  (07:03)
Ok, so that's a one part. There are other part like we have the batch system. This I am talking about the batch operation, but we are just streaming also in the streaming. 

Speaker 1  (07:13)
We have the dear tip. That is also doing the same thing and extract. I am extracting and loading the rate and do the Delta tables. 

Speaker 1  (07:22)
Then we are creating the views. We are data sharing it with the other environments. Apart from that, this is one way we are using the workflow also for some of the tasks. 

Speaker 1  (07:36)
We have the vector store we have the vector search also feature store also built-in for the rack pipelines. Also, we are doing the chunkings and weddings layer into the vector indexes that we've created. So all these things are running it badly on a daily basis. 

Speaker 1  (07:52)
With the incremental data. Those are getting refreshed on the daily basis. These things Yeah, so is that answer a question or you were asking something specifically? 

Speaker 3  (08:06)
What happens? Let's say there is a failure Maybe let's say for example, the file that you have received doesn't match with the specification. Or there is some issue, maybe let's say hardware issue how these are handled in the code. 

Speaker 1  (08:26)
Yes, sometimes. 

Speaker 3  (08:27)
How will you ensure the completeness of the data? 

Speaker 1  (08:30)
Yeah, so we have the monitoring. Also, we are doing the monitoring on the edf pattern only so that will trigger the alerts if anything fails. That's a one part I was talking about the other thing which is Sorry, I've forgot that. 

Speaker 1  (08:46)
And So you question was that how I will go to monitor it right if there is an failure in the 

Speaker 3  (08:52)
Yeah, so basically let's say there is A 

Speaker 1  (08:53)
Thank you very much. Also 

Speaker 3  (08:55)
The batch so reason could be that let's say for example the file you received doesn't match with the expected pacification. Yeah, so more there could be something else, yeah? 

Speaker 1  (09:06)
Sche. 

Speaker 5  (09:06)
Changes how you have understood. 

Speaker 3  (09:10)
Could be even schema change, or it could be, let's say some failure in the core or whatever. So how you have managed that in your core. 

Speaker 1  (09:19)
Xiaomi, how we're managing it in our code. If it is failing, then we have to simply check what's the issue, because sometimes I'll tell you what the issues that we usually face is. The sometimes the day data doesn't match with the EAP and the data break side, so we have to check this because we have the multi hop architectures, silver bronze and bronze silver and golden layer. 

Speaker 1  (09:41)
So we need to verify on the bronze layer. What's the data is and how it's populated into the silver layer? The count, everything we check. 

Speaker 1  (09:50)
Right here. Yeah, these things we check also for the scheme. Sometimes the schema got there is a difference in the schema. 

Speaker 1  (09:58)
Sometimes we see. So we have the schema evolution in the cloud auto cloud. We have added that as an option, but that also happened in the new column into the new data frame, or in the new table. 

Speaker 1  (10:14)
For the court side, if there's any failure, we got the alerts, we have to obviously. We have to debug it what the issue. Yeah, I mean if the pipeline is taking lot of time everything so we have to fine-tune it. 

Speaker 1  (10:27)
I've done the most work on the Fine-tuning so I can talk about that. But 

Speaker 3  (10:34)
Yeah, sure. I am over to you, please 

Speaker 5  (10:45)
Yeah, so Prakar, given your experience. What is the role that you have primary played? 

Speaker 1  (10:53)
A role that I primly played ok. 

Speaker 4  (10:56)
As it 

Speaker 1  (10:57)
As a lead, I have majorly played in my current organisation also, but I've working as an individual contributor but once we get the requirement, I have to create the beddesm. And then finalise with the team, and the and then we do the implementation part based on the story deadline that we have given. 

Speaker 5  (11:23)
To your acting in the capacity of a lead engineer of the development. Okay? Ok, so you mentioned you're familiarity with the data bricks platform. 

Speaker 5  (11:33)
How familiar are you with aw services? 

Speaker 1  (11:36)
AI examined extensively worked on the end of the close side also with S3 okay, the services that I've used is S3 is type functions. I've used Landers. I have used and ec 2 instances all those things I know about it. 

Speaker 5  (11:57)
So let's say that you have the requirement that there is A near real-time, ingestion pipeline needs to be designed, so you have the log information from some sensors coming in. And Are those logs need to be ingested in near real-time? But you need to be mindful of the cost involved as well. 

Speaker 5  (12:22)
The client is very particular on the cost involved. So any expansive services or any expensive offerings of AWS they won't consider even the cost. So what is your? 

Speaker 5  (12:34)
I mean, how you will base your architecture, or how you will base your design based on this requirement. 

Speaker 1  (12:43)
Yeah, it's a steaming. Pipeline, we have to build right? Because it's a real-time data. 

Speaker 5  (12:51)
No near real-time, not real-time or not. Real-time. 

Speaker 1  (12:55)
Yes, so I'll 

Speaker 4  (12:56)
People. 

Speaker 1  (12:58)
Based on the coped optimisation Okay, do I need to do two things if I can go for the batch one I can go okay. Batch means on the daily basis. We are receiving these sensors files and then we are picking those files and inserting the data. 

Speaker 1  (13:16)
Okay, the other, the um. So also first time, we have to do load the all the all the data. But for the next run, we have to make sure that we are getting the incremental data. 

Speaker 1  (13:28)
Okay, not the huge file every time and that we need to sink app the data with the source every time and load the data again to the any Delta tables or any any other table, we can load it so that approach I will figure it out also on the 

Speaker 5  (13:46)
As I know, this on AWS Prakash, not on data bricks, so 

Speaker 1  (13:51)
Ok. So I will be keeping the files in the S3 −3 type of stages, right? 

Speaker 4  (13:59)
So 

Speaker 1  (14:00)
From if the file is too old, I'll Put into the archive mystery archive, I don't remember the exact name but there are 3 types. So we can divide the timeline of the file based on the object that we are creating the buckets that we are creating. Basically, that's the first way, one way. 

Speaker 1  (14:21)
Also I incremental, I talk about, right? Um, the lambdas I will want to use because these are several less. Whenever the file comes in, it will automatically trigger the we have to configure the queues. 

Speaker 1  (14:33)
Everything so that will go into, um trigger my lambda's there and those lambdas will be served as it will don't compute the much. Um, it won't run for the whole time. Uh, that's the other optimisation that I can think of also for the orchestration purpose. 

Speaker 1  (14:52)
I can use this tough functions okay on the AW side. Uh, what approaches what flow we have to go through? And for the messages side, also, we can use the SNS if the data is taking for the a synchronous call, basically. 

Speaker 1  (15:09)
Those things I can consider also There are several option on the ec, 2 instances where we can set the minimum and maximum cluster. Ok, uh, I have done that configuration, but let me recall that there's The kind of clusters, okay, there are 3 kind of cluster that we can pick enterprise business and the standard one. We'll go with a standard 1 1st, and based on the loads, and based on their spikes, I'll going to see what kind of cluster we can use. 

Speaker 1  (15:45)
They are other tunings, we can do on the cluster side apart from the auto and auto scaling basically. Yeah, I mean, based on the memory based on the data, I'll pick the memory executes and everything code. And if still the job take a lot of time, so I need to find tune it basically. 

Speaker 5  (16:12)
They had. So you have I mean, involved a lot of ways services which would be adding to the cost. So yeah, your design would work. 

Speaker 5  (16:23)
But we need to be mindful of the cost involved. So a simple lambda based on an even bridge or Even this trigger would solve the purpose, right? 

Speaker 1  (16:34)
Yeah, thanks. So depending on the how complex application is 

Speaker 5  (16:41)
So are you aware of any vector data stores and how is it beneficial from other traditional databases? What is different in vector data stores 

Speaker 1  (16:51)
Vector data stores basically stores them beddings for the similarity search. Let's say user is asking some giving some prompt query. Basically, so that will be converted to the embedding and those embeddings will be searched in the vector stores using the cosmic similarity search. 

Speaker 1  (17:10)
Also, we have the database provided libraries also that we can use for the similarity search of the query along with the data that we have in the store. So through that way, we can search the semantic text along with the original text. We have If there is any 

Speaker 5  (17:36)
So have you worked with any actual vector data stores? Yeah, how do you use them? 

Speaker 1  (17:43)
I walked up with recently. We were working with the vectors store of the database provided vector store, but we have used a chromais a pine cone also Fai SS also, so they are the defendant also this majorly. I work with a portrait other than the vectors too. 

Speaker 1  (18:05)
But recently, we 

Speaker 5  (18:08)
How are they different from traditional databases? 

Speaker 1  (18:11)
In the traditional media database is kind of if you're talking about the mice equal or the Oracle based database, which is sequel based, basically they have the row and the column. But But this is a traditional tradition database right with a row and column, but if I talk about the vector store or the vector database, they have the embedding stored right in a list of array or something. So for each of the tests, they will create the embedding, embedding, nothing, but the array of numbers for that particular token, or maybe the token is not the right word. 

Speaker 1  (18:42)
The correct word, basically for all these things we have to do is recognise. 

Speaker 5  (18:54)
Got it. And for files, which keep constantly arriving into the next 3 bucket. Then how do you make sure that these 3 storage cost doesn't go up unnecessarily? 

Speaker 1  (19:06)
Yeah, I mean, I told talked about the S33 types of storage that we can configure in S3. So if it is too frequent, okay, I'll i'll use the standard one and I'll keep on deleting those files from those buckets that are, that is the ideal way we do it. If we want to store it for the 

Speaker 4  (19:32)
Hum. 

Speaker 1  (19:33)
Ok, have you want to stop it for the auditing purposes? We can keep it what we keep it as a we keep the 30 days of window for that particular file if it is not then we usually dump it or usually our chive it okay for keeping it for long for 3 months again. But that way we do it. 

Speaker 1  (19:57)
Or we store in the database also Eventually, it is restoring 

Speaker 5  (20:06)
So, have you heard of any the iceberg tables that are now integrated into AWS so iceberg format is also there. 

Speaker 1  (20:14)
Turn off notifications. 

Speaker 5  (20:18)
Yeah, so you are aware of the deployment side of things right like terraform or cic. 

Speaker 1  (20:27)
Share idiots. Terraform are not majorly. 

Speaker 5  (20:38)
So let's say that you are designing or you are rather working on Solutioning on ews where the regulatory requirement is that you need to have a full year of data presentation. What is the choice of data store for you? That's the first question. 

Speaker 5  (21:04)
And why 

Speaker 1  (21:07)
So we want to store the one year of data. 

Speaker 5  (21:13)
No, you will store more than one year of data. But one year of data is required for historical analytics. Which should be available? 

Speaker 5  (21:21)
I mean, as soon as you run the query so it is immediately available. One year of data must be The rest of the rest of the data you can park it somewhere else. It's not required and it's not query frequently as well. 

Speaker 1  (21:36)
Throcking, um, that's what our application is doing. Basically, we're storing all the At a time, 2023 data into the db X and rest were storing it into the EAP only 

Speaker 4  (21:47)
Ok. 

Speaker 1  (21:49)
That might save the cost. What eventually, we can use a snowflake also for the analytics purpose, if we want to use it. So those data, we can storage a snowflake and dress into the some other cheap provided tables like high or something. 

Speaker 5  (22:09)
But we were designing on AW is so-called the client is not looking at. 

Speaker 1  (22:17)
On the AWS side, we can store it into the rds. Okay Those data and dynamo dv for the I don't know if it is used for the analytics. But. 

Speaker 1  (22:30)
Ok, for one year, I mean, we have to store it into the Not sure about the AWS side, but I'm guessing. 

Speaker 5  (22:42)
Blood shift in a lot 

Speaker 1  (22:44)
Yes, nobody could red shift. You can store it for the analysis purpose. We usually use their snowflake now. 

Speaker 1  (22:50)
But earlier we use to use do that with the red shift. 

Speaker 5  (22:53)
No, since you were primarily on database move like easily integrates with data breaks. So I was also part of one of such projects where the client had. The lake, the Lake House created in data breaks, and the gold layer was there on scrubling, so it integrates. 

Speaker 5  (23:09)
Well got up these 2 components, right? Okay, so let's say that you are trying to design an even based architecture on AWS, or you were working on an even based architecture on interviews. So how would you implement that? 

Speaker 1  (23:29)
A event based eye isn't a fight or if it is a file based, we can configure it into the S3, the S3, we have to provide the notification like SNS or something, so that will trigger the notification or maybe we can configure the lambdas also that will trigger the lambda. And on that lambda, we can process our file process that file particularly If it is a file Eventually, eventually event paste. We can get the microservices. 

Speaker 1  (24:02)
Also I mean, what kind of events that are reprocessing? 

Speaker 5  (24:09)
Then, maybe a file based event? It may be a timebound event. It may be anything. 

Speaker 5  (24:15)
So, any other services where you can figure based on an event 

Speaker 1  (24:22)
SNS the queues, everything we can configure if the data comes in. 

Speaker 5  (24:28)
Thank you. That is primarily used for notification purposes. So 

Speaker 1  (24:31)
Can you notification nothing? 

Speaker 5  (24:34)
Really? Don't use SNS for triggering, but we can. But we generally don't 

Speaker 1  (24:42)
Ok. When we eventually hope you're talking about I'm not worked hard. I'm not worked on my Mother. 

Speaker 5  (24:52)
And on the agentic side of things you mentioned about drag, right? So what are the different prompting techniques that you have used? 

Speaker 1  (25:00)
Yeah, we are mostly use the Few-Shot Learning. Giving the example of what kind of data we want to receive. 

Speaker 5  (25:10)
But doesn't it increase the token size? What you are feeding so it will increase the token size. Well 

Speaker 1  (25:15)
Particularly, it doesn't because we are summarising the chats. Also, we are using these buffer also summarised buffer with the memory and summarising their context. Also, and then we are sending it together. 

Speaker 5  (25:34)
So Let us say that you have you have been provided functional requirement document from the client. And you were at the design phase, he was the primary designer, and I am the developer, right? So the functional requirement document has a lot of use cases which are very simple in nature like copying over a file deleting a file if the retention period is has expired or moving the data to a database doing some updates. 

Speaker 5  (26:04)
So very simple operations are there not to complicate it so and the client is especially inclined on making. This an autonomous activity, so you receive the functional requirements. And you have been trusted to design it in an automatic way as much as you can. 

Speaker 5  (26:26)
And your delivery time is, let's say a month. And you have around 2025 use cases to cover. So how would you initiate the process, or what would your thinking strategy would be in terms of automatic automating, this or let's say move again. 

Speaker 5  (26:46)
How would you approach this problem? 

Speaker 1  (26:49)
So we have 20, we have one month of time to deadline is one month right? Including all the test cases. Everything Is soil see the success criteria first ok, what we're trying to achieve. 

Speaker 4  (27:05)
Right? So 

Speaker 1  (27:08)
The the requirement is only to test the test cases or it's just complete. We have to complete the development and then we have to confirm all the use cases everything. Because 

Speaker 5  (27:21)
You have to complete the development. Along with some level of testing and I mean, not such thorough testing, but at least some level of testing should be there. Some evidence should be there that you will succeed. 

Speaker 1  (27:33)
Yeah, I mean I'm thinking of making it to the like the phases, the first phase, we will see what we can deliver it with a prototype or Calm protype of what we've created then we can check the feasibility of how it is behaving. Okay. And similarly, we will do the development and the QA also and whatever we are building. 

Speaker 1  (27:59)
And then so that complete phase, happy path is done and we will go with the use cases at the edge cases that we have there in the documentation. Also, if it is involved lot of experiments and everything I'll create this spike. Okay of working on the spring on the current spring. 

Speaker 1  (28:24)
Um that way, I can think of women. 

Speaker 5  (28:31)
That is a very generic thing. So Let's say that you receive the functional requirement document, right? So, can you automate the segregation of the use cases from the function requirement document in an agentic way? 

Speaker 1  (28:48)
We are talking about Langra, for I mean, the actual implementation of the agenda, or we're talking about the how the business work. I mean, once the requirement, how we approach. You talking about the 

Speaker 5  (29:04)
I've got a requirement document. 

Speaker 1  (29:06)
And after. 

Speaker 5  (29:07)
How do it an agentic way agent? You have to fulfil the requirements right based on the use cases? So Won't your starting point? 

Speaker 5  (29:15)
Be that? Let me design an agent or let me feed it? Feed the requirement document to an LLM and check for the use cases and generate the possible test cases for that. 

Speaker 1  (29:26)
Ok, talk about that thing. Yeah, we can. We can do that, we can create the land land of flow. 

Speaker 1  (29:34)
Basically basically we can give the prompts we can We can do several things. I mean the end goal would be that we have to get the edge cases of the use cases for the application to run. Okay, we can do that. 

Speaker 5  (29:54)
Okay. 

Speaker 1  (29:55)
The bankruptcy is sufficient for 

Speaker 5  (30:00)
Do you have vot? 

Speaker 1  (30:01)
Cross, yeah, I woke up. 

Speaker 5  (30:02)
Lion children open. So how do you maintain the observability from a langra of workflow, or a land graph? 

Speaker 1  (30:13)
Let me use some ML flow for logging and tracking So it just tells what the the code is going through, like if it is using some tools we can. We can see all those things are in the able flow itself in the notebook itself. So if there is any failure in what line there is a failure, it will figure it out. 

Speaker 1  (30:35)
The Father logging purpose, then we have the name. 

Speaker 5  (30:37)
Any similarity service on adws that I can't think of. 

Speaker 1  (30:40)
Cloud watch is there, but I'm not sure whether it For monitoring purpose, we use the cloud watch but not for the MN flows. I'm not sure 

Speaker 5  (30:52)
Okay, okay, Singhal, I think that's all from my end. Do you have any further questions? 

Speaker 3  (31:02)
No, so Prakar, just last thing. SQL, how comfortable are you writing squares? Suppose you have to rate yourself on the scale of 125. 

Speaker 3  (31:14)
So where do you rate yourself? 

Speaker 1  (31:17)
Jale, more than 35, because I'm working on this economy. 

Speaker 3  (31:22)
And what about python? 

Speaker 1  (31:25)
Yeah, I am comfortable with pice park 12 date around 4 out of 5. 

Speaker 3  (31:33)
And currently, you are best in which location 

Speaker 1  (31:36)
Yeah, Noida. 

Speaker 3  (31:37)
Noida Hoke. 

Speaker 3  (31:49)
Yep, nothing from my side I am I think we have covered all the topics that we wanted to discuss. So Thank you, Prakar, for your time much appreciated. 

Speaker 5  (32:02)
How do you think? 

Speaker 1  (32:03)
Thank God, thank you. 

Speaker 5  (32:05)
Running interviews and have a nice day. 

Speaker 1  (32:07)
Thank you, simple. 

Speaker 3  (32:09)
Ian, can you remain? Yes, one sorry. You can drop off. 

Speaker 3  (32:13)
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. 
