Mamatha R <mr00851166@techmahindra.com>

Speaker 1  (00:00)
On Prakesh, so this is just a quick introvert myself. Yeah, could you? Could you please give a brief about you? 

Speaker 2  (00:06)
Yes, sure. So I have around 14 years of experience working with, starting with data engineering, and I switched to the a ML from last 5 to 6 AM working with the AM. L. 

Speaker 2  (00:18)
Send a photo side, I have worked mostly with data breaks. Okay with a genius implementation and currently I'm working with emphasis from last 3 years which is into the educational domain. But previously, I have worked with the mobest channel close to 9 plus years, which is the banking domain. 

Speaker 2  (00:44)
And there also I have worked with the automised data, along with the cloud, which is AWS, data bricks, Azure. So currently I'm working as a digital contributor but We previously worked as a lead. So here my required roles and responsibilities that I get the requirement, then I create the design document around it. 

Speaker 2  (01:07)
And then I blocked on the implementation part of heavy summary for mighty will going to do that. Apart from that, we are using a Child here with 50 dairas, print and 3 mass of psi. And so my current application is more into the diagnostic data which is used by the students and the teacher, and primarily we have built-in the pipeline using the lion chain. 

Speaker 2  (01:31)
Also, we have the adf pipeline built-in for the chunking and bedding layer and the vector dvs primarily we are using the data. Bricks site. But on the staging and the pipeline side we have used the EWS three's. 

Speaker 2  (01:48)
We have the calf call also built-in for the ingestion layer of the data. Basically, we have the multio architecture where we are injecting our data into the bronze silver and golden layer. And then we have the D lt pipelines, along with the along with the databases side and then we have the ML flow for the tracking. 

Speaker 2  (02:08)
This plan for the locks cloud watch also for the locks. Yeah, that's pretty much myself. 

Speaker 1  (02:20)
Yeah, thank you. Thank you so much, Prakash so we will just have a discussion with respect to data breaks AI and malops, like whatever you have worked on right, so definitely you would have seen these kind of scenarios earlier, so this is something which we worked as a PUC as well. So just wanted to ask. 

Speaker 1  (02:38)
You ask your thoughts with respect to our scenario okay, so this is auto loader, right, so just consider we are running a very high-throughput streaming pipeline. Okay, so it's using auto loader to ingest unstructured PDF, as well as adjust on customer integration blocks into a bronze Delta table. So yeah, Delta table, it's basically a branch Delta table and then silver, real T pipeline processes this particular text. 

Speaker 1  (03:10)
And we have a data vector search index configured on top of it. Okay, with continuous sink tracking, the gold table embeddings understood, so this is something which is there already, so suddenly the upstream applications they introduce breaking change. Okay, so they are trying to nest a previously flat Jason sub object. 

Speaker 1  (03:36)
And they are altering a data type of a text field. Okay, use for metal data filtering in the RAG application. Okay, so and then you know right so auto loaders. 

Speaker 1  (03:47)
This scheme evolution mode is set to rescue. Yeah, okay. So basically the question is, like, how would you design a self-healing infrastructure pattern to catch this scheme drift? 

Speaker 1  (04:03)
Before it corrupts, the vector search index matter data. Basically, how do you reartect the auto loader to vector search pipeline to trigger alerts or automatically reconstruct vector embeddings when the data falls into the rescue. Put call. 

Speaker 2  (04:22)
Um, ok, sure I think with the merger schema in the auto roader. We have that flag. Okay as true. 

Speaker 2  (04:31)
So that we can add in, but there is another, it will create a new column at the end. That tells the data has been corrupted or not, or may. It was there only some issue or not so that flag we can check so we don't want the data to be we add initially, we need to set the alerts something as changed right, this. 

Speaker 2  (04:59)
Is what the requirement is right so. Something has changed and yeah, so when the data fix itself, we can set the alert using the right flag. With the merger scheme built-in so that way, we can do it. 

Speaker 2  (05:14)
I mean 

Speaker 1  (05:18)
Can you also talk with respect to dlt like, for example, if there is a dlt thing right? So what all can be done from a Delta light table I'm just trying to understand with respect to dlt expectations you have dlt dot expect, right? So on top of this, you can basically add certain criteria just to make sure that it fails, or else you can make sure that you are passing. 

Speaker 1  (05:40)
The passing this downstream vector sink until then, nobody is artected, just trying to understand from a long-term perspective. 

Speaker 2  (05:50)
Sorry, sorry. I miss you question. So, what is the actual problem? 

Speaker 1  (05:56)
No, I'm talking about the same problem. Like whatever you said, just can you expand your thoughts from an entire architecture perspective with the like auto loader and dlt, it's a combination that's what we use here. So DL T you have that D lt dot expectations, right? 

Speaker 1  (06:12)
So dlt dot expect like on a particular column. You can add that and then do it right. So from that perspective, and if I'll have to pause the downstream vector sink in point until they normally is attracted. 

Speaker 1  (06:25)
So how would your basically do that end-to-end is what I'm trying to understand. 

Speaker 2  (06:31)
Okay. So once we have designed that alerts. Okay, there's something has changed the drift. 

Speaker 2  (06:38)
There is a data drift in the documentation so that alert we can trigger on the database itself. Now once we have that once we figure out okay, something has changed. And we have to resink the embedding layer okay, and we have to recalculate the embedding layer and then to the embedding to the vector depositful vector search. 

Speaker 2  (07:00)
Basically, it will I am in it will automatically sink with that so that we need to do it manually. Once we have we have figured out the data, the data drift. Apart from that. 

Speaker 2  (07:15)
So once this chain is figured out, then I mean, are you asked asking me something else or is it 

Speaker 1  (07:23)
This is my assistant. This is fine. Yeah, this is fine. 

Speaker 1  (07:26)
Yeah, we'll move on to an expert, so you have got to liquid clustering right earlier liquid clustering, so just consider I have a very big gold table. Okay, so maybe customer interaction table. Okay. 

Speaker 1  (07:42)
So which is from traditional sea ordering mechanism? Ok, so it was earlier following the Z order by customer ID, as well as the interaction date. Now, I am migrating into liquid clustering to handle all the high frequency, odd streams that is coming in. 

Speaker 1  (08:00)
So we are running concurrent merge into operations like every few minutes. Okay? So over a certain period of time, the data scientist team have complaining to us stating that the look up queries from the customer facing LLM agents are seeing a massive spike in P95. 

Speaker 1  (08:21)
So we call it right. So if I work P99 %, I will so read latencies, and spark compute costs are also sky rocketing. So basically we think that okay, just to ensure we have performance optimisation. 

Speaker 1  (08:35)
We have moved from zorder to liquid trusting, but again, what is happening is liquid clustering because of liquid clustering, so the compute costs are also skyrock, rocketing as well as there is a massive spike in percentage. 95 read. Latencies, which is complained by the BST so basically what I want to understand is what we thought is going to solve. 

Speaker 1  (09:00)
The problem is creating the problem right. So how do you isolate and fix this bottle link like? Can you just walk me through the design like this concurrent upsurts or tweaking table properties, or what is basically happening in the packet because of which this is happening. 

Speaker 2  (09:21)
Okay? So basically, the liquid trusting is automatically creating the file sizes. Basically, the index which is doing the indexing at the background of Based on the queries that it is retrieving, right? 

Speaker 2  (09:38)
So it will automatically go to create these small small files. So one problem that I can think of it will create a small file problem. Okay, and there in some files, we have the very less data and the other file we have used data. 

Speaker 2  (09:54)
So the solution could be that we can optimise it, or we can use optimizer to where we can remove the small file problem. It will automatically Ok, that's the one thing. And with the other thing for the cost optimisation right? 

Speaker 2  (10:17)
Sure that's the one approach or also we can on the clusters. So we have to see whether the issues with the if we can tune the data, if we can tune the cluster clusters also so we can enable the auto clustering auto scaling basically for minimum to maximum cluster, um that also, you can do Yeah, I mean we need to figure it out whether it's a data issue or a cluster issue, so we have to trade-off the things considering both the things 

Speaker 1  (10:52)
Okay, I get it, okay. Yes, fine. So the problem is like. 

Speaker 1  (10:57)
We also thought that okay good clustering is going to solve the problem, but all of a sudden, all this happened moving away from sea order. So we just took a hybrid approach back then. Just to solve the problem like, I mean, nicotine does not solve. 

Speaker 1  (11:11)
And there was also one another scenario like the table was also partitioned by and again. We applied this liquid clustering on top of it, so this is not very similar to high. Right, so wherein Europe, partitioning and marketing, so partition, and then the sampling or bucketing will happen on top of it. 

Speaker 1  (11:27)
So this is this is a slightly different architecture, so people will not realise that. And they know combination of this partitioning, as well, as this would say, liquid clusting, they don't on top of it, and because of that, the scanning itself will take so much of time. Yeah, so next moving on. 

Speaker 1  (11:48)
Okay, so we have you worked on this catablic scene, right? So I think that we would have definitely used data fix genie. 

Speaker 2  (11:55)
I'm sorry, data bricks, gmeting, Jenny, Jenny. 

Speaker 1  (12:00)
Jin Jing? Ok, so the question is, just consider you are building a self-service, okay, text to insights interface. We are building that using data, executive or leadership teams. 

Speaker 1  (12:17)
Okay? So the data platform, it is featuring a very complex gold layer with many to many relationships like it could be a combination of accounts to subscriptions. To use whatsoever. 

Speaker 1  (12:30)
It's a complex state. So when they execute, when the execution teams is basically asking genie, complex financial queries, what happens is the underlying LLM is frequently hallucinating. Okay? 

Speaker 1  (12:45)
So by generating like incorrect sequel joints or it is it is presenting the metrics or the kps, for example, let me take arr annual recurring revenue okay so the definition of AR R varies from team to team correct? 

Speaker 2  (13:01)
Error ok. 

Speaker 1  (13:03)
ARRARR animal recurrent revenue is an example of a API. Okay, so my question is like how do you design a very robust semantic layer using the unity catalogue metric views, you have the unity catalytic views right to constrain a data bricks genius, explain how you basically use this primary to foreign key constraints. You have the local knowledge stores curuted, sequery examples within the geni to generate or guarantee that it is executing and giving at least like 99% or 98% accurate response. 

Speaker 2  (13:48)
Ok, so what I'm understanding is we have a tool with the feature table, right? So that it is taking the data from that tool, basically the agent which is geni, and at the end, it is hallucinating with that data, correct? 

Speaker 1  (14:05)
Basically hallucinating because of the complexity of the data Because of the complexity when the executive team, if they're asking for any questions, it is basically handicating and it is not generating the correct response at all. And it is misinterpreting the kbi values like AR or it is giving a different value than what I'm expecting. So like this, all this is happening in the backyard. 

Speaker 1  (14:29)
So basically the question is, like, how do you basically? Create a creative layer using the unity catalogue metric views to constrain a database genius, or explain, like, how do you basic? I mean, just walk through the architecture that is enough. 

Speaker 2  (14:46)
Yeah, I mean ok, so we have the feature table in between then, we have to design the semantic layer, right? Which is actually on the retrieval side. We need to check what documents we are retrieving. 

Speaker 2  (14:57)
So basically the top K we need to check and if it is still the ragas evolution matrices, okay where we can check the recession and the recall value of the generated text and the actual text that it needs to be generated. So we have to find tune that value. Um, so that's if we have the embedding layer and then the vector dv, and then we have the retrieval layer. 

Speaker 2  (15:28)
Okay so on the retrieval layer also what I can think is that I have seen I can add the metaprompts in between, because if we have the correct data from in the input, then only we will go to have the correct output. Okay. So initially in the initial layer, I will figure it out okay if I can restrict my metaprompts of with only the cost. 

Speaker 2  (15:54)
And then I can guarantee it with, let's say, if it is not able to find that response, just tell that it okay, the data didn't form something so on the initial air I will do that. And on the retrieval side I'll increase the top K okay, and also I will try some other approaches where I can figure out whether the document that I'm retrieving can be diversified or not. If it is diversified, I'll try to restrict it. 

Speaker 2  (16:23)
Uh, there are several parameters like in the land chain in the search type. We can add that so I'll figure out the issue on the retrieval side on the embedding side. So once these all are fixed, then I'll move on to the LLM side so 

Speaker 1  (16:42)
Okay, okay. So, have you haven't designed anything at risk at home, like for your previous projects? Anything very similar to this? 

Speaker 1  (16:49)
Yes. 

Speaker 2  (16:50)
However, do you using any current project only? 

Speaker 1  (16:53)
So what is the use case? 

Speaker 2  (16:55)
Use cases that we have the several documents that has been organised based documentation that has been injecting into the D lt tables. We have the long transcripts, basically with all the chunks sizes, then we have the embedding layer. And then we have the user. 

Speaker 2  (17:14)
Basically we are in the chat box. Okay of that internal documentation. The Queen. 

Speaker 1  (17:22)
Okay, okay, got it. Okay. And what is the success rate? 

Speaker 1  (17:25)
I mean, is it hallucinating or what kind of issues do you face when we were Fine-tuning it? 

Speaker 2  (17:30)
Yeah, initially we have basically we have the ARB team where we have where we send the sample of data to the SMS to label it. And then we fine-tune that data again with the model. So we have the multiple model versions there. 

Speaker 2  (17:47)
So that's how which is back-and-forth, with the SMS team to find tune it. 

Speaker 1  (17:51)
Ok, and also like the kps which I'm telling you right? For example, the client with whom I work with there are 800 plus odd kpa and the kpa definition is not the same across the teams. So for example, lifetime value of a customer or annual recurring revenue. 

Speaker 1  (18:11)
It would be. It would be in one way in one team, and it would be in a different way in another team, right? So the definition of that particular metric, so in these cases, if you are creating a Chatbot on top of it there are high chances that it might misinterpret and give you a wrong response, right. 

Speaker 1  (18:31)
So, have you resolved any such scenarios earlier? 

Speaker 2  (18:38)
Yeah, I mean, as I told you we have the SMS, right? They will automatically say human in the loop, so basically they are validating the relevance, correctness and accuracy of the data. Okay, and based on their feedback we find tuna our chatbots. 

Speaker 1  (18:53)
No okay. So basically it's through human. And the look only you try to do it right. 

Speaker 1  (18:57)
Okay. So what we did is we created a unified store on top of that. So weren't with the different definitions from each team, we correlated it aggregated it and nature that we greater unified metric store, okay, unified store on top of that particular data. 

Speaker 1  (19:16)
And that is being fed to the lm, which is going to give you the response so that at least the value of arr or L Tr whatever I'm trying to see it would be the same cross the portal. So that's what we're trying we're trying to do as well, fine, okay. So just moving on, you know, about mosaic AI. 

Speaker 1  (19:35)
Agent right mosc, yeah, so just consider you are deploying an enterprise, AI supervisor agent using the mosaic AI agent framework. Okay, so this agent uses various functions to very the gold table containing sensitive HR, as well as financial information across different global subsidies. Okay so there is a strict compliant rule to us stating that LLM, agent acting on behalf of a manager in Europe must never see or use data belonging to an employee in a different region right now America or something like that. 

Speaker 1  (20:17)
I mean, email should not say airpa. Airpa should not see emia and so on. Okay. 

Speaker 1  (20:22)
So how do you natively use the unity catalogue? Row filter and column mass to enforce data level security on a mosaic AI model serving endpoint. Because I know, with unity catalogue, you know, the column asking dynamic views is what we create on top of it, but since mosign AI architecture is also being used. 

Speaker 1  (20:47)
I would like to know like how do you basically use the native feature of unity catalogue on top of mosaic AI models serving input? How do you ensure that when the LLM orchestrates a tool call or executes a vector search, the users passing or token security filters the data at the storage level, preventing what I prompt injection. 

Speaker 2  (21:12)
Yeah, I'm in the united catalogue. We have the restriction of the region. Okay there we can go at the Government and the line is basically all those 3 so basically they automatically filter out the region. 

Speaker 2  (21:26)
Okay? And once we at any query into the geni or something, it will automatically figure out what region we are computing and if it is it has the restriction, it will automatically tell that 

Speaker 1  (21:41)
But how is that user to region mapping done? Do we wrote for individual users, or is it through that, sir, because we have user groups, right? Indian, tabrics, suppose you not be an individual. 

Speaker 1  (21:54)
You will be part of maybe data, scientist group or malops group something like that, right? So how do you basically do that map? 

Speaker 2  (22:03)
Yeah, not sure about it, but One second. Sure. See in the unitic catalogue itself We have them different matters. 

Speaker 2  (22:19)
Workspaces, work spaces matters Meta store also, so the Meta store side. We can restrict. We're not sure. 

Speaker 1  (22:30)
Turn on not on this question. So generally wanted to understand that, from a data security and governance perspective, what are best practices have you followed when you are architecting this? 

Speaker 2  (22:45)
Yeah, I'm in at the end. We are Delta sharing the data. Okay. 

Speaker 2  (22:51)
Also, we have some on the catalogue side. We have the risk on for the users for the um. For the growth. 

Speaker 2  (23:03)
Basically, also on the on the production side. Also, we have restriction, also, we are doing the masking. As you told column masking row level filter. 

Speaker 2  (23:14)
We have, yes, so these are things. 

Speaker 1  (23:19)
Oh, ok, so basically, is there a segregation in your team between Pi and nonbi data? Do you use different catalogues? Or how is that basically he assigned? 

Speaker 1  (23:27)
Is there a catalogue segregation? 

Speaker 2  (23:29)
Action, yeah, there is a catalogue. Segregation, correct. 

Speaker 1  (23:33)
Oh, ok, so then Pi data cannot be accessed by Eos, apart from the ones who have access to that particular group. Okay, I get it. So just moving on I also wanted to understand your perspective on the compute, not with respect to AI and all so in general there will be workflows right in database so are you using service because I see the survival is eruption rate is huge nowadays. 

Speaker 1  (24:00)
People have started adopting this service. So what are your thoughts on it like if you have to do a comparison between survival is and the watch up compute whatever we create right so which one do you prefer and which one do you think is better as well? 

Speaker 2  (24:15)
Yeah, on the streets, some of the functionality does not work. Okay even if the code doesn't work. I figure high when we have written some workflows like I recently faced that issue where the cache was not working ok in the server. 

Speaker 2  (24:30)
But for the small tasks, we can use the server less. But we have, if we have the huge data so we need to come up with the specifically, we have to align some job compute to that task. Or that workflow, and then we can find, I mean, we can add lot of configuration there on the job compute, rather than the services. 

Speaker 1  (24:56)
Okay, okay, I get it. Okay fine. And like, what is the volume of data you have to keep them on a day-to-day basis? 

Speaker 2  (25:04)
It's in the 500 GB, more than 500 GB. 

Speaker 1  (25:09)
And at you have cross account region, or how is it 

Speaker 2  (25:14)
Cross app. 

Speaker 1  (25:15)
Crazy account is nothing but region, and also it's just going to understand like disaster and recovery. Like how is that basically set up 

Speaker 2  (25:22)
Yeah, I mean that's a different team who is Admin team who is managing all those things, so I'm not pretty sure about it. 

Speaker 1  (25:32)
And what about DevOps devops? I mean, the cicd and all, is it get up actions or get clear? 

Speaker 2  (25:37)
What is that GitHub, GitHub when Jenkins 

Speaker 1  (25:41)
Are you involving that or there is a separate team for reduction? 

Speaker 2  (25:46)
I mean, not on the production side because on the production side, we have to either release notes and there's somebody from our team or maybe some other team. They will going to run those commands. 

Speaker 1  (25:57)
Oh, okay. Okay. I get it so it's a different process altogether for production And so, whatever data you deal with, it's completely structured semi structured as well as unstructured. 

Speaker 1  (26:11)
Since you also have AI. So I mean, the text and their building and all correct? 

Speaker 2  (26:16)
Yeah, it's unstructured and semi semi structured, busy. 

Speaker 1  (26:19)
Semi structure, basically, ok, fine. Okay? I also wanted to discuss with respect to the feature drift, right? 

Speaker 1  (26:26)
I think we discussed this earlier as well. But just consider, we have an automated productionised dlt pipeline. Okay, so it's feeding a gold feature table. 

Speaker 1  (26:39)
Okay, the drives and online recommendation system. So, you know, some kind of external marketing campaign, incoming user behaviour changes drastically over a week. Example, like purchases value, double or triple something like that. 

Speaker 1  (26:56)
Okay, the pipeline is not painting. Because there are no nulls or steama changes. Okay? 

Speaker 1  (27:03)
So uh, but this change in the data distribution, which is basically a feature drift. Right, causes the downstream AI model's accuracy to reduce. Okay. 

Speaker 1  (27:14)
So basically, like how do you design self-healing infrastructure using dlt expectations, or it could be Delta table history, cdf and custom custom monitoring scripts for this kind of lakehouse monitoring? To basic, basically trying to understand is there a way to automatically quarantine? The data alert them alops fall back to a safe mechanism, something like that. 

Speaker 2  (27:46)
Yeah, I mean, if it's a conceptual druft, we are talking about right? So basically the feature have the dependencies with the actual target column, right? Correct? 

Speaker 2  (27:55)
So We have to do the again we need to I mean I am not sure about the auto prune that, but we need to check the features basically, if it is earlier, the feature were different. Dependencies were different. Now we have to come up with a different feature so we need to do the Ed on that, but not sure what the auto 

Speaker 1  (28:20)
Okay, yeah, okay. Okay. So basically I'm just trying to understand like if there is a way to create a self-healing pipeline for this, which is going to automatically attract the data data. 

Speaker 1  (28:35)
So basically this is not a workflow trip, right? So workflow is not going to fail at any point in time, so just the data profiling drift and use those metrics to trigger your conditional dlt, the tasks to alert them by flow. 

Speaker 2  (28:51)
Yeah, enamel flow itself. We can have multiple. We can log multiple features, or the multiple models we can add it, we have to log it, and there we can check the hype we can hypertune all those features again, but not sure. 

Speaker 2  (29:10)
If it be done automatically, I am not sure. 

Speaker 1  (29:16)
Ok. Ok, fine, I get it. I get it okay. 

Speaker 1  (29:19)
I also wanted to ask like, have you also worked on architecting a multimodal RAG? 

Speaker 2  (29:27)
I didn't get chance. 

Speaker 1  (29:30)
You didn't get a chance, right? Okay, just give a try like with your experiences. Tell me like how would you basically design it that is more than enough? 

Speaker 1  (29:39)
So consider your organisation, it's operating across multiple Separate data prices workspace, so you have separate workspace. For staging navy, a work production free, broad enterprise data, something like that. Okay, so you have gold layer table containing multimodal metadicata like text blog, it has images, audio transcripts, and so on, so that is residing in maybe the staging workspace or workspace, a just for an ease. 

Speaker 1  (30:11)
Okay? So the AI team in workspace B needs to convert this into a vector search index, but copying that terravites of data over cloud region is very huge. Right, so I want to understand like how do you architect? 

Speaker 1  (30:30)
A cross workspace data delivery layer using unity catalogue. Central governments to expose a workspace goal data to B without physically duplicating defice. Like basically on the you can also answer from your experience with spaths, spark. 

Speaker 1  (30:49)
Based like chunking and token counting wrapping all these concepts, we have right so within the Delta pipeline to guarantee no data is sent to database vector search ever trunkets, or causes an API limit error. 

Speaker 2  (31:04)
Yeah, sure, so ok, so as you told me that we have the unstructured data, right? So at the end, we need to make it structure in a way that let's say the data is coming on the gsm format. Okay so we cannot chunk the data in between we have to have some context, so we need to make the contextual data. 

Speaker 2  (31:26)
Let's say one product, okay. We have lot of description lot of features. Everything so that we need to create one chunk per chunk ID ok, um, with all the details added there with from from that document. 

Speaker 2  (31:42)
If it has images or everything we need to use the simple text track, basically and that will automatically convert all the things into tax and text to the structured format data. Along with that, we have to figure out the chunk size chunk size should map it with a chunk tokens. Tokens should be appropriate enough, otherwise will give the error and then we have to okay once we have the chance ready. 

Speaker 2  (32:16)
Then, we can go to the embedding layer embedding layer to the Web family retrievers, everything in between. We can have the LLM also, if it is, if we don't want to, if we have the cost, if we can increase the, but we can adjust smaller LLM model to summarise the context. 

Speaker 1  (32:37)
Okay, okay, fine, I get it. But yeah, there are we also do the same thing, but it was a long route. But we had to take it them into for us. 

Speaker 1  (32:47)
Yeah Yeah, apart from all these things. Right, I also wanted to understand like if you're manageing the team or you know, you are icing. 

Speaker 2  (32:59)
Currently, my story, but I've worked on myself. 

Speaker 1  (33:03)
Ok, what was your team size? 

Speaker 2  (33:05)
Team size size was eight people. $5 for 3 kg. 

Speaker 1  (33:11)
Okay, okay, I get it. Okay, like apart from this, when you're also involved in the design of dashboarding like at the end of the day from cold air, it is anyways going to go to dashboard. So have we explored AI BI dashboard in data bricks or any other thing apart from that. 

Speaker 1  (33:27)
Like how do you basically? Operate there. 

Speaker 2  (33:30)
Yeah, we have the dashboard in the data tricks itself. So where we are using it. 

Speaker 1  (33:36)
Are you yours, aibi and touchbox that basically 

Speaker 2  (33:39)
Yeah 

Speaker 1  (33:42)
Okay, so is it better compared to tabi? Or how would you Yes, but I thought 

Speaker 2  (33:49)
Yeah, it's basically simpler than the power BI because we have to inject the data first there in the database. We have all the tables lined in. 

Speaker 1  (33:59)
Say data is impounded, I mean it doesn't go out so that is from a security concern. Also, it's really good, correct. Yeah, okay, I think I'm done with the interviewer, but do you have any questions? 

Speaker 2  (34:13)
Yeah, can you tell me about the roles and the technical stack? 

Speaker 1  (34:19)
It's completely data breaks. I mean, data bricks, architect and AI. So it's basically data breaks AI architect is how I would classify. 

Speaker 1  (34:30)
So you should have any deep expertise in data bricks tack, and also with all the recent features that the data bricks is providing mainly on the integration part as well. Right, so whatever AI architect, I told you are going to build. So how do you basically do that integration so mainly AI centric infrastructure design, so and also from a governance, as well as security perspective? 

Speaker 1  (34:57)
Have you written anything earlier? So this role demands that so in basically, data breaks AI expert? That's what I would classify is. 

Speaker 2  (35:07)
Understood. Yeah, I'm good. 

Speaker 1  (35:12)
Yeah, ok, thank you so much. I'm completely, thanks. Bye. 
