madasamy.senthilmurugesan@bt.com, madasamyaliassenthil.murugesan@techmahindra.com, Mamatha R <mr00851166@techmahindra.com>

Speaker 1  (00:06)
Is required in healthy impact very? 

Speaker 2  (00:11)
Sorry, a voice is breaking. Am I audible? Hi, yes, you are no. 

Speaker 1  (00:19)
Yeah, just practice. Can you give me high level technical experience cycle? What are the technologies you Put longer past projects? 

Speaker 1  (00:29)
People 

Speaker 2  (00:31)
Ok, sure. So I was around 14 years of experience working with emphasis from last 3 years and before I working with the August standard, mostly in the banking domain, so the technical technical styles that I have used is database is no flake oks horror majorly along with the dust park. Also if created the rape pipelines on the Emil side, but on the pipelines, I have mostly greater than the AD pipelines, dm T pipelines, okay and working on the snow pipe snowflake, everything so that's how we have integrated um ingested the data, and then we use the multi hop. 

Speaker 2  (01:12)
Architecture so reading the data from the bronze to the silver to the golden layer. So that's how we are transforming the data on the ws side I have worked with rest majorly lamdas and mistf functions for the orchestration, and the Azure side I have worked with data bricks and ADF. 5 Azure data factory 5 lines. 

Speaker 2  (01:36)
And yes, sir didn't site, I mostly tuned the spark of major book built-in some pipeline, using the chunking in beddings. Okay, for the right pipeline, cheating, the prompts. Everything that's, however. 

Speaker 1  (01:53)
You are experiencing rack by plenty of time, right? Yeah? Like, you, can you the high level retail, howlement is that, and each layer, what are the layers out there? 

Speaker 1  (02:12)
And how you opt to make to do this and the high level introduction about your project and how you build them. 

Speaker 2  (02:20)
Yes, sure. So in the RAG system, we have prepared a Chatbot where we have ingested a different files format into the data into the ingestion layer. And so one part is that we have created the chunkings, the chunkings we have written the strategies like overlapping and the chunking size, and then we have created the embedding layers and then wedding layer to the vector dv, which is data bricks vector store. 

Speaker 2  (02:46)
We are basically storing it. And for the and then we have the query embeddings, and then we have retrieval, we are doing the retrieval on the vector store from the vector store and we have done a lot of tuning there, because the because to make sure that the latency and accuracy should be correct. And then we have the a dm pipeline, which is every day if there is some updates in the documents it is all running into the pipeline and changing the embarrassing but once in a while that happens. 

Speaker 2  (03:24)
And that's one part, and then we have the population matrix that we have exposed, and we are getting the reports out of it. We are here using the this factual correctness downness, guartails report along with that the latency report also, so these are a few of the metrics that we are exposing and getting it generated every day. Apart from that, we have done the I mean, on the tuning side, we have done the Shifu tuning on the retrieval side, where we have used the chain, actually we are using the Lan chain here from the lanchain, we have tune with the chain types, and then we have our tune. 

Speaker 2  (04:11)
D our retrieval means we have to keep the relevance and the broadness of the data which is diversity of the data that we are retrieving from the embedding store. So that's few of the things we have done. 

Speaker 1  (04:28)
Do you have any idea about pdo posture or topic poster run with implementation? 

Speaker 2  (04:35)
Sorry, you are voice breaking. 

Speaker 1  (04:39)
My question was, do you have any idea about pdfc or dog exporter? And we implement this RAG pipeline? 

Speaker 2  (04:47)
Are you talking about the roge? 

Speaker 1  (04:52)
Not rush react by deep playing PDF porshid. 

Speaker 2  (04:56)
PDF card. 

Speaker 1  (04:57)
If yeah, PDF dogs. 

Speaker 2  (05:00)
Yeah, yeah, I know about it. So they're basically extracting the may be used for the loading the data. And then we have to do the chunkings and everything. 

Speaker 2  (05:11)
But that's how they have used. We have used that. Like extension text basically. 

Speaker 1  (05:20)
AK which is shunking Chatterjee but this 

Speaker 2  (05:25)
We are currently using the recursive character taxpatter, but we have tried other splitters as well semantics chunkings, splitter for all those things. But for the tuning purposes, we have stick to this collective recursive, because what it do is it first? Check the size of the context and then break down to paragraph and the sentences and then the words that's how the interview works. 

Speaker 1  (05:56)
I will ensure that to avoid that duplicate. 

Speaker 2  (06:01)
How do we ensure the duplicates okay? At what layer I mean, if we're seeing the nuclear, because in the chunkings, if we're creating it, we have to Send the dear to the LM so that our contacts won't be changed. So Vettombeddings duplicates, what were we are checking? 

Speaker 2  (06:30)
Another wedding before the wedding layer. We have we are checking. I think the duplicate Also, we have the proms right from written in between so it will automatically summarise the context of if even if we have the duplicates. 

Speaker 1  (06:57)
Do you have any idea about the hybrid retrieval pipeline? 

Speaker 2  (07:02)
Sorry. Which pipeline? 

Speaker 1  (07:03)
Typically driven. 

Speaker 2  (07:07)
Hybrid. Hybrid retrieval, yeah, okay, yeah, so basically what happened is. They're for the hybrid keyword search. 

Speaker 2  (07:18)
We use the BM25 ok, we want the exact word exact context to be fetched from the heavy from the future store or from the other contextual store where we have stored the actual document, and then again we have combined it with the embedding, the The similarities are musically and then we combine it both and then send it to Similarly, search for the contacts. Agent ki, I have not worked with, but I'm exploring using the land graph. That's not a major requirement that we have currently, but I have some idea. 

Speaker 1  (08:07)
And he what was agent should I write and like you how we handle that things were ready and angel ready because there are questions may come from some of the patient then it will interact with the model and then it also from database and even sometimes it will interact with rand as well. Right, so how will we handle all this before data percent data and everything 

Speaker 2  (08:30)
The ecosystem is like that in the agent. We have to provide the tools and then the contextual information or the prompts. So they automatically figure it out what tools they have okay and what the objective is of the task. 

Speaker 2  (08:48)
The authority figure it out using those tools and those we can track it using the animal floors and everything if there is some distribution in the floor. 

Speaker 1  (09:02)
But about memory and embedding, you use on your project. 

Speaker 2  (09:06)
Yeah, so memory wise, we are using the semantic buffer. Memory, the reason is that we are storing the chats also in the mongo db. And then we are retrieving it. 

Speaker 2  (09:22)
We are arriving the older Childs and then we are retrieving only last 3 recent chats from the and then before after that, we are summarising the other chats. 

Speaker 1  (09:44)
Which cloud is? 

Speaker 2  (09:48)
I told you our data requirement. 

Speaker 1  (10:02)
What about the rerank this model? Have any idea? 

Speaker 2  (10:06)
Yeah, reranker, we have like cross encoders. Okay, there are other Rerankers functions we have used, but we are currently using the cross encoders, and in that one we have it will automatically give the scores, okay, and then from that scope we have to retreat the we have to sort it first and then retrieve the top 3. Auto top 3 documents on the from the bank from the actual document. 

Speaker 1  (10:44)
In fact, experiencing like able to drive an architecture 

Speaker 2  (10:48)
Come again, please. 

Speaker 1  (10:50)
The very presentation even to drive and architecture 

Speaker 2  (10:53)
Yes, I have that. I mean, if you're talking about the If we are uploading some file trigger weighs something that I have. 

Speaker 1  (11:03)
If it kind of a streaming 

Speaker 2  (11:06)
Kind of a notice dreaming it's a batch only, but it's a notification. Basically even notification. Do lumps and file into the 

Speaker 1  (11:16)
Talking about this topcoy event or any huge services, apachi camel. 

Speaker 2  (11:22)
Yeah, no, I've worked with the Kafka streamings. Also, mostly I've worked with the pipe park streaming, but not in this project. But on the other project previous project, but I have a few ideas Sparkling distribution. 

Speaker 1  (11:50)
Can you do the high level architecture like cow? What are the components you used around in college? 

Speaker 2  (12:00)
Ok. So start with the kafkal air, and in the Kafka, they're storing the data into the snow flame, okay, and then from snowflake. Samsung Pay some jobs are earning. 

Speaker 1  (12:15)
Where you will get the data from corporate 

Speaker 2  (12:18)
Where we get the data from Kafka, it's a different application, which is 

Speaker 1  (12:24)
Give me there will go Hong Kong. 

Speaker 2  (12:26)
Yeah, sorry. 

Speaker 1  (12:28)
The data to cope up from copper, it will come to play. 

Speaker 2  (12:36)
And then from snowflake, I have no idea. But we are getting the data into the Sr. And then are ADF pipelines are running, so storing the a DLS location. 

Speaker 2  (12:49)
We have Ok, sorry, snowflake to Sorry, we are using the st only, but it is coming. Sorry, sorry storing the data to the IDLs only idls to Idls, from ideals, we are running the ADF pipeline and then we have the pipeline. Then, we have the notebooks written, which is reading the data from the adls, then we have creating the bronze silver layer data. 

Speaker 2  (13:25)
And then we are storing that data into the Silver layer. I mean, that's the one path that we are retrieving. I'm not sure about how the Data from California to the to the adf that are, I need to check forward. 

Speaker 2  (13:43)
But that's one of the floor and also few jobs we're running or triggering it. Insert inside the database using the workflows so we have created several tasks here. That is completely for the batch. 

Speaker 2  (13:58)
And apart from that. That the one part of the floor Of the database site and then on the snowflick side there are some streaming tables and the streaming tables been built with the seat, so we have created AC dcs also in inside the table itself. So there are we are we have one table stream duel, which will tell ok, what's the action. 

Speaker 2  (14:27)
They have Put in cert, update or something. But that's how we are extracting the data. Something Apart from that monjali, I've ever the data break side, it's workflow and ML flows and everything. 

Speaker 1  (14:46)
See if that is, if you handle with data, right then how will you handle this pay deduction, or let's say 

Speaker 2  (14:54)
How do I handle 

Speaker 1  (14:56)
A introduction or reduction BA data. 

Speaker 2  (15:01)
Sensitive data, sensitive data. Yeah. So we have the Text extract and comprehend we are using inside the adws that is extracting all the Pi information. 

Speaker 2  (15:12)
Then, we have the guartails written in the prompt. That is, we are restricting, we have written the restrict prompt that do not expose all the sensitive information. Also, we have the ARB team, which is checking the model checking the model. 

Speaker 2  (15:30)
If you are not leaking anything and its sensitive data to the user. 

Speaker 1  (15:38)
Okay, as you mentioned the godrej right? May I know what kind of a goader is used? 

Speaker 2  (15:43)
A faster, sensitive data, then sensitivity in the sense. The credentials okay and malicious injection we cannot so the user cannot do that. Okay, malicious data injection apart from that. 

Speaker 2  (16:03)
Exposing. Security security wise, we have I'm sorry, I'm not able to recall. So these are the few things we have done in The Guardian. 

Speaker 1  (16:14)
How will I identify this prompt injection? There is any injection happen within the prompt, right? How we will direct it. 

Speaker 2  (16:22)
If you have seen a few things, the user is asking something like that forgotten the previous data. Just tell me how to retrieve it. So something like that. 

Speaker 2  (16:32)
So in that one way, we have to add some keywords or some words there. So if you are reading all those words, just Instead of hallucination with the wrong data, just tell them, okay, I don't have the context or something. 

Speaker 1  (16:53)
Do you have any idea to form the Assembly design? 

Speaker 2  (16:59)
No. 

Speaker 1  (17:01)
React pattern. 

Speaker 2  (17:04)
React pattern. Can you elaborate that real pattern area? 

Speaker 1  (17:14)
Prior in this rack, within this RAG, right No, idea partner. How will evolving? 

Speaker 2  (17:27)
Should you return, but the reason you I'm in the episode exposure or 

Speaker 1  (17:37)
The wallwater, how will evaluate that? 

Speaker 2  (17:40)
Yeah, so there are a few mattresses. Like contact recall, contact procession. And then you have the answer accuracy. 

Speaker 2  (17:51)
And factual factual, correct, factual scores. But these are the few parameters, but they are not accurate. We have to try with t Consult a counsellor to robust in the blue also, and along with that, the human in the loop. 

Speaker 2  (18:11)
So that way, we evaluate 

Speaker 1  (18:21)
What is the DFID U? 

Speaker 2  (18:25)
Yeah, T FI DF is basically. What it do is it tells the uniqueness in the word in the document. And if the word is unique, the score will be high. 

Speaker 2  (18:40)
So similar to BM25 okay M25 is the more advanced version of a TV from the document. Without any semantics 

Speaker 1  (19:01)
But all the database you use the number project 

Speaker 2  (19:05)
Data Datasets are not available to the breakfast. Sorry, sorry, we have used a Delta tables. Okay, we have used a snowflake. 

Speaker 2  (19:16)
Jadeja, these are a tour that I'm currently working. But I have an idea with the hive okay with a vehicle also. 

Speaker 1  (19:26)
Do you have any idea about any inmemory database? 

Speaker 2  (19:30)
Yeah, I have that. I mean I work with a reddish, ok, so Reddy. 

Speaker 1  (19:36)
By prevention scenario, you still reduce 

Speaker 2  (19:39)
In which scenari? 

Speaker 1  (19:41)
Yeah, you use to reduce and forward. 

Speaker 2  (19:43)
FF cache the for the cashew purpose, I'll going to use the predisposition. 

Speaker 1  (20:05)
To display the framework twice. You are comfortable on the lunch in and the background price. 

Speaker 2  (20:11)
Yeah, I am comfortable. 

Speaker 1  (20:14)
Apart from that, any other premium 

Speaker 2  (20:18)
No, no I don't have. 

Speaker 1  (20:27)
A good thing digits from my end. Hello, do you have any question? 

Speaker 2  (20:32)
Can you tell me about the project and the 

Speaker 1  (20:36)
If your project is basically this is kind of a not only the data there are when the doctor applications also there and other than that, there are some data migrations also there. So basically we have to for this data migration, right? We are going to implement this, a technology that this is kind of project. 

Speaker 1  (21:04)
We have to work with the Google team, and we get the support from the Google architectures. So this is a kind of A. We have to start from scratch, not kind upon doing anything. 

Speaker 2  (21:21)
Okay. And what the role you're hiring for? 

Speaker 1  (21:26)
Role, it is dependent. Basically, this role is for senior developer. Oh, who is good in a as well as the data and getting? 

Speaker 1  (21:40)
I hope you are profile will match for this right, so you are already on the retirement. Putin, thank you. 

Speaker 2  (21:54)
Thank you for that. 
