
Tinu Purushothaman <tinu.purushotham@tigeranalytics.com>

Speaker 1  (00:03)
When are you right now? 

Speaker 2  (00:06)
Yeah, currently, Noida, working with emphasis 

Speaker 1  (00:18)
So So I'm by sirf, ran Kumar. Yeah, I'm part of SSS last one year. We're building a team, right? 

Speaker 1  (00:31)
We're looking for the candidates who are getting, you know, not only in jail, but they have also got experience in traditional Machine Learning strategies like traditional analysis material analysis time series analysis forecasting. They are good, they have hands-on agentic framework design right? Fine-tuning. 

Speaker 1  (00:58)
And also do have Thank you, assistant who has got not only they focused on delivery, but they have The ability to think out of the box to some innovative innovative work, and you know, come up with new solution, more efficient solution, and if that we can sell is ready for publication, they are allowed to publish your work. So you can also be capable of generating IP for the Organisers. So can you tell me something about yourself? 

Speaker 1  (01:49)
Your education, your belongings projects. Have you done your challenges? You faced. 

Speaker 1  (01:59)
I don't know. 

Speaker 2  (02:03)
So I've run 14 years of experience working with t 

Speaker 2  (02:18)
Initial days I have started with a detailed diet, and then I'm primarily working on the geni. I have worked on the 20th working on the application, which is moved to the Diagnostic test done by the students have been seen by the teacher taken test accordingly. From that application, we have a web chat dots if we have created where we are using the Idiom, pipelines and data books measure It is internal application. 

Speaker 2  (03:04)
And apart from that, I was extensively on this far data, blues and compromise vibration, I have prompromise to digital groups. 

Speaker 2  (03:27)
We are getting the Cheers. And there's 500 months of psi. 

Speaker 1  (03:43)
Tokensu, let's start with your one of your project. Can you discuss any of your projects that That you think it was complex for you. What was your challenges? 

Speaker 2  (04:01)
Yeah, sure, so currently I'm working on the application, which is going to chat box creation, I can talk about that. So we're getting the data from the Kafka. Okay, with a multiple file formats, we're receiving it on a daily basis, and we have the Other file system also comes into picture, which is as 3 and ADs. 

Speaker 2  (04:26)
So from there we are having this ADF pipeline created And we're getting those data, and when we are having a land chain, which is doing the first chunking, this chunking layer, it is fitting the database on sentences, and then we have the metring layer, which is doing the metding of their tokens, and then we are storing in them into the vector stock. So that's a great pipeline, which runs daily to check whether incrementally, we are loading And by weekly, we're thinking the data with t Nicky, show that it's not still. 

Speaker 2  (05:09)
Then we have the retrieval system independent language where we are having the I encoders on the encoder state for the re ranking, and before that, we're searching it based on the dense and the spars. Data on the dance part, we are doing the cocaine similarity, and on the Sparks wear using ABM 25, so we're combining them with a 7030 ratio. Then we're getting the documentation of the context. 

Speaker 2  (05:41)
And then we are doing the buy encoters. We are present because the document is huge. And then we are a plenty of Crossing order to retrieve the top K and a top P. 

Speaker 2  (05:57)
And then yeah, there's a query user can query, and also, we are exposing multiple matrices like Please accuracy call contacts faithfulness, answer relevance and Definition rate NDC values 

Speaker 1  (06:16)
You know, can you visit? Can you kill the visualisation of correct pipeline? Pipeline live on its pipeline. 

Speaker 2  (06:30)
Syria dedication. 

Speaker 1  (06:32)
R AG is Arg.. private care to discuss. 

Speaker 2  (06:36)
Yeah, this is what I'm talking about, right so retrieval layer and the generation layer. So first thing I talked about a generation layer and then I was talking about the retrieval. 

Speaker 1  (06:46)
I've been bought, but what was your strategy? What was your medical strategy? 

Speaker 2  (06:52)
Yeah, so told you right in the Chunky strategy we are doing Context is Britain, and that's the changing strategy, and then we have the embedding layer, which is doing the embedding of the tokens, again we are using the BG layer B. G. Sorry, BG model for doing the embeddings. 

Speaker 2  (07:16)
Also, we are doing the context compression where we're doing the high. We are using the high approach where the user query is getting generated with the answer through the LLM for the small model, and then we are comparing those small answer with the actual context that is there in Earth and wedding, so we are comparing this because the User can query any wake wake query. Also, there is a prompting in between before descending it to the LM where we're gartelling it with. 

Speaker 2  (07:49)
Uh, the security layer first, which is masking the Pi layer. Okay, and your other offensive words. We're filtering out some animal is also there. 

Speaker 2  (08:05)
Apart from that, we are garteling it with the output also the same thing, and if it does not know any answer, we are doing. The we are promoting in such a way that it can, it should not answer the vague queries and once this is done, then we are sending it to the lm to get the response and send it across to the user. So that's the one of the part mattresses, as I told you multiple matrices, we are exposing it, the challenge that we are faced with the incremental data that is coming across to the multiple layers to the idea of pipeline and it's all triggered base, basically with the ST and the adls. 

Speaker 2  (08:45)
So sometimes the pipelines got failed with some timeout and everything, so we have to see the whether it's a cluster issue or a code issue, and if we have to check whether it's A Data is still or something. So all those fine-tuning usually do I also worked on the other stuff, which is uh fine. During the actual module using the best okay, and So those kind of things I have done but the other challenge that I have faced, because all the things are in production. 

Speaker 2  (09:26)
So we come across with latency issues, okay, so we have to choose whether we need the accuracy or that relatency, so we have to make sure there is a trade-off between them. We prefer accuracy when the latency because it is more internal chatbots, which require, which needs to serve the exact model exact exact text to the user. Okay? 

Speaker 2  (09:51)
So 

Speaker 1  (09:52)
Maybe maybe this is not the issue. This lethalcy is not the issue of your friend design, but the RAG. I mean Not retrieval, but the RAG design you have done that is the issue. 

Speaker 1  (10:12)
Do you think like do you think like? If there are information or hidden after multiple documentation, like one document and second document and other document, then maybe that way there it is hidden and your factor. Drag is not able to capture through those Do you know number of litresence? 

Speaker 1  (10:39)
What do you think? How can you think of any other strategy any other kind of rank you get involved in? You can design 

Speaker 2  (10:48)
Yeah, then we can trade the age end, but in our case, it is not required. What I understood. 

Speaker 1  (10:55)
Dot agent is different. Yeah, no I am saying that ok, you created the vector graph you, whatever search indexing, relanking, dragas, tuning, everything you have done even after that, you for roll your RAG system, you again, do some other strategy like TP where you years that again, check their LLM parameters also optimizer, still, your letters is high, right? But generally, it may be the case that your RAG is not responding very well. 

Speaker 1  (11:37)
That's right. So what other study you can think of? So this is always the case of accuracy. 

Speaker 1  (11:47)
And letency, that is through our right Right? Any other strategy of RAG? Any other kind of no. 

Speaker 1  (12:00)
There are multiple rags nowadays that has been evolved. So I just want to know, so if you have to design another RAG that can handle this, or can you do that? 

Speaker 2  (12:17)
Another drag, I mean. 

Speaker 1  (12:19)
See the black strategy architecture. Other than Victor you can move for 

Speaker 2  (12:28)
Yeah, men to the other way would be like. We can simply use the problem prompts. And their lm, that's the simple way to This is all, I mean, we can hit it prompt, and we can send it to the LM and generate the answer that's the easiest way to do it, but for the searching. 

Speaker 2  (12:49)
Okay, let me think it that way. What the user want? It's as a tool, as you said. 

Speaker 2  (12:57)
Latencies, that doesn't matter right? Should not be the case of latency or accuracy. See if there's an issue, I'll check whether it's a generational issue or a retrieval issue if there is an issue, right? 

Speaker 2  (13:13)
SHOW. Do you do any talk about the issues or do? Are you looking for some other patterns of the rat? 

Speaker 1  (13:27)
You told that you also word on fine-tuning, so what strategy did you use for fine-tuning? 

Speaker 2  (13:32)
Yeah, if you come, I mean, we have tuned with the Lora. Landoor ranked. Estimation, adopter, adaptation, sorry, luring adoption. 

Speaker 2  (13:49)
So that way we have all the vectors, we have quantized with the with a 4 bit, we have user cube, alright, basically, where we have contaized the vectors in the 4 bit of dimension. So that way, we have added the law again, who is compressed the memory size Of the movie? 

Speaker 1  (14:21)
So how you decide that, doctor And what is the captain? 

Speaker 2  (14:26)
Yeah, walking adopts adoption. The actual weights, but we're updating the updating the Delta weights of the of the model. So Basically, how it works internally is it? 

Speaker 2  (14:49)
There is a it checked the look up table. Okay, look up table where it is. Getting those numbers from the lookup table, which has actually the quantized value present. 

Speaker 2  (15:03)
Okay, I'm getting stored there for particular vectors, so it just matches with the nearest vector. And then it picked those values from the lookup table. Let's say says 07 and will 079. 

Speaker 2  (15:17)
It will look for 08 in the lookup table and fetch that value. So that's how we created the actual vector and then we store it with the context value of the fore weight. 

Speaker 1  (15:32)
To so how you recite the doctor size, how do I You decide that after size. 

Speaker 2  (15:40)
How do I adopt, so it's F? B sixth. We are using the FP16 value, and which has the 4 bit of quantiz vector. 

Speaker 1  (15:53)
That is quite quicker. Actually, I wonder what you know, art doctor is a metric simply in your sense. So yeah, so how you decide the dimension of this matrix. 

Speaker 2  (16:05)
How will I decide that dimensions? 

Speaker 1  (16:08)
And values of the metals 

Speaker 2  (16:11)
No, I mean dimensions are basically coming up from the model itself, which is 153 6 is by default. It's based on a model, we are choosing it. What's the vector accumulator we are contact with the normal values. 

Speaker 2  (16:31)
The hope I am making sense. 

Speaker 1  (16:56)
Very simple question. I have like Suppose that. But we're solving Large language models we are solving, you can say, sequential problem right. 

Speaker 1  (17:14)
This is the kind of sequential problem sequence. There is a sequence that you are solving, so input is a sequence. Then you are finding the output sequence, right? 

Speaker 1  (17:28)
It's a sick to sec model. Okay, so previously there are some of the models, like RAG based models. Have you heard about? 

Speaker 2  (17:38)
Ragas RG. 

Speaker 1  (17:40)
Sorry, sorry, no RNN based models. 

Speaker 2  (17:45)
Ok. 

Speaker 1  (17:49)
And your main model network In any bottle, if you know any R any model that were used 

Speaker 2  (17:58)
They're worked with CRN majorly. RNN are basically having the encoders and the decoders 

Speaker 1  (18:08)
But sorry it really not tolerance, no in decoder encoder. In rdm, you are talking about transformer. 

Speaker 2  (18:17)
No, but that is also having the 

Speaker 1  (18:22)
Do you know what is the basic difference between RNS and transformer team? Both are okay, tip neural network tip tip tip networks what is different between these 2 

Speaker 2  (18:34)
Okay, I can talk about the C. NN okay, which is having the Convocational layer, then they have the cooling layer. Okay, flattening layer, and then they have the Hidden layer, then there's a software function to generate the probability and then be answer. 

Speaker 2  (18:56)
Then the output Adjust a 3 × 3 m, basically create a for a image. It will create Arg.. value first okay, and then it will go to the other layers with a 3 + 3 matrices, it just take the maximum out of those 3 × 3 matrices, and then it work accordingly, and then it goes to the there is a sigmoid, there was a sigmoid function, which were using that utter parda, issue with the sigmoid function is that it will lead to Decrease the gradient, just give the constant value for the for. 

Speaker 1  (19:38)
Try to increase the vector Indian why this is great. 

Speaker 2  (19:45)
Pelu's actually taken the maximum value, because if they're all the 

Speaker 1  (19:50)
So what kind of what kind of network is this CNN? I will guess a feat for this forward or feedback network. 

Speaker 2  (20:05)
Sorry, straightforward. Beat forward. Seat, feed forward. 

Speaker 2  (20:12)
So it's not a feat forward, okay, because that's a part of the transformer 

Speaker 1  (20:28)
South, is there any pack propagation? In C? L? 

Speaker 1  (20:30)
No. Total, then it should be feed forward. 

Speaker 2  (20:36)
Currently, it's available to the feed forward. 

Speaker 1  (20:43)
If there is no backpropagation. If that is where RLN is? So is there any feat propagation in transformer? 

Speaker 2  (21:01)
No, there's no batter information in transformer. It's a part of the department part of the neural network network. But transformators are done. 

Speaker 1  (21:32)
Have you know about the self attention multi attention When we'll discuss about hisself, but his multitention. 

Speaker 2  (21:42)
Multiple region has multiple heads. So if I talk about the self attention, it will create 3 values, Q is the what it is. Looking for key is what value does it hold and V is the actual value? 

Speaker 2  (21:57)
And it goes to the transformation and Generating the attention score at the end. And with that attention score With that attention school, it goes into the soft mail function to generate the probability and then give the output and attentions, go multiply with the actual value. Sorry before sending it to the soft Max to generate the actual value. 

Speaker 2  (22:24)
This is one of the part of so we are there is a mathematical formula between which is I mean, there aren't multiplying with the Q and 2K and divided by the under root of the dimension of the of The Matrix matrices matrix, sorry dimension of The Matrix just to have This is the value do not explore So that's that's what I can recollect. And in the multi head, they are dividing it into the multiple on legs. For the QKV it will create multiple in the multiple head. 

Speaker 2  (23:13)
They will do the transformation in parallel. Subset of 128 128 hour. Just divide the whole input. 

Speaker 2  (23:24)
And number of facts 

Speaker 1  (23:37)
You, have you bought on time series? Uh, okay. Have you heard about? 

Speaker 1  (23:52)
Let's talk about some model performance traits. So you, I hope you know what is the concept traft model trapped? So do you know about the data leakage during training? 

Speaker 1  (24:14)
Yay. To how can you first to 40s? It actually 

Speaker 2  (24:20)
Yay, I mean miss, if I talk about the leakage. If we're training the whole data, okay? Then, there is a chance that the data can fall into the testing phase, and it will not be able to, because it already knows the output, there is no need to Train the there's no Okay, let me Refresh that so basically it has 2 type feature and the temporal in the feature type. 

Speaker 2  (24:53)
If we're having the data, they present in the test Sure, it will already know the output that it will be biassed. Our model will be biassed toward the actual output right? So that's the one way also on the temperature side, which is time. 

Speaker 2  (25:11)
Are we exposing any of the feature which can tell the actual output like refund? Okay, so let's say for the exam. For example, if the user is checking the status of the product and In the test phase, we already know the answer is refund. 

Speaker 2  (25:30)
Okay, so the model will be biassed toward the output. And for the time also, if it already knows, are we training the future data? So these are the few things that we need to consider it. 

Speaker 2  (25:44)
To make sure there is no leakage. 

Speaker 1  (25:48)
So what exactly is 

Speaker 2  (25:52)
I mean, I told you, right? It should not, our model should not be biassed. Because if it already knows the answer, it will be biassed over whatever we have inputted, so it should Predict on the new data, which is unknown to the training, which is unknown to the model on which the data has been trained. 

Speaker 2  (26:14)
As I gave you the example, right? So it should not know these actualist status. What we are predicting me. 

Speaker 1  (26:23)
What is how it is different from biases and variance, you are talking about it is looking like similar to biases and variance. 

Speaker 2  (26:33)
Isn't it a two different things? My business is basically when the model 

Speaker 1  (26:38)
Oh, no, what you are talking about? You are talking, it's like you are talking about the variance. 

Speaker 2  (26:49)
I was talking about that. Our model will not predict the correct output. Because it already knows the answer. 

Speaker 1  (26:57)
Because you have Um, you have trained it on a lot of data, and it is all it trained now when you give the actual practical data and it is not able to perform correctly, just classify, ask you. 

Speaker 2  (27:13)
What I'm trying to say is it already knows the output correct? If it already knows the output, it will not predict the correct, it will not predict the see. Let's say, let me give you its own example. 

Speaker 1  (27:25)
If it is, if knows the output, then it will predict what's the problem? 

Speaker 2  (27:29)
But it could be biassed toward the actual data See all the status upcoming refund refund refund and in the one case it is correct, one case it is closed. Let's say the issue is closed now. Now, when our when we train our model correct because, it already knows the answer it, will be refund so, it will be biassed toward the refund value not to the actual value I mean, I was trying to explain that. 

Speaker 2  (27:57)
Biases and the variance are two different things biases. We, I mean, in the biasiness, if the model is not able to understand the relationship of the actual features or the actual data. And the variance is, if it already knows all the data, I mean, it is it understand the noise also that's the part of the variance. 

Speaker 1  (28:27)
So I think you wanna say that. If For the first case, like, if you're any data comes in, the test data, which is out of the data that is not seen before, either model during training, right? 

Speaker 2  (28:46)
Yeah, I mean it should happen in that way that the train data should not come in the testing If it is coming, then it's a leakage. 

Speaker 1  (29:09)
Have you heard on any traditional Machine Learning model. 

Speaker 2  (29:15)
Let's just take and run, correct. 

Speaker 1  (29:19)
0741 series, right and ok, you bought on Pichhle waterland. Positive bottle, sweeper. So I think you know what is. 

Speaker 1  (29:36)
What is the What is the optimizer problem? I mean, what is you can say, I mean, what about you? My party optimise during the classification? 

Speaker 2  (29:51)
What is optimiser? 

Speaker 1  (29:53)
Do what is your optimisation function? Then What is you can say? Error function in class in simple logistic regression 

Speaker 2  (30:05)
Okay, error function is basically the in terms for the classification. You are asking on logistic. You are asking. 

Speaker 2  (30:14)
First. Okay? Um. 

Speaker 1  (30:17)
So I think logistic is a classification model, isn't it? 

Speaker 2  (30:21)
Yeah, I mean, it could be both. We can use in the recording also, but for the classification, we generally use And it's comes with the entropy, and trophy is basically the loss function from the entropy. We calculate the loss function from the entropy. 

Speaker 2  (30:39)
Where they value lie from minus infinity to plus infinity. And And rob function is submission of your probability neck. Sorry Probability, the I mean that good cases multiple levels and bad cases probability into one minus probability. 

Speaker 2  (31:04)
So it's functioning, enter the function, so we need to What you say, derivative of that entropy function of the loss function. 

Speaker 1  (31:16)
So suppose that I want to use logistic regression for the multiclaw classification. Can you suggest how can I use that? Okay, let's start 

Speaker 2  (31:30)
But it is not made for it, because it is binary. In nature, it will predict 01. So 

Speaker 1  (31:38)
But you're saying that it can be used for regression. 

Speaker 2  (31:45)
Used to be used in the middle in case of the regression, but it's going to be going to give me the 0 or 1 value at the end. Okay. 

Speaker 1  (31:56)
Set a simple classification. 

Speaker 2  (31:58)
There is a simple classification regression, where I used it. Regression, basically the continuous value. It will give right You have not able to recall, but I have used it somewhere for the issue. 

Speaker 2  (32:18)
Let me think. Away later, maybe 5 

Speaker 1  (32:26)
Just so we were talking about logistics here. Oh, I want multiclass classification. How can you 

Speaker 2  (32:34)
Yeah, it will just create a 2 groups, okay? Whether the value fall on the first row or the second row. Okay, we can use the logistic one on the multiple one, but at the end, we're going to create 2 outputs. 

Speaker 2  (32:48)
Zerodha. 

Speaker 1  (32:59)
Go, this is a kind of linear linear problem, linear model. Linear model, linear model, this is another model. Right? 

Speaker 2  (33:12)
No, we can't see the truth. 

Speaker 1  (33:14)
Their linear moral bills were the data is linearly separable. But yeah, but my problem is not linearly severable what can you do something? 

Speaker 2  (33:32)
There are multiple ways either we can go for the clustering or we can use SP mode, okay? For maximum marginal separation of the 2 datasets And if you want to go with the clustering on, it will depends on the weather. Our data is supervised. 

Speaker 2  (33:49)
Search for the non supervised, you can do with the clustering. The centroid method automatically 

Speaker 1  (33:55)
I am talking about classification, so you should not go for CL. 

Speaker 2  (33:59)
Yeah, then we have the right to forest or the Decision Trees. We can take 

Speaker 1  (34:09)
Okay, you can go for anything. Oh, you can say you can go for a simple model here, yeah. Or posting? 

Speaker 1  (34:22)
Do you know what is the difference between these 2 

Speaker 2  (34:25)
For the boosting model, it will create the residuals. Multiple trees works in sequence sequence manner, and then it will take the residual off from the previous tree and fix those residual and minimise those residue, and then it will come up with the minimising the residual too nearly to 0 so that It can have the final output of that particular with a final output of that tree. But for the random forest, it will create multiple trees and it works on the voting mechanism. 

Speaker 2  (35:03)
Where the If our data is, it works majorly on both imbalance and imbalanced data, even if we have the imbalance data, it will create the multiple trees and the multiple number of trees will go into Are the Les variance? Okay, random forest so that it can come up with the correct answer based on the voting. That's the one thing also 40 high accuracy usually prefer the boosting model. 

Speaker 2  (35:35)
Uh, then the random forest model. There are other multiple ways of boosting method like SU boosting light boosting and for the category. It's Dad, boosting. 

Speaker 2  (35:52)
Also, random forest box on the intuitive is green purity. When information gains That's how the internet 

Speaker 1  (36:12)
Okay, let's get back to Have you ever deployed the model? Any of the model 

Speaker 2  (36:20)
I yes, I've deployed the knowledge 

Speaker 1  (36:24)
Reward for Cuban network. 

Speaker 2  (36:26)
Kind doctors, we have deployed. 

Speaker 1  (36:32)
Create image then you should have towards somewhere. 

Speaker 2  (36:40)
This one, we have this chatbots, we are using a streamlit library. We give 

Speaker 1  (36:46)
Extremely, for July season meeting it is this is UI 

Speaker 2  (36:52)
But for the author models, I was not a part of it. 

Speaker 1  (37:02)
I won't foreconceila Syria. 

Speaker 2  (37:04)
Yeah, seriously. 

Speaker 1  (37:16)
So I think I hope that you will be using this guitar. Or anything else for code management and purchasing? 

Speaker 2  (37:28)
Yeah, we're using those this. Usually, we're working on a data book, sorry, GitHub. Request. 

Speaker 1  (37:42)
Hit bucket or bidvik. Okay. Okay. 

Speaker 1  (37:59)
Suppose that um I need to decide the resources I require for a particular problem. You have one problem and you need to give they. You have to got the tip, decide the estimate a cost. 

Speaker 1  (38:16)
The solution providing plant so how can you what are the major Parameters, you will check to decide the cost. What will burden your approach? 

Speaker 2  (38:29)
For the LLM S right Or in general? 

Speaker 1  (38:35)
Cool like you want to provide a solution. Okay, consider it is a generic solution. 

Speaker 2  (38:43)
Yeah, I mean Usually check it tokens. The number of tokens we are exposing, and the cost here to And that's how we Maintain the costing, also, the cluster, which we are choosing okay for the small model. We should not be having the large cluster, so we should based on the input that we are giving it to the error based on that, we need to check the cluster size. 

Speaker 2  (39:20)
Okay, there should be fall back mechanism. If there is no large data, we are Accumulating, then we can go with the small model also. So through those fallback, methods and all those things, we also reach the cachet token, also In the cache, we can store the Relevance input, which were already been asked, and we do that semantic cashing there, so that we can generate the answer. 

Speaker 2  (39:56)
Yeah, through that way, we minimise the cost basically. 

Speaker 1  (40:13)
I do not have any calls on question. Do you have any questions to ask? 

Speaker 2  (40:18)
Let me tell me what the project and the role 

Speaker 1  (40:25)
We are looking for I already role. I have defined here. The starting job projects, we have a lot of projects. 

Speaker 1  (40:33)
In every domain, whether it is a Machine Learning whether it is forecasting, whether it is GenAI letter, it is such a genetic work-related everything and In every domain with us, if you think of in healthcare, it is perfect. Finance. 

Speaker 2  (40:56)
Thousands of hundreds 

Speaker 1  (41:00)
Then, we require a dot clean. All these particles 

Speaker 2  (41:05)
Okay, fine. Yeah, thanks for them. 

Speaker 1  (41:15)
It's close nice to talk to you. I will provide you a feedback to another application. 
