Tinu Purushothaman

Speaker 1  (00:02)
This song Team, the record sign recording this session. Yeah, I started. 

Speaker 1  (00:26)
Asura, this is a senior architect, right this rule, yeah Thank you. I could prefer so decision on this. I am working as in architect, with tighter analytics. 

Speaker 1  (00:41)
It's 2:02 and a 1 years, okay, first, I'll start to and then we can start with an introduction or your total list of experience and your recent project that you're working with. Then, what are the rules of the responsibility in your current organisation, as an architect, and then we'll proceed with the discussion. Is you can start to with your introduction? 

Speaker 2  (01:09)
Oh, sure, so myself prakher, I were on 14 years of experience working with Currently, working with emphasis from last 3 years and vote that I'm working with Morgan standard Then, CVS, and then with the banking domain si. So majorly, I've worked on the banking domain for close to 9 to cars. Cranky, I'm working with t I read application which is more into the educational domain. 

Speaker 2  (01:39)
Here, I'm working. With data bricks okay, majorly. Um, I've worked with the rax patterns on the M. 

Speaker 2  (01:50)
L ML side, okay, also created some internal projects for the Agentic applications, along with that, I have a good exposure to the data engineering side, as well with price park, Scala spark spark majority and with python so Madura, such as possibilities that I get the column from the product owner, can we algorithm the requirement documentation, okay, high level and low level, and then we will work. Accordingly, based on the user storage Um. Yeah, if I talk about my application, which is um. 

Speaker 2  (02:31)
The architecture is like we're getting that data in the multifar architecture with bronze, silver and golden layer with the silver. We have multiple sources like Kafka, and then we have files, also B empty files coming up, and then we have regular in the Gs and formats are the file formats. Basically, you receive the data, and then we Put them into the bronze layer. 

Speaker 2  (03:04)
Through the Adm P pipelines, also some of the job strengths. And once we receive all the data, then we transform it into the silver layer, and send it across to the golden layer to the downstream team to access it for the amateur team to access. It, also, we have the snow flak, and there also for the anatic purpose, so we are dumping the data there as well. 

Speaker 2  (03:26)
We're the nightly running jobs from SG to ST transformations. Um, we have used a DL t's okay idea pipelines also. Along with that, we have Delta lake's Delta tables configured for all our use cases from one source system to that source system. 

Speaker 2  (03:51)
And finally, we are, depending it to the dvaks database. On the Amer side, we have created the mill flows okay for tracing and attractability for the models. Also add up some requirement based on the prompting. 

Speaker 2  (04:06)
Okay, we have written the prompts accordingly, so yeah, that's it, the actual overflow marchite. 

Speaker 1  (04:13)
Okay? And so if you have all the experience on LLM models, so with LM models, you have used for the prompting. 

Speaker 2  (04:20)
There are multiples we have tried, but currently, we're using the OpenAI GPT for many 

Speaker 1  (04:26)
Total, because of the curacy and better accuracy. Eyes are so first I think like we have already have already worked on data bits right? Like designing the pipeline using the material architecture, so how we handle it, we get Pi data, we take most of the median architecture. 

Speaker 1  (04:46)
So how will handle this Pi information, like PID tech works, the we can here? Do you do you mask it at bronze, silver or cool? How will decide effect, for example, Pi test? 

Speaker 1  (04:59)
Then, you know, it food, it will float to tribunch care earlier and the whole day, so how Lake in each care, how will mast the detail which gave in mask and whichever tokenize? So MPs get better. 

Speaker 2  (05:11)
And I will, yeah, the data. Sorry. And the database we usually use the row, filtered or column filter for masking the data. 

Speaker 2  (05:20)
And the row filtering, we have assigned some roles. Okay, so that's why we the other user cannot access it also for the email ids and the other stuff we usually mask it using the column filter. 

Speaker 1  (05:35)
Okay, call it, filter, use mask. Yeah. In which year old Silva, which one 

Speaker 2  (05:45)
In the um Okay, in the in the silver day. 

Speaker 1  (05:53)
Okay, and is ugu, chubby? Also know about things somewhere, we used to tokenize it somewhere we used to mask it, so what is the difference between this masking and tokenization? 

Speaker 2  (06:04)
A tokenizer is basically what each words is breaking down into the simple words. Okay, and also we have to, if I talk about the Eda sides, we have to extract it, we have to laborize it. Okay, neutralise that word to simple words to fit in the directionary. 

Speaker 2  (06:26)
So this is what the token usage of the token if I talk about the other thing, what was that classic masking mask is basically we are just not showing the actual data to the user, we are just putting astitch in between the values. 

Speaker 1  (06:47)
So now we have got a new term right. That be, like, mostly people, often we are using, like liquid clustering, right? So why did the news like by way? 

Speaker 1  (06:56)
Nowadays choosing liquid clustering over traditional health partitioning, and also Z out 

Speaker 2  (07:03)
Yes, so in the earlier when we were using the partitioning thing, we have the small file problems. Okay, basically, it will create the partition with some little files, some small files. Basically, it will give the overread to the CTU to process it okay. 

Speaker 2  (07:22)
Now the liquid clustering, we have that Z. Cluster Z ordering, so Z ordering is not incremental. Okay, which means that every time the new price comes in, we have to execute that Z order command so that the files are in proper link with the ids. 

Speaker 2  (07:43)
Ok, and the row number is specified. Basically indexing of that happen. Then, we have the auto clustering, which is liquid clustering, we say, so it will it is the incremental way of the Z order only, so we don't need to explicitly run the commands for ordinance. 

Speaker 1  (08:07)
To selecting with no liquid frustrating every time you don't have to go, and first of all, see the how the people is coming everything, and like depressing automatically, it's taken to Parliament doing optimisation, it's also like we have heard about unity calculate, so in unity, catalogue, how the back in its design. So how does the architecture of the like, how the government, how in the back, and it's taking care, the unity can't look how 

Speaker 2  (08:36)
Yeah, so For different purposes for different teams for different workplaces, we have different catalogue design for Dev broad and the QA and there we have the just RBAC okay, where we are restricting each catalogue to the different workspaces, to the user, or to the teams that we are, they're using those who are using. The database so that way there's a steps to follow to configure that So yeah, that's the purpose of using children catalogue, so just give the centre 

Speaker 1  (09:14)
During powers in sign like we are, you know, right in the back end, it's kind of like we have to follow-on structure while designing your edit platlog, so what is the structure? 

Speaker 2  (09:24)
Structure wise, we have workspace matter store. Okay, those things we need to configure it. They did long time back, but I'm just recalling that. 

Speaker 2  (09:36)
So we have to configure the Individual workspaces for the For the environments, let's say for dev environment, we have one workspace, multiple workspace, but Meta store can be single. I think single Meta store and then we have multiple catalogues, we can design, then these schemas, then the tables, and then we can give the permission to all those schemas, catalogue and everything. Right with Janka and 3 by best. 

Speaker 1  (10:11)
And also, for example, teen write in the Courtyard, sometimes, like the situations comes that we don't want to like, expose our data to like few, we do, like we have to protect our data, so we can't give access to each and every member so in the core year. So how you will implement this, like role level, security, column level security. That is very important, right? 

Speaker 1  (10:33)
You can't give access to. In this, the community can look how you will implement this row level in column level security. 

Speaker 2  (10:40)
Majorly, we use the Delta share For the read access massing, we usually do in the silver layer itself and then exposing to the other Government using the Delta share. 

Speaker 1  (10:53)
Okay, so to what ignuming? What is tender sharing? When it comes into picture, Y filter sharing is mostly used when we talk about to like giving accesses, and all like more elaborate on what is temperature in 

Speaker 2  (11:10)
They sometimes there's a requirement of let's say if we want to access the plot data, okay, plot tables majorly, so what usually do with Delta share it with a dev environment to verify the car? The data in the Deven, warm and we can run the query there. We cannot update anything, but it's just for the view. 

Speaker 2  (11:32)
So that's the requirement that we usually have. Um that I mean, when we're using Delta share. 

Speaker 1  (11:40)
Okay, I'll consider that we know right in the 10th. Delta table is nothing but a parking format. The additional functionalities, right, so consider that we are having on parket 510 million reports And the requirement is to delete a single record. 

Speaker 2  (12:01)
In the Delta, sheer or 

Speaker 1  (12:02)
Earlier than the Delta table, so it's a parking table. It's a parket file with 10 union records and we have. We want to delete only one record. 

Speaker 1  (12:12)
Okay, is so what will be the functionality of the Delta table? How it will do it will delete the entire. It will do a full table scan or it will delete so how it will work in the back end? 

Speaker 2  (12:24)
Dental table, if you've partitioned it, then it will. It will not scan the full table. 

Speaker 1  (12:30)
Okay, okay. 

Speaker 2  (12:32)
So I mean, we have to do the partitioning. First I mean, based on the queries that we have written, we have to choose which column we need to partition. Otherwise you'll do the full scan only. 

Speaker 1  (12:44)
Ok, see if your partitioning, also, if that record is not present in the single partition right? So again, it will go to that so how it will go like deletioning so for example, how if you have partitioning, also, then 

Speaker 2  (13:03)
Sorry, I didn't get your questions so you want to delete 

Speaker 1  (13:04)
True, I'm telling that the data is so you're telling you, if you have partitioned the record, like if you have partitioned the Delta table right, consider that if you have partition according to the date, then if we are deleting that reports, how it's searching the table, it's going to each partition, how it 

Speaker 2  (13:21)
Yeah, I mean, if we're not specified any partitioning, then it will go to the it will scan all the rows okay, similar to the any other table, what does Delta table brings is that it will add the acid property. Okay, that's the normal table. Okay, there is no other advantage of having aditable apart from objects. 

Speaker 1  (13:44)
Okay, have you heard of deletion Victor? It is nowadays, whenver we have to delete, like, if you're performing, delete functionality, so what we are doing, we are enabling this deletion vector. Yes, it will create a small small vector and it will store in the like log. 

Speaker 1  (14:03)
It will not directly delete the table. Because what happens whenever we are deleting a record? Yes, so I think now we have to enable deletion vector whenever we know that we can this table, we have to perform the deletion functionality. 

Speaker 2  (14:18)
Okay, no. 

Speaker 1  (14:19)
Let us in this picture. Okay, that's like because I was also not delivered but like working, then I came to, yes, we have to enable this division lecture, otherwise, that will be a problem. So this is and also with the cicg pipeline, right? 

Speaker 1  (14:38)
Whenever we are pushing a good. So how it's like, how have you worked like? Have you implemented cicd pipeline for their entire project? 

Speaker 2  (14:47)
Ah, yes, I have written some of the stages, okay, in the Jenkins file, so normally we were running the landas okay. From the from the CAC pipeline. Also, we have same configuration around all the modules where we are testing the functional function testing of unit testing. 

Speaker 2  (15:08)
Everything should be done right, and then it would read the bill for those stages. We are 

Speaker 1  (15:16)
Thank you. So ugh so how can you please like how we have like, whenever we are configuring CI line and so what are the steps, how will like how it will design that CIA continuous integration, continuous deployment, so how is architecture and how you'll design the step ups in our project? 

Speaker 2  (15:36)
Yeah, the time issue should be designed. Like the time we push our changes. The CST should run automatically, and the stages that we can design is first. 

Speaker 2  (15:47)
It has to check all the basic functionality of the courts, okay, and then the function testing and all those testing should be done. And then once all those things finalise, and it should create a build. Ok, in the In the jenkin itself, and then we can have the multiple version, everything apart from that. 

Speaker 2  (16:09)
We can have the sonar cube. Also invite, we can add that stage, also, for the vulnerability. These are the things we have to do. 

Speaker 2  (16:19)
Needs to be before designing any stage of Jenkins. 

Speaker 1  (16:23)
Okay so have you designed a cluster policy in your project that what are the things we have to take care while because we know right? You can't designing cluster policies very important for the optimisation perfect. Because we can't give a random data engineer or data scientist to who and choose their own clusters like we have to go with the designing part, and it's to be that they can use it. 

Speaker 1  (16:47)
So what are the things we have to take care very by designing cluster policies 

Speaker 2  (16:54)
Yeah, this thing we normally face. But we approach to the adventing for that to design the cluster policy. I have not done that. 

Speaker 1  (17:04)
Okay, no, that is fine because a few of the project is like their administration are responsible for 

Speaker 2  (17:11)
Managing the clust. 

Speaker 1  (17:12)
Yes, yes, managing the cluster policies. And also like we know right. There are multiple options nowadays, while the selecting clusters and database, right? 

Speaker 1  (17:22)
We have plastic database cluster server as sequel warehouses and photon enable instances like for different enterprise personas, so like in which scenarios will go for classic data with cluster with scenario will go for surveillance equal warehouses, and also photon enables instances. 

Speaker 2  (17:41)
If for the adaptive queries, we use the server less. Okay, but server less has some disadvantages. It doesn't run some of the I mean, the cache, there is an issue I recently faced that and adoquer is run with the surveillance. 

Speaker 2  (18:00)
Then, we have the job clusters okay for each other. Scheduling jobs, we usually use the job cluster. And for the simple abstract 1 classic 1, and the photon enabled is when we have Long-running jobs, okay? 

Speaker 2  (18:22)
And we want to minimise the time, okay of those jobs in that case, we use the 14 enable Don't remember the actual use case. But yeah, that one, we have used that photon level for the long-running jobs. With a fine team in the course 

Speaker 1  (18:42)
It's mostly for Ud F us python, Ud S and then invent training model streaming match micro batches, you have also worked with streaming data. 

Speaker 2  (18:53)
I worked with that, but not here, but in the previous organisation I worked 

Speaker 1  (19:01)
Okay, I'm so happy heard about check pointing like, you know right. So what is the use of check pointing like? Why what happens like if like, check what is the use? 

Speaker 2  (19:12)
It uses if the job is failed, okay, so instead of starting it from the scratch, it will take reference from the checkpoint from where it take that it got failed. And it can restart from there, okay, that's the use case of the checkpoint, so we've to specify that in the spark configuration. The directory 

Speaker 1  (19:34)
Is check pointing in the Delta cold, right? And also, we know that we have we when we perform effective, right? So consider that like we can. 

Speaker 1  (19:42)
If we have perform vacuum, and we want to very data within that period like which we have already vacuumed the data set, so we will, we will be able to time travel to those data. 

Speaker 2  (19:56)
Yeah, there's a retention policy. If you've not explicitly defined that, then there is a 90 days or 30 days, I don't remember and there is a retention policy. If it goes beyond that, then we have to touchbees with the data bricks team to recover that 

Speaker 1  (20:17)
Yes, the prevention is for 164 hours. That is default, but we can set a reset that Also okay, so you have you worked with a designing of unstructured data because we have structured, so consider that we are getting structured, data, semicructured, data and structured data. And the ask from the client is that we have to invest all the data in the single target data. 

Speaker 1  (20:44)
And consider that we have to design it using data, fix. We cleanly and architecture, yeah, we have to so how you will make sure that how you'll end this structure and semi structures, data and also unstructured in the same table, what will be your approach, which tool you will use for structure, which, for semicructure, and also for unstructure. 

Speaker 2  (21:05)
Yeah, I mean, we usually at the mistakes data and we define the schemas. Ok, what is now we need to place in the table and correspondingly, we transform our data. Okay, and then we send it across to the other tables. 

Speaker 1  (21:19)
If you're rich, one was structured, right? 

Speaker 2  (21:22)
Yeah, for the structure, correct? 

Speaker 1  (21:24)
Again, for semi, structured. 

Speaker 2  (21:26)
Semi structured actor like logs or something right 

Speaker 1  (21:29)
Yes, please correct. It's in the place. 

Speaker 2  (21:34)
Format 1 format. 

Speaker 1  (21:36)
Example feature feeds we are getting cisfa. Payloads, so you don't consider copper because you have to work with streaming Money. The TP is an X simple field so that will be a semi structure data. 

Speaker 2  (21:49)
I mean, once, would you find the schema? It will be the structured data only so you can. I mean we have to write the scripts or something notebook, where we can transform the unnecessary to the structured data with the schema? 

Speaker 1  (22:04)
Okay, that we can do is we can use auto loader also to be a checkpoint we can do and schema evaluation. We can enable it at the can do only, so there will be no pipeline wake and we can, because it's a lested data, right? So better we can plat it to Nestor structure and the form of that a semi structure. 

Speaker 1  (22:25)
What about unstructured? 

Speaker 2  (22:28)
Unrestructured data like images, correct? 

Speaker 1  (22:31)
Sorry, correct images, logs email. 

Speaker 2  (22:36)
Yeah, I mean, I've worked on the application where we're generating the intent from the email. So email could be That also we have designed this, I mean, the approach would be like, we have to design the schema and then do the other things okay. So even if there any sector 

Speaker 1  (22:55)
This is how much serious like if we are trying to adjust it using your most people in our structured table, so that we have to handle it very carefully, right? Because service structured and structured data, it's very easy to interview. It was when it comes for unstructured, then you have to be very careful that we have to use 2 extra like additional tools because the interest 

Speaker 2  (23:17)
Track, do we have used for extracting the text okay from the image? Sorry 

Speaker 1  (23:24)
Sorry, sorry you can get any piece to be 

Speaker 2  (23:26)
Yeah, that's extract libraries. We have used for extracting the data here from the images. I mean, what's the use case of that, that we need to very check the first use case if you want a text out from the images, then we can have the text library. 

Speaker 2  (23:44)
Okay, otherwise We're looking for a full standard one in the last 4 digits of your phone number. Um. In the cedence, if we can Tell me. 

Speaker 2  (23:57)
Yeah Have you said sorry no, not able to recall it? That's only 

Speaker 1  (24:03)
We can use UC volume that you can explore it. Because you can take use of lnm models that we can integrate in between so that it can help us further extraction purpose. And then later on it's like, according to the use case that you use case you told. 

Speaker 1  (24:18)
Then, it's very easy for us, whatever the required text we want, we can extract it using, we can use LLM models. And then from the silver to cold air, it will be the same right. Only the problem is by extracting the data you can take help of your nlm models, so we can use UC volumes that is very important because it help storage for like, we can store binary files binary data in the volumes. 

Speaker 1  (24:42)
I think you can explore that part that I think we are having Meta store than catalogue and in the table, we are having volume also in the unity catalyt. 

Speaker 2  (24:51)
Even just a storage right stor. 

Speaker 1  (24:54)
Yes, for the storage we use volume. Follow this for your unstructured data. It's so have you worked with C? 

Speaker 1  (25:03)
D? C. 

Speaker 2  (25:05)
ACT C change it a capture, right? So yes, I've used that applications we're using it. 

Speaker 1  (25:21)
Okay, so the data that is coming is your CDC data? Okay, so how would we interested data? How you'll design the pipeline for the CDC data. 

Speaker 2  (25:35)
Yes, CDC has been basically Capture the previous historical data. If we want to capture that so for that purpose, we have the CDC even in the streams, also or maybe in the batch, we have to configure those, and even in the auto later, it will automatically create a new row, and for the with a new value and the old value. And there are multiple types of S CD 01234 okay. 

Speaker 2  (26:07)
Depending on whether we want to keep the historical data, or we just want to update the existing data. Correct? 

Speaker 1  (26:16)
Give me 1 minute. 

Speaker 1  (26:35)
I'm really sorry. Yes, auven, we talk about J DCB M rate that gets that kind of an incremental data from the course we're getting early, so 

Speaker 2  (26:48)
Sorry, your voice is a bit low. 

Speaker 1  (26:51)
Okay, thank you. Now it 

Speaker 2  (26:53)
Yes, it's correct. 

Speaker 1  (26:54)
If I was telling that we know right CTC is not held up a historical data where ITC DC is kind of a transactional data that we are getting. It will be your inserts, update and the lead from the society. Sure, my shoulders think how we will design. 

Speaker 1  (27:09)
So for example, when it comes to bronze, what will be our approach? Also, you will be appending the data, or you will be overwriting the data. What you will do 

Speaker 2  (27:18)
Yes, yeah, I mean incremental data. Right? So we want to make the pipelines incremental. 

Speaker 2  (27:26)
Okay, so there are 2 ways that we use first is first. We instructed writing to bronze layer and we delete the data from the silver, and then whatever the data frame that we have retrieve from the bronze layer, we just insert it okay into the Silver layer. Okay, that's the one of the approach then the merge into approach we usually follow. 

Speaker 2  (27:50)
So basically we doesn't touch the exist. If there is any updates, we update that otherwise we'll insert the neuron using the merging to come up. Yeah, I mean, these are 2 purchases. 

Speaker 1  (28:05)
It's, I think, in the prompt you're going for an appent. And then the bones we use, mostly use yours. Sorry, so silver. 

Speaker 1  (28:12)
We use your merge into like the statement. And to the course will be your kind of work data. All the data will be in the code, if the historical, because we are attending the data in the code right? 

Speaker 2  (28:28)
Yeah, correct. 

Speaker 1  (28:30)
Have you worked with ST type 12 and 3 also 

Speaker 2  (28:34)
I am not specifically specified it. In the Delta pipeline that we have created long time back there. We are specifying the acid type 012, but right now for the incremental pipeline, we are not doing that way. 

Speaker 1  (28:51)
Okay, this is so for you. Also, it's kind of an implemented pipeline long back you have worked with real Duke sidd type, bigger series. 18.73 so cannot early explain. 

Speaker 1  (29:07)
It's fine if you haven't heard, but can you explain like? What type 0 means? Type one means type 2 and type 3 means. 

Speaker 2  (29:16)
Yes, it was. I mean, as I can recall type 0 is just updating the existing value type 1 and 2 might be, we are keeping the both the records in the table historical data as well as the new data. Okay? 

Speaker 2  (29:35)
And not sure about the 3 and 4 

Speaker 1  (29:39)
Poor I don't want because who would hardly be going with 4 implementation, right? Because who we don't use ourades, it's mostly like we go for reserve 0. We also don't use but like 123. 

Speaker 1  (29:53)
We use 

Speaker 2  (29:55)
Yeah, so I'm not able to recall that what is 3, but Could you update? 

Speaker 1  (30:06)
Ok, 2 is kind of a one. You told 0 will be kind of an 

Speaker 2  (30:10)
Come to it. Yeah, absolutely. Then 11 will be keeping the historical data historical drove along with the new neural row Like something new, I think I'm too Insulin. 

Speaker 1  (30:31)
Corrects, it's totally different. Okay, I also just wanted to ask you, so do you have experience on anequal or your only book in a pocs, also, like how work for in any rfs, like, for example, any project comes, so you're only responsible for what we say in your project. Or you are also involved in additional arifuse, because if some project comes to people call you for other projects like your suggestion or anything, because it tiger out that it's not like we have to only work for our project, it's like a petitional RFD comes. 

Speaker 1  (31:12)
So then we have to also work on those additional rfs. 

Speaker 2  (31:16)
Yeah, I have worked on the cross. Uh, functional teams. Okay, I mean, yeah, I have exposed to that so on the PO. 

Speaker 2  (31:26)
C. Sides, yes, initially, basically, we create the in the same project, we create the spikes, okay for the for the pocs, where we have to create the documentation with the scoop feasibility, everything that I have done. And on the other teams, we have to have work on the Okay. 

Speaker 1  (32:01)
So in your project, the technology that you have extensively work is in on data breaks, and also your years, you have also worked with better trade data-driven architecture rate, so how you have implemented this Meta, driven. It's like in the adf for in database, so how you have implemented. Is this better data-driven architecture? 

Speaker 1  (32:22)
Collination, architecture. 

Speaker 2  (32:24)
Sorry, which architecture validation? 

Speaker 1  (32:26)
Major data, major data-driven architecture. So what is method data-driven architecture, when we see, what do you mean by Meta data-driven? 

Speaker 2  (32:34)
You have an event based Architecture, we have designed it using the lambdas. Okay? Also, we have used the yeah, if some files has been uploaded, we are Giving notification to The Landers, and then there the end of this lender will going to execute all the code. 

Speaker 2  (32:59)
Um, that's a one way. Also, we expose the APIs okay. Bungy, the sweater, uh, to the different teams to access it, microservices we have built-in yeah, and these are the Do you have a dashcam? 

Speaker 2  (33:17)
And it's just an opportunity to get back to the street and lockdown. 

Speaker 1  (33:23)
Have you also booked on data quality because automated generation of chase and data quality reports? So like how you've implemented this 

Speaker 2  (33:37)
Sorry, come in. Data quality 

Speaker 1  (33:40)
Yes, data quality checks. So you have automated this, because, uh, nowadays, data quality is very important, right data B. So in tiger. 

Speaker 1  (33:47)
Also, it's a framework is framework. Is there so for example, the tailor quality checks they perform right for each and every pipeline so have you implemented in any data quality checks framework, anything like that. 

Speaker 2  (33:59)
Hey, you talk about the sonar cube or something. 

Speaker 1  (34:02)
No, not, so it's data data quality, you know, right? Data quality checks that we used to perform. 

Speaker 2  (34:08)
Great in the silver layer. We have to have to specify the constant, but otherwise I have not done that. Data call it checks. 

Speaker 2  (34:25)
Ultimately, 610 years specify what the data quality needs. I mean 

Speaker 1  (34:29)
Data qualities like few of the chicks. So for example, if your data is coming from the source right? So some of the like basic check needs to perform, for example, the data, the data type is correct, or not, or that, for example, if we are having any primary key, right? 

Speaker 1  (34:43)
So we have to check any that value, so duplicate values should not be present in the in the primary column, right? That is a very important check. So we need to talk about sorry kind of kind of a basic check. 

Speaker 1  (34:55)
So these objects, mostly what we used to do. We used to automate kind of a mandatory checks for any of the pipeline, right? 

Speaker 2  (35:02)
Okay, we have done it in the notebook itself while transforming the data, so we check the null value is missing values. Okay, we check the duplicates values. Yeah, but the basic checks we usually do for the specific columns. 

Speaker 2  (35:17)
The value should be correct, okay. 

Speaker 1  (35:19)
Okay, so tell me one thing, so we have one feature optimised, right? And we also have auto optimise, correct? 

Speaker 2  (35:27)
Okay, feature optimism. 

Speaker 1  (35:29)
Optimise, an auto optimise. So what is the difference between optimised and auto optimise? 

Speaker 2  (35:36)
Um. Okay, optimise, basically, it will Once again, auto move Uh, it just cools the data. Okay, um, if there's a small file, let's cater the small file problem. 

Speaker 2  (35:56)
If we have A Records spread across the small files. It will just cool coolest them. Okay, make it a big file. 

Speaker 2  (36:05)
Uh, that's the use of optimise. I think and optimise it will automatically. We have to just specify it while creating the table, I think, and there it will, then we don't need to run that command every time. 

Speaker 1  (36:22)
Okay, so open auto optimise is having 2 additional features, right? So what are the 2 additional features that optimise is having that make it like distinguished from optimised 

Speaker 2  (36:35)
Yay and I read it. We usually use the autop, sorry, optimise with the Z order. Ah, or the vacuum command. 

Speaker 2  (36:50)
But traditional feature, I've not been recaller. I heard I read it somewhere. 

Speaker 1  (36:56)
Fine? Because when we talk about database, right? So in data brits, we know that there are multiple optimisation features. 

Speaker 1  (37:03)
There is data skinness and all right, so there is an functionality that is aqe made up in spark right spark AQ. So what are the optimisation features that Aq takes care in this spark? 

Speaker 2  (37:19)
Okay aqi, we have to specify for this Tunis, with some parameters, like screw join, is equal to enable us true, and there we have to specify the advisory partition partition size. Okay, lot of other stuff related to this Unus. Also for the joint purpose, it will verify the table size and based on that it will do the broadcast joint automatically instead of this hot mode. 

Speaker 2  (37:50)
Join. Okay, these are the 2 Two things I can recall it. Otherwise. 

Speaker 2  (38:04)
I'm just thinking about the bottle that spark has okay. First thing with the joints. Okay, other thing is the A partition, pruning, I think. 

Speaker 2  (38:16)
It's automatically by default with this park, but maybe the order joins. There are some issues. So these whole things cater by B. 

Speaker 2  (38:27)
Your audience. A queue. 

Speaker 1  (38:40)
It is mostly in this in this year, also worked with ews S3 and London, right? So with all withdrawal cloud technologies, you're having experience 

Speaker 2  (38:51)
They work with the EWS and major So with the WS I've used as 3 lenders, okay, ecr clusters And then step functions also for orchestration. 

Speaker 1  (39:06)
Okay. 

Speaker 2  (39:09)
I've worked on the ED plus glue also, but long time back. Currently, we're using all spark with 8 database. 

Speaker 1  (39:17)
Utispatvati's with Azure, or with tws with Azure. Okay, so I think you have mostly working with CTC not to the SCT1 incremental loading. And can you please tell me like in data breaks, for example, we are facing some. 

Speaker 1  (39:41)
What are the optimisation techniques that we can opt for like? Whenever there is a issue going jobs, taking more time to consider as work, those park joggers, taking longer. So what are the and we found it that there is there is issue with not at this park him. 

Speaker 1  (39:57)
There is some issue with on the data breaking. 

Speaker 2  (39:59)
Great, thank you. 

Speaker 1  (40:01)
What are the optimisation techniques we can perform? 

Speaker 2  (40:06)
Your first few check whether it's a cluster issue or a data issue. So based on that, we take the decision so it's a cluster issue. We have to check the size, okay number of competitors, memory and the number of codes basically. 

Speaker 2  (40:22)
We have to fine-tune it using the hit and dryer. So one thing is that the other thing is, if there's a data issue, then we need to verify in the code, how many shufflings has happened? What a number of shuffles that it is creating, so we need to increase the number of sales depending on the depending on the data, also going to see whether it's there is some skiness in the data or not, that easily we can see using the UI. 

Speaker 2  (40:57)
Apart from that, yeah, we can have the broadcast joining. The tables are In less size, < 10 around 10 MB. Joints, then we need to see what are the order joining orders? 

Speaker 2  (41:15)
What is the driver table? Correspondingly, we need to take decision also where to see. We don't need to expose all the data to the other environments, or maybe the other teams we have to strictly apply the filters there. 

Speaker 2  (41:32)
Um. Yeah, these are the things that I have done that. 

Speaker 1  (41:40)
Broadcast Junior Kim is also. Yeah, okay, when we talk about data breaks, right? So how the architecture of data brings Outstructured, so what are the components? 

Speaker 1  (41:54)
Which component is responsible for what? 

Speaker 2  (41:59)
Yeah, I mean In the data breaks, the run time engine is a spark only okay, and then we have the storage layer, and then we have the computation layer. So all those three things are loosely coupled, and for that. Then, we have the Delta delta tables in between the in the runtimes engine, and then we have the computation layer with the computation, we can increase the number of cpus codes everything, and then we are the underlying data storage layer, which is the data table Delta table, and we have just external allocation. 

Speaker 2  (42:41)
Also, we have managed and external table that we can create So data will be lying in the parky format. Okay, and then we have the log file also, which will Track all the transactions that has been happened on that per parki file. If they some update, it will integrate a new park file. 

Speaker 2  (43:04)
Okay, um, along with the new log file, okay? So if there's something I mean, if the, if the whole data is committed, then only it will create a new log file, otherwise it will use the old one, something like this. 

Speaker 1  (43:26)
Okay, and so we have, we know that community catalogue is mostly useful governing, so there is also mostly use for governance, and also, there is a page that captures the main thing in 

Speaker 2  (43:39)
Unity, capital, sorry, captured lineage. 

Speaker 1  (43:42)
Here is so how it to electric dimension. 

Speaker 2  (43:49)
Even if we have one table, we can see where this particular table has been used here. So that's the overall need of the linear. But apart from that, I don't know. 

Speaker 1  (44:03)
Okay, so there is a key with called a system access table image where we have to give the target full name where this equal to and there are we can target source table, full name, targetable, full name and works beside me. These are the and we'll get all the details so we can go with system. Access table that we can do And I think also, you have worked with the key, a right in an immortal ways to Also I think I have prepared overfitting topics for mine in terror. 

Speaker 2  (44:36)
Okay. 

Speaker 1  (44:37)
So, do you have any questions? 

Speaker 2  (44:40)
Can you tell me about the project? 

Speaker 1  (44:44)
Sorry, Prakash, so I can't be able to tell you about the project because now there are multiple requirements and tiger, which is coming because of this. Hiring is going on so like for multiple data, architect positions and senior architect positions. So currently, now we won't be able to tell you which project will you will tap according once you join tiger analytics and according to the requirement, you will be tacked to a new of the project. 

Speaker 2  (45:08)
Is it mixed with the AI or it's just yes? 

Speaker 1  (45:11)
That's mixed too there because in tiger. Also, now it's very important that we are also going through Chennai chennai. Certification everything, because now like in any of the project or there be pressing a data engineer at the target and we are giving a perish water estimate. 

Speaker 1  (45:26)
Also, mostly we are automating things using AI. We are creating AI agents, and you know, like once raw, the I agents is created, the most of the job will be done with that all right, so So I think once you get hired and you choose, then only you'll get You know which project you will be working. I also don't like it's generic having it is going to understand. 

Speaker 2  (45:53)
Okay, here, I'm good. 

Speaker 1  (45:55)
Okay. Okay, I Prakash us. I'll give my feedback to team sure, I'll get back. 

Speaker 2  (46:01)
Sure, thanks for that. 

Speaker 1  (46:03)
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you for nice 
