nishita.mishra@tothenew.com
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Play that function in like the grant water type book, and that table that schema a catalog or schema that are typical. And then the row piece, then that consumption will need to add so applying these one. Then, the regional I am the belongs to one region. 

Speaker 1  (00:22)
Say that cannot have a bank or region. When I'll be just login, do it is then my reason it could be crunter. I can only see this kind of bed. 

Speaker 1  (00:32)
I cannot see any other region. 

Speaker 2  (00:39)
Okay, let's say you have your injecting a high volume of data. Okay, let's say from event over a Kafka. Okay to a Delta lake table. 

Speaker 2  (00:52)
Antonio, you are seeing a duplicate records for a late arriving event. Okay, which is impacting downstream? Oh, which is the golden layer? 

Speaker 2  (01:03)
So can you come up? Can you help me with the Antoine solution? Which will guarantee exactly one's processing? 

Speaker 2  (01:13)
How will you 100D? Du? Duplication ischemia revolution and everything 

Speaker 1  (01:19)
Yeah, so Before I notice that we are having that at the high level, like, in the realistic data, when we are getting into that. And we are using this with either. We are editing it from a Kafka or any kind of the eventual so that kind of four things we are editing it. 

Speaker 1  (01:40)
So in this case has to communicate, we will read it, then in those back inside pieces will be created. That's processing internally, so I have to follow 3 layers. And then say, let's folders, I need to create, in my electrories. 

Speaker 1  (02:06)
So then after that image of the street where the data would be keeper coming to the raw area, it could become and there, in that case, I have to in the raw case, whatever it is come then I have ID enabled everything. It will be when I just read it. Read then there I need to I'll. 

Speaker 1  (02:31)
Use more schema in the group so that option I need to enable it. So in this case, whatever whenever any data any schema would be getting sent in that a source like all the data, it will be part of the undo, the Break up, that pipeline and it will be keeper coming. So after that, I have to write my receiver letter. 

Speaker 1  (02:56)
I am to write out the data cleansing and order notifications to take it there. I need to do, and I have to write the advice for that python code for that drop duplicates. As we should be retailed, entire record on the duplicate records from that row are specific Colombia. 

Speaker 1  (03:16)
So I wasn't like in business or so once like some of the there will be some specific columns. So based on that, also, if that would be not, then we'll also ignore that. So and based on so that also I need to or I need to pass in that arrow, I need from the crickets there, I need to pass in the arrow in terms of alumni so that it could be gated legit or the data would be get cleaned and that if the final, the filter data framework. 

Speaker 1  (03:47)
I got Darcy could arrive into like a idea of daughter, right? Stay by schedule that I need to add to add. So now to see what layer it will be having only all the curated data. 

Speaker 1  (04:02)
And after that, I will have this support player like in that player or the irrigations will be based on the business. But things whatever can be accomplished on that I have to do in that aggregate, in that gold end. So there I have to perform my aggregations like the joys, and the also the group guy and I think I will apply that logic inside that holder. 

Speaker 1  (04:29)
So this way I have to I have no desire in mind, Madeleine architecture and I will write this piece of the words in each office layer so that I can award this the duplications. And I like in my business last week. 

Speaker 2  (04:48)
Türkiye. And how do we handle the scenario where you find the checkpoint is put corrupt? So how do you handle that scenario? 

Speaker 2  (05:01)
How will you recover that? 

Speaker 1  (05:05)
Oh, yeah. So we will talk about this automotive order. Things like when we'll need that. 

Speaker 1  (05:12)
Because automotive can be read or the touchdreaming data. So like either one of the multiple types, it will keep a coming. Every some seconds it will be ingested to our ideal city is coming so batting a lot of logical peak or and the automotive teacher will be at a checkpoint location. 

Speaker 1  (05:30)
So you are saying that checkpoint location, you could take corrupted. 

Speaker 2  (05:40)
I don't know getting hit 

Speaker 1  (05:42)
I was asking like if the checkpoint got the checkpoint of the automotive, it will begin to break then how will it Yes, so in this, then automatically it will be After the rate at administer, my calendar time could be not hit So that pain we cannot because not a dictate that because the technology will be getting delegated. Then Does schima and Gabriel? 

Speaker 2  (06:25)
And everything will be lost. 

Speaker 1  (06:27)
Yes, you cannot be able to make a complication. If the things so come back, what I have to do like all the data I have in that the raw area in everything I am having in this raw air. So all the data is there. 

Speaker 1  (06:48)
So come there again and need to apply my incognique. I need to Hi, I'm getting back to conduct a role to the crons layer again. I have to go turn my Pike lane which will be used to seek offset. 

Speaker 1  (07:05)
So based on that offsetting, when I do this, then whatever the data will be there, they need to be not. 

Speaker 2  (07:12)
Yeah, that's the one way. But you have a high volume on data, right? I mean, millions of data is there. 

Speaker 2  (07:18)
In the Brownsley, or maybe so how you will go now? Maybe not in The Bronx layer before the bronze layer. Okay, you have the high volume, and you're certainly a checkpoint or correct? 

Speaker 2  (07:32)
So is there any way you can store that high volume data somewhere? In what we approach 

Speaker 1  (07:44)
So we stop. Hi. You don't want to be a kid in that time. 

Speaker 1  (07:50)
I will directly investing it higher than it will be coming in. 

Speaker 2  (07:55)
He's died. 

Speaker 1  (07:56)
Let's talk Victoria, 2 injector events of Sofi capital, like the Microsoft that service should be capable to handle all the We load up the time event, so compare All right, so I am following this up. 

Speaker 2  (08:17)
Okay. Um, okay, you've opened the database. Also, right now, right now Yes, okay, so let's say in as your data breaks your, or maybe in The pipe my job is taking around 8 plus hours. 

Speaker 2  (08:34)
Okay, daily and it is missing the S. L. List, right. 

Speaker 2  (08:38)
And desire. The file size isn't TVS. Then, having drawing segregation and incremental loads. 

Speaker 2  (08:48)
Can you walk me through the troubleshooting steps? And optimization strategies that you will use 

Speaker 1  (08:58)
So this is the This activities we are getting in our detention. Is the most common time? It's the critical process, so the program to solve that, I need to go to this is perhaps New York, and they are acting to see that the data set likely the pakistanism, which Pakistan, which is taking a long time. 

Speaker 1  (09:21)
And what is the problem? So by I start my problems from there, then I'll be going to the state by step and I need to go to that database so it will be the database. And so that attain, I come to there and again, interpreter logging must be there. 

Speaker 1  (09:40)
So in that logging, when I get there, I need to say I need to execute is anything great breaks, and also that information that also I need to gather. And after that, I'll come to this notebook. What another power it is as having this EU I. 

Speaker 1  (10:00)
It's time for it must be that there will be some criticism of the data. Some of these participants first take me a long time. So like that, the schedule those things you could be saying but like the timing and it will be discovered that so much time to give the data by looking into the tag, I come to the hour. 

Speaker 1  (10:26)
I will find out the first piece. The source of the data calling of the data, how it came so suddenly, particularly as expected, as suddenly got program might become problem. In my joints and all before the joy what, kind of whatever the remaining category are there I? 

Speaker 1  (10:47)
Need to take that one. So and I need to check that number of partitions, how many number of participants are coming into that like in that an EFD C like creating of that particular data that also I need to say and I will see that joy must be written in such a way that it will be directed, joy must be written so we should be promising decision but what I have to do I have to follow the joint strategy so the joint strategy as well is described we treat. So irony, only based on that, like the broadcaster, and if it is not implemented, and this hour is the data private joint request that can I just follow that? 

Speaker 1  (11:34)
So there will be one intend with one data print that will be less amount of data around with 10 to 150 in between that and another would be the data which would be the data is more and that can be comparing competitor products and its implemented and the direction, then they are in implement this product so we are looking like a planet of one of some fast items and the second of some I like to follow, like if I see that both of the dfr, both have the moderate, like one load data and not see some of the GP of the data, then I will be there that I have some collaborative. 

Speaker 1  (12:15)
I will not go through that because there has suffered, it will be requested to be memory time like a one of the data trends used to be kicking one of the neighborhoods the memory could be not, then it will be again through this way out of my money issue. So for that again I will go to this. Option I go. 

Speaker 1  (12:33)
This is more like supper sophomo so that strategy I need to follow, because it will be not, it will be reduced that out of memory and disrupts or number faster for these hanging into father so but faster. It's when I get to go to this optimization, where I make them optimizing. One would be in the storage layer another layer task for me some layer in the monitoring layer so the storage layer gives the data it will be directly increased and into the hour data may be hierarchical structure like any folder structure. 

Speaker 1  (13:12)
That time I have to add the partition over there so that I can give it to that based on the debt and today are based on the region and as well, I need to add a context for that will be the stories where it will be optimized and second one or the Transformers in the trans. 

Speaker 2  (13:31)
Take the Woodman, yeah, submit a just wanted to understand. What is the difference between clustering? Okay? 

Speaker 2  (13:42)
And the partition I'm excited. What's a difference between clusting and partition? 

Speaker 1  (13:52)
So magnesium means that there is a ticket asset, and that data into Smart smartphone jumps, which would be in a different film test, small jumps of the quarter unit, create and restore it. And that could be called us Pakistan and clostering, I'd say that. I'm having you see some But I'll say 

Speaker 1  (14:38)
Based on their data and catego 

Speaker 2  (14:39)
You can hardly implement the. How will you implement a question? 

Speaker 1  (14:46)
The implications implementing that like insect, we are implementing the clustering. So for example, like we are using this optimized command and in that optimized command we are using and where we are impacting this gender. 

Speaker 2  (15:04)
What is that honest? Yeah, what is that order? 

Speaker 1  (15:10)
So if you do dish to further a pair in air in a physical order. So like in the data, it will be like, in fact, we are having a sequel server say that cluster index we are creating, we are creating the data in store. We need strategical order if you live even at the gender, then we would be optimized for competitive. 

Speaker 2  (15:28)
Can you give me some example? 

Speaker 1  (15:31)
So, for example, that we are having that we are doing that index, the index will and we are Hiking here. We have a good hike. The data into this circumstance, the data will not follow in order. 

Speaker 1  (15:46)
But when you will apply index, then you say that cluster index will apply in the sequence. Then, the data will be stored in it will slow with the actual physical order. Like, if you want to help you get after that. 

Speaker 1  (16:00)
Second chemical car, then you go after 1:02 like that. It could be sorted the order introduced. So like in this case, in fact, you will apply the gender. 

Speaker 1  (16:11)
Then, in this case, the data also includes store email, physical or 

Speaker 2  (16:17)
Ok, I'm going to hear it. So the last thing is instrumental or not incremental. If they are uploading more data into it, it will automatically apply the indexing there or it will not 

Speaker 1  (16:38)
I've recognized. 

Speaker 2  (16:41)
What is user optimize? What is the use of 

Speaker 1  (16:45)
I wrote some of the hikes like the data dot the Indian dot right like we are at the middle ride in the middle. Yes or nice and small fights. It is getting generated. 

Speaker 1  (16:56)
And when you produce not 5, it's generated every time you deal that you need to take a long time soon soon. 

Speaker 2  (17:01)
Private is creating a small file. Sorry, Howard is creating a small files. 

Speaker 1  (17:07)
So based on that package, so for example, we are having a 5 high TV or 5018 of data. 

Speaker 2  (17:15)
Tonight, I'm not talking about the partition. Let's say I don't have the partition. Okay? 

Speaker 2  (17:21)
It's only after the cluster. Will it also create a small files? 

Speaker 1  (17:27)
No, impacted, that means there are too much air multiple packages. So those are necessary passengers or necessified, which are in North Korea, like the it would be too reduced. That to delete those hikes for financial. 

Speaker 1  (17:41)
So yeah you, think this optimized and. I would interpret some policy. We are adding to that service after some deaths, then it would be 

Speaker 2  (17:50)
What is retention policy? What is the retention policy? How do we define it? 

Speaker 1  (17:57)
Hey, so in that optimized Superman, just to optimize the table, then they are. We are giving that number of days. We are adding so that would be based on that gigabyte for 47 deaths and we have increasing that sometimes. 

Speaker 1  (18:13)
So And so in this case, that of high sea, no vital Pape, the I'd say the checkpoint in the dental level, then the unnecessary flights it will be kept or other data types automatically is getting related. So this will be not required in the 

Speaker 2  (18:35)
Sorry, drinkers. No, no I didn't understand that. Why do we need the optimize? 

Speaker 1  (18:46)
So enough down to heights like inflation, Delta and arital law. When we are creating the data log, we are. It generates that multiple transaction types and so to lead to delete all these unnecessary flights we are using this optimiz. 

Speaker 2  (19:03)
I think what I'm in. There are necessary films 

Speaker 1  (19:07)
So, for example, for example, today we are having created a data of like the data and data log. It is already created and automatically after technology got created and now new next time. When we create in the passport, it will be needed from that checkpoint. 

Speaker 1  (19:26)
After the checkpoint, so now the past sequence, whatever the rating has, it was created, that would be unnecessary. That would be not required because the sequence they already created. So in this case, all the flight pay things here. 

Speaker 1  (19:39)
So those fights generate, we are cleaning it. So using this third optimizer that we are just adding that so in this episode, it's unnecessary getting 

Speaker 2  (19:55)
Okay, how do you plan the auto cluster? I'm sorry, how do you apply the auto cluster? Liquid cluster. 

Speaker 2  (20:10)
Yeah, liquid clustering, or have you heard of it? 

Speaker 1  (20:17)
I took a decelerate these things only I had forgotten that, but the things I ate 

Speaker 2  (20:26)
And how do you implement that rollback mechanism? 

Speaker 1  (20:34)
So we are having that time travel. So we look at personnel who are likely we are implemented. In that case, we are going to be we are meeting as a person. 

Speaker 1  (20:46)
The person who is getting created. So based on that person, do that particular hit so that we should be taste about this the time travel or the sunrise. And that or the particular person we want to ride that one only get. 

Speaker 1  (21:04)
So this concept is called a rollback. 

Speaker 2  (21:08)
Ok, what is auto loader? 

Speaker 1  (21:12)
Artful motors say that we are having streaming data, and it will be keep and coming the data. Pick up like multiple high cities keep on coming. So in this case, we are implementing the to read the inspector debt. 

Speaker 1  (21:26)
Data we are using this particular order so that will impact the data brings teacher and. When to read the animal, we call you work on the cloud platform. Either kind of be there. 

Speaker 1  (21:39)
So otherwise you will be not work. So in this car that we are using this cloud fights that parameters we are using to read that 5 so it would be created. Whenever a new fight would be complete. 

Speaker 2  (21:55)
And what is the alternative? Hi Bixby alternative of auto cloud auto loader 

Speaker 1  (22:07)
Just going here, it could be the string that defines it to be coming The past 1000 days, the real-time data will want to go. Then that will 

Speaker 2  (22:22)
Okay, have you heard of copy command? Yes, I mean, can you tell me the difference of where I'm going to use copy command and where I'm going to use copyright? 

Speaker 1  (22:38)
Five people might say that we are having 

Speaker 2  (22:41)
When I wanted the observer, which you have worked on 

Speaker 1  (22:45)
Ok. Yeah, so the property comment we are using order. I have used that there is a sequence of data commental live data coming and 2 acceptance data. 

Speaker 1  (22:57)
We are going in that bottle order way. But if you are having a specific sum of the heights, are there. And we adapt dance processes, where we wanted to be able to copy those prices that I will do in this copyright. 

Speaker 2  (23:15)
Arrika. Yeah, I have done with the interviews of me. Okay, then I'll share your feedback with the chatter. 

Speaker 2  (23:31)
Thanks for thank you. 
