aastha.sharma@turing.com - organizer
prakhar
amit.yadav@turing.com
arvind@interactivetbs.com

This content was generated by AI


Speaker 1  (00:00)
Going to record this interview. I hope you are fine. Thank you. 

Speaker 1  (00:05)
So we're already delayed 10 minutes, so I'll try to just cover it up next 50 minutes because I have after that another interview. So procur directly, I'll set the agenda, then start with the interview process. Okay, we are going to skip the introduction part. 

Speaker 1  (00:21)
Basically, the interview going to be 50 minutes next 30 minute. We are going to talk about the theoretical questions. You can answer to this question. 

Speaker 1  (00:30)
Based on the project, which you have done relatively agentic ki agent ki system, Jai, or any rack pipeline. Whatever you have built question will be mostly covering this sections of agent kilm land draft landscape, rack pipeline evaluations, observability, these kind of things we going to touch upon after that, I think half of the time will stick in here next half of the time, we are going to do kind of a hands. On coding ground. 

Speaker 1  (00:57)
Does it make? 

Speaker 2  (00:58)
Yes 

Speaker 1  (01:00)
Correct, so let's get started. So can you explain me Tool call implementations, agentic system 

Speaker 2  (01:09)
The phone call implementation. 

Speaker 1  (01:11)
Yes, how do you implement a tool call in a agentic system which we have built? 

Speaker 2  (01:17)
Yes, so basically. We define the Tools with the aggregate tool annotation, and we have to Bind those 2 and automatically It our agent, basically A2I mean oxygen agent would automatically look for those tools that will cause them correspondingly based on the prompts at 11. 

Speaker 1  (01:47)
So think Prakhar, very simple scenario, have you worked with autogen or any other framework too? 

Speaker 2  (01:54)
I've worked more than opportunity. 

Speaker 1  (01:56)
Autoen, okay, nice, so think like you're going to build a Chatbot very simple Chatbot, where there will be LLM. And there are few tool calls receive 2 or 31 tool call. They may be waves, another tool call, maybe something custom which you have written. 

Speaker 1  (02:18)
Thank you this too. Let's not complicate it. So whenever the query comes Your Chatbot get the answer so Chatbot either directly give the answer using LLM or if you require it, do tool call and provide the answers, right? 

Speaker 1  (02:37)
So for example, if you wanna write this tool, what are the things you keep in mind before writing a tool tool? Means I'm just thinking as simple as that is a python function, only accustom tool right? And you convert it in a tool, right? 

Speaker 1  (02:53)
I mean, whatever framework specific if you are using autogens, you know how to convert those function, call in a tool if you're using any other framework lanks and langrup, and there is another way. I mean, similar kind of a paradigm, but yeah, maybe specific to framework, there might be some syntax at terms may be different. You got that right? 

Speaker 2  (03:14)
Amina, okay. Okay, let me start with t Clear. Oh, one is the lines and answer. 

Speaker 2  (03:24)
One is the hygiene part, so a simple RAG will be there right for the documents. It is able to search it okay through the dance or sparse. That's an separate task to configure the search. 

Speaker 2  (03:40)
Okay and then basically the rack, and then we'll pass it to the 11 if they have to guard in the lm saying that if it is not able to find the answer, then we will see it it needs to go to the agents. So that's a separate part. So basically there will be a we can start, we can have that implementation of the router and the different tools we have. 

Speaker 2  (04:07)
We can configure, I was just thinking of creating a simple rap. And if it is not able to answer, then we will move to the agentic. 

Speaker 1  (04:15)
Why why you're creating raag prakher? My question was simple, did you understand what did I ask 

Speaker 2  (04:20)
Yeah, you want to have a simple Chatbot. 

Speaker 1  (04:24)
Right? Simple Chatbot, you have LLM I have 2 tool call integration. That's it nothing more than that, keep it simple. 

Speaker 1  (04:31)
Okay, let me as follow-up question. Okay, so this is simple scenario, which we have built, suppose that you have built that. Now whenever you are giving a question you getting the answers, right? 

Speaker 1  (04:40)
So while getting the answer for a given question, how do you know that whether the tool call is happened or not? 

Speaker 2  (04:50)
Through the loggings or mill logs tracing, you can figure it out. 

Speaker 1  (04:55)
Okay, let's suppose that the client is not allowing you to use any kind of observability tool or ML flow logs are any other tools. They said that hey, I don't have any partnership with vendors, they say very sensitive client right? They generally don't approve for any kind of tools immediately. 

Speaker 1  (05:17)
They takes time, so they said, hey, Prakhar, I think you have to build these small Chatbot. Now how would you observe log? What are your strategy without having those observability tool? 

Speaker 2  (05:34)
In the agent itself, we have the streaming. And that will automatically locks everything, whatever tools all happen. So through that way, we can do that, otherwise, the other goals will be. 

Speaker 1  (05:47)
In streaming, what is streaming? 

Speaker 2  (05:51)
It's a method, okay, where it, whatever the call happened inside the LLM or through the agents, it just locks them 

Speaker 1  (06:01)
No, but I understand is streaming is nothing but it's a live kind of a answer whenever it is giving the token, it is just printing that token so that instead of waiting for entire answer to be published you are it is just publishing the token so that you start reading this is called streaming in Chatbot. That is not call streaming what you explaining. But yeah, there are something available for that. 

Speaker 1  (06:26)
What 

Speaker 2  (06:26)
Step, sorry. 

Speaker 1  (06:29)
This is not streaming what he explained. What did I explain? That is streaming? 

Speaker 1  (06:32)
But what you are explaining that is something else, I think you are close to that, try thinking. 

Speaker 2  (06:39)
Show the exact graph streaming, or 

Speaker 1  (06:44)
No, I think anyway, so you were right like in LLM. You know, whenever you print the LLM output raw output. It has everything have you ever seen, like LLM rahput ever. 

Speaker 1  (06:59)
Just get the agent and print the row, don't structured? It generally, what we see LLM, structured out like plain English text, just go and print the raw Jason, you would see there, everything is available, like all the argument, the tool call null. If there is some tool call, it will say, function, call, what is the Max tokens. 

Speaker 1  (07:19)
What is the latency? What is the output? What is the input? 

Speaker 1  (07:23)
So sorry I think this was first question Prakar, so that's why I give answer but now it will be one way only I will just ask question you need to answer. Okay, so let's start from second downwards, okay. How do you handle long-term memory and your agents? 

Speaker 2  (07:40)
Long-term memory in an Egypt. Usually do the In the agents right I will semantic memorial buffer memory. We usually choose The classes that we usually 

Speaker 1  (08:06)
Can you explain semantic memory? What is semantic memory? 

Speaker 2  (08:09)
Yeah, in the 17th memory, it will check the corresponding highway. It just maps the actual meaning with t 

Speaker 1  (08:21)
What is difference between episodic and semantic memory? Episodic and semantic. 

Speaker 2  (08:29)
I know about the buffer and the semantic note. 

Speaker 1  (08:33)
Where did you use buffer memory? 

Speaker 2  (08:35)
Yeah, when we have the long list of chat? Okay, so there we are taking. 

Speaker 1  (08:42)
Does artisan support buffer memory? Does autojan have any class for buffer memory? 

Speaker 2  (08:49)
Not sure about it because I'm talking about the RAG one, not the agent one. 

Speaker 1  (08:52)
So you for RAG, which framework you are used 

Speaker 2  (08:55)
I've used the line chain. 

Speaker 1  (08:58)
Ok, there, I see. There's a Buffalo, very concept. Okay, so you have used landscain for ren, and for agent you have used autogen, is that correct understanding? 

Speaker 1  (09:09)
Ok. What is your process for managing state? And context 

Speaker 2  (09:16)
For maintaining the state's Actually, for the state one, we usually have the land graph, okay, not the land chain, but we're not maintaining the states there. 

Speaker 1  (09:31)
Let's say you have to maintain a state, then how would you maintain that state? 

Speaker 2  (09:36)
I will use the simple dictionary with threats. Okay, with the sessions and that way we can maintain them. 

Speaker 1  (09:46)
Dictionary is mutable or imutable. 

Speaker 2  (09:49)
It will be it will be immuted. 

Speaker 1  (09:53)
You can't send dictionary, you can change now. Let's say there is a name tracker. I can update that name prakher name Astha, so it becomes mutable mutable, right? 

Speaker 2  (10:05)
Yeah, it will create a new table every time. 

Speaker 1  (10:11)
So you can add anything right, mutable. What do you understand are mutable and mutable? 

Speaker 2  (10:16)
Mutable, if we can change something correct? 

Speaker 1  (10:20)
You cannot change. 

Speaker 2  (10:24)
Dictionary dictionary, right dictionary, we can 

Speaker 1  (10:27)
Python dictionary, right? Let's say there is a dictionary. 

Speaker 2  (10:31)
That you can change it, but like couples, we cannot change. Update. The news at the top 

Speaker 1  (10:40)
Okay, prakur, you have worked with rack pipeline. 

Speaker 2  (10:43)
Yeah, that taught me 

Speaker 1  (10:45)
You're very confident and Reck pipeline. Let's start from there. So what kind of chunking strategy you have used? 

Speaker 1  (10:56)
And why did you use that chunking strategy? 

Speaker 2  (10:59)
Yeah, I mean we, I have used the context sentence aware chunking. There we have passed the separators and the overlap, and they took at the size that you want to size. There are multiple, also. 

Speaker 2  (11:24)
There are fixed chunking, also where we provide the size and the overlap. 

Speaker 1  (11:30)
Okay, why did you choose that chunking strategy? 

Speaker 2  (11:34)
Uh, chunking strategy to give the context to the LLM. Also, we are storing into the we're creating that chunks, we're getting in the impediments, so all those chunks relevant will be embedded and stored into the leftoctor database so that for the user query, they can be semantic surge along with it. 

Speaker 1  (12:00)
Okay. So any other chunking strategy Prashar? 

Speaker 2  (12:07)
Yeah, I told you fixed chunking, and the 17th Chunky, do I 

Speaker 1  (12:12)
Okay, so fix and what framework we have used to implement that Lanchan, only 

Speaker 2  (12:18)
It's just a class. 

Speaker 1  (12:21)
Okay, it is recursive characteristic. What are those 2 parameters, it accept? 

Speaker 2  (12:28)
The pitch size and your overlap. 

Speaker 1  (12:32)
Chunk size and chunk overlap. What is chunk size? You have taken a very big 

Speaker 2  (12:39)
Usually take the 1000 okay, 1000 chunks. 100? 

Speaker 1  (12:55)
Okay. My question was if you take big chunk size, what is the problem? 

Speaker 2  (13:01)
Have you take a big chunk size, um? So they'll be token, issue token. Sighs will be overflow to concise. 

Speaker 2  (13:13)
Overflow, problems will be there. 

Speaker 1  (13:15)
Why prakra? Let me explain you why you think like token issue. So let's say you have taken 10000 chunks, okay? 

Speaker 1  (13:23)
I have taken 100 chunks, size Okay, you have taken very large strength size. I have taken very small tongue chunk size so chunk size is nothing but whatever the documents is there that tokens you have taken around 10000 let's say at high level, I am assuming one token is one word which is not exactly, but let's assume that right at a high level so 10000 token you have taken, I have taken 100 tokens only. And that tokens, after changing, what do we do, we pass to the embedding model? 

Speaker 1  (13:53)
Right? So if you pass that embedding model embedding model, what does it do it convert those chunk into a vector representative. Isn't it? 

Speaker 1  (14:02)
So let's say any beding model we have used. Let's say of 8 700 length right vector length, so those chunk size, which you have passed, which is 10000 it is going to represent the 7 700 embeddings. Mine also the 101 also 700. 

Speaker 1  (14:18)
So where is the token issue? 

Speaker 2  (14:23)
Yeah, I mean, you're talking about a dimension that if you're going to create, okay. 

Speaker 1  (14:27)
What you're talking tell me, I didn't understand you understand my thinking, what I'm thinking, what based on your conversation try to convince me. What is the problem? 

Speaker 2  (14:36)
Yeah, you're right that it will go to create the embeddings at the end. Okay, but there will be I mean, it will not be sufficient to search for the query, right? So let's say it is, let's say my context is huge. 

Speaker 2  (14:55)
Okay and I'm writing some way query, so the mapping will not going to be um, because it will find the similar meaning. Okay, from that token, basically on the embeddings, so if you're not going to match There will be a problem with a matching. Do not be able to find the correct relevant mapping also Because there will be a matterator of the chunks, will that will going to be stored? 

Speaker 2  (15:28)
Sure, I mean, what I understood. It will not go into find a similar meaning. Because if we pass along context or long jump store 

Speaker 1  (15:48)
Transared, aladdy. 

Speaker 2  (15:50)
Yeah 

Speaker 1  (15:51)
So let's go for the next step part embedding model you have used 

Speaker 2  (15:56)
Have you used ABG model? 

Speaker 1  (16:01)
Which model? 

Speaker 2  (16:02)
BGE open. 

Speaker 1  (16:04)
Busy, okay, okay, what was the dimension? 

Speaker 2  (16:08)
100 and 1500 something 

Speaker 1  (16:12)
That you, why did you choose this? 

Speaker 2  (16:16)
Why did we choose that? That was the Yeah, that was the ask basic 

Speaker 1  (16:25)
You are a data scientist, you should decide, no, if someone says that hey, you go, yeah, I use that, tell me that's 

Speaker 2  (16:31)
To that after tuning it, we find it that's appropriate for me. 

Speaker 1  (16:36)
Okay, alright. Which vector database you have used? 

Speaker 2  (16:41)
We are using the vector store provided by the database 

Speaker 1  (16:45)
Did it agree? What is the name? 

Speaker 2  (16:50)
Vectors, too sorry. Vector story. 

Speaker 1  (16:57)
Do you know what indexing does it use is? 

Speaker 2  (17:01)
What indexing does it uses? Make sure all 

Speaker 1  (17:08)
You know, what do you mean by indexing? Do you understand indexing concept inducted database? Can you explain? 

Speaker 2  (17:17)
Okay, so for all the it will store a key value of the vector with a corresponding chance. Okay, so all these chunks will going to be indexed. 

Speaker 1  (17:29)
Very good, what is AN 

Speaker 2  (17:32)
Yennis, I mean And if for the neighbour so it will find the nearest neighbour I mean, how does it work? 

Speaker 1  (17:48)
Basically indexing algorithm is family of AN what you state's very high level. It's 100000 feet away. It lies in the family of Ann algorithm, all the indexing algorithm. 

Speaker 1  (18:02)
There is a name called HNS W inverted file indexing product contigations. 

Speaker 2  (18:08)
Sorry, search and ANM is basically the searching. The nearest label 

Speaker 1  (18:17)
Okay, how do you improve reranking? How do you improve improvement? 

Speaker 2  (18:22)
Yeah, multiple ways to do it. First is the we usually configure the MMR which is responsible 

Speaker 1  (18:30)
LNR ok. Can you explain what is M? M? 

Speaker 2  (18:35)
So they're relevant Chang that we received. Let's say it is coming. 

Speaker 1  (18:40)
So you said, see Prakar, you are contradicting your contradicting each other. See you said mmr, and then say saying that reciprocal, ranking that is called Mr. mm R is different. 

Speaker 1  (18:55)
Mmr is maximum marginal relevancy. You said, but your name MMR and you saying that rescue to ranking all things are always 

Speaker 2  (19:02)
I can't talk about that, see it tells the index of the local rank of the relevant document that we have received, let's say it's come in the second position so the formula is one divided by R. So it will give you the point 5, let's say so 

Speaker 1  (19:19)
What is mean? Then it is M. R righting, you explain what is M. 

Speaker 1  (19:25)
R? 

Speaker 2  (19:25)
Mr. is basically tells how diversified we want the data from the LM from the searching solution. 

Speaker 1  (19:32)
Again I'm on ranking only. I'm not talking about maximum marginal relevancy. I said MMRMR see you said M. 

Speaker 1  (19:41)
R right now, I'm asking MM. R. 

Speaker 2  (19:45)
I told you I am talking about the mmr, only, so finding the diversified data from the from the search, how diversified you on the data. 

Speaker 1  (19:57)
How do you calculate that diversification? 

Speaker 2  (20:01)
Yeah, there are several. I'm just recording I ready to read about that. 

Speaker 1  (20:08)
Government implemented this 

Speaker 2  (20:09)
No, I want to replicate map through mapping or 

Speaker 1  (20:13)
Curry I think now it's open to you. Let's peak one topic which you have implemented, and which you are 100% confidence. Let's take that topic topic is yours. 

Speaker 2  (20:23)
Yeah, the rack pipeline. I can talk about 

Speaker 1  (20:27)
So I improve the retrieval in ripe pipeline. 

Speaker 2  (20:32)
Okay, I told you about the MRM. R. 

Speaker 1  (20:35)
And then my question, just follow me. See if I am giving that much liberty, then you should listen to me. As you know, I'm saying that have you worked on retrieval improvement? 

Speaker 1  (20:48)
Okay, so this forget about these 2, no more ammr and M. R. R. 

Speaker 1  (20:54)
It's forget about this. Any other techniques you know, for improving the retrieval. 

Speaker 2  (21:01)
Um. Okay. So If there is some issue that we find in the there are several things right starting with a chunking. 

Speaker 2  (21:13)
Okay, then the embedding, so if we're not getting the correct data Song, ok, we check the We check several metro draigas metrics. Basically, okay? 

Speaker 1  (21:31)
Bottles. 

Speaker 2  (21:33)
Recall value. Okay. This is context. 

Speaker 2  (21:35)
Recession, answer relevance, and your Faithfulness, so these are 

Speaker 1  (21:42)
Do you know precision at the rate can recall at the rate K? You understand this, I'll create a scenario based question, be honest. If you are not clear, then I think senior best question do you difficult? 

Speaker 1  (21:55)
If you are clear, then only I'll ask tell me you are clear with that resistance. Okay. So my question is, let's say in your RAG system, your recall at the red case, very high. 

Speaker 1  (22:07)
It's almost 100%. Okay, you don't need to bother about that. But precision at the rate K is very low. 

Speaker 1  (22:18)
What are the things you would look at? As a first step, recall is very high. Precision at the rate case is very low. 

Speaker 1  (22:26)
What may go wrong? What are the things you will start? Looking immediately. 

Speaker 2  (22:33)
Yeah, the call is very high. That means the data that we have retrieved Vs the ground data is almost equal. So that's why the recall value is high. 

Speaker 2  (22:45)
And the precision is basically Whatever the query that we are sending to the bottom and the Okay, the precision right questions. And With the actual contest that we have The the answer that this LM is given. Okay, so there is some the I'll check for the Precision is very precision is very good. 

Speaker 2  (23:22)
So I'll check for the Blood sugar checks, the answer is not accurate. The twin cancer is not Save the recall value as high recession will be low. 

Speaker 1  (23:44)
I mean, this can happen. That's the scenario lens in your pipeline. 

Speaker 2  (23:50)
So I'll try to map both right precision. Both the time both cannot happen. Bixby Try to find a comment 

Speaker 1  (24:03)
Sorry, but this is a real problem. You know, you will not get both are balanced and both are always up. You may get, in real scenario, sometimes recall is very good, but precision is down as a data engineer principles, GenAI, scientist, you need to understand why it is going down. 

Speaker 1  (24:21)
We have to improve that it is not always like you will get kind of a easy problem where you see both are high, both are low, you need to improve. There are the tricky situation, and these are the most of the scenario gates, sometimes you will get not sometimes, so many times you will face this. 

Speaker 2  (24:38)
Maybe I'm not facing 

Speaker 1  (24:42)
I'll let prasari, have any questions for me. Thank you, thank you, bye all the best. 
