
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Can we some of the camp? Yes, sure. 

Speaker 1  (00:15)
Yeah, okay, kya. 

Speaker 2  (00:19)
Let's start with a brief introduction for your set. 

Speaker 1  (00:22)
Yes, sure. Uh, so myself, prakha I were on 14 years of experience in yahi and L along with that I have a good experience on the data engineering side as well. So um, current time working with emphasis on previously, I work with the um. 

Speaker 1  (00:42)
Banking domain ah, which is norgan, standard and si. So currently I'm working on the application which is more into the educational domain. But overall my appearance is in banking domain. 

Speaker 1  (00:55)
So currently we have an application where we are using the teacher and the which is used by the teacher and the students. Okay And based on that, we are getting the grades there also, we have created the chatbots kind of application where we are putting all the documentations, and then the user conquer along with that, we have another service, which is Which is the getting the feedback of the agents through the calls. So these are 2 models that one are working on. 

Speaker 1  (01:34)
Also, we have built-in some media pipelines on the returning side. Along with that, we are working with this data breaks as park is Kana, and sorry, snowflake. 

Speaker 2  (01:48)
Ok, can you talk about your database experience like Weather, have you used determines? 

Speaker 1  (01:56)
Ok, so in the data breaks, we are using it for the for the notebooks for running the jobs and pipelines. So all those things we do. Apart from that, we have used the amalgows. 

Speaker 1  (02:09)
Also worse Some of the model versions 

Speaker 2  (02:14)
And which project is this? 

Speaker 1  (02:17)
This is AI ready. Adi, yeah, this is I ready. I'm talking about the irid application, which I'm currently working on. 

Speaker 2  (02:29)
Can you start from the problem statement? Side, like what exactly were you solving there? And like? 

Speaker 2  (02:34)
What was your role in that? 

Speaker 1  (02:37)
Yes, I were working as a individual contributor. And so I can talk about one of the problem checking that we have. I can talk about the Chatbot first. 

Speaker 1  (02:49)
So when the chatbots we have the list of documents. Okay all the documents all the PDF and all the dogs, okay all the transcripts coming up from the videos so all those things we have added then we are doing the chunking symbols, okay, and then we are storing it to the affected database. Vector database we are using the pindbs, and then the user can carry it through the proms, and then using the similarities based. 

Speaker 1  (03:23)
We are just giving them the answer that was the problem sitting, and how this is not solved. 

Speaker 2  (03:35)
Ok, so from your control 

Speaker 1  (03:41)
Yeah, because they are asking me to relocate to Bangalore, and this is my work for home opportunity. So I don't want to relocate. That's why I'm looking for that change. 

Speaker 2  (03:54)
Are you planning to continue with all from home? Or are you planning to be now? 

Speaker 1  (03:58)
Yeah, I'm planning to Admin. I can work from office as well but it should be in near my location. Where are you, sir, Noida? 

Speaker 2  (04:09)
Nide potted. Okay, let's talk about, like out of all this project that you've done. Which one would you say has been the most interesting or challenging? 

Speaker 1  (04:26)
Yeah, I can talk about the other one where we are. Giving the response. I mean the feedback to the agent feedback of the agent, so the application was that we are receiving the multiple transcripts, and then we have to, so let's say there will. 

Speaker 1  (04:47)
There was a huge Transcript, right? So for each of how we are generating Transcript, choosing the quinities software. So first those transcripts get there in the databases. 

Speaker 1  (04:58)
Then, we are enhancing those transit using the stitching method or vivid. We are removing some lot of um unwanted calls using the bird model. And then once we have that model, then we are sending it to the llms for the for the training for the output. 

Speaker 1  (05:18)
Basically so in between we have used the cashes as well using the cashew tokens LLM tokens basically and then we are getting the output in the prompt as well as for their multiple cases right is a temptative carrier sold or not. All those parameters then we were for each of the parameters. We were getting better, normal and then we are getting that responses. 

Speaker 1  (05:46)
And the reason, along with that in the in the journey. So we have also we have the AI arbt, which is which is our smmes, basically, they are validating our data and using some agents, sorry, angular application we have building and they are going there and then they're doing the verification. So that's what the application was so the challenging part was the learning. 

Speaker 1  (06:16)
First of all, and the things that keeps on changing. Okay so maintaining that as well. Then, we switched to the lancheon. 

Speaker 1  (06:26)
Also, we have created the pipelines. These were the few challenges that we faced. 

Speaker 2  (06:40)
Have you designed any design or implemented any system from the scratch? 

Speaker 1  (06:47)
No, I didn't get any chance. But I figured chance I led. Hot hot here, ok. 

Speaker 2  (06:57)
Ok. Luxuries launched a lunch troops on the bottom of the potato. And how are you using AI? 

Speaker 2  (07:16)
In your workflow, right now 

Speaker 1  (07:20)
So we are using the LLM models, okay, like OpenAI models. So that's how we are using it. You see through the prompts and everything. 

Speaker 2  (07:35)
Ok, is that for code generation? 

Speaker 1  (07:38)
Ok, no, for the code generation, we are using the co-pilots GitHub copilot, so we are for the code generation we are using it also in the database we are using the genius. What are you doing, Jenny? Is that Jenny jenny? 

Speaker 1  (07:56)
I mean that's an AI for the data means. Auditorium. 

Speaker 2  (08:03)
Ok, got it, got it. Got it. Any, can you talk about a use case where you used it in database like what was the problem statement and how did you use it? 

Speaker 2  (08:13)
What was the outcome? 

Speaker 1  (08:16)
Um, ok, so let's on the lunch inside we have to, so let's say we have one API, okay, for the concurrency purposes. We have used. I mean, there are multiple Multiple multiple parts we have used the notebook, but I'm telling you one of the parts we are we are synchronising or we are making the threats okay for each for all of the request and we want to train them to the LM so on based on that we have created the executors. 

Speaker 1  (08:48)
To the polls, executive pools and there we are sending that request and each request is running parallelly. Sir, there we have used the data graph. Recent, your IO Vs Miss you. 

Speaker 1  (09:02)
Also, we have a consume. The rays also, but B that was that that was not able to perform. So that's why we done that. 

Speaker 1  (09:14)
But we are using the basics. What's what? 

Speaker 2  (09:25)
In terms of text tax like besides python, what do you use primarily? 

Speaker 1  (09:30)
We use in the piece park. Ok, if I spark scholar's park 

Speaker 2  (09:36)
No. How about any experience with Java script? 

Speaker 1  (09:45)
Yes, I have davas trip I have. I have worked on the angular side as well. Long time back typistic, basic, basically, so in mobile 

Speaker 2  (09:58)
Have you? Didn't you stand with production systems like production life systems? 

Speaker 1  (10:07)
No, why didn't get chance you're talking about deployment or 

Speaker 2  (10:11)
No, no, no. Just like working on process systems. Right? 

Speaker 2  (10:14)
Like, let's say, let's say there's a process system. You got a bug and you had to resolve that bug, did you face? 

Speaker 1  (10:24)
Yes, I did. But not much exposure on that 

Speaker 2  (10:28)
Ok, so all these stuff that you built, it did not go to production, is it? 

Speaker 1  (10:34)
Yeah, it is it. Is there in the production but so we work on the users storage right? If something comes up, then we create a user tour? 

Speaker 1  (10:43)
And then we work so basically we are fixing their production issue but. Not specifically going there and facing it all the way. 

Speaker 2  (10:54)
Ok, then talk to me about Most complicated bug that you have solved. 

Speaker 1  (11:04)
That comes with the pipeline. Ok? So basically some data is not appropriate to pars. 

Speaker 1  (11:12)
Okay, so there were many things from the feature engineering side when we are doing the eds. So there we face lot of challenges extracting the features out of the single feature that was challenging because that requires a lot of business knowledge. So we have to communicate with the business people to understand the business first and then we will come up with the minimal features that can make and train off. 

Speaker 1  (11:37)
So those were the things that were challenging. But the rest was easy. 

Speaker 2  (11:49)
You hoped to the US clients, right? Yeah Can you tell me your understanding of the sprint process when it comes to working with the US clients and it? Did you face any challenges in that process? 

Speaker 1  (12:09)
Yeah, you're talking about the agile. Yeah, jail challenges. You can talk about what we do in the running street. 

Speaker 1  (12:21)
We have the backlog, then we have to groom, that okay, first. And then we comes up basically we get the epic and from that epic, we have to create the Requirement, basically the documentation that we need to do high level and low level. And then we create the stories around it, the stories are created by the master only. 

Speaker 1  (12:45)
But we give our we have the refinement core okay in the refinement, we have to give them, okay so how much time it will gonna take and has so first we get a design documentation. First, then we take that time, then we can implement the stories. So based on that, we create the multiple tasks accordingly, but on the previous print, we have to make sure that our design got completed. 

Speaker 1  (13:07)
Then, only we switched to the next print. For the implementation. The refinement is done, then we have the 15 days of spring with demo then we have 3 months of psi. 

Speaker 1  (13:19)
Again we give the demo So that's how we usually 

Speaker 2  (13:33)
You built a lot of AI. ML system, which one would you say has been like, the most rewarding or the one where you had told, you know, Put a lot of effort. 

Speaker 1  (13:47)
They are the current one. The current government. I worked on the ticketing system also, but that was already. 

Speaker 1  (13:54)
I don't know if it is still work because that was built on the previous model before the ChatGPT. Sir. Yeah, I have the knowledge of that. 

Speaker 1  (14:07)
But it's not that also was challenging. But the current one is more interesting and challenging. You can see 

Speaker 2  (14:18)
What sort of brain are you looking for going forward? Like, given that you have some back and experience some AI experience, right, yeah, how do you look at going forward. You 

Speaker 1  (14:30)
The same role I'm looking for not interployment. What if I get chance I can at overall more into development? I am looking for 

Speaker 2  (14:40)
What development in terms of it just back and systems are like age integrity. 

Speaker 1  (14:44)
It's agenting, a agent. AI is Ok. Agent, a models pipelines that I know 

Speaker 2  (15:01)
Ok. Yes, Russian classical models, decision tree, neural networks Can you talk about this? You've mentioned SBN decision, tree naive, bias and neural networks. 

Speaker 2  (15:20)
Do you understand what these are and like where like where are they used? Which scenario are they used? 

Speaker 1  (15:29)
Yeah, for the E d's purposes, we used to have this sbm. All the regression that we need to do random forest just to check the performance of the model. And to understand the data, is it linear nonlinear? 

Speaker 1  (15:41)
So based on that, we pick that model, neural network are more into the advancement version of the American city where you can't Where you cannot predict based on the classification models where you have the hidden layers, okay, and the input and the multiple Things you can do I win in. Terms of augmentation weekend, that's a part of the training. Then, we send a dear to the deep learning hidden layers, we specified and the outcome. 

Speaker 1  (16:12)
So basically we used to do that for the classification model if we are not able to solve the problem with the basic model. 

Speaker 2  (16:28)
Ok I'm good from my side. If you have any questions, you ask me. 

Speaker 1  (16:31)
Yeah, can you tell me about the project and the rules, please? 

Speaker 2  (16:41)
Project is basically there a an analytics provider like AP2BS in the construction domain, the companies from Sweden. Basically, they capture a lot of data about construction projects, right? Like manually automated ways platform to people who want that Getter, right? 

Speaker 2  (17:09)
Like people who want to work on customer points like architects and stuff. Right? So they started in one geography. 

Speaker 2  (17:17)
They acquired basically similar companies in other geographies. Also, so now they have 45 different products with like, you know, different text, different structures, different data structure. And all that right. 

Speaker 2  (17:32)
So now they are looking to basically build a global platform right and at the same time upgrade their platform when they're doing this, because a lot of like manual activity. And manual personal there right now in their current systems, right? So they want to be able to do as much as possible, use AI able to its fullest. 

Speaker 2  (17:56)
Like potential, right, automate, most of it improve basically the kind of insights they're providing to their customers the kind of analytics they're providing, right? Yeah, that's basically the point. 

Speaker 1  (18:11)
Ok, ok, understood. Yeah, good, yeah. 

Speaker 2  (18:17)
Ok, thank you very much. 
