This content was generated by AI


Speaker 1  (00:03)
You can pick no problems you 

Speaker 2  (00:05)
I just messaged him. 

Speaker 1  (00:07)
Yeah, you can go So let's assume like your consumer job is already rated data from the topic right now. You want to re-rate a data, how you will like, read the data game. 

Speaker 2  (00:23)
Okay, sorry, sorry, I'm lost. So you said, I'm reaching the data from the passport topic. 

Speaker 1  (00:30)
And your job is already read the data, right? You commit the offset, right? Then, now you need to re-read the data again, right? 

Speaker 1  (00:39)
How you will rere the data. 

Speaker 2  (00:44)
It's already personed, or it's not processed. 

Speaker 1  (00:49)
You can assume anything like it's a processed or not processed, right? It's just like you consume date from your first job, and then you committed the offset. Right now, you need to rewread that data again. 

Speaker 2  (01:02)
I'll read it from the target system. 

Speaker 1  (01:06)
Don't no, you need to be read it from the kafata topic only. Is there any other way you can think about that? 

Speaker 2  (01:16)
Why we're keep storing it after its processed event? 

Speaker 1  (01:21)
Any other consumer can also read it right, or sometimes it happen like we are reading it, write that data, right? We write down the data into the raw raw air, right. Then on the bronze layer analytics layer, we get to know, like that data is corrupted, or some like mismatch of the data. 

Speaker 1  (01:38)
Now you need to reprocess the data How you will do it? First, you need to read it again from the topic. You can assume that scenario. 

Speaker 2  (01:49)
I mean, what the kaffca do is it just steam the data to the multiple subscribers one of time? And if it 

Speaker 1  (02:02)
So it will now. Could you please repeat it again? What 

Speaker 2  (02:05)
Right, just send out the data to the multiple subscribers. 

Speaker 1  (02:09)
This multiple subscriber, it sends 

Speaker 2  (02:12)
Multiple cons. 

Speaker 1  (02:13)
Or you or you need to be consumed, right? It is not sending the data to the consumer you need to be consumed it from the topics right? Data is data is located in the topics, right? 

Speaker 2  (02:27)
Okay. I mean, I'm just thinking 1 second, so it comes in. The See if it is not processed. 

Speaker 2  (02:36)
Okay, let me talk about the relay first. So if it is, there are multiple scenarios, one scenario would be that data is processed. Read it and it been dumped into the bones layer at the layer. 

Speaker 1  (02:50)
Right? 

Speaker 2  (02:51)
Repeat has not been done right? So if it is not been read, it will be there in the In nethew, it's in the topic itself. I mean, the consumer, what you said Q so those things need to be, we can retry that okay, or it will be retried as per see in the SMS. 

Speaker 2  (03:13)
Also if the message doesn't goes to the correct, if it doesn't consume correctly, it will be going to a DL and DL Q has the right choice methods, right? So that needs to be configured. So if we're going to reach our earlier. 

Speaker 1  (03:28)
No, but my question here is preca we already consumed it. We committed the offset right once the offset is committed, then. You have given the acknowledgement to the Kafka topic like I already read it. 

Speaker 1  (03:42)
But now you need to be re-read it again, right? Is there any other another way you can think about how you will read it. 

Speaker 2  (03:50)
But I have the data in The Bronx layer, correct. Whatever we have the data in the source system, it will be there in The Bronx layer. 

Speaker 1  (03:59)
Yeah, it is available in the bronze layer, but you will get to know like data is like A. There is some issue in the bronze layer. Something happened, deleted or something, right? 

Speaker 1  (04:09)
It can be happened everything with the bronze layer. I'm just giving you a scenario, right? How you will tackle that situation. 

Speaker 2  (04:18)
Yeah, I mean, while Okay, not on the carforce side, but on the adless side or on the pipeline side, we just keep the data into the archive. 

Speaker 1  (04:29)
Operator I'm not like good in the S. Your cloud, I never worked on, right, I'm just giving you a basic data engineering stuff, right? 

Speaker 2  (04:38)
It was after not maintaining it. So I'm not sure about it, I can talk about the pipeline things. But I've got it. 

Speaker 1  (04:45)
You're not maintaining Okay, so what you are handling on the Kaza side? You are handling only consumer jobs or how it 

Speaker 2  (04:54)
We are considering job. 

Speaker 1  (04:55)
That's a like a logic that logic should be used in the consumer. Only I'm giving you a clue again right. If you're handling the consumer right, then on the consumer side, you are like committing the offset, right? 

Speaker 1  (05:12)
So you can handle it through consumer only not the on the Admin side 

Speaker 2  (05:20)
Okay, I am not able to understand the scen. 

Speaker 1  (05:23)
What you can Slario is like AI will make it simple right? Let's forget about the kafra ok? There is a one source system. 

Speaker 1  (05:33)
You are extracting the data from the source system right? And once you extract the data, then you are lending it onto the S3 location. Or any Annie in your cloud button right? 

Speaker 1  (05:46)
Jesus bucket or your blob storage. Anywhere right? So once that data is landed on the S3 or some other buttage, right? 

Speaker 1  (05:55)
You are committing, you are acknowledging the system, right? I have read it right so that they are like updating the offset as well. That is your water water marketing column, you can say right? 

Speaker 1  (06:08)
You are updating the time stamp right? You read it now like you get to know in your S3 layer right? When you process the data and like you are you publish some reports there on the reports you get to know, like there is a like an issue in the data, right, or might be someone deleted the records or anything can happen right now just assume it like you need to reprocess the data I know. 

Speaker 1  (06:32)
Like on the production side, nobody can delete the data, right? They don't have the permission, but for our situation over scenario, we are deleting the data. Now, you need to reprocess the data right? 

Speaker 1  (06:43)
You need to re extract the data how you will re. Extract 

Speaker 2  (06:46)
Yeah, I mean, I can tell you what we do is once it lands into the still avision of ADS location, we push that file into the archive folder, okay with a time stampa right so so that we get to know okay, this particular file as process and move the file folder now from that folder, if you want to reprocess it, we can Pick that file for that particular date, and then we can recrocess. It 

Speaker 1  (07:15)
To how how you will like, pick that pilots are like a manual effort, or it's like automatic. 

Speaker 2  (07:20)
John, it never happened like there's some issue with if there's some issue with the opposite team, also, they have they take care of. 

Speaker 1  (07:28)
You're saying, like, so let's assume you are now explaining like some piles located onto the spree location right? You process the data once the process is done. Your logic, you implemented a logic like that. 

Speaker 1  (07:42)
Raw air file is moved to the archival folder. Right now, you need to reprocess the data. How your process will go onto the archival because it is look, so if we trigger best. 

Speaker 2  (07:55)
Check if you're looking for a new push again and to that location. It's going to process it 

Speaker 1  (08:00)
So it's like a manual effort, right? There's a manual you need to. You need to upload onto the S3 location or some other buckets that will generate an event, right? 

Speaker 2  (08:12)
Are you considering our side if you want to do that? What we do is we ask the opposition team to load it again because of their some disturbances in the data so we don't do it manually. It's other teams up to Quick kehta, okay. 

Speaker 1  (08:29)
Okay? So On the steam didn't do there is a letter if I will ask you like to make it automated, right? You need to be right from logic in your code, right? 

Speaker 1  (08:42)
Could you please handle that scenario like you don't need to be 

Speaker 2  (08:48)
Okay, what I can think of is the validation? See, I'm just thinking 

Speaker 1  (08:55)
The validation is the like a thing we always implemented right whenever we are expecting. The data pile is landed on our ST location, we start the validation right? What is the file format of the files? 

Speaker 1  (09:06)
How many records we are getting? What is the naming convention? We are, we are falling or not. 

Speaker 1  (09:10)
What is the size of the file? All these things we started once the data is landed other than validation. 

Speaker 2  (09:16)
Sorry, can you please advertised? What can happen on the file site so that we need to reproce it again. I mean it from deleted. 

Speaker 2  (09:24)
The data is used from the bones layer, okay, or maybe this could be one of the scenario. Some data has been committed some or not. Okay, this is the other scenarios, so are these scenarios or 

Speaker 1  (09:37)
Let me let me explain you okay. So scenario can be anything like either I deleted or like from the source system, we get it like multiple records are generated to the one ID right, that can be possible right, one too many relationship, but that should not be the case in our production right, but it is they are like push that data due to their some. Source system corruption or something happened there side, right? 

Speaker 1  (10:00)
They push the data, and now you are getting the multiple records. For like, we can say that duplicate records or like one to many relationship generating anything you can assume. Now you need to reprocess the data. 

Speaker 1  (10:12)
The main question is you need to reprocess the data. You can take any assumption like file is deleted or anything, right? You just need to reprocess the data, right? 

Speaker 1  (10:24)
Because your ETL pipelines should be like that. If you want to reprocess the data, right? You don't need to be add-on the like manual leopard there, right? 

Speaker 1  (10:34)
It should be just, you need to pass on some parameter, and it It should be triggered, and it can handle all these things. 

Speaker 2  (10:43)
We can change the watermark column of not change. Update the watermark column to the previous change, and then we determine the job so 

Speaker 1  (10:51)
Update to update is supported in the That you had. Launch layer or huger analytics layer. Are you using any like open table format table? 

Speaker 1  (11:04)
I think you are not using it. 

Speaker 2  (11:06)
What we usually do is we update the work amount column to the previous date. If you want to repool the data again, then we just run the journal going to Delete curvature cooking just reflect the data from that particular date. 

Speaker 1  (11:22)
Any other any other process you can take 

Speaker 2  (11:26)
I'm not sure it's open source. 

Speaker 1  (11:31)
Open table, open table format like aparthoody and aparthe iceberg. And that make, I think that margin update statement, as our likely to supported, nowadays clearly cleared about aperture. 

Speaker 2  (11:44)
Sorry to win the silver layer. 

Speaker 1  (11:48)
If its courses, so how you will update the how you will update that watermark columma, on your S3 location or your adls, or your Gs budget, how you will do it. 

Speaker 2  (11:59)
Dear, okay, these are too many scenario. Let me talk about one so for more than a day, so one scenario would be like, we have the for one particular ID, we have multiple records in the silver layer, we don't Put the duplicates, so we usually use the merge command to update if there's an update from the bronze for that particular. ID we just update it, otherwise you will insert it. 

Speaker 2  (12:24)
Protect for diagnostic, usually use a large generator and for the other scenarios. Which sorry for about the You are asking something like property questions, sorry. 

Speaker 1  (12:39)
My question was like how you will update that watermark column. Anyone HD FS intellect, sorry, data lake or US3 data lake or your ADS data lake. 

Speaker 2  (12:50)
First of now, we are doing it manually. We're not sure about 

Speaker 1  (12:53)
Thank you. So you can think about, because, like As Anna like, I ETL designer retil pipeline designer or data architect, you need to be think about these scenarios, right? While building your retail pipeline. 

Speaker 1  (13:07)
It should be supported by historical load incremental load read, try if you will do the retry, if you need to reprocess the data right? 

Speaker 2  (13:14)
If it fails in the ADF patrona, we have the option to retrieve from that particular 

Speaker 1  (13:19)
The failure failure, like even you can resume it from the air flow as well from anywhere you can resume it right, but if you need to reprocess the data, right? How you will handle those scenarios. 

Speaker 2  (13:32)
Reprocess from the start right from or from any layer. 

Speaker 1  (13:39)
Prom, like a year from any layer or like a from scratch, you need to start it from the injection, right? 

Speaker 2  (13:45)
Injection as a tool, you need to update the bottom-up column at that fee as of now we are doing with memory, but other processes. I have not Maybe aware of. 

Speaker 1  (13:58)
You have you burnt down the spark. Take on it. Can I ask you through the ships? 

Speaker 1  (14:16)
And you mentioned, yes, one more thing you mentioned about the CDC, right? So how you guys are handling the CDC greater. 

Speaker 2  (14:25)
We have that patient, the patient character 

Speaker 1  (14:28)
To visibility. 

Speaker 2  (14:30)
So that is reading the transition. Send the updates on south update. 

Speaker 1  (14:36)
Okay, and now I have one more question. Okay, so let's assume like your data is landed on the adls, right? Now you are reading it. 

Speaker 1  (14:45)
The data like from database notebook using a spark, right? How you are reading it. 

Speaker 2  (14:53)
Resume the spark, probably okay. Isn't a table we have the date in the table. The bronze table will be reading it and this citizens. 

Speaker 2  (15:08)
Actually, the file we are reading it as a file in this box. 

Speaker 1  (15:17)
So like, for every, like for each of the sources, you guys are like following that approach, like once the data is processed, then we are moving it into that type, right? For every source, you are following that 

Speaker 2  (15:30)
Or 

Speaker 1  (15:31)
Or you are, you guys and 

Speaker 2  (15:35)
Okay, even if it is stable nail for every source, we are maintaining the files only at the end. We are receiving the file at the earliest location and from where it is getting location. Unit is a database. 

Speaker 2  (15:48)
It's A 

Speaker 1  (15:50)
Okay, so let's assume proter. We are not moving the data into the archival. Okay, right now We are receiving the daily data right? 

Speaker 1  (15:58)
So let's assume we received yesterday. Some files like 10 files we receive. Now we are receiving of 5 files now totally is like a 15 files, right? 

Speaker 1  (16:08)
But tomorrow you receive tan files and you process all those tanes. Now how you will handle that thing like your spark job will read-only the new files that is, like a 5 files. You received today. 

Speaker 2  (16:28)
These are The Times Okay, I didn't go getting the new file. Okay? And there's a file as well. 

Speaker 2  (16:40)
It has to be read on the same particular day. Okay, and that is going to be low. Tablet? 

Speaker 2  (16:49)
If it is how it knows that we are reading the same file on the same particular day. 

Speaker 1  (16:57)
Okay, let me explain it again so you received 10 files yesterday. And your spark job rate those 10 files and process Is that clear? 

Speaker 2  (17:10)
It's there in the long-term table. 

Speaker 1  (17:14)
Maybe you process into the analytics layer as well. All the data is like, published and reports are generated even the Machine Learning model is trained on that. Okay, now let's come to the first stage where we started. 

Speaker 1  (17:27)
Now you process the tan files today, you received the 5 files, right? As a chunk as a data lake, you holding the historical data as well right yesterday day, data as well. And today, data that as well. 

Speaker 1  (17:41)
Now your job should be capable like it rates. Only the neural files, those 5 files, not the whole bunch of the historical data. We need to read, how you will handle that scenario. 

Speaker 2  (17:51)
Yeah, that's not really bad. So GDP done also return to the bronze clear, with all the circle data on the silver data side, we take the data from the bronze layer of the current time stamp, and then we go to the single layer. We're removing the all that you look at data. 

Speaker 2  (18:09)
And that 

Speaker 1  (18:11)
Current tends to that is like a dynamic day to your building, like Great. And let's assume like now like A. Your job is stopped from the last 2 days. 

Speaker 1  (18:27)
Now, your current current tense logical, not work here how you will handle that scenario. 

Speaker 2  (18:34)
It's not rained from 

Speaker 1  (18:38)
Last 2 days. 

Speaker 2  (18:40)
So that's a workflow, right? Brown silver end. If the bronze is running, the silver has to be run correct. 

Speaker 2  (18:46)
And if the data is not there in the bronze layer, that means the data is in the and some other layer. So we need to pick that data from this, what water mark column 

Speaker 1  (19:01)
There is only files, not the like a table, so you are storing. For water, mark table right for water mark column, you need to be create a table first. 

Speaker 2  (19:12)
Okay, guilt and do what the issue is. What happened is clear. The copy command ok in the idea of pipeline, which is actually reading the data from the table, okay and converting it into a file into the aerial location, something that whole data from the bottom-up column to the medius location. 

Speaker 1  (19:34)
Okay, that is the like a landing zone of your data link, right? Okay, that data is dumped. Now how your silver layer will get to know like which files we need to read. 

Speaker 2  (19:46)
I mean, if the data is there in the ideal location, it will go into the bronze layer. Bronze layer will have all the rate of the previous data also. But in the Silver, we just picked the recent data with the time stem, which is created where we are maintaining 2 columns, which is create an update detail based on that we are picking read data to the single loan. 

Speaker 1  (20:11)
Didn't have you created it? Any table on the top of the raw air or silver layer 

Speaker 2  (20:19)
It was no need of it. Whatever the staging table or something can do 

Speaker 1  (20:24)
Right side, right? I'm talking about 

Speaker 2  (20:26)
Practice validation and Dq checks. Table is there, but not as specifically staged. Because that's the complete 

Speaker 1  (20:34)
From where you are, like getting that timestamp column 

Speaker 2  (20:39)
We're creating it in the long-term itself. 

Speaker 1  (20:42)
While dumping the robon layer So in a bronze layer, you create that's why I'm asking like you created any table on your raw layer or bronze layer. You said no. 

Speaker 2  (20:52)
Bones, table is a layer is a dessert table. ITV a stable 9. So what I'm saying is romance, is a table okay, DBS table silver is also a table golden is also a table dB. 

Speaker 2  (21:05)
Yes. T. 

Speaker 1  (21:06)
Okay. 

Speaker 2  (21:08)
In the EDS pipeline, we are having the copy command activity, which is reading the data okay, based on the time step a bottom-up column, it just read all the new data and dumping dump it down into the adolesc location, okay. And once you landed, data 

Speaker 1  (21:31)
Once that file is landed, then it will update that information automatically in your row table. What do you need to run anything for updating the matter information? 

Speaker 2  (21:43)
Now Mata information is already there, right? So if you're going to pick that metal location, okay, this is 

Speaker 1  (21:51)
Not wrong, like adls, is adlc, is storing your physical data that is your file right? What about the matter information you are using? I think unity catalogue or something right? 

Speaker 1  (22:03)
To they are like, if any, let's assume, right, so you are getting a 10 columns right now in a csp file or in a party file. Now you are getting a 12 columns in a new file. So how your unity catalogue will be updated? 

Speaker 2  (22:19)
Now there is a merge schema and schema regulation right that we need to configure inside the notebook. Those option will be usually, so we don't fail the job. We just process the new columns. 

Speaker 1  (22:36)
So you have, you implemented that logic in your jobs, or it's like A So every time you will use the margin schema for every 5 yeah. Now let me after a few question on the stock. Okay? 

Speaker 1  (22:59)
So let's assume right, you have this. You have this spark job, right? When you are submitting a spark job to the spark cluster, explain me the spark architecture, but will happen at the background even once the like a and also explain like when the job is triggered when the stages will be created right. 

Speaker 1  (23:18)
And when the when task will created all these things in a details, right? 

Speaker 2  (23:24)
Look so on the database side. We have, we submitted the job, there are two things, control pain, and the data plane, so on the control plane. All those resources can output even the unity gateway, often cluster management Rescheduling, all those things have been done and then it reaches to the cluster, which is our data print to closes it. 

Speaker 2  (23:49)
And that's where these path comes into picture. It has the driver and the water nose. 

Speaker 1  (23:55)
Thank you. 

Speaker 2  (23:57)
Also, it has maintaining the other external locations. Maybe it can be database, or it can be any as 3 locations readily less location now. This, this part will go to execute the job and with one job we have, we can have multiple stages, and one stages, you can have multiple tasks. 

Speaker 2  (24:19)
So that's how the process going to be happening. And it starts with a driver note. Okay, the driver node is basically your orchestrator for executing your job, so I mean, it will just maintain the it will ask the cluster management or even the catalyst optimiser to create a plan for running the job. 

Speaker 2  (24:46)
And if it is doesn't able to find some tables or something, it just will be exception, and then it has a worker notes to execute those particular tasks registers, kind of scheduled as a driver. 

Speaker 1  (25:01)
So Google assign those worker not to the 

Speaker 2  (25:04)
It's that part of the driver driven rival, move. 

Speaker 1  (25:07)
So driver will allocate all the resources to that Then, what is the use of the resource manager here? 

Speaker 2  (25:14)
Resource manager is maintaining the all the matriate of the worker notes. What has the number of course rising tutors? And do the names, everything, nor does 6 main deep dust manager. 

Speaker 2  (25:32)
Driver asked the cluster manager if it is that particular job can be executed by that particular mode. So that's the part of the customizer, we'll check okay, how much capacity it has, and then yesterday will disallocate the zone. 

Speaker 1  (25:51)
And so let's assume like you are reading a some cf pile using a spark dot raid dot CSD okay, 1DF is created now another DF is created from that DF right? That is, you are using some filter operation. DF2 is greated, the free you are like. 

Speaker 1  (26:10)
You implemented some group by logic. So how many stages will be created here? 

Speaker 2  (26:22)
Okay so far. Reading is one stage. Can we create a new data framework from the old one? 

Speaker 2  (26:31)
We're not seeing the stage. Narendra group 5 will go to greater new stage, which at stage stage Now we're going to process that. And Yeah, I mean, 2 or me, 2 will be created. 

Speaker 1  (26:52)
Now let me ask you some due secret question. So are you comfortable in the sequel pricker? 

Speaker 2  (27:06)
Yeah 

Speaker 1  (27:08)
And have you worked on the ws cloud as well? Because I can see in your resume at his mention. 

Speaker 2  (27:15)
I wonder. 

Speaker 1  (27:16)
So with services you used in AW 

Speaker 2  (27:19)
I use like as 3 lambars. The session is due commission also I don't created them, but I have used them. 

Speaker 1  (27:32)
Fine to lambda and has 3 okay? So what is the cold star problem in the lambda? 

Speaker 2  (27:39)
Okay, cold start problem is there are 3 sections of the clusters. This is how cold and wrong. So To London, the cluster needs to be started, right? 

Speaker 2  (27:52)
Otherwise, it will take time to execute to at least run it and then at least start. And then it will go to run. So, if it is, it should be warm. 

Speaker 2  (28:01)
Okay, that means whenever the request come, it should be handy, the cluster should be ready. 

Speaker 1  (28:08)
Yeah, lambda, it's a cluster. 

Speaker 2  (28:10)
Yeah, I mean behind that the cluster is executing the job. It's a surveillance testosterone. So if it is cold, then it will take time to start. 

Speaker 2  (28:24)
If it is warm, it is half started if it is hot, it's already started. If the concept is like 

Speaker 1  (28:45)
Let me do a simple question being with 

Speaker 1  (28:58)
Do we have a one table employees right? We have attribute employee ID and employee name. Okay. 

Speaker 1  (29:05)
And we inserted some values inside a table 1 247. You can see these are the ID and Alice Bob Charlie, David is the name here you can see, like some of the ids are missing, like 35 and 6. So it's just an example, it can be a like millions of records there, right? 

Speaker 1  (29:26)
Provide writing the sequel, you need to be think in that direction as well, like it can be a many records here in the table. So we need to identify like which ID are missing. 

Speaker 2  (29:41)
First way, I can think of is the The cursor is the one of the options. But I'm thinking without recursive. Except With the ID is also I mean, if I give the ID name with the ID. 

Speaker 2  (30:13)
If So if I differentiate with the ID Let's say 812041 - 10. 

Speaker 1  (30:30)
How you will implement that recursive function here? All you mentioned like Because it can be a solution, how you believe implemented. 

Speaker 2  (30:40)
It needs a baseline, which is your. Let's say. Your list of numbers and numbers. 

Speaker 2  (30:50)
So We don't have the baseline and it will jump in it with the industry. IDN + 1N is the baseline, + 1 is the line. And So that way You can do that. 

Speaker 2  (31:13)
I've us. 

Speaker 1  (31:14)
Let me give you another problem. Let me give you another question. So do you have a table loggings, right? 

Speaker 1  (31:24)
We are storing the user. ID and login data. Alright. 

Speaker 1  (31:29)
Now, we incited values here. You can see even the date as well. So we need to find the user who lodged in for 3 consecutive days. 

Speaker 2  (31:43)
In fact, 3 captivity The sea because I was talking about the differentiating with the idea. Identify taking a difference in the ID with those ids, we're going to be mapped with as a group Rabina, I just, I can tell you about the process how you can do that. I will create an ID Idea is going to be 364, divide and Substituted with the existing idea I need the difference going to be matched accelerated from 000. 

Speaker 2  (32:57)
If it is long 

Speaker 1  (32:58)
We have the longitudinal column. 

Speaker 2  (33:02)
So I'll group by not group. If it is clear, logging on one infrastructure, second, September September. Okay, find chatting with 123, so the group will voluntee 0 okay, if you're doing 567. 

Speaker 2  (33:23)
The idea is 450. I saw the cloud of the 

Speaker 1  (33:33)
That if you are able to solve it, that's good to solve it, and we can do what is the next question as well. 

Speaker 1  (33:51)
Are you familiar with the data set as series Could you please explain each of them and how you can implement using this model? Without using any moisture S CD 2SD0, then you need to explain like how you really implement AC CD 2 using this product without using a model state. 

Speaker 2  (34:21)
As an ICT one is like overwriting, the Cold values to his inserting a new version and H CD 3 is like 

Speaker 1  (34:35)
I'm asking about 

Speaker 2  (34:43)
Yeah, city 0I think we are. I think one is the overriding. Okay, otherwise have been a new quality new row. 

Speaker 2  (34:55)
And third one is keeping both the originally and minerally growth I think these are the SCT0 voltage Probably in actually 0B. We know we Sorry recipe, the override the value second is the we keep at equity as a new role, and third is the way keeping both the values. 

Speaker 1  (35:46)
Without massing. 

Speaker 2  (35:53)
Without using a March statement And we don't have to apply any logic there because it's to rain. If the bronze layer, we have that thing about Government, if we are not doing anything, it will be a city tied to all because, for each of the rows for each of the ID, you will get in a multiple values for particular column, that's a city. Maybe this state. 

Speaker 2  (36:26)
Can be changed, right, so user cannot begin a Pand. 

Speaker 1  (36:30)
But trikkar, you had all air is not all Your analytics layer will give a submit layer. You are sharing that analytics layer tables will give your vitamin, with your data science team to model training. 

Speaker 2  (36:48)
Yeah, that's a part of the business requirement. So if there's silver layer needs to be having both the rows, then we have to design climate in such a way. 

Speaker 1  (37:02)
Because your main suffering layer is like analytics layer. Your reports will be generated on the analytics layer, right? We need to see like how many active users are there, right? 

Speaker 1  (37:14)
Delta attractive, some of the users are deactivated at some of the users are activated. 

Speaker 2  (37:29)
How many ways what I'm thinking is? If we're not applying any logic, there And that because of the Golden layer, we do not have the elevated data. What is the centre here? 

Speaker 2  (37:40)
We'll be keeping already. Hondily, the entire updated data for the And on the ground there, we have just solid data. The zealu control continues 3 tables, and 1778 cm, doesn't require government. 

Speaker 2  (37:54)
We can't keep a check-in the seller. Do you want to keep it both as a role? 

Speaker 1  (37:58)
Now the business requirement is like we need to implement that is an analytics layer over final layer because we are exposing that final layer to other steel right? Some reporting team we need to generate a report like how many active users register? How many active users we have in this month, current money, right? 

Speaker 1  (38:18)
No, in analytics layer already has some like deactivate, the deactivated accounts are also there, right, some active accounts, are there, right? It implement SD2 type, then you can Give the exact numbers there, right? Because you need to be marked some of the users on the latest data. 

Speaker 1  (38:37)
Active or some of the users deactivated, right? 

Speaker 2  (38:41)
Yeah, the silver layer. We will not keep that deactive user because it's already under drawn layer. Active players and then we can aggregate the data into the door saying that of this particular month, we have this many active active use of fear in a global way. 

Speaker 1  (39:02)
So how you will handle SCT to type main question is here, right? There is a logic of implementing std to type right, you said like you need to be maintain a historical version as well, right and the latest version as well. Now you will maintain both the records in the same table. 

Speaker 2  (39:21)
Let's say for one particular idea. You can have 2 values, correct? Timesha, applying the even the merged logic. 

Speaker 2  (39:38)
Also right? We are updating that 

Speaker 1  (39:40)
No, no, we are not using any pulse logic. 

Speaker 2  (39:44)
Automatically come as a with the same idea, we don't have to do anything. 

Speaker 1  (39:51)
Okay, let's assume like today. You received the like the phone 1ID. You received the 3 records. 

Speaker 1  (40:00)
Then, which one? Because right now in your analytics layer, all the poor records are there right? 

Speaker 2  (40:05)
Okay, so let's say if the one of the Call. 

Speaker 1  (40:11)
Precker, have you designed that? Yes? D? 

Speaker 1  (40:13)
Have you ever used S CD to anywhere in your project? 

Speaker 2  (40:17)
If we're what do you usually happen? Is let's say in the source table yesterday. It was 10 records. 

Speaker 2  (40:23)
Now we have in the source system itself itself. They have deleted one record like 9 records are there, but in our deviate table, we have 10 records. So we are maintaining the delete column saying that if the one particular idea has been deleted, we just have to delete it from our end also in the details. 

Speaker 2  (40:42)
So we are maintaining what column. Is that answer question no? 

Speaker 1  (40:49)
It's different. 

Speaker 2  (40:52)
Okay. 

Speaker 1  (40:53)
Okay, no problem. Okay, so we can wrap up the interview now precaut, if you have any questions, you can ask 

Speaker 2  (41:01)
Where I can tell me about the role. 

Speaker 1  (41:05)
So role is like a they have the multiple position of that, right. So it's a kind of data architect role, right? We are hiring for the like a senior senior manager level, right? 

Speaker 1  (41:17)
I think you have 1414 years of experience, right? It should be like a senior manager, so who will like handle the like designing the etm pipelines right? Because right now we have the multiple projects On our plate, right, we required a lots of data engineer here, right? 

Speaker 1  (41:32)
So we are hiring on each of the labels like Junior labels, senior label and the like a higher senior label architecture level, because we require that architect level experience as well. That's why we are like, considering the profiles more than 10 years, even we are considering the mid middle level experience as well, right? So it's a kind of like data, architect level position. 

Speaker 1  (41:54)
We are And it's like a totally on the EWS cloud, right? Okay, any other questions? Thanks for good. 

Speaker 1  (42:07)
Thanks for your attention. 
