This content was generated by AI


Speaker 1  (00:03)
Can you repeat that, please? 

Speaker 2  (00:06)
Asking, how does your multi agent system handle incorrect outputs, or if there are any disagreements between agents? 

Speaker 1  (00:17)
Okay? Depending on the Again you're talking to things, disagreement and the invalid out 

Speaker 2  (00:26)
Incorrect orbits. 

Speaker 1  (00:28)
Output, okay, so for the incorrect outputs. We have the gardens. And accordance also interact output in what sense I mean, the data is wrong, or is it not? 

Speaker 1  (00:42)
Giving the relevant response 

Speaker 2  (00:45)
So you are saying, implement responses, you can see 

Speaker 1  (00:49)
Hey, really won't respond that we have several metrics to expose to check what values were driving like recall, they have and the precision and all the regulators matrix will actually check for validating the output received from the lm. And the other thing was What is the rhythm schedule? 

Speaker 2  (01:14)
To those agreements between the agents 

Speaker 1  (01:16)
Yes, let's disagreement between the agents right? Let's say. Sir, we have in our tradition. 

Speaker 1  (01:25)
We are using the routing agents and multiple different massive agents. So take care of the elaborate on the disagreement part 

Speaker 2  (01:38)
So if it on 2 agents are not agreeing to what your asked, or what you know, in terms of what they have to bring in the output, so there is a disagreement with what you're asking, and what they can 

Speaker 1  (01:51)
Okay, let's say so we need to. We need to validate these skill sets, and the cards. Basically, we have to make it more aligned with the agent response response. 

Speaker 1  (02:05)
So in that case, we need to check it there. What is the actual issue is? And then we have to verify the metrics that we have exported. 

Speaker 1  (02:15)
These are the two things majorly, I will check. Look on the agent. 

Speaker 2  (02:21)
Okay. Okay, and how did data breaks contribute to your GenAI platform? Yeah, what as to your views, data breaks in India. 

Speaker 1  (02:32)
Yes, so on the data bricks part We are. We have treated the multiple model versions. Okay, and we have the endocrine serving endpoints. 

Speaker 1  (02:44)
Also, we are using the feature store vectors to store their vector store for the environment and feature store for the Delta tables data, along with that few of the computes, we have configured aligned with the event models. And then we are few furflows we have written around the this whole application where some are taking care of the multihop architecture, like silver bronze and bronze and golden hair, so these are the few things that we have figured, also exposing the metrics on the dashboards of the data. 

Speaker 2  (03:30)
So what are the architecture? Have you personally built prakan? 

Speaker 1  (03:36)
As I told you right? I have built the incremental pipelines, etc pipelines as part of the Azure, ADF and database, including their cough responses. So we have 2 systems. 

Speaker 1  (03:52)
One is the batch and the streaming on the batch side. We have configured popular matter data on the tables and the processing strategies load strategies where we will check If it is a file based okay. It needs to go with the batch or the incremental approach based on the size of the data, and if it is instrumental, we have to validate the water marks and primary keys aligned with the matter data, and on the streaming parts we usually do the cdcs and then sending the using the dipasium as the CDC connected the sender response to the task task topic and to that task topic we have in the database. 

Speaker 1  (04:36)
We are reading that and then we usually get the insight of date and delete records and through that, when we maintain that pipeline, the multi other architecture. 

Speaker 2  (04:52)
Current station, can you walk me through one RAG system from injection to final response at a very high level. What are the different steps different flow expected flow? That is 

Speaker 1  (05:11)
Serve the wrap pipeline, okay with the idiot pipeline, as I said, we have the chunk in layer. In the chunking layer, we are splitting the data across the sentences. Social sentence splitter, keeping the Chunk sizes around 500 MB U and then 500 MB and then we are the embedding layer where we are storing those chunks in the embedding or vector formats in the vector store, and then we have this searching algorithms, which is basically doing the combination of the your dense and risk parts approach intense, is basically, the cocine and spars is basically your BM25 approach T FI D keyword approach this. 

Speaker 1  (06:06)
Once we are combining that thing, then we are retrieving the path K before top. K. We are doing the buyer coaters. 

Speaker 1  (06:15)
For the rewranting along with the cross encoders. And then we're sending the data to the LLM through the prompts. And we're generating the response. 

Speaker 1  (06:28)
Also, we have Several checks and several retrace logic scene Then, we are evaluating the metrics using the Regass metrics, yeah, I mean, these are the few things we do. Also, we're keeping making sure that whether we need the data in the diversified data from the genre from the LLM, or the only the specific relevant data 

Speaker 2  (06:59)
Okay. Where are you currently located, prakrit? Where are you based on those 

Speaker 2  (07:15)
What is your rootus period in your current organisation? Emphasis 

Speaker 1  (07:20)
Yeah, I mean, notice period is correct. I'm serving lasting days 7th of September. I mean next too much. 

Speaker 2  (07:32)
7th of September, and when I already have an offer in hand is said the reason why we Put on your papers and serving notice. 

Speaker 1  (07:43)
I know, actually, my company asked me to relocate. To be a different location. Can you give me a moment? 

Speaker 2  (08:30)
Oh, isn't any other offer which are the final stages of interview or 

Speaker 1  (08:36)
Yay, it's in pipeline. 

Speaker 2  (08:41)
Okay, so are you expecting anytime soon, or suppose if you have an offer in and maybe in a week or so, what would be your key differentiator? If you have offered from written WD opportunity, and you also have another one. What will be the key differentiator that you look for in? 

Speaker 1  (08:56)
Yeah, sure. I mean, so. Is it a few questions before answering that? 

Speaker 1  (09:02)
So it's a raise the office and it's a hybrid or a remote 

Speaker 2  (09:12)
So this is a report role. This opportunity is a remote objective over the working from home. However, to pick up them to collect the laptop, you have to go to Bangalore office. 

Speaker 2  (09:22)
Now, let's say, and what are the key things that you're more inclined for this opportunity like to understand? 

Speaker 1  (09:30)
Diagnostic looking for the remote work. Because I'm working from remote, from around 45 years. Turning for the save, that's my first preference. 

Speaker 1  (09:42)
The other preferences, they're not getting the not getting the offer from the Noida. Maybe I'm getting it from the Gurgaon which is not too far but still I have to travel. So these are the 2 criteria I am keeping in mind 

Speaker 2  (10:01)
Okay, alright prakr, I'll explain the process that will be one assessment link that will be shared with you a very basic level of questions 2025 and securs will be there and once you complete that there will be one client round of interview for around 1 hour duration. Okay? And once you cleared that on boarding or background checks will take 2 to three weeks of time. 

Speaker 1  (10:26)
Oh, sure. 

Speaker 2  (10:26)
So this is the typical timeline that it will take, and I hope you're aware with a kind of setup that you have for this opportunity, your payroll. You will be an employee of basically a vinity technologies while you work with an end client, which is alignly, and you'll be working with it. I lead through WW T you will have an engagement manager, or you will be typically reporting to WW T while you work with L. 

Speaker 2  (10:50)
I. D. Do you have any questions so far? 

Speaker 2  (10:55)
Anything that you want to ask 

Speaker 1  (11:00)
No, I'm good. 

Speaker 2  (11:04)
Great, thank you. Thank you for your time prekar. You will have the link probably in the next 2030 minutes. 

Speaker 2  (11:12)
Thank you. Having your rest of the day, nice 

Speaker 1  (13:16)
So basically, when the validation failed philasra failure strategy, along with that is the Dq also fail. It will pass the failure strategy if it is bad, then Jata. And if it is again, failure extremely, it will send it to the details. 

Speaker 1  (13:35)
That's the only thing I need to pay. 

Speaker 1  (16:11)
So here we will add the alerts. 

Speaker 3  (16:30)
Third, when they tried countless 

Speaker 1  (16:43)
But in kima breaks his happening at the it's not there at the validation. If the validation we are asking the figure strategy. 

Speaker 3  (17:18)
So in your interviews and validation classifications, failures classifier, the ones trigger ones followed. 

Speaker 1  (20:45)
It is 900 century 

Speaker 4  (29:25)
Hello? 

Speaker 1  (29:31)
How many? You have featured. PL case consolidate data load F DL 

Speaker 4  (30:15)
Yeah, happy. 

Speaker 1  (30:17)
Hi. 

Speaker 1  (30:28)
Turn type, we want to peers every 

Speaker 4  (30:32)
Floating Spain kuch services. Linked service. Do jariye 

Speaker 1  (30:48)
Nike. 

Speaker 4  (31:25)
NUC and NBO is a prompt details. 

Speaker 1  (31:31)
It's from Eric jegners. 

Speaker 4  (31:33)
Kuch uneet services. 

Speaker 1  (31:49)
Our FDN dot 

Speaker 4  (31:53)
1510. 

Speaker 1  (32:32)
He broadcasted a reference name. Did your reference name or anushma? Who brought the BXR? 

Speaker 4  (32:53)
Yeah, an activity sorry books besides till you know 5 monthly 6178. 

Speaker 4  (33:11)
Play Abhi door. 

Speaker 1  (33:35)
Looking for changes in the middle of the alarm. And just the black can answer 

Speaker 4  (33:52)
Oh, yeah? 

Speaker 1  (33:58)
How change? 

Speaker 4  (34:07)
Okay. Is consolidated in pain? 

Speaker 1  (34:17)
Yeah Pearman, dress. 

Speaker 4  (35:17)
All Manne were breakha detailwala. 

Speaker 4  (35:40)
Stay Yeah, happy, yeah. Toh iske Andre, h*, he get Mein jaoge. 

Speaker 4  (36:02)
Jaisamaram ka file. I'm sorry. 

Speaker 1  (36:15)
Secure the phone. 

Speaker 4  (36:15)
No good change. Pair ko recording secretary. Veera books, no deployed details job. 

Speaker 4  (36:36)
Mambae, human am I ran through deliberate, henna see dots equal to 5 usko ratnan. Uske pass vacut, approve karega Toh wah run hoga. Tu jaise yahan pe isne ke liye jitna bhi Jabir jitna file, se sampran karna h*. 

Speaker 4  (37:17)
Please play some good delete the lake. Previous voltage and notana enjoy feature ranch banario feature runner. He purane is duharat, radial ka script, hai, usko, rekhna hai. 

Speaker 4  (37:46)
Complete complex huge number, but in devad ko karna, he looked look at all my generative debt that already created enough. Toh ye kisska aisi execution, a ponse of remains mego control. 2 vacant security. 

Speaker 4  (38:24)
All 4 recording ki jaise create table karke Toh Kahan table. If not exist? 

Speaker 1  (39:10)
Marcosa Teji global proud Mein change karna. 

Speaker 4  (39:19)
Robin. 

Speaker 1  (39:25)
A job chalti hai global 

Speaker 4  (39:29)
Open browser to change me about local key local chain mehnat. 

Speaker 4  (39:50)
Aruba, case concerned Vala, that is correct. A pipe neem, Diya hai data factory ka ulgu is piped into all conservation. 

Speaker 4  (40:30)
Because some left the books local in changed. Yeah, to go to internally chart which I am taking now. If it's a chance of tap one more. 

Speaker 1  (40:44)
Taken 2. Ivanojico Dav vanai were up 35 on 11. CFD. 

Speaker 1  (40:51)
N. K. 
