This content was generated by AI


Speaker 1  (00:27)
We can start. Awesome. April, I would just need a quick intro of your total. 

Speaker 1  (00:33)
It experience and then your element, Machine Learning, data science experience. 

Speaker 2  (00:40)
Sure, so Horn, 14 years of experience, working with it with data engineer, along with ML And 5 year close to the AM from last year. I'm working with t Agent AI and the RAG system will image. I'm displayed with the data engineering Pipeline instrumental loads. 

Speaker 2  (01:09)
Data Bix immediately, I'm using, along with that, I'm using the corner of the Azure edf pipelines for the ingestions and the multi AAP architecture for the refinement. And cough for the steamings, batch and implemental and outside. Also we have any 

Speaker 1  (01:45)
Given So the role we're looking for is actually a role that you'd be working directly under the CTU of our company. And it's yeah, so basically whatever new features are coming in, the agent space in snowflake or the data engineering space. So We need to do quick rapid prototyping and present it to the clients, so you would have a team with you, but yeah, so it would be kind of an individual contributor role as well as a collaborative role. 

Speaker 1  (02:28)
But it's a non delivery role, but under CTO for like rapid prototype, so I am here to test your AI Machine Learning skills. There would be other rounds to test the data engineering part of the role also. Um, could you explain Ugh, why accuracy fails in some data science use cases, and why precision and recall is useful. 

Speaker 2  (02:59)
Yeah, I mean, if we're considering the negative cases, and if it is possible when the recall value we have to consider. If we're talking about the rad one Where the recall is, even if it is high. That means we are getting the Relevant as well as irrelevant data. 

Speaker 2  (03:22)
That's why the recall is high. But if the precision is low, that means we are getting the noisy data That since we can say the closession is high and the recall is depending on the business requirements, we need to choose. 

Speaker 1  (03:38)
Can you give me a good business example of precision and recall? 

Speaker 2  (03:44)
Simple example would be like in the fraud detection cases. We don't want to miss any case which is especially saying this is the this is actually the Not, it was actually fraud. We don't want to miss those cases. 

Speaker 2  (04:03)
That's why we here, we will prefer the repair values. Even with the cancer detection, precision is when we are singing opposite. When we're the email system where we are saying, the spams can be, the correct email can be Spam. 

Speaker 2  (04:24)
Okay, and we don't want to miss that in that case, we'll use the 

Speaker 1  (04:30)
How do you control? How do you control if you want more decision more recall? 

Speaker 2  (04:36)
No precision, more recalled, and we have this at 10 Depending on the data. We calculate the finishing value even if it is. There are some other FM also FM Beta, also, well, as we usually calculate based on the Based on the imbalanced data that we have So you want to focus more on the recall value, then we will choose the, or maybe the registration value. 

Speaker 2  (05:10)
Then in that case, we will go with the FM Beta. A funny score is majorly works. Most of our time when we have the equal weight is of the accuracy and the precision 

Speaker 1  (05:28)
Got record, right? How do you choose the Optimal threshold in precision record. 

Speaker 2  (05:36)
Yeah, I mean, we see the FLT V greater than 75%. In that case, we verify ok trade office matched. The FPR and Tpr values are getting correct. 

Speaker 1  (06:02)
Good. Quick question on, we might have worked on this regression classification algorithm. Linear logistic random forest so logistic regression is a classification algorithm. 

Speaker 1  (06:16)
But why does it have a regression in its name? 

Speaker 2  (06:22)
Okay, so it basically Okay, logistic basically is the classification where it will give the output in the 90 format 0 and 1. But for the regression thing Set reminder to recall that. I mean, it just gives the probability under 01. 

Speaker 2  (06:53)
That's a use case of the logistic. So in that case, it just operates out the 2 classes, that's a majorly 

Speaker 1  (07:02)
Yeah, so every classification algorithm does that. But why does logistic have regression in its scheme? 

Speaker 2  (07:15)
I mean, I'm not sure about it. 

Speaker 1  (07:20)
Noise. What's the fundamental difference between renewable executive 

Speaker 2  (07:27)
Yeah, I mean, so the major difference is that random for us here multiple trees in family using the magnile, boosting approach, and then using the Assembly methods uses the voting method to calculate the output or the response. With the boosting approach, it will create a sequential trees and history left from the previous tree using the residuals. Um, too. 

Speaker 2  (07:57)
Minimise the loss function. And there are multiple ways of boosting, like HCB. LGB and cat boosting. 

Speaker 2  (08:08)
Random random forest basically used for reducing the variance in the data, and even the data is in better set works perfectly. 

Speaker 1  (08:28)
Okay. So you In running forest between multiple trees in parallel correct, and how is the data split there? Like, why does visit it uses variance, right? 

Speaker 1  (08:44)
Why does it reduce variance? 

Speaker 2  (08:46)
Yeah, it reduced the grain because we have the several parameters do set like the number of trees. So more. The number of trees, the better, the better will be the output better, how you say Because of the number of voting, they will go into and based on that, we can average, that voting and get the correct answer so weaker model, give the higher Better response, that's about In this also, it uses the Guinea and the information gain find the random forest to that way it just comes. 

Speaker 2  (09:27)
It just try to reduce the appearances every time for each of the tree. Also, there is feature randomness randomness in the In the random forest, it will automatically Set those features only, or maybe we can set that limit also. Based on those features, you will create the number of trees and 

Speaker 1  (09:55)
In exit, yeah, in exit post. Also, we have more number of trees, but why does it not reduce variance? Why does it random forest reduce? 

Speaker 2  (10:07)
Why does no gradient is basically reducing the loss function? Over the multiple trees in the sequential It also uses the regulator disradient. It is green boosting. 

Speaker 2  (10:27)
So basically it is this recalling battery How is it reducing the variances? Okay, so it is reducing the variances. Because there are 

Speaker 2  (10:53)
Because of the randomness feature, they come up with nearly, they are creating multiple trees based on that. 

Speaker 1  (11:10)
We can move to these embeddings, so have you heard of glove embeddings previously? 

Speaker 2  (11:21)
So love for that. Okay? 

Speaker 1  (11:25)
Jay budwey's voice transform embeddings better than the previous love. Embeddings, what changed? 

Speaker 2  (11:32)
Okay, first of all, they are very They are very huge dimensions. Earlier, we don't have that like the word also dimensions are few in 500 and maybe less than 500. But now the models comes up with the future 100 embedding models, the name more than that. 

Speaker 2  (11:54)
That's the one thing where it will give us the I mean that searching would be similar. It will give the similar searching very fast than the if we are using the other traditional models. And also, Transformers are basically decoders, specifically not encoders. 

Speaker 2  (12:15)
That's why it is cedibat, was equation? I forgot that 

Speaker 1  (12:21)
I was saying via transformer based remedies, better than the older embeddings. 

Speaker 2  (12:26)
Yeah, this is the one of the reason I can. I can team off because of the number of embeddings, and The huge word the huge victory could create. 

Speaker 1  (12:42)
How do you solve overfitting? In Machine Learning? Use cases in data science, use cases. 

Speaker 2  (12:48)
How do we reduce our fitting? Ok. Starting from the traditional novels, if we look How gonna reduce the overfitting? 

Speaker 2  (13:03)
We did to that, okay? Which model we are working with? Let's say we are working with t Simple random forest, where we're seeing the test training data, is getting more valued amid Moreover, more productivity than the testing data. 

Speaker 2  (13:24)
So in that case, we will see that it has learned a lot of noise. Okay, so we're going to test, tried to reduce that noise using the regulatorization. That's the first step, or I mean, we can use that as an 

Speaker 1  (13:39)
Yeah, what is overfitting mean? By the way, what is overfitting? 

Speaker 2  (13:43)
Thinking is like the moral is learning. The noise Apart from the actual relationship of the data search, we try to minimise that noise, uh, using the regularisation. That's the first step 

Speaker 1  (13:59)
What's the difference between L1 and L2? 

Speaker 2  (14:02)
Yeah, lasso and rich so lasso is basically make your features or 0 okay, just to 0. It just cut that irrelevant features. And where reaches visually shrink? 

Speaker 2  (14:20)
Your features? Okay, I'm shrinking the weights of the feature. You just consider those 530 medals. 

Speaker 1  (14:27)
Keeping reach to that, and why does last go to that 

Speaker 2  (14:34)
That's how that's how they penalise the huge error So the more the error least, the whole penalisation will be done on the regulation inside. 

Speaker 1  (14:49)
Terra karbappa, why doesn't the region go to 0? 

Speaker 2  (14:52)
What is the reason for 

Speaker 1  (14:54)
Why does the ridge regression not go to 0? 

Speaker 2  (14:59)
It yet because there is a mod of because of the function, they're using the A mod of weight can absolute value of the weight. So that's why 

Speaker 1  (15:11)
Redge uses their last 

Speaker 2  (15:13)
Rich uses. 

Speaker 1  (15:23)
You said you are worked on drive. Also, correct. A If I give you like 1000 Wikipedia articles and I ask you to build a RAG system, how would you start? 

Speaker 1  (15:37)
Give me high level steps. 

Speaker 2  (15:40)
Okay, so RAG is basically on the Army structured data. So add Try to do the okay. I'll try to do the Chunky first if chunking, based on the simple semantic search. 

Speaker 2  (15:55)
So all the similar texts will come in Wang chunk. Okay? Depending on the size, we can have cap the limit of each sum, and then they'll send it to the embedding. 

Speaker 2  (16:10)
In the embedding, it will going to be written to the vectors. Before that, detox will be done. And that embedding will come a story into the vector store, or maybe any vector store, we can choose 

Speaker 1  (16:26)
Which embracing model? Have you used like while you are doing that? 

Speaker 2  (16:30)
Your B g's model released 

Speaker 1  (16:34)
Easy, okay. Talk for. 

Speaker 2  (16:38)
Yes, so this is one of the steps I would take a pipeline for this. Once it will be done, and it will be um incrementally changing by weekly or something so that there shouldn't be driftness in the data. 

Speaker 1  (16:54)
What is a recursive text splitting? There is some thing that we do at recursive tax splitting. What is it actually including 

Speaker 2  (17:01)
So in the recursive taxes, multiple ways first is a fixed size chunking, or maybe the sentence aware, so in the fixed size we can add the The page, the junk size and your overlap, and on the other which is sentence aware, we can add the separators. Okay, so separator in the sense if it is a one sentence, it will split into 3. If there is a paragraph, it will convert into the sentences that is split us. 

Speaker 1  (17:38)
Call yeah, you said you'll pass it to an embedding model. Generate embedding storage window vector store next 

Speaker 2  (17:46)
Search algorithm, I'm searching, I'll use the dense centre spars. In the dense, I'll use the cosine similarity basically. For any query query and D actual embeddings, which I stored there in the electric store. 

Speaker 2  (18:03)
I try to search for It and again. I'll do the keyword match searching And I'll do the trial-and-error and to see what the trade of us better accurately accurate result based on the try to combine both the project and find a trade of how much percentage you Want To keep it for dense and as part Once we have the correct data coming up from this search, then I can do the reranking also. Latency into mind. 

Speaker 2  (18:49)
Then, after you ranking, I'll send it to the L ML M will generate the answer for me and 

Speaker 2  (19:07)
I'll expose the multiple metrics. Ugas matrix would be one of them other than that, there are several other N TCG M. R. 

Speaker 2  (19:18)
Mr. sorry, these are the values KPIKL divergence, there are several others. There are several other psi values, so those values. 

Speaker 2  (19:28)
Are you gonna expose? Also, I'll use the I'm logging with mill flows portrasibility, observability. 

Speaker 1  (19:40)
Cool, awesome. Yeah, I'm good from my side. Prakhal, no draw something. 

Speaker 1  (19:48)
Okay, I'll speak. 
