This content was generated by AI


Speaker 1  (00:00)
So listen, I'm waiting for the interviewer. Let me check if he's joining. 

Speaker 2  (00:10)
Yeah, Mike is not working, so they will drive new temperature. 

Speaker 1  (00:15)
Give me just a second. Can you hear me? 

Speaker 2  (00:18)
Yeah, yeah, I can hear you yeah. 

Speaker 1  (00:21)
Okay. I have some issue. 

Speaker 3  (00:28)
Extend to all display. 

Speaker 1  (00:40)
Okay, let me see if he's trying again. I accept them by the way. 

Speaker 2  (00:55)
Yeah, I can hear you. If I just gave me 

Speaker 1  (01:54)
Interesting shake and safe joining. Yes, definitely. By the way, but maybe he's in another cool. 

Speaker 1  (02:02)
Now, let me see That's which happened when you are. You joined the economy. 

Speaker 2  (02:18)
Okay. 

Speaker 1  (02:21)
We have experience era. So basically, I think you will be part of my team if interview goes well, basically the project that opened up the extension of the I'll get projected the section of the scope, and it has the country's Something like a webpage, internal webpage that should be able to have something like And I think a Chatbot That will allow you to play specific data center, okay, asking the AI to provide you implication on specific data centers has been important in data picks, and as well like we are using the ews platform so the aim of this pro. 

Speaker 1  (03:22)
Based on what my it's my understanding is that you should be able to query something that will provide it to the business for the analysts specific deficit based on what they need. So let's assume that maybe they are part of manufacturing I want to know specific data on manufacturing area that will allows you to prepare a dashboard that will be used for having kpis. I don't know whatever, so it's a very They are a very large scoop. 

Speaker 1  (04:00)
I see that shaky joint a shake, thanks to joint 

Speaker 3  (04:05)
I had so much joy in my computer. That's why I told pro. 

Speaker 1  (04:10)
Okay, no, no, no, probably no problem at all. We just joined. Okay, so we have the cracker here that is Connie's and from connies and Tim so sheikh, I think, you know what is, let's say the aim of this meeting so basically we need some one internal based on Tanya's request to interview prakare to see if he fits our needs for the project that he needs to join. 

Speaker 1  (04:39)
Okay so if it is fine for you sheikh, I will leave you. And with the pracker here in the cool and yes enough to that, you can send me a feedback so we can see if we should move forward. Or not, based on your feedback, okay? 

Speaker 1  (05:03)
You there. I see you are on music. 

Speaker 3  (05:09)
The tack is fine, so okay, yes, so that is totally fine. So we can get started, actually. 

Speaker 1  (05:18)
Okay. Yeah, I will drop the cooler so you can be free to interview him alone okay? 

Speaker 3  (05:24)
Okay, fine, thank you. 

Speaker 1  (05:27)
Bye, bye, because thanks simply by s***. Bye. 

Speaker 3  (05:30)
Thank you. Prices. Give me 1 minute. 

Speaker 3  (05:34)
I will open up some Resource for you to See. Yes, okay. So apricos, can you tell Some of your experience in engineering, like what kind of application you have built so far If they're in production, if their plc is and Then, we can discuss further about those 

Speaker 2  (06:19)
Yeah, sure, so. I was working on the educational domain and I was working on the banking domain majority. So Starting with the education of when we have played a Chatbot where they were We have implemented the along with that's some guardian, and then that's specific to the internet users used by the teachers major and for the approvals, the user can answer. 

Speaker 2  (06:59)
I've been the user can carry anything, especially to the cognition, so we have implemented the pipeline for the checking and bedding and showing the embedding to the vectors too, along with that, we are finding the not the fine treating, but increase the accuracy of the chatbots majorly, so we have implemented the 70 cache of the year. Okay, and On the line graph we have implemented the rack system along with the vector store, and then we are combining that approach, and for the searching part, we have at rather rear anchors and toolkits. 

Speaker 2  (07:35)
We had multiple approaches, like career, I think hide approach for the curry transformations. Also, we tried a lengthy extractor at 10 feet rolls for the improvement, and then we are sending the data to the element gateways for rate, limiting and Distinct rate, limiting and your fallbacks, major and then it goes, check the model on the if it is not able to give the response it a corresponding time, then we have to fall back to the our lower model. Also on the junking part, we were embedding, we were taking the documents from the adf pipelines and sending it to the ads location, and then we are possessing it to the database, so we have the old first passing that data with t Section wise data document i.e. 

Speaker 2  (08:34)
then we're creating the chance out of it story that through the vector stories, as with their meetings for the fast retreat. We have implemented the rba C abacies, all those things for the security purpose. Producers should be accessible enough to check that data inside the database. 

Speaker 2  (08:56)
Okay? And Yeah, that's pretty much from one of the patients that I have worked on. I've not gone up other projects deliberate with the whole thing like bird we are using bird. 

Speaker 2  (09:12)
If you're one of the chat agent, I'm not the agent, but agent feedback activation was there. I used a role model board for the analysis. From that I have loved with pise park as well. 

Speaker 2  (09:29)
With a major league with a database and some services on the Airbnb side also 

Speaker 3  (09:37)
Thanks. So my name is sheikh. I am part of roberti. 

Speaker 3  (09:44)
Operation on the D DIT load later digital data and IT I'm working as a senior data scientist and leading a team of AI Engineers and developers, I also do certain backend developments and also starting data science development, and also I have to work on ETL before and other data processing. Things so from an experience you discuss about chunking, right? The document so there is scenarios when a document has a large table. 

Speaker 3  (10:31)
A table spanning multiple pages So how do you see that as a problem, and do you have any solution for that? 

Speaker 2  (10:43)
Yeah, I mean, if the document is large, okay, so we can explain why the page Y is split. Okay, and then we can pass the data with the particular sections, and then we can create the chance out there, so that way we can do so. 

Speaker 3  (10:56)
Yeah, but then you have the, let's say fifty-fifty page document. It was led by pages. And then it's too much of a chunk for no reason. 

Speaker 3  (11:11)
So in the 50 page document, maybe 4 pages are the table spanning clothes. 

Speaker 2  (11:21)
Okay, so if it is in the 50 pages, we have two things, right? Table, same images and everything and the texture as well. So we can as we have to pass it with the different model. 

Speaker 2  (11:33)
If it is image we have to use a GPT-4 

Speaker 3  (11:38)
Let's say we discard image. There's not no important information in the image. We are only interested in the text, but there is a situation that We cannot split the cables because we miss the header. 

Speaker 3  (11:54)
Or we might reach out to a contacts limit of the invariing model. If we keep large amounts of taxes into one chunk, right importing, impairing more will throw out so errors that I don't have enough together. Yeah, so there is 2 problems, one is then if there is a large table, then how we can chunk it, but if the table is only 2 page small table, we can put them together into one chunk, then how we should do it. 

Speaker 2  (12:25)
It is a large table line. We said two things, right? We missed the header. 

Speaker 3  (12:33)
In large table I'm chunking, right? Let's say it's a 505 page table, and I need to split it into 2 chunks. I am going to miss the heritage. 

Speaker 2  (12:47)
So you want to escape 2 jumps on the right? 

Speaker 3  (12:51)
If, for example, let's say you need to set some limits on the chunks rate. Let's say not by talking. You have put a limit of 1000 characters. 

Speaker 3  (13:06)
It's putting the table. What will happen? 

Speaker 2  (13:10)
Yeah, when okay, so let's say if we are using the recursive splitter. Okay, so it will, I'm going to check the It will try to champion with the paragraphs and tense and everything, and that will be sentences. Because considering that token limit also, we can, I can think of summarization if we can do 

Speaker 3  (13:37)
Not don't we don't we shouldn't bring AI here. It's purely because we need to save cost. We want to give the raw document as raw as possible. 

Speaker 2  (13:49)
Okay, so you're talking about the Chunky layer, how we can chunk that 

Speaker 3  (13:53)
Yes, without any AI, no, we haven't even went to the embedding. We're creating the chunks, and then that will be then embedded and save individuals too. 

Speaker 2  (14:07)
Yes, how will I change the last English right? Yeah, I mean, without using that, then we can Okay, without using the library also or 

Speaker 3  (14:18)
No, we couldn't celebrate or you need to know. Then how a library will implement this display for the tables. 

Speaker 2  (14:28)
First, I'll get the data started from the table. And So we want to make sure that there is the chunks that we are creating yet. Should be enough for the contacts window. 

Speaker 2  (14:46)
This is what I ask yes. 

Speaker 3  (14:48)
Now not for the context window like you can experiment of 10000 characters, 20000 characters, 1500 characters in one single chunk. Hello? 

Speaker 2  (15:03)
Yeah, I got 

Speaker 3  (15:05)
So that is experiment for how much context we want to send. But so when you are chanting, like 10000 documents very less likely, you will Test this rather, you will choose some simplified way to chunk it and realize that, okay, this is fine enough from, let's say from experience, and I don't need to do the experiment that how big I can make a chunk, let's say I fixed it to 500 tokens, 700 tokens. And I think this is fine. 

Speaker 3  (15:44)
I will not do optimization in this here, but in some other layers. 

Speaker 2  (15:54)
We are studying it as a junk for that particular 

Speaker 3  (15:58)
So we have the document document is converted, we have one now chunks, so first we make the chunks now. All you want to make the checking as simple as possible. But still certain things. 

Speaker 3  (16:13)
We need to think of that. What you do with the table breaking in the middle. And this kind of this is one of the cases. 

Speaker 2  (16:22)
It is why is a document ID okay, then the page we can mention it, okay, then the chance. So at that time, when we are retrieving it, we will get a whole chunk. Okay, for that portal document ID 

Speaker 3  (16:37)
But. Do you ever tried some content enrichment? Before you do them marrying Got the chance. 

Speaker 2  (16:48)
We were using the depressive tax later on at the end of it. Can you specify what the content is? So 

Speaker 3  (16:59)
The chunk is from your document right? That you can invent and put that in the victory's room. But this is just a piece from the document It doesn't say I from where this piece is. 

Speaker 3  (17:14)
India and you don't need AI for that. So Have you ever? Let's read that anthropic document where they were sending the whole document and a chunk And create a summary of that chunk with respect to the document, and then add that into the content. 

Speaker 3  (17:35)
Of the chunk, have you ever read that? Do you recall? So what they did, let's say you have 3 page documents your chugging page by page. 

Speaker 3  (17:50)
So what they were trying that, let's see you send first page and also the whole document To get a summary for that page. 

Speaker 2  (18:02)
Yeah, that's what I was saying. But page, Y we can summarize that and then 

Speaker 3  (18:08)
Yeah, so then you add that. I Chamel it to the pitch at the end and then embared that Yeah, this is going to be scalped when you will work with teaching of the documents it's not going to work, so you need new content enrichment in a very cheap way. Possible? 

Speaker 2  (18:29)
Okay, we can remove the some stove works okay? 

Speaker 3  (18:35)
No, that is the latest, not recounted enrichment. You are removing, you are doing Kix, cleaning. So a card from adding AI summary, what kind of content enrichment is possible? 

Speaker 3  (18:50)
After the chunks, you get into the chunks. 

Speaker 2  (18:59)
We can remove the 

Speaker 3  (19:03)
No, you can you should remove? You should add more. You should enrich it. 

Speaker 3  (19:08)
Yeah, you can post process, remove multiple new lines by one That is the content enrichment you want to. You have the raw chunk, and you add more extra to it so that it helps the receivable. 

Speaker 2  (19:28)
So you're saying we have to keep the contacts window aside. Korea, not welcome that 

Speaker 3  (19:37)
Let's say you have a chunk, right? This junk will send to the AI but you don't embed that only that. So let's say in your vector cable or index, you have a you have a content field which has a chunk text. 

Speaker 3  (20:00)
You have an endless content field which has the chunk test text plus some enrichment. That's why you vectorize. That's what you use for search. 

Speaker 3  (20:10)
But that's what you Don 't use to send to the AI You said the actual content of that chunk, but for a vector search, you vectorize the chunk plus some metadata about it. 

Speaker 2  (20:25)
Yeah, matter of be maintained right for documentary, chunk idea everything. 

Speaker 3  (20:32)
Yeah, so where you I mean, where you have it? 

Speaker 2  (20:37)
When we are creating the chance right in the recursive character in the material to specify all these 

Speaker 3  (20:42)
Yes, but this is this. Metadata contributed to your factory and bearing. Then, that's that's the problem. 

Speaker 3  (20:50)
Right, so you can make your chunking simple, you don't think about it. So what you can add, you can add into the enriched content junk that page is third is 7 page N is 9. The document title is whatever the title is and then do you ever used a library called yaki? 

Speaker 2  (21:14)
Okay, hard of it, but not 

Speaker 3  (21:16)
Yeah, yet another QR extractor so you can if these are cheap, or you can use a Bart, you can extract some keywords. Add that into that chunk that will enforce more. Then, that makes you an enriched chunk, that you will vectorize, and you will use that first search. 

Speaker 3  (21:37)
But for AI, you will send actually after search. You get this whole thing. But you will send the actual content to the AI To produce a response 

Speaker 2  (21:48)
We don't learn this kind of part, but only the Yeah, so 

Speaker 3  (21:54)
Make a search. But at first, then you kind of finish this up with that. Now now you have the chance now in the index, what kind of decoratives you have used? 

Speaker 2  (22:09)
Have you used the database in Qatar store? Okay? 

Speaker 3  (22:18)
I mean, the vector database like PHI is chromatb, which one 

Speaker 2  (22:23)
Database internally, we have in the database vector story. Could that we have used 

Speaker 3  (22:30)
The Christian, which, who was the provider of 

Speaker 2  (22:34)
But just data breaks only inside the datab. 

Speaker 3  (22:37)
Has a vector stripped, okay so on the vector index level. Have you done any optimization? 

Speaker 2  (22:48)
Yes, I mean. At the time of selection, we have choosed a standard or a storage optimized one. 

Speaker 3  (22:56)
Do you know the algorithms available for a vector store, how it do the search? Can you tell me one of them? 

Speaker 2  (23:06)
Yeah, there were 21 is a tennis W other one is the IV. And in the NSW, we have the level wise, searching if data starts partitions, level wise. 

Speaker 3  (23:19)
So yeah, so if you do content enrichment, and let's say, if you've set H and S level 200, which means that is your neighbor. With enrichment, it works if you use H and SW right. And you have done content enrichment. 

Speaker 3  (23:39)
With adding the start page and page of the document idol, then the keywords right? Then these neighbors are I've seen better than without this Englishman. Of course. 

Speaker 3  (23:52)
You can use AI to add more enrichment, but this is not scalable. So The cheapest cheapest enrichment. You can do this way, and your H NSW will perform really good. 

Speaker 3  (24:08)
Yeah, okay, now. We rancor early schooling, so you get a school so Just reincorporate, automatically add it to your factory score or you. First pull top and reply the rental game. 

Speaker 2  (24:22)
Yeah, first, we have to retrieve the data, then we apply the crossing data. And then finding the 

Speaker 3  (24:28)
And which cloth in barrier applied? 

Speaker 2  (24:32)
Rich cross and cooler this 

Speaker 3  (24:44)
Okay, which means it's a database own crossing quarter. Let's say for example. 3 anchor models available from cohit coherenc. 

Speaker 3  (24:59)
That is a crossing quarter. And there is a lot of open source wants. So So which means now Let's say you have the The back end of the Reck system You want to serve that, you want to serve that application? 

Speaker 3  (25:18)
You need to have a Chatbot, right? So now I will share my screen. So let's say this is the conversation In a chapter, so can you tell me for OpenAI? 

Speaker 3  (25:41)
What are the rules available to send messages? 

Speaker 2  (25:46)
Yeah, system user human 

Speaker 3  (25:49)
And there is a new role error you know about it. 

Speaker 2  (25:58)
I know about that. 

Speaker 3  (25:59)
They have added the system roll, you know. 

Speaker 2  (26:05)
This is the day I said that right system go 

Speaker 3  (26:07)
The system road, now they are telling it's better to be developer, this road should be called so because developers setting up a system prompt on top of OpenAI system prompt OpenAI already has one system. So they try to call it no developer. Which is something new? 

Speaker 3  (26:26)
Still not? Yeah, so let's say now, I'm interacting with this backend, right? Put the rack system, I have other. 

Speaker 3  (26:38)
Let's say 3 more tools, which provide me a method about the documents that if I ask him to list all the documents related to xfi and search exit is not going to work. It need to go to a Meta that is store to list the documents for me. So one is simple, vanilla search application and one is agentic application. 

Speaker 3  (27:12)
New built agentic application or just nls, watch app Okay, so as you take application. No, I asked this question to the user, right? And then the role is assistant assistant. 

Speaker 3  (27:33)
Got the response that I ask it again on an assistant responded again. So my question is, then how should we secure them? And pull them when you'll come back to that same session 

Speaker 2  (27:52)
Yeah, so in the land graph, I can tell you, we are maintaining the checkpoint in the checkpoint. We are maintaining a body V saver with a third ID, and then the Friday, spoon, use your ID message. Current note and the current estate of their note. 

Speaker 2  (28:10)
So all those things we are maintaining if the message reaches, let's say some threshold, then we were summarizing the previous record and then keeping their top 5 at least in 5. But that's how we have the reducer and message 

Speaker 3  (28:27)
So the summarizing the complexion, this memorization, you add it or 5 that creates your, but then when you ask a new question. Where this new summary and the session comes from. It was true that in the same table, you rewrite all the conversations. 

Speaker 2  (28:48)
Or yes, we rewrite, actually. So we have the right 

Speaker 3  (28:51)
And then you don't have access to the older one happened. 

Speaker 2  (28:55)
It knows about the context, but not exactly 

Speaker 3  (28:58)
If I want to analyze User history, a message history, I will lost them, isn't it? 

Speaker 2  (29:07)
Yeah, we just retract redact, we just we just extract 

Speaker 3  (29:12)
Have you ever tried to see on the Mongolia database? How langraft saved this data. 

Speaker 2  (29:20)
Yeah, I created it created in the key value only, but created the shards basically partition. 

Speaker 3  (29:28)
Can you read your debt data by just quarrying that 

Speaker 2  (29:31)
Yeah, we can read that with a seat. 

Speaker 3  (29:33)
You would read the text. Can you read like this conversation from what it's saved by the plangraph? 

Speaker 2  (29:49)
It maintained the I didn't try it happening, but I think we can read that 

Speaker 3  (29:56)
Because how you will evaluate manually, your response and freedom. Yes, and also, let's say, for example, you can have disliked one of the answer How you will see that what the answer is disliked and what could be the reason for that plan graph, save a conversation as a whole. So this whole conversation should be safe in one, go, we'll eat again, add more stuff, save it again that you're asking another question, pull that again, add more stuff. 

Speaker 3  (30:32)
Save it again, and it'd want to save spaces on the cost of visibility. And it uses message plague, which is a binary formlet to save the data, and you will not see the data. But, if you query, you will not see what the text is. 

Speaker 3  (30:51)
Yeah, so message that is, that is a good thing about message back, but then, even if you implement another layer on the table to make another table for analytics that so that they can query and see what's happening. 

Speaker 2  (31:07)
Yeah, I tried ids and user ID. 

Speaker 3  (31:11)
Yes, so Auto syrup of this auto syrup. Land graphs of this case is not good. It's it's, it's not very good for large production application. 

Speaker 3  (31:27)
You lose more than your game, you gain speed, but on the cost of visibility, and there is a lot of headaches, because you need to then reparse everything you need to use message back to retranslate. It's a very huge headache job for analyst person. 

Speaker 2  (31:47)
You'll do it. 

Speaker 3  (31:52)
But. Now how do you provide citations? When you provide an answer How to prepare the citation? 

Speaker 3  (32:04)
Because user one to click on the citation, you'll see, okay, that is the part of the document. It's producing my answer. No, I mean, even in line. 

Speaker 3  (32:17)
Okay, so I kept providing some 

Speaker 3  (33:12)
This is a chat application. I ask a question 

Speaker 3  (33:40)
So I got a citation here. And it's siding from a table. This is a rescue query, it ran that query. 

Speaker 3  (33:49)
It'd find that and provide user. Okay, yeah. So when I respond, I must provide a citation. 

Speaker 3  (33:57)
So how I do it 

Speaker 2  (34:01)
Again, the moderator itself, we have not to specify from where we have achieved that data In the 10 kids, we had to add that 

Speaker 3  (34:14)
No, the farm that chunk you produce the answer. Now, it's a engineering problem that how you send this evidence to the front-end. Your EI had responded, right, so your AI had responded to this part. 

Speaker 3  (34:39)
Based on what based on this New data. So yeah, I see this data. And it responded. 

Speaker 3  (34:52)
But which means the context is used for AI to produce answer, also record to B. Seen by you. No, how do you attach this context? 

Speaker 3  (35:07)
And then how do you use this context? How do you store this context? 

Speaker 2  (35:12)
Yeah, there are several ways, 1 way 1 way I can think of is that we have here, studently filing and the motivator and then associated with the filing and document ID and everything we can a student into the S 3D or maybe some other location extended location for that cortical 5 okay. If you just file or something, you need to show up. If it requires a rule also I mean, if it required a sequel also so that we can configure it as a tool. 

Speaker 2  (35:43)
And we can run that 

Speaker 3  (35:46)
Yeah, yeah, so one caveat of using, S3 Today you have a file version one You have produced your answer on 5 version 1 now. File version one is deleted and file version 2, it's inserted, and if you will travel to your previous session. And clear on the response, it will not sign file version one. 

Speaker 3  (36:11)
It will show you an error that I don't see the response. 

Speaker 2  (36:16)
I don't see 

Speaker 3  (36:18)
Yeah, because the answer is there, but the reference is not there anymore because it's keep replacing. It's keep updating his version, which means you cannot rely on a static source, which means the answer produced for you with the reference should be stored immediately into a table so that it keeps stay with their session ID. The answer, which means It's a rapid task. 

Speaker 3  (36:46)
Do you need to get the content for the context which agent used to prove the answer and save it into the database. You cannot use the reference to a steb, because that is keep changing. And Yes, and because of this engineering problems In large production, applications like it's very difficult to use. 

Speaker 3  (37:16)
Like glandrass or something like this? Another thing is For example. I can ask in general, so are you. 

Speaker 3  (37:38)
Using some, let's say coding agents for code. 

Speaker 2  (37:45)
Yeah, I mean we were using the database Jane. 

Speaker 3  (37:50)
Apart from that, maybe, if you know, do you know about what is the skills in a coding agent? 

Speaker 2  (37:59)
What are the skill is skill set right? When you're talking about? 

Speaker 3  (38:02)
Yeah, so this skills, there is a certain term called skills encoding aging books and skills. This kind of thing, so I hope is I don't know I'm not interested, but skills. Yes, you know what? 

Speaker 2  (38:13)
First, we're talking about the agent. There is still an apart. 

Speaker 3  (38:18)
Okay, so what the skill does, actually what helps how skill helps an agent. 

Speaker 2  (38:25)
Okay, in the skill side. We specify what the agent want to achieve, and what he is, actually, let's say, if he is a Peter, we have to specify the role basically, and then we have to assess what you need to achieve. What is what are always 

Speaker 3  (38:48)
Yeah, what is the difference between the What is the difference between your actual prompts, your guideline and the skill 

Speaker 2  (39:00)
I think. Okay, we are specifying the role for one particular region. What you can achieve, creating the boundaries. 

Speaker 2  (39:15)
These are two separate things I can have and they it's the same thing. But in the agency specified as a skill. 

Speaker 3  (39:26)
So that Agent instructions is a generic instruction. What it can do, but it skills are specific workflows separated, when agent requires, it will load that one so that we can save context. Yeah, so let's say I have created a skill and also let's say I am using a LLM which released on 2025. 

Speaker 3  (40:01)
It doesn't know all the new things happened in the first API, but because of the cost, I want to keep using that region that LLM right. How can I make that agent still relevant that LM is still relevant? I can create a scale on the new implementation of a sustained Pi how a fast TA application can be built. 

Speaker 3  (40:28)
Then, I can save there as a skill And then I can Ask agent that used that skill when you develop first TP application. Only during the first debate development, it will use that skill, otherwise not I don't add all this in other prompt alteration, because that will then always be in the prompt skills are on demand loaded. So and that's how you can reduce a multi agent system to only one agent with skills. 

Speaker 3  (41:06)
So let's say you had 5 agents doing 5 ecstatic things You can have one agent, and you can define your skills that for SQL tables. That's how you access that query you run, I think the relationship between the tables Now, you said you're the advantage in you tell when someone either asks about something which is related to that, is school table, you need to search your use. That is skill XYZ that is skill and that is skill, then load it and then produce the answer. 

Speaker 3  (41:40)
You can have Time skills, and then whenever needed. Agent will load them, understand them. And then Because I skip now there is one important thing is missing. 

Speaker 3  (41:57)
Here we discussed is now OpenAI also role has a role which is tool, which is 2, is tool, is a defined role in Copenhagen. And the skills are provided through a wrapper of tools. So let's see if you have a page and context which is growing. 

Speaker 3  (42:25)
So your first interaction that you thought that you needed a skill You know, at this scale, and then you have a user and the assistant, and it's going like this. Because this skill is loaded once it will not load it anymore because skip in that in context you are sending the whole context every time to AI with a new question to get the set The same thing you're seeing here that you have a cortex limit here as a money value, but it's a context limit. The first question costs 0.9. 

Speaker 3  (43:08)
Which is quite high, because probably to do just a lot of tokens under the roof. Yeah, so and you could see what it does. Actually it answered this question 3 skills. 

Speaker 3  (43:32)
It has its own prompt, and then it owned it. It found that look, I need to load this skill, which has more instructions, I have to use this table. And this is the main skill that can define, and from this MD file, it knows that I need a resource. 

Speaker 3  (43:50)
And this is a resource guideline for this question. Or for this type of question. And then it understood that I need to prepare a skill query. 

Speaker 3  (44:04)
And execute that I see the response, I produce this answer. Now you could have added 5 tools or 5 agents, you just have marked down descriptions with one agent, and it works as the pipe agent will book with more contact with more engineering effort. So as an example, I can show you I didn't see him. 

Speaker 3  (44:41)
So So I have this is, then let's say an agent. For whatever way, the agent is defined, agent has a capability and get quality No agent has skills, so the skills is a one skilled MD file. So that child defines high level. 

Speaker 3  (45:08)
This is called advertisement of the skill. So this part In the during the agent runtime, when agent was built first These advertisements of the skills, all is added into the system program at the end. And from the advertisement it knows that which is skill is for which purpose And then when it needs it really the rest on demand when it read the rest, it might think I need to read one of these resources because these are separate tables. 

Speaker 3  (45:44)
I need to know maybe the geographic locations then I read that resource separate first and then produce my answer. Produce my escale credit. Okay, I have finished all my questions. 

Speaker 3  (46:01)
I wanted to ask if you have something I can discuss for 

Speaker 2  (46:08)
I am, it is more specific to the chatbots, or some other 

Speaker 3  (46:15)
So At the moment, it will be Some of the parties we already have an application. Some bugs found we need to fix them. Or we need to add new features to that on the existing application and in future, when the new request will come for a new application will be built a new application, it could be anything. 

Speaker 3  (46:43)
But it must well have AIM L out of the product. Our team doesn 't build any lab applications, which is itself, software. It must have to be yeah, I am a solution. 

Speaker 3  (47:01)
And at the moment, email solution is very less likely, gas solutions are coming, which means it's agent tick, chatbots or agentic counter generation, or But it's kind of something this, but at the moment there Agents only produce what to do, but they don't do themselves. Because healthcare is a very restricted environment, everything have to be cautious about that. If we let agent to change something, should we do that or not. 

Speaker 3  (47:38)
So now it only suggests user and built on that user can do what he thinks best. And that came down to mostly chatbots, but Intelligence is has a difference some childbook required to be 90% correct, and 90% correct. Otherwise, that project is closed because less than 90% is correct, is not acceptable when you are dealing with financial debt. 

Speaker 2  (48:07)
For example. 

Speaker 3  (48:10)
If you, if you can, if you tried, and if you failed, it's not fine. But we cannot I have that in the handle of users. We have to close them. 

Speaker 2  (48:21)
And what have we used ortigen, or what for the agents? 

Speaker 3  (48:25)
No, we don't use framework, I show you some problems. That's why I use them and I stuck with them. And I don't use either a vanilla or we have our built-in agent which we understood and built. 

Speaker 3  (48:42)
For example, the thing skill I showed you At the moment, I know framework has it. Yeah, hey. 

Speaker 2  (48:50)
I think. 

Speaker 3  (48:52)
Autism, not Microsoft agent framework is having it act like I cooled their repository and seeing them and building my agent my framework. So I know what they have and there is skills who works differently. For example, and there is skills, always make a read from the file path. 

Speaker 3  (49:13)
The problem is so then what I can do I can create tickets for to them, and I can wait until they fix it. That's why I don't use it. So wait. 

Speaker 3  (49:23)
I have agent coding tool available to me, I don't need to rely on someone's framework, I can just pull that and I can fix. And I can make what is what requests for me. So then what was the then I had to do? 

Speaker 3  (49:39)
Because I already read operation to the file system to create their skills. So if I use the async API which is Fast API, it will always block that read right so II make I make separate skill provider, which, when the agent in the build time, the skills are loaded into the memory which is stay in python's memory now it's async. Anyone can access it, no, Io read. 

Speaker 3  (50:06)
That feature, if I have to I have to wait for the feature if I want to rely on Microsoft to have it by themselves. So I don't want to have it, so that's why these chatting sessions, how memories are and those things like we don't rely on camera at the moment because none of the frameworks is fulfilling that goal, and also from the observability perspective. It's quite complicated now let's, for example, our agent has middlewares, we attach those middle wears, it's automatically locked the usage of LLM, like the thing I showed to you, like the cost, and everything primarily log that to a table in the SQL, so at the analyst quite at the table. 

Speaker 3  (50:55)
See, for agent X it costed this month that many dollars. The X user is the most costliest user. He used it the most. 

Speaker 3  (51:07)
Until so, the reporting required to be made, so we have no choice. If we use abstraction frameworks, then those things bring from those frameworks is quite complicated. So I tried those and I gave up and we don't give 

Speaker 2  (51:24)
I worked on this landraft majority and planchet, but I really wanted to explore this even 

Speaker 3  (51:35)
Okay, cool. Then all good. I will provide the feedback to Whenever my type omits, so thank you. 

Speaker 2  (51:45)
Okay, so thank you. Thank you. 

Speaker 3  (51:47)
Kiwa. 

Speaker 2  (52:30)
Yeah, yeah, it 

Speaker 2  (54:30)
It's going to be advertised. 
