
Speaker 1  (00:00)
We're going to talk about the hypothesis. Testing, the hypothesis system will test is average, serving size equal to 100 g. Sony, this is my hypothesis testing what we'll do is we find the food category food category is let's say salt number of ingredients is 24 okay. 

Speaker 1  (00:19)
Now we do the an over test, anover analysis of the variance, okay, kya sub category ka, average, same hai. The average of number of ingredients divided by between the group variance FIS greater than group. The mean mizada difference FIS greater than Then, group ke meada defender. 

Speaker 1  (00:52)
Grade nikalte, allverage submission of N. I. Xi minus X grand ka whole square N is the group. 

Speaker 1  (01:04)
SSW Hota hai submission of summation of Xi minus XIO whole square and MSB will be SSB divided by K −1M. SW is equal to S. Yes. 

Speaker 1  (01:15)
W divided by N minus K and FIS equal to MSB divided by MSW. Let's take an example. This is a group size number three. 

Speaker 1  (01:43)
The mean of the bread Munich lega. 11 mean of candid galgia 6 mean of milk sabka, Sam divided by N. Sabko, Liya ab Maine chakkiye between the variance and within the variance Toh peelami between the variance Toh ismein hamara, Hota hai. 

Speaker 1  (02:15)
And which is number of group Neem minus. Meanwhile's grandma plus candies, 3 hair candies, with a number of industrial multiply away mean minus. Grandmind kaholeskar, similar way for the milko Wali, between the variance And SSW which is within the variance lotham Mara design, a Brazil calculator 10 − 11 ka olisar + 12 − 11 ka holy square + 11 − 11 ka whole square, which is 2 same way. 

Speaker 1  (03:04)
Thomas total assist MSBSB divided by K −1K is 3, so which comes out 18.99 MSW is S wide N minus. KSW is 6 divided by N is It's a simple save, 9 total minus K is 3. This is equal to one So F values, 1899 / 1, which is equal to 18.99. 

Speaker 1  (03:37)
Can you so F value effective size for N square? Nicolas B plus SSW which is effective size FIS very large. That means average is different. 

Speaker 1  (03:51)
I will represent group came nyunga, difference, take a group K meeniska difference. A terror difference so fist P value F1 way calculate P value is F Mara, 1899° of frequency one is K −1° of frequency 2 is N minus. K. 

Speaker 1  (04:14)
0265P is equal to one minus F observed. So 1 − 18.99, which comes out to be Enormous wind came marks 5016 Agar. Question 55. 

Speaker 1  (04:35)
Laitu, thicker, normal nikke 90 Toh bahut Jayada h* Jaye. The svendra news distribution car have curve show Karta hai. Okay, so what is the P value P values in normal 20 kg marks 5060 mracose students is fine. 

Speaker 1  (04:58)
Okay, but on 19 lay, the debt is very rare. AP value E values are rearest. Okay, I've distribution karke, small F value common hair so P value is F equal to FIS equal to 80.02%. 

Speaker 1  (05:27)
P value are greater than 0.05 fail to reject H not if P value is less than 0.05 reject, H not Less than 05, with rejected the snort. I'll be value. Less than 0.05. 

Speaker 1  (05:47)
Tunnel, the rearest hair. To restore, chances, hair hamare. TMR H not h*, that's not reject. 

Speaker 1  (05:59)
To be H not reject h* Gaya fatten H1 Mara, no hai Toh kya sub categories, ka, average same hai, no, so each average serving size not equal to 8 gravity or So hypothesis testing, grand let's take the answer example, grand gram and Amal ka, average serving size equal so gram, and Mal has the same average serving size. H notice 5 g is equal to 5MM and H1 is 5 g is not equal to 5M. So we're making 2 Group DF14G and other for ML. 

Speaker 1  (06:48)
And here we'll do the comparison So we'll need, we need the test value. Or 2 groups, anova Values then F value, then we will get the F value So we have the formula, which is T-square. S is equal to 2 square. 

Speaker 1  (07:13)
FIS equal to T-square, correct, so and T is equal to H1 mean minus X2 main divided by_root of S1. Play holy square, NOnePlus 2. If 3 plus group then anova, only if we have the 3 plus groups, then we will use anova otherwise TW will refine so T value we are getting −23.057, if we have to form the F which is T-square, so we will do the T-square, which is very huge. 

Speaker 1  (07:50)
And P value is S is huge, pre valuably very, very less, and if F value will be less the P value will behind, so if P values less than 0.05, that means we have to reject the hypothesis, and FPS GIS not equal to 5%. That's what I understood, so we have the Cohens D effect, which tells us the size so P value, extreme small hair, which is 0.003, let's say and D is equal to H1 mean minus H2 mean divided by S pool as pool D is calculated from the value. From the formula N1 −1S1 is bar plus N2 −1S2 square divided by N plus N2 −2, and D is equal to 2T divided by under root of D. 

Speaker 1  (08:38)
F this formulation. Sunmen of G minus Mino families were less than 0G group. Ka. 

Speaker 1  (08:51)
Average service size is less than ML huge difference. So G ML ML MIT ok hypothesis, do group? We will do the test G plus we'll gonna do the unoverable test. 

Speaker 1  (09:05)
Show team rupt DF marij DF. Gd FM LD FM IT F include 927, which is used the PMRA03 aage as badha, the pee Chhota hoga, that means we have to reject the habit. Next is cheese square test CH square test. 

Speaker 1  (09:29)
Categorical variable ka relationship check karna T is equal to ruin to current variable total, so we have expertise summation of OI minus EIO whole square divided by EIY is the observed value. EH expected value, so let's say food category Vs search category Mr. plus check Y search category distribution Alag, hai hamare food category se, so brand Vs food category check if kuch brand specific category dominant Karti hai. 

Speaker 1  (09:58)
Kya. So is there any specific brand which dominates the Categories. Let's find out suchispar is coming up as 552 3P value 0.008 F value is very large, so cheezewar is also very large, which is observed is very large than the expected. 

Speaker 1  (10:25)
And for example, Pran, he has 1 to 10 values wheat. It contains wheat. Some contains wheat, some contains not so 0 and 1. 

Speaker 1  (10:35)
So brand aka VTS QL78 total is 100 similarly, brand BC brand C And So that's why, if I do the all summation. Is equal to 0. 0 0 8. 

Speaker 1  (10:58)
Brand and veetka, proportion. You're by the 2 200 Wheat is just for brandy. Wheat snow is for brandy. 

Speaker 1  (11:17)
Similarly, brand so rose Amari 100 or Amara: nikla 115 bjn sk value 70 2025 divided by the total, which totalist comes up 2:30 tomorrow, each Wife 50 okay, brand a wheat noki value 50 again, Brand B weight ESK value, brand weight monkey value. X. Let's a brand seek away. 

Speaker 1  (11:57)
23 north. Are we 25 tumhen sabkar, Samsung karna? And we'll get some values, 555 per K. 

Speaker 1  (12:12)
The degree of freedom is room manuscript column −1. The T values reject the hypothetical value is less than 0.05. Put category in search category. 

Speaker 1  (12:28)
Zomato, food conclusion, India may 35% change restaurant hai dominance caref, are the big restaurant having maximum outlet Barbie and drill type restaurant rating, Jayada hai kisi, alcohol hai establishment rating voting and Photo. Bangalore is other restaurants? Okay cuisine? 

Speaker 1  (12:55)
North Mostly budget-friendly average cost to 50 to Israel Aata hai price ranger restaurant average cost attribution to the Restaurant treaty coalition is 0 5. So we have confusion and confusion matrix, when I am looking at Then, we have products X equal to average cost plus votes Y equal to rating category. Good battery worst. 

Speaker 1  (13:24)
Then, we apply the random forest T PF and FET N RTPS 104 7, which is 00 value FN is Rocky value minus T. P. FIS colonke value minus TPT N ka. 

Speaker 1  (13:46)
Total negative. Total minus Tb plus FN plus FP TSM RF prize, 2 into president to recall UN Y session price recalls, 8034P value OnePlus nearly 0. So average rating Bangalore is equal to average rating. 

Speaker 1  (14:06)
Delhi Yeh, main hypothesis Alcohol plus restaurant is equal to higher eating 50 value FV Cohen P value Chai square Cohen, you so many Um. 
