
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Educational domain basically. Sir, move majorly worked with Starting with the data engineering ice architects park python, and then I walked on the racks, also on the AM side. I've done the eds on the when I was with There I have got performance in analytics idios, on On that tradition. 

Speaker 1  (00:33)
On the right side, I will check what's measurement also walked on. The agentic applications also using the Land chain linegraph work captures Yeah, that's just my 

Speaker 2  (00:57)
So I seen that air transition from The data engineer profile through Genia, right Why the soup are you undo? Switch towards the data you decide. 

Speaker 1  (01:10)
No, that's why it's required. Obviously, so I got a chance to work with the formal communal tools also. So that's why that 

Speaker 2  (01:32)
So what exactly you have worked from in the Chennai side so far Infosys, what kind of work we have done project we have done. 

Speaker 1  (01:41)
Yeah, when I have currently working with t Which is major new chat box? Here we have dumping all the data, and at the end, the user is square. It's a private Jack bought, okay? 

Speaker 1  (01:58)
Usually the opposition only. Where we have different layers, I can talk about like changing and weddings. We have tried to find it using our Laura. 

Speaker 1  (02:16)
For the specific domain models Apart from that, there were several issues that is that is kick came up with which until I'm wedding here. Also, we have used the llms, which is open GI OpenAI GPT-4 model. We are trying different models also, but that is the one that we are currently using similarly for the embedding. 

Speaker 1  (02:42)
Also, we have to try different, then we have fine-tune. The re ranking has a regulatory layer using the reranking approach by encoders and multiple and 12 cross encoders. To make sure that our chat boots are Have no relatency, should be accurate, less and more. 

Speaker 1  (03:06)
No attend. Hopefully that I have, on the other applications, also where we have designed a legent, we should decide which dribboot, it has to take Basically, here we're changing the hand we're extracting the intent from the email. And based on that, you intend to go through the planner region plan agent decide which other approach they need to take, like as to update some values, basically. 

Speaker 1  (03:44)
Basically so that we have I have built-in there. Also I have used a bar BERT model for removing the data. Also, there is an weather evolution that I worked in. 

Speaker 1  (03:56)
I asked last year which is related to the Transcript that we have received based on that Transcript, we have Evaluated, the Agents of feedback agent that is also the in-house project that I have 

Speaker 2  (04:26)
So the major shoot the checkboards that we built is this year, the aggregation too much right, primarily that are the heavy government, so how to avoid this solution in that case. 

Speaker 1  (04:41)
Yeah, the major problem comes in. The generation layer or in the retrieval layer, so to test those 2 layers. We, what we usually do is we pass the chunks into the oil, and then we see the generated output of that, if the output is correct, that means the retrieval way as a problem. 

Speaker 1  (04:58)
And if the output is not correct, and that generation layer has a problem. So fixing the generation layer, we have multiple matches. We actually reported on the daily basis like we have the actual faithfulness accuracy, sorry, answer relevance. 

Speaker 1  (05:17)
Also, the context decision on the retrieval side. We can recall and our New justification rate, this one Discounted, cumulative green value, and then we check the context decisionly, so these are the few values that we check based on the regular parameter. Based on that, we decide whether which area we need to look at, and then we deal accordingly. 

Speaker 2  (05:52)
So let's say that you need to build an AI agent which should basically automatically fixes the data quality issues. Right? What your approach will be. 

Speaker 1  (06:05)
Fix the data quality approach. 

Speaker 2  (06:08)
Data punch issues. 

Speaker 1  (06:09)
Data quality issue. What does that mean data quality? I mean. 

Speaker 1  (06:15)
It could be. 

Speaker 2  (06:16)
To air pollution, what's on does that mean? 

Speaker 1  (06:24)
There should not be any special character every candidate 30 like that. 

Speaker 2  (06:30)
Yes 

Speaker 1  (06:33)
So my coach would be initially. I mean, we will be restricting ourselves to use the LLM extensively. Okay, before that, we have rejects and agricult. 

Speaker 1  (06:44)
We try to tune the data on the base level. And then we'll go to the alarm to decide, okay. If still, there are some issues that the element can take care, then we can do so majorly. 

Speaker 1  (06:59)
We have to, if we have the unstructured data, we have to make it structured data with the correct format, and then we can use the other element of the period 

Speaker 2  (07:16)
How we can Put this into production 

Speaker 1  (07:21)
Yeah, there are multiple ways. Basically. Are we're using the database? 

Speaker 1  (07:26)
So the data break side, we have different instances, different work cases. Recently, it is using the contaminatic administrator. We have restricted our data in carb. 

Speaker 1  (07:40)
You're done. So that's all on the other layer. I'm not sure because I'm not done But I work with a cicd models and other things. 

Speaker 1  (07:57)
That way we can 

Speaker 2  (08:46)
Yes, sorry particles. What is the agent is required in the production right? There is a need for implementing some certain observability and monitoring mechanism right? 

Speaker 2  (09:04)
So for the agent that he just explained the little party right if we need to Put this into the observability, what kind of observability you will be holding around it. 

Speaker 1  (09:18)
Observability, ok, has a tool if we can expose multiple Dryas parameters parametric, apart from that, we can use the you can guartail, our prompts. That's another way to verify even at the human and loop, the lms judge for the verification of the data received the lm. These are the few ways we can Add those info for monitoring. 

Speaker 2  (09:53)
So when I say observability, going to understand 

Speaker 1  (09:58)
I think. 

Speaker 2  (09:59)
It was a little bit 

Speaker 1  (10:03)
Sorry, I thought if it is like monitoring or it's a different type. 

Speaker 2  (10:08)
You tell me how the monitoring and observably, two different things, or same things. 

Speaker 1  (10:17)
Observability means how the model is performing, right? So that way, we have to expose the matches through that we can check 

Speaker 2  (10:28)
What about the solitary? 

Speaker 1  (10:33)
That we can see the latencies. Okay, how accurately These are the differences 

Speaker 2  (11:02)
So you have personally used dws, but I have seen a resume right? I got used to eliger. 

Speaker 1  (11:09)
Yeah 

Speaker 2  (11:11)
Okay, cool. So for the search laser type, there are three different things that we use primarily like, so if we are using a Jew or we can use as your AI search right or you can evaluate the pgvector approach. If you are using poster simple help, there is a mechanism called fires. 

Speaker 2  (11:33)
Right? Fai. Yes. 

Speaker 2  (11:36)
So I need you to tell me like which of these should be used in which kind of use case. But whether to how will you decide, okay, which one of these fields do 

Speaker 1  (11:50)
Okay, so we're talking about the vector databases. So FSI S is used for the local local searching. All the 3 are using the embedding search. 

Speaker 1  (12:03)
Okay, using the comparing with the query using the cocine similarity basically. For the we have pine cone chroma TV okay. These are the jewellery based databases, but for the PG vectors, where we are studying the vectors of the particular token, right? 

Speaker 1  (12:28)
So and then we have, if you want to change the locally, you can go for the or few irises, if you want to scale app the activation, we can go with the best I gone for remedy. Or any other vector in the middle? If you want to keep the cost and everything consistent, then we can go for the biggy vector where the data is not much more or not much less. 

Speaker 1  (13:00)
In a motor data, you can choose a PG 

Speaker 2  (13:10)
Okay, thank you, so I'm good for my side efficiency for me. 

Speaker 1  (13:15)
Can you tell me about the role and that project 

Speaker 2  (13:20)
So the role is Engineering engineer only, okay. So the actual work is going to be to build A AI layer on top of the data science layer. So the phase 2 of the work on the project phase one was all about the data, enjoying work, where they automated a lot of do a lot of greater pipelines, etc automated those. 

Speaker 2  (13:51)
I think to that they also set up the whole infrastructure for this whole project, right? There will also be some of the data in which you were from the line, but I think data is formulated. Work is done now. 

Speaker 2  (14:04)
They are into the building the data of different data models, and as the gmai has already picked up, so they are thinking if they can basically have a GenAI layer on top of their data, I say, so. It's hot the work is going to be 

Speaker 1  (14:22)
Okay, understood. Thank you for watching. 

Speaker 2  (14:31)
Okay, thank you 
