
Speaker 1  (00:00)
For them, some enhancement that we want in that system, and then accordingly, we'll be adding the comparance. Basically, we'll, be designing the components of that system so. We can you, know implement, the new encement that we want in the existing product okay? 

Speaker 1  (00:17)
So, and feel free to ask questions like whenever you feel things are not clear. Okay, so the use case is around a Chatbot, a single Chatbot. Okay, it is connected to the database is like it is connected with my miles fuel. 

Speaker 1  (00:32)
The database mungu DVS 3, all the places where my data is available as of now and based on my plain English query and one thing sorry you need to share your complete screen and open a not fitness. Then, you can use this notpel to write anything while doing the discussion and you can opt for you know, you can, we can communicate everything verbally as well. That is also fine, but we will keep this not fit open. 

Speaker 2  (00:57)
Vishnu, note that you shared one. 

Speaker 1  (01:00)
Any place where you can write 

Speaker 2  (01:08)
Yeah, I'm sure. 

Speaker 1  (01:14)
Okay, so let me start from again, so it's a Chatbot. Basically, Chatbot is connected with the my school Congo TVS 3, all the places gather the Datasets that the database no need to write no need to write. I can restrain. 

Speaker 1  (01:29)
So you can use this to, like, if you want to literally communicate something through, if you like to, you know, write bullet, coins try to doing communication, except for you, we can keep it blank as well. There is no constraint around it. So This Chatbot is already stable based on my plain English query. 

Speaker 1  (01:46)
It's got it to be a little bit, uh about the path like great to go to find the suitable information and ingest it and provide the panel output to you, that trends me in plain English, okay, so if I say provide me some my personal details, it can go to my skill, write the proper skill. Varies in fetch, the data in just the data provide me the panel output in the plain English or in how your format I want okay, in the same manner, my skill Mong vector database as well. 

Speaker 2  (02:17)
Okay, all so that for the pointers. Yeah, for the point of help, right? I mean, we have the my secret database. 

Speaker 1  (02:29)
You can write anything like whatever you write. It's fine. 

Speaker 2  (02:33)
There will be one database or multiple database 

Speaker 1  (02:39)
Vector database as well, whatever active vector database you want to choose, you can choose. That is also there in the system. So it's basically like the whole rg system already established. 

Speaker 2  (02:50)
Okay. 

Speaker 1  (02:52)
Today Wasn't further, okay, so this system is capable enough to invest my plane. English query access the data from the right place ingest it provided in the right answer and it is capable enough to, you know, if he doesn't have the information it will not help this in it, it will not be provided with the wrong information, it will always say like I'm not having the information. I cannot do it like not hallucinating. 

Speaker 1  (03:16)
Secondly So this is a proper rg system. Things are working stable product is live already. People are using it. 

Speaker 1  (03:25)
Okay, so no need to bother about it whether it is stable. Some detecting in that and you guys very simple, we don't need to think about it. We can consider its plot ChatGPT. 

Speaker 1  (03:33)
Anything is fine for the UI now the enhancement that we want in this Chatbot is first. With time, while interacting with this Chatbot, I can, you know, talk about my preferences? Basically, it should retain my preferences, such as if I say, please provide me answers in the table format. 

Speaker 1  (03:55)
I like it or don't write lengthy. Paragraph, just provide me the bridge points. All The Times it works for me. 

Speaker 1  (04:01)
This is a preference from a user, right? So it should be having like, it should be able to catch that preference and use it going forward like in the next month. If I'm talking through the Chatbot, it should be able to know. 

Speaker 1  (04:12)
Okay, this person likes our putting the table per metal full performance, so this should be able to track my personal preferences. Okay, that is first second, it should be. It should be able to retain my personal data or whatever information I am providing to this Chatbot hidden there, such as suppose this Chatbot is there and I'm asking this Chatbot like okay I am having 2 loans, one from sdfc bank, one from SBI Bank. 

Speaker 1  (04:41)
One is car loan. One is house loan. This is the EMI, this is the principal component and like likely. 

Speaker 1  (04:47)
I'm gonna complete in 5 years plan. On something for me, so I can complete it within 3 years like that. Okay, I am doing that particular communication similar to Churah. 

Speaker 1  (04:55)
It is investing the data. It is providing the answers all these things it is doing properly in an a proper manner right now. What I want is now, this data should be retained easily. 

Speaker 1  (05:08)
That means if I talk to this Chatbot after 2 months or 2 days, and if I say, okay, I am planning to purchase a bike. The rest. If it should be able to say, okay, it's good, it's just the right, but, you know, you're having 2 loans, which is running unpromised, even promised AI. 

Speaker 1  (05:27)
It's not right time you should not go for it but let me know if you still want to proceed so this time it is having the data right? It is using that, yeah? 

Speaker 2  (05:35)
What is the contact? It can answer any query or its 

Speaker 1  (05:42)
Whatever if you want to restrict it to a domain that is fine. We can keep it general, that is also fine. So for now, any domain which you want, we can take it like thermosis or technical accounting. 

Speaker 1  (05:52)
Whatever is Okay, we can beat in 2 bill, so choose one we can. We can align our examples with them. 

Speaker 2  (05:58)
No, let's make it general. 

Speaker 1  (06:01)
Okay, good. So general, but the example I gave it was regarding the loan, but there is a possibility next time I can talk about like, okay. I'm having 4 members in my family, okay? 

Speaker 1  (06:10)
2 kids. One Wife, okay. My parents are there. 

Speaker 1  (06:13)
I'm planning to go there to watch a movie Kashmir for visit. Okay, then plan something for me, etc. Etc. 

Speaker 1  (06:19)
After 2 months I can again say, okay, I want to go and trip this time, it should be able to say okay, you are having family here. Are you also including them or not? This time this data is also written. 

Speaker 1  (06:30)
So this system should be able to retain my data Two things. First, my personal preferences should be retained. Second, my personal data should be written These two things are a very beneficial. 

Speaker 1  (06:45)
This is the requirement Now to you any questions you want to ask for motivate, I can provide the answers, or I can provide the examples. 

Speaker 2  (06:57)
Okay. Okay, my sequels, okay, then Make a user information, and he's got to be a little bit of a conversation. 

Speaker 1  (07:17)
And you can add many components you want, like, there is no restriction because we are upgrading this head, but right? So you can add more databases, more that databases. Whatever you want, red is whatever you want to add, you can add those as well. 

Speaker 2  (07:43)
So what we're asking should I buy it A Bike or not, ok. 

Speaker 1  (07:50)
Yeah I'm planning to purchase a bite. Film, right? 

Speaker 2  (08:02)
Let me do the reverse in the interview. 

Speaker 2  (08:41)
Is it able to 

Speaker 2  (09:08)
Display administration list is it related 

Speaker 2  (09:48)
The return search for the current 1994 

Speaker 1  (12:37)
We are revenue in 10 minutes, so you can take 2 or 3 minutes more. Okay, then let's discuss over at least we can have something a bit, okay. Definitely, no one still. 

Speaker 2  (13:54)
Surprisingly, yeah, I mean We can talk about Yes, I'll start with the user query. So basically I start with here where, in the Mexico I am getting the user details of ID and AI recite in the moment I will be storing its conversation based on the user ID. I'll summarise it and store it into the vector TV. 

Speaker 1  (14:42)
So conversation to summari, like to summary of the whole communication, and it will be stored in that person. 

Speaker 2  (14:50)
Accept related to the particular user 

Speaker 1  (14:56)
Pickunism, there is only one 

Speaker 2  (14:59)
Yeah, I mean, yeah, it can be a yeah, that's fine. There's only a multiple user references are getting stored now. I'll search it based on the dense centre. 

Speaker 2  (15:10)
Sparse approach, spark equipment or process similarity for the factor only. All the 3 details and create a history out of it, and because I'll check whether the data is present in the history or not. So I'll take the last 5 conversation of the user, because it would be 1000 many lines of the conversation. 

Speaker 2  (15:37)
I'll check whether it's the history is there to the question I was asked if it's torn if it is met, if it's relevant to the Let Mexico purchases relevant to the history or not. Okay, if it is then I'll pick those data from the cache. Otherwise I'll pick the whole history. 

Speaker 2  (15:59)
Holistry, and then I'll again go to summarise it. Sir, I can have the contact either. I'm getting the contact from the history or the cache or from the whole history. 

Speaker 2  (16:15)
Then, I'll pass it to the prom. In the street itself I will have the format. Okay, what it has been asked for our bullet points or anything with the actual context and the ask. 

Speaker 2  (16:27)
Okay, so in the ask, I'll measure it, the role of the prompt, so I'll create the categorised role. I just says, explored of the financial expert. And this also I'll figure out based on the similarity search. 

Speaker 2  (16:42)
Okay. 

Speaker 1  (16:43)
Okay, so sorry to interpret, I got this system. Actually, so let me Put one question, and you help me to understand how it will work here, okay. Off. 

Speaker 1  (16:57)
Same worry. It is having a loan information Okay. Until and right now you're saying finance. 

Speaker 1  (17:05)
There is a possibility I might have told good amount of things that should be planned not just my loan. Good amount of things Now this financial expert, you are saying, it will be going to that particular space where I'm having like my context, which is my chat history, which is, or it's summary, maybe is like I'll be trying to find only that summary that jedestry, which is relevant to finance right. 

Speaker 2  (17:34)
Based on the creation that I'm asking the but 

Speaker 1  (17:38)
Okay, okay? So my question is this time? I'm planning to purchase a bike right And my summary. 

Speaker 1  (17:47)
Fiscal, my conversation could be very long, right? I might have talked multiple things about my personal finances in multiple sessions. Though I'm one single user. 

Speaker 1  (17:56)
Okay. So good chat history we are having if you're doing summarization of the chat history so summary will be very crisp, right? It may not have all the information, just a summary. 

Speaker 1  (18:06)
It cannot tell each and everyone right? And we're trying to adjust the summary History, and if I'm saying like I'm talking about the purchasing a car, but if you go for the vector database and try to retrieve the similar channel. It'll be trying to find something which is related to purchase of buying gets it those words right? 

Speaker 1  (18:27)
How will you relate this query with something which is related to my loan? Because in my query, I did not even mention the loan. I just said, I want to purchase it bye, that's it. 

Speaker 1  (18:38)
I did not even mention about the room, so how will you direct towards that bird? Where like it should literally go and check the loans. 

Speaker 2  (18:47)
Yeah, in that case, we have to create twos. I mean, in the moment, debate will be, yes, your conversation. Okay, we don't have to summarise it. 

Speaker 2  (18:56)
Here we have to store the whole context, okay, into the veteran store language will do the searching, okay, based on the query that you have asked for it will search for it in the vector store itself. It will find that corresponding embeddings or similar meanings And I have to be spark search also. Because Or either I have to watch Either we can create A Your Logical context. 

Speaker 2  (19:40)
Which means that it will create a structured data But structured data should have some domain, correct? Here it is, asking the general question. Could you lay to the bike? 

Speaker 2  (19:56)
It could relate to the anything medicine or something, right? 

Speaker 1  (20:00)
Okay, now we can restrict it like first structure you could assume as automobile, second is finance. Okay, these 2, then how will it go? 

Speaker 2  (20:12)
Yeah, I mean with denvini to route it okay. There, we need to specify the router. Based on the categories that It can go into category. 

Speaker 2  (20:28)
It could be, let us say it could be finance. Okay, then we will granilize all those categories and categor. 

Speaker 1  (20:37)
Okay. You can resume any 2 or 3 more every morning, so ultimately what I want is my query. Is I want to purchase a file. 

Speaker 1  (20:56)
Now, help me to understand how your system will help me to reach to those particular information which is related to my loan. This is late, my query is provided. I want to sir. 

Speaker 1  (21:11)
That's airport, this English query into the system. Now do whatever the system can do. 

Speaker 2  (21:20)
Yeah, I went. The router thing will not come here, okay. As Make the structure data in such a way I mean, I in the query itself from the past conversation, I have to understand the user. 

Speaker 2  (21:43)
In that case, I have to see I have to. Extracted information like a horse. Location. 

Speaker 2  (21:55)
What else liabilities? Salary, your maybe range of salary. Uh, if he's asking about the bike, then I have to make sure that what is his budget? 

Speaker 2  (22:15)
I have to ask all those things. And 

Speaker 1  (22:19)
Obviously, like it will be saying like you have any loan your regular and still like still still you wanna go ahead, tell me your budget like that it will be having those kind of things like this system will ask. But the tension is, how will it reach to my retained information which is already there in the it should not ask that it should simply, you know, refer that 

Speaker 2  (22:41)
I'm taking two things and one is asking the bike purchase. And is asking, can I ask for medicine? What is your 

Speaker 1  (23:03)
In this scenario, it should be like saying, okay, you are you want to take this medicine, but you're having sugar or diabetes. So it is 

Speaker 2  (23:12)
So yeah, I was trying to understand the structure of the data, understanding the user. I mean, I should try. I will go to extract the information. 

Speaker 2  (23:30)
Here I can use a small model. Okay. Where if you don't creates some structure context of the user, it can tell something about the user and those things. 

Speaker 2  (23:49)
I can store them into the longer TV. That is specific to be Users 

Speaker 1  (24:04)
So it's okay like instead of going with this again, this time like you can trigger different example medicine as well. Instead of I want to purchase a car, my question is, can I take a more 650? And I'm having a small fever, can I take it simple, okay, now it should be having my information, whether I was having cancer in the past. 

Speaker 1  (24:27)
Sugar, whatever, how will it exist by query and then reach to that information? 

Speaker 2  (24:33)
Yeah, I mean, see this will also work here. Right? What is the age okay? 

Speaker 2  (24:38)
What kind of disease you have medicinal information? If in the previous chat he has become made it So those things I will extract it as much as I can from the smaller lump. Okay, neither 

Speaker 1  (24:58)
Cool cool no, no. That is correct. That is correct. 

Speaker 1  (25:01)
Actually, we can use something to affect this information, and we are saying this. And this is the last question you mentioned a structured data, right? What will be the structure? 

Speaker 2  (25:12)
Yeah, I mean structured in the sense because I'm storing that in the mongo db, there should not be any structure, but there might be some columns right columns in the sense to understand the user. On the use from the user perspective, all this information that I can extract, I'll extract it, so that's what I what I want to do. 

Speaker 1  (25:35)
So you're saying, table table will be used to say, kind of table right, a rigid scheme up. Yeah? I had only these questions, so do you have anything for me? 

Speaker 1  (25:48)
That one was 

Speaker 2  (25:49)
Yeah, can you tell me about the project and Row is 

Speaker 1  (25:55)
Uh, rule is like score development. Along with R&D for this day so 95% of the time is one of the dedicated 2 development, either some kind of development or some kind of R&D and then apart from that in, you know, business discussion with the business team, global savings, like what they think the requirements or whatever you want to push next in the market and I think HR must have already made. We are working in the accounting domain, so the platform we are having service, we are having pro platform, it's in accounting domain, and we theore platform, we have automated the regular tasks, which an accountant does or accounting pointers for the major companies, so this is the product and currently since last 1 / 5 years. 

Speaker 1  (26:42)
Our main pool, or we could say, like, we have unligned ourselves with the AI where the same capabilities. But more risking and smartness we are introducing with the AI, so user has to do minimum stuff needs to provide minimum information, and the system it should be, you know, able to do rest of the things for him quickly. So this is the broad over. 

Speaker 1  (27:05)
I am providing not like everything in detail, but this is what you are having an insurance points. 

Speaker 2  (27:12)
Okay, thanks. 

Speaker 1  (27:14)
Thank you. Thank you so much for your time. 
