
Speaker 1  (00:01)
So DF0 plot dot Pi yo task. Date. Period of data frame so data bundle dot head DF dot plot. 

Speaker 1  (00:17)
Karni XY, can't visit line tamari line ban jayegi kind is equal to area. Kind is equal to BAR H barchart. Kindly difficult to bar kind is equal to sweater data. 

Speaker 1  (00:32)
Task. And it comes 500, 300 period of data frame Data hai, caller task index So adhyam, food tables are F. C. 

Speaker 1  (00:49)
Underscored, honour brand ingredient serving size serving unit food category search category. Check null count, and the percentage filled with brand owners, as unknown, because what we're doing is we're doing a stepwise cleaning and the EDS then we're doing, then the step 4, we'll go to do the clean ingredient data, then we'll gonna describe it, top 15 brand owner count. They will try to at the bar chart. 

Speaker 1  (01:18)
Okay, target store Walmart. Total topic is not 10 foot categories. Okay, ingredients token is an array. 

Speaker 1  (01:28)
So ingredients complex break karenge in rent, ki lunche karenge ticket Chad banayegi hum log based on the ingredient, length, barchatra, and Instagram, top brand ingredient length historical. This shows branded. Have brands have the large count ingredient? 

Speaker 1  (01:45)
Okay, so search category count search category Maya warange grape counts are 200 200 food category count. Let's say popcorn seed and vegetable oils say counts again serve unit size. Ji sabse badhaya, which is more than Mal. 

Speaker 1  (02:06)
Serving unit size chart all ingredients created like sofa, split and explored as token. Okisham explore kar diye ingredients, word cloud of the ingredient, average number of ingredients. Per food category, add column in DF allergen. 

Speaker 1  (02:29)
FC induskar ID food category, milk hai, soy bread and burns. Train model to predict what from ingredients provided so logistics rational Marathi of IDFC as bast hai. Then we have displayed the data test data pay prediction on logic curry. 

Speaker 1  (02:50)
And we'll let the procession recall accuracy score. So we got the difference cross 98 okay, so encode food category food categories are Braden, burns popcorn category encoded are 8 and 9, let's say. Predict the category encoded based on the ingredients. 

Speaker 1  (03:22)
Show Kara, using the random forest, we get the A furi score is 70 Okay, accuracy is 80 precision and recall is 98 and 78%. Then we've calculated the confusion matrix, okay with actual and the predicted. And based on that, we have created the accuracy precision, we call an F1 school. 

Speaker 1  (03:50)
Precision is tipper on ticket plus FP recollege TP on T plus F. N. Turn the Confusion, metrics circulation is It's the ingredients are popcorn nuts. 

Speaker 1  (04:08)
Peanuts, salt food categories, nut snacks. Now the gives um category category where landbook and code karenge you gave him a Poore stuck. Bixby ko, call availability, one ticket random. 

Speaker 1  (04:25)
We will use the random forest prediction of category confusion matrix of the Y test, and Y prediction is N harray, where we have alcohol. All noodles. All noodle is 0111. 

Speaker 1  (04:43)
Okay, then we have calculated the TP of alcohol DP of F of alcohol. Tip of alcohol would be an area of iron INJINI sorry. Sn will be calculated based on the Awesome of rose eye minus Tb. 

Speaker 1  (05:10)
Okay, some of all zoos, noinus TP. And FP of alcohol would be some of column, I minus TP. Chennai would be total sum minus T PF minus sum of T PF N and FT. 

Speaker 1  (05:34)
Rose ka sabke minus TPC minus. F. So that's how we gonna calculate the Precision department. 

Speaker 1  (05:47)
Everything coffee. Green vinegar, mullasses, green vinegar, yeast, a carrence, multiple Sarah. 

Speaker 1  (06:11)
This is testing. So if you do the hybrid testing 
