
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Disease in the secular system markets, so I have pilot embodies for another project in the mind. 

Speaker 2  (00:06)
Sorry. What wages is sold? What was your source? 

Speaker 1  (00:10)
If source is an hrc, stomach at data is coming from the HR system. 

Speaker 2  (00:14)
No N the system, what kind of data format you are 

Speaker 1  (00:19)
Is it like it's this system? You can like streaming data. Okay, whenever they employees they hire, they will generate the one file Jason file. 

Speaker 1  (00:29)
Okay, that then that file will be placed in the adls. In asujan, that file is based in the ads, we will process those file. We are currently we are extracted file and we are structuring. 

Speaker 1  (00:41)
The structure we are converting to the structure format and we are inserting the data to the sea sequels about sequence serve. We are following the mediane architecture, the we have a landing stage and transaction technology. So we are inserting the data to this landing tables after some time we are in see because of we have sp procedures. 

Speaker 1  (00:59)
Those processes will process in the data, like processing data from planting to the staging film. Staging, they analysing the data that procedure, which type of transition they have accepted, is select higher first or they higher or termination that Poe or job could change or store transfer. So these kind of panels in the way we are doing in the staging. 

Speaker 1  (01:20)
Then based on the that the transaction we are updating the transaction, the transaction tape like Aia new termination program so whereas we have updated in the transaction table from other downstream system. I said they are picking the transaction. Suppose if the view higher we sent for new higher employee, we won't be having employee ID. 

Speaker 1  (01:42)
Right? So see other terms of what they will do. They will pick up the transaction from the power table and they will assign create the new employee idea. 

Speaker 1  (01:50)
They will assign a regular power system transaction tables. Then yeah, this is a source of this is the flow of data. And here we are, we are doing to lead, we are great. 

Speaker 1  (02:02)
And these are one way of data flowing streaming data flow. Once this is done. So we have we have to one more project is there. 

Speaker 1  (02:11)
We're seeing the same here, we have one more project like small project. So we have to extract the data from this half 3 system looking HR system. And this CPR system. 

Speaker 1  (02:20)
And we have launched Mister, I'll set a gap from trade system. We have to extract the data, and we have to place it in the adls. So because they wanted to identify the data disturbances between these 3 system and suppose they hired, they transferred contemporary from store a to store B but that is not reflecting in the other non system they wanted to identify such data. 

Speaker 1  (02:44)
So for that, we are every day we are exporting that data to the area. So from there they are analysing the data. But here we are, using that adf to extract and transform road loading to arise adms. 

Speaker 1  (03:05)
One is streaming data. We are passing on hrs down to the rg system, and we are another one is we extract the data from all the systems to the adls to analyse the data extract the data. 

Speaker 2  (03:16)
Thank you. So what are the recent challenges you've faced? 

Speaker 1  (03:21)
See Sometimes. In current projects, I can say like I said it one more project cooking current project they know much but in either I said other project multi hours even I have mentioned either in that project what not technically but some business perspective we have faced lot of issues so like problems you know and technical. 

Speaker 2  (03:48)
Donald Trump. 

Speaker 1  (03:51)
Okay, but technically, I just say like 

Speaker 1  (04:05)
Sometimes Our system is okay CBT system. We are maintaining the CBI system. Sometimes we have to extract the data from the HR system. 

Speaker 1  (04:17)
The system is existing in the I mean that system is managing by the different vendor and other constant systems of their managing by the other vendor not capturing so other vendor so sometimes we are facing not able to connecting and extracting the data. Like, suppose we are getting lot of deadlock issues, deadlock data. So we are not able to extract the data on Tamil. 

Speaker 1  (04:50)
Some is going job is failing due to deadlock issues and from others because of other constitutions because they are doing lot of operates on the system. The day tables, actually while we are extracting the data from these tables. So that is, that is, I'm like, I can say, challenging. 

Speaker 1  (05:08)
Have connected with them and then we have provided the like which job is and causing that issue and which table and we from our side we have provided information screen to investigate there to investigate so then they're investigating but I mean I mean they are not responding until That is one challenge we faced, actually, because that is a because on 

Speaker 2  (05:34)
Set the data with Samsung Pay sign on the spark side. Have you faced any challenges? 

Speaker 1  (05:40)
On spark side yeah, yeah, so on spark side right side? Suppose in while yeah, I said right. We have to extract data from we have extract data in form of Jason 5 cycle to jaissemble, so sometimes what they will do sometimes we have scheduled one job. 

Speaker 1  (05:58)
We are basically we will receive 2 types of files. One is the Delta and one is SIM file Delta. Whenever they will immediate that Delta bill will generate whenever they will make any changes for any employee that file will be placed in the areas we will process that is not an issue and sometimes in another file I said full file in full file what we have crossed batch price processing. 

Speaker 1  (06:23)
We have processed batch file you can we have we have our own processed around 12 PM UTC? So sometimes what they will do. They will not place in the full file. 

Speaker 1  (06:32)
The full file is for every store. They will generate one full file at the end of the day. That fulfil will contains the all the employee information. 

Speaker 1  (06:40)
You are working on the restaurant or scope, so sometimes what they will do. They will not only they will sending them around in us. We have around 30000 stores in restaurants sometime. 

Speaker 1  (06:53)
They will send in the only the 10000 stores and after 12 PM. They send in the remaining files, but we have a job we have scheduled only the till 12 PM files only we have to extend the data, sometimes they will send in the after 12 PM. Okay, we are skipping those files so that is the one thing but for that also we are like we have mentioned like if the in the file name they will mention times damping based on the time stamp which this was the issue and then research app then we have implemented the solution then based on the time stamp. 

Speaker 1  (07:29)
We are extracting the 5 after 1 hour till We are extremely good job till 2 PM, 2 AM, so if any price after arriving 12 PM? Also, we are checking the time stamp and we are processing those files that is one challenge from data website. 

Speaker 2  (07:50)
Have you faced any squeezes in the daytime? 

Speaker 1  (07:55)
Yeah, 2 yeah so sometimes see I said right so sometimes what they will do or see this decision issue okay because in recent times I think or around the which is 5 to 6 months back due to some issues at their end deployment issues they will they have generated multiple files for a single store for single source. Their generated 5 to 6 files like that, we have around 130 stores for 30000 × 5. It will be more file size around 55 around 55. 

Speaker 1  (08:33)
Yeah, around 5 okay, that time data also huge, right? So other time, we have faced these issues. Like we are not able to this data scenarios while partitioning the data unevenly distributed, because that is not usually we are receiving the data in 2000 files, but we may at some time we have received 50000 files. 

Speaker 1  (09:06)
We have used data so that time data will be distributed animally and the data tunnel happened. To handle that, we have implemented like A He barched out that the reportitioning and asked the joints. Joints are a shortage of joints to handle this one and also to reduce the fights. 

Speaker 1  (09:29)
Okay, we have received more better. ISO to reduce the files we have to reproduce the files for that we have using the coales because we have around 50000 files, we have to reduce those files. We have to remove the 2 Cricket files. 

Speaker 1  (09:46)
Okay, and we have to remove 2 Cricket files and then we have to process only the only unique files. Okay, for 1 store 1 file only we have to process. Yeah, yeah, we have we have a face that you should. 

Speaker 1  (10:04)
In this case, we have filtered, only processed. We have filtered application. We have processed only unique files. 

Speaker 1  (10:10)
Yeah, immediately, we will be resolved condition. 

Speaker 2  (10:13)
Industrialists were talking about him. 

Speaker 1  (10:15)
Yes, yes, I mean, yeah, you know the data. Like usually, we received 35 some. We received suddenly we received more files more data so that in that case and also duplicates also entertaining. 

Speaker 1  (10:32)
So so that time judges must happen. So for that no next time we have nation, we have removed all of these files and we have passed away there. Unique size so yeah, unique data. 

Speaker 2  (10:51)
How do you handle duplication? 

Speaker 1  (10:53)
Calm, see, so we assume So while extracting the files. So while we have extracted data and we have placed that data frame from data frame, we have removed the 2 tickets at a crore duplicate data, suppose one user we have unique ids. We have G we can call it GA and global entity, so so then, based on the that gid, we have removed the duplicates. 

Speaker 1  (11:25)
Then, yeah, we have removed the duplicates. Then we only have processed whole unique gids. 

Speaker 2  (11:36)
Ok. What is clustering and liquid clustering? Sorry, what is clustering and liquid clustering? 

Speaker 1  (11:48)
Treasury, like So Jobs. The scope of Viola. Growth clusters. 

Speaker 1  (12:03)
Okay? 

Speaker 2  (12:10)
Okay, what is clustering Vs partitioning? 

Speaker 1  (12:15)
Partition individual sequence segregating the files into the smaller files database segregating the data to small smaller files. We can we have a different type of partitioning, so we can create partition? So it's like raise partition like rash partition, like we have okay, just raid distribution cigaretting the files, okay, partitioning, so And then clustering, right? 

Speaker 1  (12:47)
So clustering also like something like we can create the Like Something like that index 

Speaker 2  (13:08)
What is my Microsoft party? 

Speaker 1  (13:12)
Micropartitioning, I'm not much aware of it, because 

Speaker 2  (13:17)
What is the end of the Z order? 

Speaker 1  (13:23)
So is an optimisation technique in database. So whenever sometimes suppose we have one table, well task table or 5 way then we have once we so how this verdict Varna. So suppose whenever we implemented, that order order files will get a suppose splitter into the 3 files. 

Speaker 1  (13:45)
Okay, one untable splitter into the 3 files. Data will be 1 to 10. We have ids suppose in each file. 

Speaker 1  (13:53)
Suppose first file we will contain that one book 4one before 4 and the second file will contain. 5 to 7, another film will contain the 8 to 10. Suppose harder. 

Speaker 1  (14:08)
Whenever you use Z order. So it will be ordered first. It will be ordered then it will be divided into the files. 

Speaker 1  (14:16)
If you are not using judder, it will like it will be simply partition in the files like 114511 file 67. 915, like one order data. Okay, when we use this Z order, it will be first. 

Speaker 1  (14:38)
It will be ordered and then it will be splitter as it files. The statistics will be stored in this somewhere and collect first file mean value and second file Max on first file Max value and the same second value. Second file mean value second first file second file Max value and third file mean value and Max value. 

Speaker 1  (14:58)
Max ID whenever we use this disorder and query when we filtered, suppose ID4. This ID 4 will be in the first first 5. The first part I can say so it will go and check. 

Speaker 1  (15:13)
What is the main value and what is the Max value? Then, phone number okay if that is existing in that file, it will return that record. And then no need to go for other file because the 4 is existing with the only in this file because we have ordered right in other file. 

Speaker 1  (15:29)
No need to check if 56 other files something like same like suppose we wanted to filter 9 1st 5 it will compare the 1st file 9 will not be there because meanwhile we've one match valve is 4. You need to check all the values just to check the mean but meanwhile Max value and then if it is not there. Then, we will skip that file same. 

Speaker 1  (15:52)
Similar way. It will like that it will directly go to the third file and it will check whether 9 is existing because 8 to 10 data will be existing in the third file it will only written the third file data neither it will be increased performance of the query. 

Speaker 2  (16:11)
What is high, cardinality and low cardinality? 

Speaker 1  (16:17)
High cardinality, Mishra. Suppose. Suppose. 

Speaker 1  (16:32)
Agenda column teachers earns, oh, we agenda column in gender column. We have all the like only we have 2 values. Maybe okay, only 2 values, female and female. 

Speaker 1  (16:41)
Okay so this is real number of unique values are placed. So then, but total number of values is more, right? So here, if you cancel like A Hardenacism. 

Speaker 1  (19:16)
Sometimes we have to look up to look up tables and look up data. We are extracting the data from and to the data frame. Sometimes in, look up tables. 

Speaker 1  (19:30)
Like Oh, sometimes what they will do. More than where we will receive a suppose we will receive more data. You can say If see, if you want to use broadcast joint so one data frame should be small, and other data frame will be huge. 

Speaker 1  (19:55)
So sometimes these smaller data set, as I took up only we have only around 10 MB of 10 mbr at 15 MB of data. So sometimes what they will do. They will insert a duplicate data. 

Speaker 1  (20:10)
In that case, the tenum, we will go to the 20 MB 30 ambay, so in that case, we are fishing issues. Okay, we can broadcast joint contains only we are in this broadcast. What this broadcast will do. 

Speaker 1  (20:25)
The it will distribute the data amid the data across the exporter side. So so excluded. And then sometimes your data is used. 

Speaker 1  (20:36)
So it will not working properly again. Suppose, even if you are distributing data across the excutors, while joining the data will be Duplicate it, right, so it will be taken more time. So yeah, that time we faced that ratio and to resolve that no every time we are whenever we are doing the I mean, we know the issue sometime they are inserting wrong data for them to handle. 

Speaker 1  (21:05)
Techno, we are implementing. Before join mot, we are filtering the database. We are only we are checking the data that Put together if they do a surgery, then we are removing the database. 

Speaker 1  (21:17)
Then we are just doing the podcast join. Yeah, that way. We think. 

Speaker 2  (21:25)
Ok, sure. I'm done with the interview and I'll share the feedback with hl. Thank you for 10 
