
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Here, I will give the detail analysis of the stellar data set. Uh, so here we'll go to see what separate the Galaxy star in the Q So object. Here we will be accessing the telescope, and with that telescope where we'll be getting the The answers in the range of not the answer but it will tell us the Colour band okay. 

Speaker 1  (00:37)
So there are So let me start with that. So you'll gonna see you, G. R. 

Speaker 1  (00:43)
I. C. This is all the spectrum colour band and colour spectrum band so U is mean ultra Violette, green, red in Fred and Z. 

Speaker 1  (00:56)
And then you have the red shift. 

Speaker 2  (00:59)
Okay. 

Speaker 1  (01:00)
So what we're trying to achieve is we want to separate What's upredis, Taylor objects that we need to identify. So initially, we have the 

Speaker 3  (01:14)
Um. 

Speaker 1  (01:15)
We have the, let's say we're creating a distributed plot, distributed plot. We're seeing everything is normally distributed except the referee, which is rightly skewed. And which is falling under the values of 0 and 1 And then we have the heat map where we can see the all the Values are correlated with the other, which is highly correlated with the other There's you can see the ultra Violet is Illucorated with the G. 

Speaker 1  (01:55)
Okay, and all the colours are highly coolerated. So that means that if in one of the colours, the red is maximum, on the other Band also, the red will be maximum, okay? Maximum rightness so that we need to identify That we can see through this heat map created, so GIS highly correlated. 

Speaker 1  (02:24)
With R collects 91% and R is highly correlated with the eye, which is again 95% Okay, NRZ is also 1991%. So what we'll gonna do is we will go into Substract the colours from each other. Let's say you to G2R2Z so that we'll get the individual colours. 

Speaker 1  (02:55)
Andre shop will keep it as same then I'll plot the pair plot here we can see The U to G right, so U to G We have What? You 2G. G2R. 

Speaker 1  (03:21)
Okay, so here we can see that GIS majorly. In U GIS dominating. Ok. 

Speaker 1  (03:36)
The UG and GR. Jesus dominating, okay and I don't know how to read that one. We'll gonna see later, so Q So Galaxy galaxy. 

Speaker 1  (03:52)
G okay, so it will tell me the Galaxy. Veles is highly populated among yougy, and Gr. Okay, we'll see it later. 

Speaker 1  (04:07)
No, we're gonna see the train colour correlation. Now the coalition has been changed, okay, ug and Jug gar is 33% maximum. We can see is GR NRI And RING RRR INGRFA look up RI and GR ok this one cab. 

Speaker 1  (04:36)
We'll see that Galaxy S high, dominating other than the QSV and star Which is highly correlated? No, we'll gonna do the PC analysis. Pse feature bhi ugris and JJ. 

Speaker 1  (04:57)
You'll first try to standarise them all of them. Okay, and then we have the explained parents ratio of lambda, one divided by lambda, OnePlus lambda 2 okay. So these are the PCA PC one values. 

Speaker 1  (05:17)
So with UG it has 0.4 with GR at 0.1 with RI 0.1 6IG 0.1 5, and at shift is 0.08, you can see that almost 60% of the variation I explained by the 2 components. A 60%. No, we'll gonna take the PC 2. 

Speaker 1  (05:45)
And then we're gonna transform it. 

Speaker 1  (06:01)
Now if you plot the PC one and PC 2 Okay, then we'll gonna see it. Covers the Galaxy's Q send a star. Predicting the data into 2 dimensional, pointing belonging to different classes from quite survey. 

Speaker 1  (06:19)
Okay, then we've projected our data, and here we can see the results. Equally, in the distribution So for guj, we have 5 components, PC 12345. Getting the Values. 

Speaker 1  (06:43)
Of this, this range If yes, how we get APC 5 We can make as many as species okay, not that 2, but these are the minimum. Dimensions that we need to Siddi. Reduction. 

Speaker 1  (07:09)
PC 01 represent a global colour factor contrasting the colour indices with red shift. Capture the PC to capture the contacts between the Ultra red. This is a one 

Speaker 2  (07:28)
Okay. 

Speaker 1  (07:30)
PCA 2 pc, 3 reflects local spectrum red wavelength. 20 effect of the ultra mission in the red light. Okay, because we have the 5 field, we have the 5 PCA right representing each one of them okay. 

Speaker 1  (07:50)
Within the 2 And if we calculate the mean and standard deviation of the PCA one and the PCA 5 of all the classes, why we're doing it Because he want to access how well the principal components. Print the object class. Is it so we can see that for the Galaxy? 

Speaker 1  (08:15)
It's 0.7, main. Its individuation is 0.8. Okay? 

Speaker 1  (08:22)
And Then, we can see the violent plot Boxfort also. So PC analysis, if we see the fiscal in the P value Also, they will be trying to Correlation, mattresses, I mean, heat map of the PC one and the UG so how they're correlated, is PC 4 is correlated to the U. G. 

Speaker 1  (08:58)
Okay, and GRS correlated with PC one. IRI schooled with the PC 3 ok. Spanning trees, we have calculated Yeah Yeah, I mean, I don't know what else it is. 

Speaker 1  (09:25)
You're trying to do. 
