
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Who can now we'll calculate the P value? T-test to determine if population mean is equal to Some value example, if we want to know Is the main height of certain Species is a 15 inches. Does this we would collect random sample of 20 plants? 

Speaker 1  (00:24)
Find sample mean and standard deviation and perform t-test to determine if the mean height is equal to 15 inch H not is main height is equal to 15 inch H1 inch, it will not be equal to 15 inch T is equal to sample mean minus mean divided by standard deviation divided by under. Root of sample size so X by minus mu X bar minus mu divided by standard deviation and divided by under root of N which is sample size P value needs T-square. Okay? 

Speaker 1  (00:57)
So 2 tiled, 6 significance values, so P values less than some alpha level, like point 00010.050.10. Based on that, we can regret H not Reject the astron sample −14 individual 3 main population is 15. Random sample is equal to 2050 = 14 − 15 / 3 divided by root of 20T is equal to −49° of freedom would be. 

Speaker 1  (01:32)
London sample size −1, which is 1920 − 119. So from table, it falls between 1.328 and 1.729. Where were alpha is equal to? 

Speaker 1  (01:48)
0.190.05 P value for one side test is between point 12. And 0.05 ok. So 0.0520.1. 

Speaker 1  (01:59)
Let's take mid value,0.0752 side multiply by 2 = 0.15. So Y is equal to (−15) + 2X for energy is equal to 0.8 loudness. Okay, so P value is relationship. 

Speaker 1  (02:18)
Real or just luck. Relationship value, yeah, positive value calculate karo, so refer T distribution table ek T distribution table APIs less than alpha P is greater than alpha bataya, alpha is the level of significance. Telugu, test degree freedom. 

Speaker 1  (02:41)
T is equal to 1.95° fatimes of tan. Based on table, go to the data frame row and check where T value lies. So P value is 0.02520.05 P value is equal to 0.25 + 0.05, which is equal to 0.075 = 0. 

Speaker 1  (03:02)
So P is less than 0.05 significant P is greater than 0.05, which is a luck. Okay, so here the P value is 0.001. So 0.1% chance result happen randomly. 

Speaker 1  (03:17)
It is equal to 4.6°. Freedom is 18 to tale test P values less than 0.001, so P value is equal to 0.001 × 2, which is equal to 0.002, which is less than 0.05. So there is a significant trigger result, not no luck. 

Speaker 1  (03:43)
Also in the statistical, we have 2 types, descriptive and inferential descriptive. We have mean medium mode frequency inferentialists, unover regression decision tree and neural network. The distribution is into class with is equal to main minus match derived total Group is 7 to 12 frequencies to turn into 18 frequencies, 3319, 24 frequencies for normal distribution of amerota ET power (−1) / 2X minus mu, / 7 divided by whole square divided by Sand aviation multiplied by under root of 2 Pi. 

Speaker 1  (04:26)
So X minus mu. And why? So why is going to access barrel? 

Speaker 1  (04:35)
That's why, as it reaching infinity from both and wise EE ke power minus X square. Move the hill if middle list not equal to 0 shift to mu. EX minus me, okay, width, control norm. 

Speaker 1  (05:02)
Stern division is 200 now. Stand deviation is 10 exponentially developed in small hill become worthwhile. Ok X minus divided by 0.5 is high. 

Speaker 1  (05:17)
He'll become narrow. So big stand division, zoom out, wide hill, small stand division, zoom in narrow hill. Booster, multiply by the Send Vishwa vishwa. 

Speaker 1  (05:42)
One divided by San division under root of multiplied by under root of 2 Pi, we want total area equal to one like probability 100%. If area is too big shrinkage, if it is too small, stretch it. So if we integrate EK power minus X minus muka, whole square divided by 2 Assistant division holds, which is equal to Send division multiplied by the as a restaurant evation multiplied by the √2 Pi stand division of probabilities varings, okay, which is equal to X1 equals divided by N. 

Speaker 1  (06:25)
Sample is X −6 carcoons, one numerate analysis ED otta central tendency. Ticket. Random, we have the outlier treatment caping and flooring limit outlier exponentially, smoothing Sigma approach, keeping and flooring Mein kya Hota hai care 100 aa Raha hai Toh weekende's eaten by boys 100 lads, coming capping, a maximum value man lost 10000 So this is what the caffeine is all about sigmoid. 

Speaker 1  (07:10)
This work when data is nominally distributed, we choose rule. Magnitude of 2 > 3. It could be outlier, so Z is equal to X minus mu divided by the stand division. 

Speaker 1  (07:21)
Z tells how many stand division away from the main. Kilometre per hour? Why are you 365X ₹360? 

Speaker 1  (07:29)
Within the middle of the second division arrives, 60% within 2 Sigma N25 % percent, and the outside is the rear capping Sigma is US equal to mu + 3 instant divided, and abses. The upper limit lower limit will be mu, − 3 standdiviation, expansion times series, smoothing and shrinking. HT is equal to alpha HT + 1 minus alpha ST −1 Play alpha is full. 

Speaker 1  (08:04)
Alphi's full slow hard for pig ball alpha. Small gentle ball will come to you very slowly. Alpha's big, which is hard ball, will come to you fast quickly. 

Speaker 1  (08:15)
ST is 0 to updated value XT is equal to today's value ST −1 is equal to previous value. Core, meaning average sum weight of today plus some weight of yesterday weight is equal to alpha + 1, minus alpha, which is equal to one. Slowly alpha XT + 1 minus alpha ST −1 alpha is equal to 0.5 LST −1 is also 10X is equal to ST is equal to 0.520 + 1 − 0.5 × 1010 + 5 = 50, which is equal to 20 + 10 / 20 to 50 alpha is equal to Alpha is equal to 0.4SG (−1) = 10X is equal to 20, so alpha value Mein nikalte Hain, trust today a lot equal trust missing value may impute with zeros Mein medium mode for categorical second minister filling with mean use similar group examples. 

Speaker 1  (09:23)
Plan, call timing sage. Now we're gonna talk about the seasonality data to avoid find multiplication factor. M month is equal to New Year divided by new month. 

Speaker 1  (09:41)
Trigger. Buy virt analysis, Cricket skater plot correlation. Wise, always dependent on check for dependency or correlations, is not a variable transformation distance one. 

Speaker 1  (09:57)
Instead of choosing all distance from houses, we can take meaning transformation of create ratio variable, which is next relevant to the business taking log. If this is, take log a 1% instead of fix if aggregate, take EX instead of X. Okay, thanks dollars. 

Speaker 1  (10:23)
Call. Crime rattan price of house okay, lock transformer lock clinic always try to make it clear. Okay, that's why non usable variable PG dot get the missed D. 

Speaker 1  (10:38)
F. It will convert 201 based on the category. Delete the variable, which has low cardinality with Y. 

Speaker 1  (10:48)
Linear regression residue, some of square to Y minus Y bar. Coefficient. Xi minus XY minus Z divided by summation of Xi minus X Barco, whole square winters have been noticed to Y minus BAX Standard error in coefficient Is equal to San division whole square. 

Speaker 1  (11:17)
One divided by N plus X Marko, divided by summation of XN −1. SEB one cows, vegetables, division collision, XY minus X bar cover. Send division isn't variance? 

Speaker 1  (11:33)
RAC is equal to 100 of Rs is divided by 1 / 295% chance that interval will contain true value of P1B1 minus. 2 stand division, beautiful, stand division of B1. To disapprove, X not calculate, the T value T is equal to Beta one minus minus minus (−0) / 0 divid, one value probability of observing any value. 

Speaker 1  (12:04)
Tee or larger than T small Philippe. Value means there is an association between the predictor and response Less than 5% to have relationship P value should be less than 0.5. Ticket. 

Speaker 1  (12:21)
Horris is the RSE is average amount debate from the regression RSE is equal to 100 root of one divided by N −2. R. S which is equal to one divided by N −2 summation of YA minus YR whole square. 

Speaker 1  (12:36)
R square is a proportion of variables explained between the value 0 and 1R square is equal to TS minus Rs divided by TSS is equal to one minus RSS divided by TS should be greater than 0.5 is a good model. FIS equal to TS minus. R. 

Speaker 1  (12:53)
S divided by P divided by RSS divided by N minus P −1 FSF is large. It is high chance that one by Yb is Wrongly, classified. Categorical values, okay. 

Speaker 1  (13:16)
Lower P value, the more significant variable is determining Y to get. All values SNS dot add constant X multi MSc mean square error winner. Okay, bias girren's trade office. 

Speaker 1  (13:33)
Error due to linear model plus a mount by which predictor function change. If we change change data set plus variance of the error. Trade-off if we try to decrease one by changing model flexibility, the other one increase Show classification model. 

Speaker 1  (13:55)
Logistic L Gld a knm logistic formula Hota hai Eb naught plus BOX got by OnePlus EE ki power B naught plus B1X. Sigma, it function maximum likelihood method Correlation mattress. Deter normalisation X minus minus duadem Max X minus minus minax scale Axis scale is equal to a plus X norm B minus. 

Speaker 1  (14:32)
A data stand rising that is score is equal to X minus V divided by stand division. When units are completely different and will categorical, data P dot get damage will add column and assign 1 and 0. Feature engineering polynomial feature N is equal to 3X naught X1X2X3 windows method is equal to XX mean is standard. 

Speaker 1  (15:00)
Regression is led to regulation rich regression L1 regulation loss elastic net elastic net regulation. 9 projects Linear regression. Amazing equal to Delta X divided by Delta. 

Speaker 1  (15:15)
Y Okay. Store chest Gd local minima, global minima serum vino initial Cara's tensor flows de optimizer sigh Adam Maya hyper parameter. Then, we have the loss binary cross entropy, categorical, cross entropy, sparse, categorical cross entropy. 

Speaker 1  (15:50)
Run classical level model first. If they don't work them, move to deep learning hyper parameter, optimisation manual Adam. RNS props randomised search CV grid sur C Hyperparameter tuning kiras, classifier, great search accept parameter parametch, size epoch, intersection, dropout, dropout, regularisation, CNN vendor CNN 2DCN 3D convolution ReLU polling. 

Speaker 1  (16:24)
Actual function, so we know 10H S10 X ReLU Likhi ReLU, Max out elu. Okay, is step function, not best for multiplication, linear functions. We know 10H −1 komavan Y is equal to Z divided by OnePlus equal minus ZX + 1. 

Speaker 1  (16:55)
10X2. To Bixby X −1. Redu. 

Speaker 1  (17:04)
Image let model V GC 16 RSS net 18 RSS net 50 LST moto encoder GE N transformer revision time series face detection object detection, financial forecasting translation. Logistic regression. Transform linear to logistic regression using sigmoid. 

Speaker 1  (17:27)
Okay. Then, we have minimise confusion matches apart. Why is the material data set only 1% positive, so it model decide to predict everything negative, it will have 95 %es. 
