
Speaker 1  (00:02)
So here I'm starting my presentation on the stellar. WhatsApp, the Galaxy star and the ocean, so we'll be doing the statical analysis of the stellar data set. So, in this notebook, I want to take a step back from the classification model and ask a different question. 

Speaker 1  (00:24)
What actually separates Galaxy star and also object? So using the PCA graph analysis and the classical statical method explore the hidden structure of the several data scientate, how much class information is preserved after dimension dimensionality reduction. So the key observation that I have seen is that I'll go one by one okay, so here we'll be Showing the different matrices, one is the confusion matrices, matrix, confusion matrix classification report accuracy scores and balanced accuracy score. 

Speaker 1  (01:17)
So what problem that we are trying to solve is that we need to identify Whether it's in Galaxy, ok or a star or Q So Great, so Here. We started with t Data load, ok with train and the test. So train has having 567 K7577K records with 12 dimension and test as 11 dimension with 247 ke. 

Speaker 1  (01:55)
This is just half of it, half of the train data number of columns that we have. That we will be removing. Is the ID okay? 

Speaker 1  (02:10)
And the main column that we are keeping it as URG IZ and the red shift. So will be performing some edies on it. So we have to do that, we are doing. 

Speaker 1  (02:26)
We are populating the Instagram, okay? To see the distribution, and here I can see that The for the alpha, the range is from 122 to 6160 to 60 is the range of the alpha Delta distributed majority. 10 260, but I can see the huge range in the 0 as well. 

Speaker 1  (02:57)
Okay and GIS also left squeeed squad. And your You is a sari, I is Distributed. Normally, okay, maybe some Left discount. 

Speaker 1  (03:24)
Similarly, R is also left is huge, and red shift is majorly Write institute, ok. Similarly, we can see the value for the US. Also, the range is between 15 to 30 and for the Z. 

Speaker 1  (03:43)
The range is between 14 to 23. So when we are seeing you, humans ultra Violet band It measured the object brightness. Okay, G measure the brightness in the Blue-green visible range. 

Speaker 1  (04:13)
Okay? Um. Now we have the hour, which is red. 

Speaker 1  (04:17)
Bad. I measure the brightness at the transition between visible red and the near-infrared wavelength. Please measure this sandir, all the brightness measurement done by this parameters. 

Speaker 1  (04:35)
Rozz were red part. Eyes for infraband. So they have, the range is also. 

Speaker 1  (04:48)
You has a range of 355 km Then, it increases with GU GRI and then G that's the Sorting order based on the wavelength, and then we have the red shift, which is Z. Quantify the discussion towards longer values. Now we have the, if I can show you the heat map here we can see the U is more correlated with t Ji, okay, and G and R. 

Speaker 1  (05:29)
So US small caller with GNR GIS more correlated with t You and this is I and G also GIS also political with I. And G and R is correlated with t ING only you is not correlated with INC. Uh, I think that's That's it. 

Speaker 1  (06:13)
Red shift is more correlated with t Gets more correlated with zee. 

Speaker 1  (06:51)
Okay, so now we're substructing UG. RR. I. 

Speaker 1  (06:56)
C. Okay, to see the pair plots. Show the colours right Okay, so for the US. 

Speaker 1  (07:15)
I don't know how to See about this spear plot. But looking at the heat map riu GRI ZI don't know why we're doing the UG and GR Also, decoration with that one is that is GRS more Correlated with t R. I Similarly, Rs. 

Speaker 1  (07:53)
GR. So we have the PC features UGRRs IZ and red shift. Okay, we have to perform the standard scalar on those features. 

Speaker 1  (08:10)
And if we perform the PC on that one, we will get some mattresses, see that almost 60% of the variation has been Not understanding this one, and then the PCA. The number of components we wanted to Okay, now if we're doing it This is also not understanding with 2 parameters, only regulating this Galaxy or so, and star Even after projecting the data into 2 domains Allowing to different classes from quite celebrated power Separate spotless, classification, Nova, Scotia and 2024 56 earlier, we said on, we need only 2 features. 

Speaker 1  (08:57)
I don't know. What this represent? And PC one Vivia, protects the mean standard I don't know, also if we look at the subclots. 

Speaker 1  (09:12)
This warrants also not able to understand I'm going to take a closer look. But why we're doing it? I don't know, uh, fixes sepludes. 

Speaker 1  (09:26)
Okay, box port boxboto, I'm not understandable. Then, we have the heat maps, heat maps earlier. Also, we have calories known also why we're doing it. 

Speaker 1  (09:41)
Levi's, with the different PC F features of the heat map, how they are cooler with the PC S let's what we'll try to understand that and Udaija Graff also That also spot confusing. Ok. It's the same thing as a surgery issue seemed to use aggressive issue, also Tyler on now, supportive television. 

Speaker 1  (10:14)
Thank you for watching. The Kenny classification is also classification, which one belongs to vote, to understand the features. And this is also not clear to me. 

Speaker 1  (10:28)
In the heat map also here, what we're trying to say is confusion matrix. Okay, will you turn on the actual Show Galaxy S predicted 72 times QSD is predicted. 964 times Galaxy. 

Speaker 1  (10:53)
Okay and 593 times The Star This is so confusing. Give me some steps to understand all this 
