
Speaker 1  (00:01)
However, on 14th years of experience working with Details engineering, team and with the GenAI ok? So have a good exposure to the spark. Side data, which side is snowflake? 

Speaker 1  (00:16)
And apart from that On the GenAI side, I have built the rap pipelines, mostly with the lantinny and dandruff. So, kar Indian, working with the Maha emphasis from last 3 years before that, I am working with the August standard from the August angle I have majorly worked on the eds there and few models on the NLP. And Last year's I'm working with emphasis, which is the client is basically having the education domain. 

Speaker 1  (00:54)
But overall, my experiences in the banking domain usually The operation that I mean, having is the Use Bixby students and the teachers and for their diagnostic tests, so we have multiple data for data forms that are getting injected, they start from the Kafka, and then to the data bricks side. And then we have the chunking and betting slayers, all those things, and then we've treated a Chatbot also in the chatbots we have Exposing several metric to check the accuracy and all the other forms of parameters that we have for evaluating the chat box like a recession recall, precision and everything. 

Speaker 1  (01:39)
Apart from that. I've done few analytics on the edsides. For the banking domain for maugust, Taliban. 

Speaker 1  (01:49)
Apart from that currently, I'm working as the individual contributor but I worked as a lead before. So we have 50 days to print and then my roles and responsibility. Is that I get the requirement from the stakeholders? 

Speaker 1  (02:04)
Okay, and then I read it and then create the documentation around it. Okay, and then the implementation low level design everything. And then I walked on the user storage assigned to me and then with a double at the end. 

Speaker 1  (02:18)
So that's how I work. 

Speaker 2  (02:22)
Ok, so you mentioned like your background is from data. So you have worked on Chennai projects already chatbots and stuff, and do you have experience working in coreml technologies as well? 

Speaker 1  (02:39)
Yeah, coramal, I have 

Speaker 2  (02:42)
Ok, can you like walk me through any co ML solution that you have worked on? 

Speaker 1  (02:51)
Ok, so I did the as I told you in the bogus handle if we have the risk risk assessment, so they have the market wire in place. So we that's the front of its data and the back of his data, and between, we have to figure out the actualness of the documents that we have. So there we have used multiple models like random forest measuring, but with some boosting algorithms, we have tuned at hyperparameters also, and then we have come up with lot of matrices also exposed. 

Speaker 1  (03:35)
So That I did in 4 years back, so I need to recall it more. 

Speaker 2  (03:41)
Ok? And Like the recent chatbots you mentioned working on, so just like in a general way. How many different llms or LLM providers? 

Speaker 2  (03:54)
Have you had a chance to work with, like or T oc project or self-learning? 

Speaker 1  (03:59)
Yeah, I mean, we have tried a lot of llms like for the airports, we are trying to Integrate it with Nova pro, but that has few challenges. Then, we switch to the we have tuned the database LLM. Also, but these are not sufficient. 

Speaker 1  (04:20)
Later, we have astrobic cloud Claude. Also, then at the end, we switch to the open air. Even Because of the costing and everything 

Speaker 2  (04:35)
Ok? And What kind of RAG a workflow or pipeline have you worked on? 

Speaker 1  (04:42)
Uh, what kind of okay? Switch kind of internal documentation. Okay so that they have exposed so within the augmentation, we can ask the questions later to it. 

Speaker 1  (04:56)
Okay, or the jargons that we are having. Those were the chatbots that we have built crowded. 

Speaker 2  (05:05)
And you mentioned some NLP work also. So are you familiar with anyr or things like that? 

Speaker 1  (05:14)
Sorry, any R. Yes, I have worked on that anywhere. I mean, these are the name entity. 

Speaker 1  (05:24)
Models, right? 

Speaker 2  (05:26)
Bright red. Okay, so let me ask you a simple question. Let's say that I'm building a search retrieval related pipeline. 

Speaker 2  (05:38)
Okay, I have a huge corpus of you can say data that is coming from different sources, but at the end it's all text data. Okay. So it is single modality, no no image is nobody is just text, and I have a similarity search engine and in parallel. 

Speaker 2  (05:58)
I also have a keyword search engine. Okay. So for my similarity engine, when a person asks a natural query, I can just run the cement of processing. 

Speaker 2  (06:16)
What I need to do on the query to run it through the keyword search as well. 

Speaker 1  (06:23)
Majorly, we use BM25 okay? Which is the enhanced form of the tf IDF. Get the retrieval of the documents basically tune at also with the top 5. 

Speaker 1  (06:36)
I'm basically the number of 51 that you want. 

Speaker 2  (06:40)
Then, no okay, let me reinforce my question. Let's say that I have a HR resume finding product. Okay, so let's say what it does is we allow recruiters to search for candidates that they can hire, right? 

Speaker 2  (06:55)
So we will have a huge corpus of resumes in the database, and if let's say you Prashar wants to hire a python developer in a mid senior position. So you log into the portal and you can type there, like, I need a python developer with the 5 years of experience. And then our semantic search engine will kick off and start doing this semantic search on the data. 

Speaker 2  (07:21)
But when you say I want to find a python engineer with 5 years of experience. How do you pass that query to the keyword search engine? 

Speaker 1  (07:33)
Okay, we will create the embeddings. Ok, the weddings we have the vector store in the vector store. We can find it okay if they're using a database. 

Speaker 1  (07:43)
Otherwise, we can have several other embedding databases or vector databases that we can try. 

Speaker 2  (07:52)
Ok, so have you have you worked on tfid F vectoriser? 

Speaker 1  (07:58)
Yeah, I have used that. 

Speaker 2  (08:01)
Ok, and when you create Ata tf, Ida vectorizer, what kind of dictionary size does it come up with? 

Speaker 1  (08:14)
Digital size? 

Speaker 2  (08:17)
Yes, like if you, if you look at generic embedding models, they all have dimensions and sizes, right? So when you work with a tf idf, what kind of dictionary size does it have? 

Speaker 1  (08:32)
I know about the dimensions of the embedding. I recommend more than that, no or something different. 

Speaker 2  (08:39)
Yeah, so like dimension is similar to the sizeer vector size right? So when you that is, for embedding models like, you know, Amazon Titan and stuff, but when you have to a tf idf vectorizer, there what is the size of the like the actual embedding or the dictionary that it creates? 

Speaker 1  (09:00)
That depends on the features. I don't have any columns. I'm not sure of 

Speaker 2  (09:07)
Ok, and let's say that since you've worked with dimensions, how would you explain what is what is an embedding? 

Speaker 1  (09:16)
I'm betting some nothing but the form of vectors, which is converted from the words. Right into the dimensions that we have the model that we have chosen. So by default, it's for a small model. 

Speaker 1  (09:32)
It will be 1500. But we can increase it to more like $4000. 

Speaker 2  (09:38)
Ok, and if I talk about the kind of embeddings, do you know like how many types of embeddings do we have? 

Speaker 1  (09:47)
Yeah, we have semantics. Okay, wedding, we have contextual embeddings. Yeah, that these are We have actually 5 embedding, just recalling 2 on the Open K. 

Speaker 2  (10:11)
Okay, and are you familiar with what is a spar? Some wedding. 

Speaker 1  (10:18)
Yeah, I know. Okay, so 

Speaker 2  (10:22)
Can you like differentiate, dense Vs pass? 

Speaker 1  (10:26)
Yeah, the dense we usually use the BM25 along with the which is basically the whatever we are retrieving it from the document that we are keeping it along with a similarity search. So both we are combining it and then sending it to the prompt. So this is the dense Wake up in the one part only then it's a response. 

Speaker 2  (10:53)
Ok, and have you worked with any sparse embedding model? 

Speaker 1  (10:58)
Sparse, some wedding model. Maybe I have tried it, but not sure. 

Speaker 2  (11:06)
Ok no problem. So when you like when you talk about classic NLP, you know, most of the metrics, there that were used in earlier days were related to distance, only right? Like, what if you calculate even like in fuzzy search? 

Speaker 2  (11:24)
You will see there is 11 style distance, Manhattan distance and all that, but when it comes to vector M beddings and similarity, you will see that it is calculated using the cosine similarity, right? So what is the reason that we have now come to use? You know, coccience, solarity, instead of word distance. 

Speaker 1  (11:46)
Wordisons are mostly distance based gradients. Cosine, similarity. Sorry, what was your question asked? 

Speaker 2  (11:59)
Like, why do we use Coco science similarity? 

Speaker 1  (12:02)
Because it's walk on the an cosine angel ok Terra, less, that angle size would be. I mean, the angle would be a more similarity. The words have, and also, they are into multiple. 

Speaker 1  (12:14)
We can have the multiple dimensions, right? That also, we can store it. What else? 

Speaker 1  (12:25)
Heavy percentage, a deep words are more apart than the angle would be 90 relief. It is 45 or less than it will be similar. We can tune that also we can at the threshold, basically, and for the distance. 

Speaker 1  (12:44)
If we talk about we have for production we have the regression models on everything I mean, do you think that I can think of I mean 

Speaker 2  (12:57)
Ok, alright. Are you familiar with dot or tayu? 

Speaker 1  (13:03)
Sorry, call me. 

Speaker 2  (13:05)
Are you familiar with the draw dot Tay? 

Speaker 1  (13:08)
Drawotype. 

Speaker 2  (13:12)
Wrong.io 

Speaker 1  (13:13)
road.com. It's sorrow time. Oh, yes, I know. 

Speaker 1  (13:18)
Here we apply. 

Speaker 2  (13:21)
Can you can you just share your screen? And open blank drawer type page. 

Speaker 1  (13:33)
I'm sharing my Son. 

Speaker 1  (13:49)
We are able to see my thing. 

Speaker 2  (13:52)
Yeah, ok, so let's say that we have A We have to create a solution. To a problem here, okay. And it is a mix of you can say, search and Chatbot. 

Speaker 2  (14:10)
So what we are doing is there is a certain marketplace that is Running a website where users can search for products. Okay, now this marketplace, they want to modernise their website, so they are like everyone's creating chatbots and all that. So let's do that. 

Speaker 2  (14:34)
Now you are going to propose a solution to them and the problem that they have is they don't maintain a proper db of their products. But instead they have a data, like where all the product data is already present. Okay, so like snowflake or something. 

Speaker 2  (14:55)
And from there we will be like, you know, pulling the data, you can say and creating a chat potential. 

Speaker 2  (15:20)
And fetch the appropriate, let's say Up 5 candidates, top 5 products and present them to the user. Okay, so now you as an architect, have to walk me through the solution with the individual components that you'll think that you will need and how we translate this requirement into a working solution. That would be ultimately like obviously go to a production level environment. 

Speaker 2  (15:55)
So Let me give you like a sample Jason first. Let me check. Ok. 

Speaker 2  (16:25)
So this What we will do Let me give you a paste instead. 

Speaker 2  (16:50)
Ok, you can open this This link as well. 

Speaker 2  (17:05)
So this is like a Jason, which actually is the product that ultimately you have to fund. This is the format of data that comes from your data label okay, so there are 5 products here. This is just for us sample to make you understand the kind of data we are delivering. 

Speaker 2  (17:25)
So this is something that we have in the database. There are 2 kinds of purposes that the product will have quantitative and qualitative. They are a mix of different kind of data types. 

Speaker 2  (17:36)
You can see So this is ultimately what the users will be searching for using the Chatbot. Ok, so if there's like this certification, you see in the Jason. So user can also mention that that this product I am looking for should have this certification. 

Speaker 2  (17:53)
So there your product that you provide them the list. It should meet that criteria as well. Ok. 

Speaker 2  (18:04)
Thank you for watching. So the first step would be to like ingest this data, right? So we can start from there and go till the end of wherever you like, hook up the LLM models and create the UI 

Speaker 1  (18:20)
Ok, so this data, we're retrieving it from the snowflake, or let's suggest 

Speaker 2  (18:28)
It can be any data source, no playing Elastic search. They all support this and blow. 

Speaker 1  (18:35)
And then we have to create the Chatbots, okay, related to this document, correct. So we need to Ok. 

Speaker 2  (18:50)
And this is, let's assume so this out of this sample, like the sample being 5. But the ideal production data would be close to 1 million products. 

Speaker 1  (19:09)
So this is the data okay to conduct my phone for me. And then okay, assuming we are creating a Chatbot in the database. So we will need, and also this is the Do we need to consider the data updates every day or My incremental data set everything where to consider that or we have 

Speaker 2  (19:40)
Vehicles consider it being a monthly thing. So updating of or adding or new data would be a monthly thing. So if we have like at the end of month comes up and we have 3000 ink products so we add those 3000 products. 

Speaker 1  (19:58)
Ok, so there are two things. One is the data already there. Okay. 

Speaker 1  (20:04)
And because it's storing directly into the snowflake. We need to make sure that whenever the data is got injected to the snowflake, we have to Whatever the target source that we are Storing our data into that also needs to be updated correct. Or do we need to have only the snowflake as a source of truth, or maybe the LK or maybe the weekends were software as a source of truth, and then we have to create a Chatbot. 

Speaker 2  (20:38)
No, so our data like will be the source of truth. So whatever is there in the table that is ultimately what we can show. 

Speaker 1  (20:47)
My complexity. Open. However, you can fine. 

Speaker 2  (20:55)
And let's assume that we would also want the client to prefer. Maybe like AWS based solution or something like that. 

Speaker 1  (21:05)
Would you replace this condition? I have worked on the database side. Okay, so can I use it or specifically? 

Speaker 1  (21:20)
We want only on the L. Wm. 

Speaker 2  (21:27)
So if I am not sure like, let's say that if you have an actual solution working, how would you go for the deployment and all those things? 

Speaker 1  (21:37)
Yeah, I mean the database itself. We can have the communicator there. You can have the 

Speaker 2  (21:43)
No, but I am not sure like the customer would not definitely be want to be tired into a data breaks thing, right? That's not something they want. So ultimately, it can be assured, it can be AWS, or it can be gcp, so our solution should be tied into a cloud architecture. 

Speaker 2  (22:04)
Managed cloud cloud. And that's what I mean. 

Speaker 1  (22:08)
Ok. So if we want to create the chatbots from this one, we have to Ok, just thinking of the first I'll think of the Ok, let's start from the Chatbot site. Ok, the user is quering. 

Speaker 1  (22:31)
The data. I'm taking the bottom down approach. What is the user? 

Speaker 1  (22:50)
How can we write it inside the 

Speaker 2  (22:53)
Adapt, just double-click or you can add manual text as well. 

Speaker 1  (23:23)
The modern leadership of my file. 

Speaker 1  (23:38)
Discriminates, history. 

Speaker 1  (23:54)
Can you set up? 

Speaker 1  (24:42)
I can't. This is two things more than a month. That's the one side of the story. 

Speaker 1  (24:55)
On the other side Remove the title and see it coming up. 

Speaker 1  (25:29)
Call Abhiraj. Send notificants kind of administration. Similarly, such companies returning This is the wind palace today. 

Speaker 1  (25:49)
Now we have to Get a data from here. So you can have The data changes the journey's format. It's AJN is coming in this format. 

Speaker 1  (26:07)
So we have the data in the Jason from which is coming So either we can To the pipeline. Forget about getting the generation. We can see pipeline here. 

Speaker 1  (26:39)
Right from here on a journey. Make the photo pipeline. Send blo. 

Speaker 1  (26:54)
Having been there, autoimmune distribution snapshots. 

Speaker 1  (27:13)
It is reading the directly go to the north park AI only. Sparky. We can store it into the In the LODV. 

Speaker 1  (27:37)
The fact that we can do, there are multiple ways in case parks and other spark. We can Last pour it into the air. Divisibility is nothing but nothing El. 

Speaker 1  (27:52)
Arabian students. As many Donetsk and Show, this is 1.9 The hook. I'm going to send a return to the. 

Speaker 1  (28:12)
Let's get deep. So here we've got to Use the JioSaavn. The situation, let's say it's coming from here. 

Speaker 1  (28:28)
And then we are storing the data to the Jason was sent Indian views. On the other hand storytelling routine is here. We have to do the transformation. 

Speaker 1  (28:50)
Hero is going together. Transformation. And once the transmission is done When we will reject from the TV turned for debrank these seven things Now the data is in this form So we have to transform the data. 

Speaker 1  (29:16)
Identify so the database will going to have Can the database will be going to have ID Name category end. Turn on qualified. Didn't treated property. 

Speaker 1  (29:38)
Capacity would be 100 My quality with me. 1602 different thing. Can show up if I talk about the qualitative form. 

Speaker 1  (29:56)
Pictures chemistry. Considering application. These are the basic ways. 

Speaker 1  (30:06)
The features The essential mathematician. Turn, this is a quantitative Some constant designs have product information model Features for me. 11, so what I can think of right now is, uh that we're getting the Data from the car formed with a snowflake into the Gs N format, and then we are doing the transformation on the spark side and storing them into the dv. 

Speaker 2  (30:52)
So what is what does it mean by doing a transformation? 

Speaker 1  (30:56)
Transformation means we're getting the data into the Jason format, right? So Jason, we need to transform it, right, making internet data frame and everything. And then it's Creativity columns correspondingly for each of the products and then extracting all the information into the data frame, and then we are storing that data frame into the TV. 

Speaker 1  (31:25)
Ok. So once this is done, then, we will start with the chunking layer and bedding layer vector dv layer for all the huking products. 

Speaker 2  (31:37)
So how do you chunk a Jason data? 

Speaker 1  (31:43)
How do I chunk the gym? Retrieving the data from the db, what if we want to watch It? On the Jason side, then we can split 

Speaker 2  (32:01)
You know what like what will? What will you chunk here? I if I look at the product data that we have? 

Speaker 2  (32:09)
So how will you chunk it? And what will you chunk there? 

Speaker 1  (32:13)
Oh, okay. I'll select the category category in the sense this is the category I'll select few columns. Okay, let's say the because I want to create the embedding. 

Speaker 1  (32:32)
Weddings of let's say the user is searching which is the best. Battery lips. Let's say battery battery which is having the storage capacity of something, right? 

Speaker 1  (32:46)
Add any parameter? So considering the all the features, along with the category, I need to I need to retrieve all the columns which is having all the category of the all the features of the category along with the category name. So these are the depending on the User query user can query on the category site feature site. 

Speaker 1  (33:17)
Okay, yeah, so these are the okay. Obviously I'll consider the category and the qualitative property and the quantitative property. Because I will be creating the columns. 

Speaker 1  (33:29)
I mean, extracting all the details into the data frame and creating the columns and then storing them on a TV. Well, consider those columns which are having the Max. The user can ask the query the user can query. 

Speaker 1  (33:42)
So once I'm beding layer is done, then I will use the BM23. 

Speaker 2  (33:47)
What does water role does chunking play Here? 

Speaker 1  (33:52)
Okay, so the chunking is basically Splitting the data, I've been giving the context of the data, basically and then with that chunking, we can Basically get the key words of every tokens and then token, we will add it to them, basically, the world we are getting. 

Speaker 2  (34:17)
So what will what will the embedding layer consists of here? 

Speaker 1  (34:21)
I'm waiting layer. We will consist of the The category. Ok. 

Speaker 2  (34:32)
Ok, no, so what kind of embedding would you think you'll be making? 

Speaker 1  (34:40)
Sorry, what kind of embedding? Ok, it will be contextual lambedding. 

Speaker 2  (34:50)
Ok, so what kind of bedding model do you think you will use? 

Speaker 1  (34:57)
Currently, where using the bge A model which is the contacts jealousy. Caffeine is running forward. 

Speaker 2  (35:14)
Okay, so voted be a Jen embedding or a sparse embedding. 

Speaker 1  (35:20)
It will be A Is sparks in bedroom veggie cause? 

Speaker 2  (35:27)
Ok, so sparse embating, you are saying it will be a sparse embedding. So how can you make a sparse medding a textual? 

Speaker 1  (35:38)
Spark embedding, we cannot make this array for the contextual. We need the 10 hours, somebody, no, no, what I'm thinking is at the end. In the vector dv. 

Speaker 1  (35:49)
We have to store the categories right. We can store the categories only and specific to categories. One second. 

Speaker 1  (36:00)
As special 2, Peter categories, unhealthy Alexa for the EC for the first That can be heard Hindu. In the vector dwells, I'm just thinking in the vector dv. We don't need to store much information. 

Speaker 1  (36:17)
The category would be sufficient. Because at the later end, we will be searching the exact feature of that particular category from the database. Maybe from the feature store. 

Speaker 1  (36:31)
So that's what I was thinking to do having the spark embedding there with basic information storing about vector dv, and then 

Speaker 2  (36:43)
So how will you map the user query to the search like user says, I am looking for a battery with minimum 500 cycles. 

Speaker 1  (36:56)
Ok, so first I'll figure out the category. Okays, talking about the talking about the battery and from the database side, because we have all the data is there. For the battery, I'll fetch that data can add some logic like the size should be greater than 500 or something. 

Speaker 1  (37:15)
All the logic has right rooted there. And then on the features store ok? And then I'll do the ranking and everything and then send it to the other 

Speaker 2  (37:28)
Ok, and you realise that like not all of the products might have categories in built. So what do we do? Then 

Speaker 1  (37:41)
Ok, I will not be able to add the category as a list explicitly, and then I'll do them waiting. And then story to interpreted you so that whatever the data we have in the TV, it will automatically 

Speaker 2  (37:57)
So explicitly, as in you will ask the user to select it. 

Speaker 1  (38:02)
Yeah, yeah, that could be the option or or we can specifically the list of categories in a list itself explicitly in the and then we'll treat them. Because the categories will be fused. 

Speaker 2  (38:21)
So if they are products that have missing categories, so how do you handle them? Like on what basis will you assign them a category? 

Speaker 1  (38:32)
I got up poem. Ok, so in the betting embedding, there should be strong enough. 

Speaker 2  (38:43)
And there is also a chance that a product that is a generic product like headphones. They will have multiple categories. They will have electronics. 

Speaker 2  (38:53)
They will have sound all music or something like that. So there will be products that have single category that have no category that have multiple categories. So how does how does your solution handle that? 

Speaker 2  (39:07)
Because if I say we have a total Broader size of 1 million products, then N number of combinations are possible. In that 

Speaker 1  (39:18)
Okay, that. I'll focus more on the meding layer. On the impeding head, then it should be mapped to one of the categories it should be. 

Speaker 1  (39:29)
The similarity search should be more. Let's say user is asking for the headphones be different text than the embedding should be. Should know what he is talking about. 

Speaker 1  (39:43)
So that's threshold, we need to set. I didn't see anything embedding clearly. We can use the We can use the Contact number wedding here with amend. 

Speaker 1  (40:08)
The dimension would be more, ok? 

Speaker 2  (40:19)
Have you have you worked with Azure? Foundry, AWS pedrock any of the cloud providers. 

Speaker 1  (40:26)
Decide work with ADF. 

Speaker 2  (40:29)
Viraton, AD 

Speaker 1  (40:30)
Are you doing? 

Speaker 2  (40:34)
Ok, alright? And Since you've used, I think OpenAI model include models and all that can you explain what is the purpose of the temperature parameters? 

Speaker 1  (40:50)
India is a miraculous idea for the creativity. We said, the temperature. So low temperature means less creativity for no creativity. 

Speaker 1  (40:58)
Higher. 

Speaker 2  (41:01)
Yeah, no bet I know. But like, what does that value actually do inside the model? 

Speaker 1  (41:08)
I've 

Speaker 2  (41:09)
Higher temperature means more creativity, right? So how does the value bring out a more creative result? 

Speaker 1  (41:18)
It will automatically generate the output philosophical setting of temperature as 0. It will look inside the context of what we have sent it to the documents. 

Speaker 2  (41:30)
Give you a scenario where you can explain so let's say I have 2 LLM models. I mean the same LLM model one is, with 0 temperature 1I have 1 temperature 1.01.0 versus 0.0 I give the LLM models the same prompt which is write a poem on seasons of the weather or something like that right a poem on rainy season, so I have a model 0 temperature? I have a model one temperature. 

Speaker 2  (41:59)
What do you think happens then? 

Speaker 1  (42:06)
Ok, we said the channel. What we usually do is we set the temperature blue for the Whatever the document that we passing, it will get the context from here they are on it. 

Speaker 2  (42:21)
Ok, and are you? Are you familiar with the how our decoder only transformer works? 

Speaker 1  (42:27)
Yeah I'd work on the shelf attention. 

Speaker 2  (42:32)
Like the temperature? Where does the temperature fit in the transformer layer? Which value is it multiplying or the temperature? 

Speaker 1  (42:45)
Soft maximum option, which soft may function at the end. We have 

Speaker 2  (42:51)
And are you familiar with the top P value? What is top P value? Do 

Speaker 1  (42:56)
Top 10 topics. Pay the probability schoola. 

Speaker 2  (43:00)
So what does that do? It is also used for creativity control. 

Speaker 1  (43:06)
Sorry I didn't try that. I mean 

Speaker 2  (43:11)
Ok. And okay. So in a like just a general question, you can stop the scenes here, like in your current role. 

Speaker 2  (43:20)
If I have to bifurcate your responsibilities or the nature of the activities that you do? So, how much is it towards? You can say, leading or doing things that are not coding Vs how much of it is actual hands-on coding like how would you split it? 

Speaker 2  (43:41)
Fifty-fifty 6040, like 

Speaker 1  (43:43)
But it's 80% more development. And 24 to 8% is to the design and publicity. 

Speaker 2  (43:51)
Ok, so when you say code development, which language are you talking about? 

Speaker 1  (43:57)
Yeah, majorly python. 

Speaker 2  (44:03)
Ok, so how much overall experience would you say you have in python? 

Speaker 1  (44:10)
I'll share around. 10 plus II 

Speaker 2  (44:17)
10 plus ok? 

Speaker 1  (44:20)
Miza leaves with a pipe. 

Speaker 2  (44:23)
Can you can you help me understand what is a difference between a shallow copy and a deep copy? 

Speaker 1  (44:30)
Shallow copy and a deep copy. Okay, in the shallow copy, it's just the references we're creating, but in a deep way we were creating the actual object. 

Speaker 2  (44:42)
Ok, and which of these is faster in terms of cpim? 

Speaker 1  (44:47)
Faster would be the sherrowon, only One. Was it was a creating the reference of the actual existing object? Show secret time in video I mean 

Speaker 2  (45:02)
Okay, and when it comes to like any LLM models you must have gone through their like the pricing pricing scheme and pricing tas. Right? So everywhere you see they have 2 kinds of pricing. 

Speaker 2  (45:16)
One is the input token pricing. The other is the output of open pricing. And everywhere you will see, the output token pricing is going to be like at least 4 to 5 times higher than the input token rising. 

Speaker 2  (45:31)
So one do you know why? Why is that? 

Speaker 1  (45:36)
Yeah, I'm in the kind of the output that we are asking to generate. In, let's say in 1000 words or movie. Because At the end, the token matter right token cost matter. 

Speaker 1  (45:51)
So if you're asking him to create large document so the token would be high. And that's why the price would be high. Hide. 

Speaker 2  (46:02)
Ok. Ok, and you mentioned working on random forest model as well earlier, right? Yeah. 

Speaker 2  (46:20)
So in a general sense like, I have a phrase that you know you associate with the random forest model that it helps you prevent overfitting. Ok, so what is it in the random forest that helps you prevent the overfitting? 

Speaker 1  (46:41)
Okay, it's a treebold tree based model. And it's run parallelly, and then it works on the Voughed, as a bagging, okay, I'm just recalling so It will combine all the scores. Eat each trees are generating and then give the accuracy. 

Speaker 1  (47:08)
So all the weak models, or maybe less weak model. They will come up with t With the score, okay, a Reno forest score Heavy sorry. What was the question? 

Speaker 1  (47:31)
Why the it helps in overfitting? Yes. Okay, the Ok, because it is reducing the noise Ok, out flier, understand the relationship Vita with a feature falls also And That's how it helps to get the 

Speaker 2  (48:08)
Ok, prakir, I think that's all I have from my side. 

Speaker 1  (48:12)
Sure. 

Speaker 2  (48:14)
If you have any question, you can ask or we can close the ball and look forward. 

Speaker 1  (48:19)
Priya, company and the product. 

Speaker 2  (48:24)
No, so we don't have a product like this is just a generic. I think we are doing for you know, increasing the size of our team data science team. So we do have a different you can say, accelerator solutions, white label products that we have built. 

Speaker 2  (48:39)
But this hiring is not dependent on one of them. It is a general hiring, so right now we have around 14 people. Different people in the data science team in the technical side. 

Speaker 2  (48:50)
If you involve the non-technical books, then it will be creating or 19 something. So just a generic hiring. But the in terms of project we are Democracy like a service based company. 

Speaker 2  (49:01)
So we have clients ranging from America's region, Europe, region, method, east and even in the Australian side, as well. So that is quite diversified. But yeah, as such, there is no like product that we are looking for something. 

Speaker 1  (49:21)
No K. Yeah, I'm good. 

Speaker 2  (49:25)
Ok, thank you for your time. 

Speaker 1  (49:27)
Thank you. 
