
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Working with the deducting python district analysis, the component of the analysis is Science are describing the past set up Interceptual, what happened in any context? The candidate is a table, descriptive analysis comprehension data Using the summarise, it is the first 2 records of the First first few regards and 2 columns, so we have to set the call option with maximum display dot Max column commerce, so will this purely survey it set options? To find the summary of the data point persuader, list down all the columns list bracket data frame dot columns. 

Speaker 1  (00:49)
The other way to print a data frame with a landrock column is to transport the data frame and display the column as read rows and rows as column. Fruits and domestic colonoscopy. There is another method dot input due dot input, so it shows a value of 130 against every column, which indicated the columns. 

Speaker 1  (01:16)
As any missing value pondas, automatically influence the rate type of the column by indusing the value of each column is a type currently infored or contained. Taxes and the column is too far. As an object, continuous, very well, deeply involved as 2064 60 various categories variable and encode as objects as shown as the object of information in this judicial pandas formed 7007 TV coming to your intelliger type. 

Speaker 1  (01:46)
And revenue for colonos, objective The refund consumers to look around 26 to 5 kiboff. Plan, there is another thing where we have to find the DF dot I location is the number capacity. Kitne Roos, kitne rose hamare 4 to 9 porri. 

Speaker 1  (02:08)
There's a column between 4 column, and then kitne hamein column share one Calling for. Valley controversy occurrence of E Juni values in a column. For example, you would like to know how many players from different countries have played in the IPL. 

Speaker 1  (02:29)
Then, the method value counts can be used. It is Okay, fode dot control dot value comes. So her country corresponding dikhalaya kitni, kitni values, hai, Indian, corresponding 53, and if you want to find the percentage service value is equal to 2 and 200 km for each playing role ages of the player at the time of option are preferred to 3 categories. 

Speaker 1  (03:08)
The player is less than 250 category 2 minutes. That the age is between 25 to 35. 2 categories, we can cross a through 8 hours in purpose. 

Speaker 1  (03:34)
Sort value, Canada DF dot short value markers, Seoul prices kitne 0 to false 0. If you want to create a new call by applying the basic administrative operation on the instant colour for example, let's say we would like to get a new feature. Which is the difference between the soldiers and the base price? 

Speaker 1  (04:18)
So D FB C is a premium executive DF sold price minus DF base price. 

Speaker 1  (04:46)
To create a data frame, we can call reset indexion below the return data structure so TF dot group by 8 correct season. 

Speaker 1  (05:06)
There is a merge method. Aggregated DF comy March Chennai, so sort column sought price by age roll. That Mysore price is yesterday. 

Speaker 1  (05:25)
Group by age Seoul price taught me in the. And then we have a data frame from the reset attendance, and then we have sold priced by age rule where group I was age and playing role and a sold price of mean that reduces index. Okay? 

Speaker 1  (05:43)
So these 2 are getting more space on the age How it's how is it able to outrage? John? So because the sold price is same in both the attitude, it will automatically remember them to_x and_. 

Speaker 1  (05:59)
Y surprise X come from the left table, which is sold priced by age row and Seoul price by Y come from the right table. It's so plus Seoul price_comparison. It's a new data set coming out from the March The tree name where the column is equal to and the cardigress. 

Speaker 1  (06:21)
We will provide the dictionary with the column name and the corresponding correct column name. And then in place is equal to true. This is going to rename the call if you want a new column change this, making our purse sold price age roll minus Seoul price AIDS judged by Seoul price ago method and in the apply, we'll call the lambda method lambda function so lambda, and then we'll get a let's say X that's the column. 

Speaker 1  (07:01)
The things that you want to perform here so X dot Column name Seoul price age role, minus rack dot Colony, which is Seoul priced divided by rack dot solid price husma 1X is equal to one So let's say what the filter out the column named 6 skater than 80. So we've used the data frame data frame data frame, and then inside the bracket to score bracket, we'll use a data frame 680. It's going to record all the Ram records, which is greater than 80, and then we have to pass the columns that you want to show in double brackets. 

Speaker 1  (07:39)
The square double square brackets and the column clear name comment 6. So if the data does it from the column, so we can use the data term dot columns, and we can specify all the columns. That will go into add all the columns. 

Speaker 1  (07:53)
There Now we have the data frame If you want to convert Something with a period to lumeric can be used to convert any column with non numeric data time to columns in numeric data time. Who stand tomorrow? Everything can be done I think can be done so there will be specify the column. 

Speaker 1  (08:19)
In the data frame bracket Mein column, errors errors. Can the team type of course Rays and ignore raise Mein Hota hai? Ki? 

Speaker 1  (08:29)
If raised an invalid parsing will raise an exception, it will raise an exception course is it will uh set the Nan in case of the invalid parging and ignore then the error will be ignored. It will run the input. Set to drop all as well as we have D. 

Speaker 1  (08:52)
F. Dot drop any and subset is equal to column name of horsepower. General DVF lane will replace the value with whatever the values we have provided. 

Speaker 1  (09:05)
Bar chart is a frequency chart for qualitative variable or categorical variable. Apart can be used to access the most occurring and least occurring categories within data set to draw bar chart. Call the Assen dot bar plot. 

Speaker 1  (09:20)
I just seen library. The data frame should be passing the parameter data to display the average sold price Buy EH category. Pass solid Seoul prices wide permitted and ASD X parameter, so to display the average solid price Okay, buy each categories. 

Speaker 1  (09:44)
So S and dot bar, not XMRGY majestone. Price data is equal to and data frame will be sold price by H. So if we're going to create a power chart, now it will be average, sold price is higher for the category. 

Speaker 1  (09:58)
We can also create a bar chart which I group by the third gate. For example, prices soon for category that is playing road. The parameter Hugh take the third variable as parameter. 

Speaker 1  (10:14)
In this case, we can pass playing role as a huge parameter, so Sn dot bar plot XY plus XY is sold price. Q is the playing role. You will see a key playing role data market sold price and score comparison. 

Speaker 1  (10:32)
Here, Instagram is a plot that shows a frequency distribution of a set of continuous variable so invested inside into the underline distribution. For example, normal distribution of the variable outliers, stiffness, etc. To draw a stone invoke the hist method of the metro library. 

Speaker 1  (10:48)
The following is an example of how to draw a store for the solid price and understand its distribution plot dot histe IPL option DFS old price. Restaurant show that Seoul price is rightly skewed. Most players are option at the low price range of 25 to 50G to 500 Okay, where rescue players paid very highly motion, $1 million. 

Speaker 1  (11:14)
By default, 10 bins in the restaurants, we have to pass. The bins is equal to 10. 

Speaker 2  (11:20)
So distribution plot ke utha marapas, distribution density plot depicts the distribution of data. Over a continuous interval COVID density plot is like smooth historian and visualised distribution of data over a controverse interval. So a density plot also give insight into what might be the distribution of the population. 

Speaker 1  (11:43)
Dancing clothes like smoothie, Instagram and Vishal distribution data over a country syndrome. So density plot also gives insight into what might be the distribution of the circulation? Withdraw the distribution plot to weaken user disclot of the sea bone library density plot for the outcome variable sold price is shown in the figure 27. 

Speaker 1  (12:03)
Sn dot disclot, so IPL DFD F and the Colony is so priced from this plot. Some slom ek History rumpy, South America, lowest in the highest values for IQR so to obtain min Max, 25% × 100% value in the box board. Let us send the registration value of the box. 

Speaker 1  (12:33)
Play a variable box, so plotted box cut DF sold price and the box cut for the sole price with medium line okay? That will tell us the boster. If you want to retrieve the value the Key, okay, uh, in the boxary, return the minimum maximum value of the distribution. 

Speaker 1  (12:57)
And then we have the whispers, so for item in box racket may stop back in my capital delay, and for item in box I can look back in it 25 and 75% range, and if we need to find the medium then for item in box medium again, so we'll get the medium value. We'll find the outlier to humblock DF. Bracket DF sold price greater than oga, maximum value. 

Speaker 1  (13:29)
Hum, and then we'll select all the columns in rubber. Is car bracket, a warm shoc? Now we'll compare the distribution. 

Speaker 1  (13:41)
The distribution for different categories can be compared by overlapping the distribution. For example, the sole price of player with and without capital captains, captaincy experience can be compared as below the social can be compared by trying to distribution for each category and overlapping them in one plot suppression dot displot Karama DF and the column name is D. F. 

Speaker 1  (14:04)
Kept stancy experience is equal to one ticket. Select Kara colour hum log NE dal Diya, yellow label as capital experience and similarly as a dot discount. Hamne, Gopal captaincy experience 0 to 01. 

Speaker 1  (14:19)
Colour and plot dot legender. The comparison plot for the soil price, whether Virat captaincy experience is shown in figure 2.10, it can be observed at player with captaincy experience seem to be higher paid. We can also calculate the playing role Vs sold price box plot. 

Speaker 1  (14:43)
So this is a medium Para, so an example of complaints, the Seoul price for each play of a different playing room is shown in figure this one send box plot XMR play role YMR soul price, and data is all over B. F. So for the observation on the plot, dispose the medium sold price for all-rounder. 

Speaker 1  (15:04)
Rupaye and batsman are higher than the bowler. And the wicketkeeper Old Daughter who are paid more than 135. 4 time 0 USD are not considered out. 

Speaker 1  (15:37)
More than this, I'm not considered, have relatively high variance. Is it outlined the Batman and the wicked keeper category? Injection, we have already found that MH1 is audio on the wicketkeeper category. 

Speaker 1  (15:51)
In setup, 2 variable plotted along 2 Axis and resulting pattern can reveal correlation present between the variable if any relationship could be linear or nonlinear. Our special property is also useful for accessing the strength of the relationship and to find. If there is any outlier in the data, the scattered product are used during regression model building to decide on the national model that is whether to include a variable in regulation model or not. 

Speaker 1  (16:15)
Since IPL T20, it is believed that number of sixters a player has hit in the passport have influenced sold price as cattle plot between sold price of the Batman and the number of sixes, the player has hit can establish this correlation. The scatter method lip can be used to draw the skater cloth, which take both the variables. We will draw the skater plot only for bat 1 playing the role figure took a want to show the skater plot between 6 correct, so to have the data frame, we will select only the rows having the playing role as badman, they can turn the DFD Fc roll results electrically X1 yx may. 

Speaker 1  (17:02)
Ambulk status cancer dot 6 dot super prices 

Speaker 1  (17:25)
between the number of 6 hit by the batsman and the solids sold price. So now we have a peer plot. If there are many variables, it is not convenient to draw a scatter plot for each pair of the variable donation relationship, so a pair plot can be used to depict the relationship in a single island which can be produced using the pair plot method. 

Speaker 1  (17:44)
This is sample we'll explore the relationship with the poor variable Sr BE V6, which we think may be influencer feature in determines the suitcase of the pattern so influential feature would be Sr BAVE6 % Seoul price. Now we created the pair plot of the DF with influential feature and size will be too How come I didn't understand this? For all the correlation, avsar seems to highly correlated with sold price compared to the S. 

Speaker 1  (18:15)
R. B. The coalition value lived in manisvalu, assigned decades whether it is a positive or negative cognition. 

Speaker 1  (18:24)
-1.0 indicator perfect negative correlation, whereas + 1.0 indicator perfect positive correlation collision only can be computed during CUR method. If you are Samsung. And we can plot that Using the heat map method, data frame dot C URL and not equal to true 
