
Speaker 1  (00:01)
Expansion distribution expansion in the silver continuous distribution. That is traditionally used for modelling time to fill a electronic component. The exponential distribution represent a process in which event occur continuously and independently at a constant average rate. 

Speaker 1  (00:34)
How much time the media function is lambda into EK power, minus lambda X The current land is just keeping the rate of occurrence of the mean of the expansion distribution given by Mumbai lambda and the exchange of one by lambda square. For example, time to failure often system follows an exponential distribution with a mean time between Failure of 1000 tower calculate the provided data system will fail before 1000 hours. It will not fail up to 2000 hours, the time by which 10% of the system will fail. 

Speaker 1  (01:11)
Results of these as follows. Since time to federalize 1000 hours, lambda is equal to 21 / 1000 calculate. The probability system will fail before 4000 hours. 

Speaker 1  (01:23)
So it will be cdf. Okay? 1000 and Given the probability system will fail before 1000 hours CDF to take the number of hours mean and expansional distribution. 

Speaker 1  (01:42)
So Cameron distribution up to value of 1004 the exponential distribution will give the probability that the system will fail before 1000 hours. Uh, his stats, exponential CDF take the number of hours mean and scale of the exponential distribution at the parameter to calculate CDF 06321 to find out what is the expected range of return for 95% interval to calculate the values of gain for 2 San deviation away. From me, I'm bosal resolution that is new + 2 sand divided, but advanced setical embassy. 

Speaker 1  (02:18)
We can use python diabetic liability contains subtrackages for analysing different distributions for example, method to analyse normal distribution are given by stats. No. The interval method of state or non gives the conference at 12 for a novel decision stats of normal interval takes 3 parameters, alpha location alpha is the interval, for example 0.9490% over it is a population perimeter distribution. 

Speaker 1  (02:50)
It is needed for the normal distribution scale. It is a scale parameter of distribution to stand deviation for normal distribution. State that November interval 0.95 location is uhxo, key and scale is galaxic gain instead of deviation. 

Speaker 1  (03:09)
Gain at 95% confidence interval. -0. 25820.0266. 

Speaker 1  (03:22)
Other important distribution is Beta distribution. Gamma distribution, viable distribution geometric distribution better distribution. Is it is the container distribution, which can take value between 0 to 1 Government institution is used to model weighting time in different contexts, we can model time Until the next end, event occurs using the gamma distribution. 

Speaker 1  (03:44)
Why will distribution is very popular distribution and reliability theory? Exponential distribution is a special case of viable distribution in exponential distribution. The rate of occurrence of an event is constant. 

Speaker 1  (03:55)
But using vibral distribution, we can model increasing rate of occurrence of an event over time. Geometric distribution is the binal distribution is about How many success then the geometric solution? How many failure until a success? 

Speaker 1  (04:12)
Thank you. Hypothesis hypothesis tests are broadly corresponded into parametric test and non parametric test. Parametric test are about population parameters of a distribution such as mean, proportion and evation assistance. 

Speaker 1  (04:29)
There is a nonetric test are not about parameter, but about other characteristics, such as independence of event or data, following certain distributions, such as normal distribution. Okay, so how do you To sample 2 sample tea test, the temperature deposit has a difference between 2 population men, crystal divide and crunch in the middle of the corner. 2 population needs to population mean healthy drinks. 

Speaker 1  (05:07)
Display disclots. Can you please Jessica tea test 2? Test separate test two separate Scientific protests dot test_IND that takes 2 independent sample. 

Speaker 1  (05:34)
Return the test statistics. Sometimes we need to analyse whether an interactions such an event Training program marketing promotion treatment for specific illness and lifestyle changes may have significantly changed the population parameter value such as mean before, and after the information objectives. In this case is to check whether the difference is in the parameter value statically significant Before & After the intervention or between the two different types of intervention, this is called a pair sample test and user comparing two different intervention applied on the same sample. 
