
Speaker 1  (00:01)
Okay, so for the iris, I d's one spectacular with spices. So first we have to find the northern values, drop pides, okay, scutter ploto the species ball blocks plot of the species correlation heat map. That we reached from rows and column, changing the colour Finding the correlation. 

Speaker 1  (00:25)
SPN import SV. C. Axis suspicious length and width, petal length and width. 

Speaker 1  (00:31)
Voice, the species accuracy's one find hyperplane WIXI plus B is equal to 0 and prediction rule is sign of W dot X plus B if FX is greater than 0, then class one else class 2 and maximum margin is 2 divided by magnitude of W. SPM solve minimum of half W whole square. Why is WXI plus B greater than one soft marginous optimisation is equal to main of half W square plus Penalty parameters submission of AI which is error tolerance colonel polynomial kxi XJ is equal to Xi dot HJ + 1 power of DRBF is equal to KXIX Je to the power minus. 

Speaker 1  (01:27)
RXI minus X za whole square support vector only some vector determined boundaries, so WXYWIXI plus B is equal to I. Now we have the fan prediction argument Max effects, when FX to FX the decision function is summation of alpha YKXIX plus B example one Vs zest. Species to number features is X equal to XOnePlus X2X1, X2 hyperplane WXOnePlus WX2 plus B is equal to 0. 

Speaker 1  (02:07)
So W is 11B is −4, so X1 plus X2 is (−4) = 0 prediction function is sinot WX plus B check. Each training point affects Setusa is 1402 fx will be based on the formula actually −24 sign negative, so sabosa, positive to other value boundary XOnePlus X2 −2020. X1 plus X2 (−4) = 1X1 + 2 − 4 = (−1) point touching. 

Speaker 1  (02:40)
These margins are the support vectors. Final prediction is organ Max, of effects. Petal length is 5.1 petal width is 1.8 decision stories. 

Speaker 1  (02:51)
Theatosa −0.5 very vergy colour is 0.8. Virginica is 2.1 okay, so vague, calculate ke liye Gradient Descent. Use Hota hai W minus learning region to gradient. 

Speaker 1  (03:17)
Suppose X1X2Y is 2 3 10Y equal to W1XOnePlus W2X2 plus B random waste + 3 select, then we calculate the Y prediction, which is comes up to be 5 error is actually 10, the vibration is 5, so we've calculated the error which is P minus. YQ minus −5 error co minimised connectically weight change aggraction. Come hair badhao, then we'll gonna increase the weight okay. 

Speaker 1  (03:50)
Now we have gradient, T is equal to (−5) × 2 into the −10. So we're 1 − 0.1 × (−10) 0 2W 2 is great, − 5 × 30 − 15 weight 2 = 1 − 0.1 × (−15), which is equal to 0.5 bias is gradient is equal to average is equal to 5. This is equal to 0 − 0.5 × (−5) = 0.5. 

Speaker 1  (04:16)
Phir vibrant Y02 into 2 + 1503 + 0.50, the viprant of 12 over year actual 10th, produce weight to minimum. Here we'll talk about the logistic regression, which is importing the logistic regression. First, we compute, the Leno commission of the factor Z is also doubled + WX1XOnePlus W2X2 and W3X3 by sigmoid function is one upon OnePlus equal −, it gradient is equal to P −, Y and here Y minus Y bar X putamara. 

Speaker 1  (05:02)
W and B is Y minus Y bar? What's Cost function will operate in descendant via quality calculated Nair will talk about the Canyon classification keenever kennyver, classifier import key and never classifier. For a test point X it first computed distance between X and Every training point select cake's closest neighbour predict majority classes among the neighbour distance formula would be under root of summation of Xi minus. 

Speaker 1  (05:42)
YI ko, holy square. FK is equal to 5. That means 5 nearest point, which is equal to 5Y1Y2Y3Y1. 

Speaker 1  (05:52)
Choosing the best KK range is equal to 127. Test is argument mexic, riski accuracy is equal to F. K. 

Speaker 1  (06:06)
So I don't know how to Help me in the math function. Now we have received Now we have the ROC receiver operating characteristic curve model. Ke performance show Karta, hai, different threshold per FIS equal to FPR fall. 

Speaker 1  (06:29)
Positive rate Y is equal to Tpr 2 positive false positive rate, so Tpr is equal to TP1TP plus F AFP R is equal to S. P. Upon FP plus TN. 

Speaker 1  (06:44)
Clearly you can get the threshold is 0.8060.40.2 so greater than is equal to 0.8, that means Hui. So let Tpr equal to 1FPR zold 0 for 1 confusion matrix RX 0.0.1 for that high combination RO saver's search threshold plot kiya, Jaye au C is also R. C. 

Speaker 1  (07:11)
Karke. Since P value is greater than 00, we can change the application so P is equal to 15 alpha metal. At type 1RC probability PT1 is equal to alpha alpha is 0.055% chance. 

Speaker 1  (07:27)
A galat reject karte,0.010 %, 5 is 5%. 101 is 1% PT is greater than T0 to 0.05. When set T is equal to 1.812 aatha hai isliye yahi value Rahe. 

Speaker 1  (07:51)
Okay, T values integration of FDT0 to 0.05, if change Agar, change one is safety value, change h* jati hai. They said, dear value, normal distribution. Fast number. 
