
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Example of the binocular distribution is let's say fashion trend online company. It is observed that one0% of the customers return Hota hai return their item purchased by them for many reasons, such as size, only 20 customer purchase item from the fto. Now we have to calculate the probability that exactly 5 customer will return the item probability that maximum of 5 customer will return the item probability that more than 5 customers will return the item. 

Speaker 1  (00:31)
Purchase by them, average number of customers who are likely to return the item and the variance and the certificates, the number of protein soology is a probability at exactly 5 customers return the item, so expected number of successful trial is 5 to 220 probability of successes, biggest 10%. Marpas, John. Return. 

Speaker 1  (01:04)
Inability. So by stats that by no dot PMF520, and the probability successful trial number of trials. And the probability Rs 0.03, that is the puddled exactly 5 %ability in the item is approximately. 

Speaker 1  (01:27)
3% to visit visionalize, how the PM fries was increasing number of successful trial majority list of fall possible number of success, 028 corresponding PM failures barplot, as shown. Tu Jaisi heart, a number of items, returned at Prem fuel in Kali. Dekheini bhi, Mr. 

Speaker 1  (01:49)
number of items written, come Hota Ja Rahe Hain. Or PMS bikam. So data frame colour success range from 0 to 21 PM F on the probability in colour, the probability under dikhenge, with a number of Item return. 

Speaker 1  (02:21)
For the second case where we have to probably at a maximum 5 customer will return the item maximum 5 will be CDF. Review the CDF. The stats at Bay noon CDF 520.1 commenced 0.9. 

Speaker 1  (02:40)
Probability that more than 5% will return the item purchased by them will be one, minus Germany precedia colonically. Average countercover average pen into the virus P variance. Several 2 and Perez's 120. 
