
Speaker 1  (00:01)
Sovelistm, BI last TMR GRU I'm not sure about it, I have to learn it, uh, transforming GenAI. Encoders, only encoder decoder decoder only encoder only is Paris. Beautiful city I love Paris. 

Speaker 1  (00:19)
It will be converted to the S1S2 Can I go inside the bird or Robert cital goes inside the bird ALBERT Robert And Class labels and good for the classification sentimental sequence tagging US and Annia limitation is no generation, no generation of text. It is used only for the translation summarization. Okay, image captioning. 

Speaker 1  (00:55)
Attention. All is needed, okay? And the decorator only is, if nothing has the encoding. 

Speaker 1  (01:08)
It has the decoding, only like GPT 12 and drama Gemini. Claude, their controlled via prompts promotes are 0 type and few shots translating this to Hindi translate with example Transformers, the base of ChatGPT. Okay, so base of the ChatGPT is transformer. 

Speaker 1  (01:33)
Deep learning is Ann tabular form CNN so images are an LS. T. NGRU by LST M sequential text data neural network uses architecture sequence sequence task task So we have Add an normalisation, feed forward then again. 

Speaker 1  (01:56)
So input for the encoder is input. Embeddings, that goes for multilateral attention. Then, to the add an normalisation N feed forward at normalisation, feed forward disaster hierarchy. 

Speaker 1  (02:11)
The output that we get is output enabled multi attention and normalisation linear softmack. Again we'll get the probability, so impact of the transformer ML P is resolved. Democratising, multimodal geniumification of the deep model Heuristic approaches the NLP is resolved ML R NLP resolve heuristic approach ML RNN LSD M and the transformer democratic AI. 

Speaker 1  (02:45)
Pretty pretty trained model multimodal capabilities, GenAI Chennai, unification of deep learning NN text NN images. Now, we've transformed to solve any type of data Set the paper is Attention is all you need. You don't need full text for the encoding and decoding encoding in Hindi. 

Speaker 1  (03:08)
Can we get in the English? 

Speaker 2  (03:15)
It's self return. 

Speaker 1  (03:17)
Q attention score that you usually get multiply with the V. So this is BERT is bad direction and quote representation of transformer. I don't know the actual math of it. 

Speaker 1  (03:33)
But complication is bird base, but large. But tiny, but minion, bird small but medium Access encoder. Encoder LS12 for bird, base for largest 24, tiny S2 −4 smallest 4 medium is 8 attentions. 

Speaker 1  (03:53)
Head is 12 And hidden units 768 embedding subanti, the base model kitna. 12 years ki, attention head is 12 and the embedding layer is seventh. Dimension is 768 for birth base or yahi maar birth, large. 

Speaker 1  (04:12)
Phir mediums. Aguilar. Ok, can codder, layer S24 attention and is 16, and Diamond Head is multiple units 128. 

Speaker 1  (04:29)
Are pretend and fine-tuning? Humlon, karte Hain. Instead of creating my model, I use a pretty model and create only the final layer. 

Speaker 1  (04:39)
Bort is trained. Okay, mass language modelling, and next sentence prediction. Mass language modelling is ML masking few random token. 

Speaker 1  (04:50)
Is she loved with chocolate? She loved masked with chocolate masked type of mask tokena first is having one token mask any position. Random token, 10%, no changes. 

Speaker 1  (05:03)
10% ML M significance is burnt, is bidirectional. RNR it has the hidden layer transformer is the contextual embedding contextual embedding Vs the hidden history so contextual hambuding, captures the conceptual meaning of the word. Raj went to the bank bank can be river, or the financial institution sequence information which word comes after another decoder architecture is architecture is same like encoder prediction. 

Speaker 1  (05:41)
Next sentence Ram went to - Ram nexptis went next bird. ChatGPT prompts encoder gives the output first embedding happens RNN LLM then the vector then the decode, then the output biodiversal encoded transformation, which is burned for transformer, helps in sentimental analysis tech classification question and answer. So Raj went to America Amazon forest. 

Speaker 1  (06:13)
I work in Amazon But will understand the context But is stack of BERT encoders, GPT stack of decoder transformer comes into picture because they understand contextual information and deal with high corporation data. But pretend mass lm Paris is a beautiful city. I love Paris, so S PF is their C. 

Speaker 1  (06:40)
L. Yes. Is there CLS Paris is a beautiful separator SPI love Paris S. 

Speaker 1  (06:48)
E! P Teji Samara, BERT Mein jayega. Is a BERT input embedding token embedding segmentic position? 

Speaker 1  (07:05)
Ah, each word is Convergent road token sequence embedding is one segment sequence Often coding. Positional coding sequence one and sequence, 2 of the encodings, the final embedding is all the summation of both embeddings. Ok, so master's, language modelling is Type type types are auto regression language model. 

Speaker 1  (07:39)
Unit direction auto encoding language model biology auto regressive LM GT open a process, a beautiful -, high probability word welcome use cases, text summarization, auto encoding language model bird. Then, where the Robert robustly optimised brought approach mask was only masked language modelling. Performance of robber's RoBERTa is very large than the bird large, trained with more data BERT into 10 times Okay, is the Robert bird train on 16 GB data into 10 times it will become 160 GB for the Robert large mini batches 2:56 to 8:00 batches. 

Speaker 1  (08:33)
Large white level B.P white pair encoding large training time, bigger vocabulary size technique passing Train on the 160 week, 160 GB on 122 43 to GB. 100 GP1 day, distil butter discility, bird. BERT version battery version of the bird configures 112. 

Speaker 1  (08:59)
Quarrena, cama wonder 10. B conflict reduce to 6 To your 500 Digital Birt is reducing encoder and parameter to 40%. Uh, size reduces 40% speed increase as 60%. 

Speaker 1  (09:23)
Then, we have the training of distil, but pretend with ML M objective is to optimise the triple loss. Ticket. Large model. 

Speaker 1  (09:35)
Alm lambda M distilbert predict mask token loss district losses for large pretend. Teacher smallest Child distance distil loss file-transfer of the knowledge cocaine distance loss is Ram is going to the temple, Ram goeswara temple, minimise the cocine similarity. Distilber train on 16 GB of data and not on 160 GB but it has Less encoder. 

Speaker 1  (10:05)
Elberta is a light bird. Overcome bird limitation sentence order prediction. It published on some time when distilbutt came ALBERT Alberta trained on 12 million parameters, but bird was 110 million conflict same on the bertler, but 18 times few parameters less. 

Speaker 1  (10:31)
18X. Parametre, okay, so what is this? Difference in the albertise parameter addiction to 89% loss function is NSP used in the bird hair So P used sequence wise order wise ALBERT monitorment in the order speed large 1.7 bird base cross parameters sharing is 3 techniques, all share parameters are same only feet forward network only mini head. 

Speaker 1  (11:08)
Attention layer but dimension is 768 vocabulary. 3000 pert is equal to input embedding 3070 68, ALBERT input is 300 crores and tempus and cross 7068 gives 300 crores 768. Input. 

Speaker 1  (11:31)
GPT is generative pretend transformer It has a decoder only Prompts usually give input to the embeddings. Blog, and then we get the output. Block mask, multi hydertension. 

Speaker 1  (11:56)
Seed forward network. Several layer normalisation, operation Okay, so it has the position encoding also 

Speaker 2  (12:08)
Self attention. Make transformer powerful? 

Speaker 1  (12:12)
Important part of the input, single attention mechanism, how had worked When input pass through embedding, she separate linear layer goes into mass multi head. Attention layer 2 other is Q and the other is QKV actually. Multi head attention before learn about single head attention. 

Speaker 1  (12:42)
Multi head individual head on Top X ok each other input to already head. Same, each head weighs a different concatinate, cleaning output 

Speaker 2  (12:56)
Mass multiple mass self attention. 

Speaker 1  (13:00)
Leftover of the original encoder decoder transformer model encoder see full sentences, but decoder see translated word first part gibr doesn't have encoder. Decoder. Are predicting a word decoder to see the word Block boxes feed 4 network multilayer perceptron, railu, activation drop out layer ad and nom nomination. 

Speaker 1  (13:31)
It helps in proper backpropagation of the gradient and help tremendously reduce the problem of vanishing, gradient and exploding gradient problem. Position a medding input is prompt to transformer. Tensor transformer does not know sequence. 

Speaker 1  (13:50)
To different meaning the bir 

Speaker 2  (13:52)
Is the Boy's boycott? That's two different meaning 

Speaker 1  (13:58)
GPT training is basic. Self. Supervised learning sample damage tasks target area fine-tuning transformer learning mobile net Inception Vs for image classification after in the LLM GP5 second stage of training functioning pro model generate answer rined by the human body. 

Speaker 1  (14:21)
Backpropagation continues, LLM has the contact window input prompt. Can you describe AI is a token, let's say, and it will divide into the multiple tokens. That's a 4 taken fort token. 

Speaker 2  (14:38)
Lam, except 16th, fee. 

Speaker 1  (14:43)
16 king input tokens. Regrettable augment generation prompt reduced token pass into the Alam motil. Transformer, the tea in GPT knows how to direct attention to specific part of input to guide their selection of output, such as verb tension and objects. 

Speaker 1  (15:11)
Prompt engineers are of 3. What we see is the context format task exempts for 7 and 2. Prompt tuning. 

Speaker 1  (15:30)
Prompt structure. 

Speaker 1  (15:44)
Home? LSM locality sensitive hashing token word hello world. Hello, big small small bill similar data points in buckets. 

Speaker 1  (15:56)
Shingling and Jakob jakobd index Camera Jacob index is S1 intersection of QS1 union of Q. Use alarm finding simulator and Put in a bucket and with query duje'd, index and shrinkling skit is stepped documentation. Similar item in the bucket, second step is worth with query bu shangling and Jakob, indexing and final similarity. 

Speaker 1  (16:31)
Help me with the tool bindings okay? And tool scheduling in a language framework. I want to know about the smot. 

Speaker 1  (16:46)
UK random unique sampler ROC AUC one hatter encoder pipeline Keras is a rapper cancer flood model parameters in convolution, 2 days layers. And then we have the RL recurrent. Neural network data point is dependency time series. 

Speaker 1  (17:13)
Sequence complete sentence completion types of iron one. Input is one output is one binary classification problem When input model output one image capturing multiple things in image sentiment analysis management transformation vanishing gradient because of the sigmoid in hidden layer, all we use sigmoid, gradient or derivatives, tends to 0. So we have to use that Reado. 
