
Speaker 1  (00:01)
Okay, now we have been the dinner regression, so we need to calculate predicting the MB salary from the great 10 green in 10 marks. Tunnel coupon one contain the surg of 50 graduating MB students of a Business School. And their responsibility percentage of salary based on the product number is 150. 

Speaker 1  (00:28)
Corresponding, we have percentage in great 10 and the salary Now we are personal status, focus, sudden purpose, founders, lively numbers. Library read seriously antified, feature X and Y Mukesh data centre change and validation set import states model agreeing with the model using ULS method. Setting up panda sprint option to print national value up to 4 does not. 

Speaker 1  (01:01)
We are set to understand option, precisions will hold line with equal to 100 read CS. P. And then we have the info, it will give us the normal values. 

Speaker 1  (01:11)
Screening feature action. Yet the state model library is used in python. For building the static model U LSE P available in the state model of the UPI is used for estimation of parameter for simple linear relation model, the US method. 

Speaker 1  (01:32)
Du Kolkata takes 2 parameters, Y and X for example, percentage will be X. And several Dubai, while a heavy available in the state's model or DP estimate only the proposed of X parameter to estimate regression coefficient B not a constant amount of one needs to be added at a separate value as the value of the colonremains seen across all the centre. The parameter estimate for this feature of column will be will be the intercept. 

Speaker 1  (02:00)
So at constant Assam statesman.at constant MB salary, deer ok, and the percentage rate 10 And if we look at that X we have constant on one and Percentage in the game nasterian, growth training and development from escaland model models provides the ability to split the various substantially into training and the condition data set. The parameter train size takes a fraction between 0 and 1%. For specified, training set size The remaining sample in the original set will be test of the validation set. 

Speaker 1  (02:40)
The record that are selected for training and test set are renewable sample. The method takes a seed value in the parameter named random state to fix which sample go to the training and which one goes to a desert train assisted woman together. The metal return 4 variable as below train_X contains X feature of the training set train and so vacuum the value of the response federal variable for the training set test_X contain X feature of the test set test count_Y contain the value of the response value for the test set for a student model. 

Speaker 1  (03:13)
Selection input train test system Team exchange tests chain light testwy, train test split X, Y train size equal to random 0. The tint of equipment the change side will be 80% of the data is used for the training level. Remaining 20% is used for the validation level model and remaining, putting the model. 

Speaker 1  (03:38)
We will use the SMD2 LF if the model is in the QLS method. So this is one of the method and pass extreme The fit method on uls US is Ordinary leases, ordinary leases square is the formula Hota hai SSE is equal to summation of error YI minus predicted position ok, and B Beta one hat will become Beta one and Beta 2K values are in Karnataka Beta one again, summation of Xi minus X bar into YA minus Y by 2X minus X bar ko Y nau to the Y bar minus Beta 1X bar ye example relationship. Urinas, chainwald algia has winter. 

Speaker 1  (04:44)
Parameter manufacture model information to the variable which contained the model parameter accuracy measure the residual value solving urgently. Printing the estimated parameter intersecting them till the parameters 30587% in radial 3560 to the estimate market written as salary, is equal to coefficient, which is 30587 or 285 plus Percentage turn into the percentage of return percentage in return was 355 87383, which is an x-axis, the percentage of the grid. The question can you interest today for healthy? 

Speaker 1  (05:29)
1% research in the great length of several health to include increased by Chief 560 but 587. Show complete quota, hai. It is important to calculate the regression model kit before it can be used for the patiling. 

Speaker 1  (05:59)
Measures are used to do the simple linear location model. Coefficient or determination, which is the ice pack? You know, hypothesis test for the regression coefficient analysis of the various got overall model validity important for multiple linear regression residual analysis to validate the regression of consumption outline analysis. 

Speaker 1  (06:19)
The appearance of outline can significantly impact the region parameter so cofficient data nation, which is R square. The primary data regression is to explain the variation in why is the knowledge of fax, the profession of determination and measure the percentage of variation in white screen by the model B not plus B Beta, 1B not B Beta naught plus Beta one into X the simple denar generation model Beta into the vision. In outcome variable model unexplained variation, as shown in the Coupons, there is one in the outcome variable that's been by the variable unexplained variation. 

Speaker 1  (06:56)
So there is variation in Y screen does not least B not plus Beta X plus variation, and Y notice the variation in the Y It can be proven mathematically, that SST is equal to S. Sr plus SSE so SST which is total, YI minus. Y bar, the whole square summation is equal to Why hat minus Y bar ka whole square commission plus YI minus Y bar ka whole square, which is SC. 

Speaker 1  (07:37)
YI minus. Mean of Y Rahul spark is equal to Prediction. Predictively, minus mean plus value minus Prediction. 

Speaker 1  (07:59)
Which is which will be equal to value, YI minus input, YI minus mean this by Is equal to values. Predator value minus mean predictive value, minus mean plus Actual value minus predicted kids. YI bar is equal to B. 

Speaker 1  (08:27)
Naught. Add plus B no D Beta, one at X1 is effective values that symbol is used for denoting, the estimated value as GIS the sum of square of the total variation as far as the sum of square explained variation. Due to regression of it Add S0 songs for unexpluration, the coefficient of dramation asked S Sr. 

Speaker 1  (08:56)
Divided by S. Yes. T. 

Speaker 1  (09:00)
Which is equal to one minus. SSE divided by SST. The coefficient of determination as a following property, the value of the R square lies between 0 to 5 mathematically R square is the square of coefficient regulation. 

Speaker 1  (09:20)
To correlation coefficient, where R is the piercing correlation coefficient R is possible to small R square higher R square. Indicate higher one should be careful about this. Is sturious leadership? 

Speaker 1  (09:37)
The heaviest test for the regression proofs The regression coefficient weaker once captured the existence of dinner in the open, reviewing the future. If Beta 1 is 0, we can compute that there is no statically significant reasons between the 2 revenue. It can be proved that the sampling distribution of detail is AT distribution. 

Speaker 1  (10:01)
The null and the alterative hectices are isn't Beta? 1020H Beta 1 is 24 0 0. June 2002 0HA Beta is not equal to 0. 

Speaker 1  (10:18)
The corresponding test statistics is given by T alpha by 2, N -2 is equal to Beta, one had tweaded by AC Beta one hat. Turn off the standard error festival of the reservation. Cofficient is given by SE Beta. 

Speaker 1  (10:37)
One hat is equal to SE divided by under root of Xi minus mu ka voice as well. Where H is the study relation? Is the study division error of the student value of YI and the residual and given by SE is equal to under root of YI minus prediction divided by N -2. 

Speaker 1  (11:02)
The hypothesis test is 2 till test. The test statistics is AT distribution with N -2° of freedom, 2° of freedom are lost due to the estimation that 2 reservation perventor B north and Beta one. S Beta one is the student error of error of the regulation coefficient. 

Speaker 1  (11:22)
Beta or not? That's Group, we can check the overall validity model using anova. In the case of multiple delivers, the nerve alternative hypothesis are given by X naught is equal to Beta one is equal to Beta 2 is equal to Beta K is equal to 0. 

Speaker 1  (11:48)
As if not all degression, cofficients are 0. The corresponding F statistics is given by FIS equal to M Sr divided by MSc Sr divided by K divided by SScD administration, where msr is linked to Sr CMS C is equal to SC divided by N minus K -1 Tar, meaning squad education mean squad, respect for checking visit models statically significant only Using the python, so the function summary 2 Print the model someday. Which contained the information required for the diagnosing regulation model for somebody to is a method. 

Speaker 1  (12:36)
This is almost model ulsu. I have independent variable salary ticket date. A number of observations model concepts have one had R square markets log like 

Speaker 1  (13:01)
T is greater than 0.6 R IT -25%, 75%, and 7%. 

Speaker 1  (13:26)
Scottosis, Durbin, Watson jerkara JB probability of End condition number from the summary output shown in the table 4.2, we can infer the following. The model R square value is 0.00211 that is, the model explains 21% of the variation in the salary that P value is 0.0029, which indicator is strategically significant relationship. Add significance level of 0.05 between the feature percentage greater than the surgery of the quality values are F. 

Speaker 1  (14:01)
Statistic of the model is 029, which indicate that the whole model is categorically significant. Note that in a simple linear regression, the P value for P test inductors will be sale. Same, since the null hypothesis is the same F visibility square in the case of S. 

Speaker 1  (14:17)
M. L. 
