
Speaker 1  (00:00)
On that one. So on the database side we have this pipelines dlt pipelines. I have worked with streaming also, batch data. 

Speaker 1  (00:10)
We have used the idea of Azure pipelines for the incremental load and the full load. Also, we are using ads along with that. We have. 

Speaker 1  (00:22)
The adws H3 is built-in for some of the jobs and workforce also have work with on the database site. Apart from that, we have configured jamilflows also in the database itself. And I work with a snow flip also in the snow flick, we have created the steaming tables, snow pipe injection data. 

Speaker 1  (00:42)
Um, that pipeline I have created also, so this part on the database side on the Uber side. I work with a step function for orchestrations and lambda. Also, in between along the along with that on the genius, creating all the orchestrations pipelines, basically, using the embeddings, uh, chunkings, okay, and vector dB also for keeping them bettings and so, apart from that, I've used the embedding models. 

Speaker 1  (01:17)
Okay, I have used the chunking strategies. I've tuned those strategies. Also, apart from the I've worked on the spark tuning, also on some of the jobs. 

Speaker 1  (01:30)
Keeping the skinness and everything align. Apart from that, I've worked on the other model, which is more into the evaluating the agents. So what they have how they performed while giving a while on the call with the customer, and based on that we have created the flow like we have different parameters. 

Speaker 1  (01:54)
And then we have met and not one condition using the prompt engineering and the bird models we have trained that Also, we have worked on the evaluation mattresses on the dashboard. Like few parameters like accuracy processions, recall values, phenomenals, all these been listed there in the dashboard. Also I've worked on the analysis side as well on the ID side of in the Morgan standard for few of the Datasets and then we came up with the predictions also and telling the right model. 

Speaker 1  (02:31)
Okay, yeah, that's pretty much from my side. 

Speaker 2  (02:37)
Ok, so overall, just to small rise about infusious experience and out of that, how much is on relutive air? How many years have we've been working on? 

Speaker 1  (02:46)
Yes, it's a good thing to do 7 years. I'm working with Jennifer Lopez. 

Speaker 2  (02:51)
Jannaii, I did from 6 years. Okay, so you mentioned only like the RAG pipeline. What else should you work on on Generative AI? 

Speaker 1  (03:02)
Yeah, yeah, on the other hand I have used the land chain majorly. Okay, we are working with langmage. Also for the mattresses, yeah, for the agent kii, we are not using it but we are planning to do it so with the right. 

Speaker 1  (03:20)
I have mostly work with the right pipelines and less on the other model which is agentic one. 

Speaker 2  (03:26)
Can you explain the right pipeline that you could 

Speaker 1  (03:31)
Yeah, so start with the ingestion layer, so we have different 5 formats. We are getting it into the bronze layer. Then, we have the refined it. 

Speaker 1  (03:43)
Then, we refined the data to the other layers like silver and golden and then we have the in between we have the chunkings, so we have different strategies. We have tried it for chunking, like currently we are using the recursive character taxplitter. But we have used a semantics on the context window and all those things for the chunking strategies. 

Speaker 1  (04:05)
Then, we come up with the embarrassing. Also, we tried it windowing the conceptual and the contextual window and the embedding on right now. We are using the open AI embedding model right there and then we have the vector dv, where we are storing all them weddings, everything right now we are using pine cool, but I have worked with the quadrant and snowflake quertex, so uh that we have tried it and then we have the user query. 

Speaker 1  (04:36)
Coming up, we have the prom temperate, certain that is garteling the query along with that where we are specifying the role, okay and the role of the tone and the task everything we are defining and we are surprising, also based on the chat hits, chat history, and then we are sending that data to the LLM keeping the um sufficient window for the context, and then we have Tokenized, I'm in tokenisation, keeping the minimum number of tokens to be sended to the LLM's along with that. Yeah, then we are sending it to the we have tried multiple LLM models like rock OpenAI and we tried it with the cloud. 

Speaker 1  (05:28)
Also, rest of the cloth. And yeah, these models we have tried, so we have tune that chat GI mean the rap model. And then to reduce the latency cost and everything and we have these parameters also which we are showing up in the dashboard. 

Speaker 1  (05:47)
The relevance factor the relevance rate, basically, hallucination rate, accuracy, precisions okay, are these things we are displaying it. 

Speaker 2  (06:00)
Talking about what about the retrieval part? 

Speaker 1  (06:02)
Yawned treatments in retrieval party. We have used the conversational. Double-double Jain, and there we have specified the parameters for the top Kok or top P parametres the number of relevant searches we have to use also we have used the ranking also reranking um, so that also we have tried, uh, we have used the M. 

Speaker 1  (06:27)
Mr. thing, which is maximum margin relevance, so there are other parameters also, like refining. Okay and basically how those things work is for the refining. 

Speaker 1  (06:41)
It takes all chunks in place, and then it will generate the output of each of the chunks. And then it will give the output, so that's a cost that is not cost-efficient. So for the cost efficiency we have used the mmr. 

Speaker 1  (06:57)
Along with that, we are getting the top 20 retrievals, keeping the duplicates remove. Yeah, those are the things that we have done. 

Speaker 2  (07:08)
So how have you basically how large was the team, and what areas were you part of 

Speaker 1  (07:15)
Yeah, we have we are working with agile, so I have around eight people including QA. And I'm into the problem, went often 

Speaker 2  (07:26)
Okay, so any specific areas of this RAG pipeline that you contributed to? 

Speaker 1  (07:31)
I've been almost in all of the areas where I got the story where I have to reduce the latency, ok of the mode. So I trained it, I tuned, basically the rack model. 

Speaker 2  (07:47)
How did you tune the run note? 

Speaker 1  (07:50)
Yeah, I tried with different strategies like the thing. The thing that I told you right checking the different cluster. I mean, the chunkings embedding models. 

Speaker 1  (08:01)
Then, the top territory will reranking. We have used the hybrid search. Also there, keeping the BM25 and the deep search. 

Speaker 1  (08:13)
Sorry, dense search in between in red denser. We are checking for each of the parameter like body title and the other parameters we were having that and then we are generating the ambitions and out of that we are again fine tunes and embedding, sending to the Then, again we are sending it to the embedding models. So I tried with a chunking strategy. 

Speaker 1  (08:42)
I have tried, as I told you mmr, refined the other things were there. So I tried those things um, so using the land chain, basically, we have I've configured that RAG. Also, we're what we're doing is we are generating the report also at the end for checking the model drifts. 

Speaker 1  (09:06)
Was there along with that? We have the multiple parameters like accuracy, recessions, precision and the reforms. 

Speaker 2  (09:15)
Previously, so how much was your knowledge-based how many documents were there? And what kind of 

Speaker 1  (09:23)
Show the doctors because we are getting the data onto the Delta tables. Okay, so the file size not specifically, I don't know, but we have the different formats coming up in the kafarka, and then from the Kafka, we have multiple formats, like avocado okay, sometime ORC and those are dumping it okay, there are 2 ways 1 is there they're sending. It to the ADLs and the other way they are sending to the kafaka. 

Speaker 1  (09:52)
For the CDC S part, they have created the incremental pipelines for getting the data implementing it and sending to the database, so the file size are not sure. Maybe the data is coming on the TVS. 

Speaker 2  (10:10)
Not about the size exactly, but know what sort of documents is text based what formats are there? Is it working? 

Speaker 1  (10:18)
It's a multiplier model coming up in the as I told you like the Gs N format sometimes in the file format. 

Speaker 2  (10:27)
Okay, so how would you go handle this pipeline if there are images embedded in your documents? 

Speaker 1  (10:33)
Yeah, for the images we have the separate separate library for extracting the images. Also extracting the text out of it using the extract. Also, yeah, I mean that I am not aware of there might be using the vision, also vision libraries so that but I am not aware of the images. 

Speaker 2  (10:58)
Are you remember of any vision models but you could use? If you had to 

Speaker 1  (11:05)
Yeah, I mean the vision one I mean, I told you about a tax. It is at O. C. 

Speaker 1  (11:08)
R or something. What are not sure. 

Speaker 2  (11:13)
Extract this for text, right? So you're asking about image understanding. 

Speaker 1  (11:18)
I know about the conceptual thing. How the images I mean, using the convocational models we can extract that But I'm not sure. 

Speaker 2  (11:32)
So have you what sort of did we have? You used for all the nvidents, and all of the 

Speaker 1  (11:38)
Yeah, so currently we are using the pine cone. But I work with a cotton runners like what is 

Speaker 2  (11:47)
And have you worked from any agentic frameworks? You said you have some 

Speaker 1  (11:52)
Is kar Diya? Yeah, I know about the crew, but my current project. We are not using it. 

Speaker 2  (11:59)
Oh, good, how did book? 

Speaker 1  (12:01)
Yeah, I mean, for talk about the agentic ecosystem. They work as the act they have to act on the basically they get the tools we have to define the tools basically, and based on those tools, the 2 agents will have to come up with the solution. So if they summarise it, they let's say tools could be searching on the web. 

Speaker 1  (12:28)
Okay, tools could be our custom functions. Also that we have to specify based on the business needs. So in the crew, there is a chain, right? 

Speaker 1  (12:37)
So in the chain we have to specify the LLM, and then the model, what lm model we are using, and then we have to specify the all the tools in between with some tasks. And then we have to run that Uh, sakru UI is just a framework that gifts to performers things. 

Speaker 2  (13:02)
Ok, have you heard of or used planra for any other framework? 

Speaker 1  (13:10)
Ok, land craft, you're talking about? Yes, I know. We are not used along. 

Speaker 2  (13:17)
Okay, and in crew, why do you think it's a chain based mechanism? 

Speaker 1  (13:23)
Sorry, come on, come in place. 

Speaker 2  (13:25)
So in cru AI, why do you think it's a chain based mechanism? 

Speaker 1  (13:29)
It's not a chain based mechanism. It's just the parametre that it needs to work right, so I'm talking about the parameters of the crew. So it needs the model. 

Speaker 1  (13:40)
It needs the tools. Okay? And the task. 

Speaker 1  (13:44)
Of course, so it's just Okay depending on the things we can paralyse it or we can run it sequentially, right. So if there's a need to check-in the Web, the Web weather to check the relevant, I mean we have to search in the Web relate to that specific information. It will retrieve from there, and then it will inject that data just to make sure the context should be remain. 

Speaker 1  (14:13)
Same for that particular thing. That's why, but we can make it sequential and the pedal. But I've not worked on the event. 

Speaker 2  (14:29)
Okay, so you mentioned a lot of experience on the cloud part of it. Have you designed any into and cloud architecture? Can you talk about any design? 

Speaker 1  (14:41)
Yeah, sure I guess I have designed that so when while working with the agentic feedback system there I have created that pipeline using the ad of pipeline so we are getting the data in the O rc format and then we are dumping it some talking about the one flow where we are dumping the data into the adls, and then we are doing the 1 time 1 time pull to the data in the Delta table. Ok um, so there we have that script running in the pice park, where it will doing to do that. In the notebook, we have wrote that. 

Speaker 1  (15:22)
And then, once the full fresh is done, then we are incrementing the data using the time is done, along with that some primary key. So that next time it will take the maximum time step, and then it will go to query from there. Okay. 

Speaker 1  (15:39)
And so that we will get the incremental data. And once we have the data again, we are sending it to the bronze layer and from bronze to a silver layer. So that's the one part also I have configured some workflows inside the data breaks. 

Speaker 1  (15:54)
In the workflows, we're creating the views for the exposure to the to the users. So there we have the we have scheduled the workflow. Basically, so it will run daily after at around 8 PM and in the workflow, it will just refreshing that data. 

Speaker 1  (16:16)
So that's the other part. Apart from that, I work with the air flows before. For orchestration, I work with these tough functions and londons, so that's a separate thing. 

Speaker 2  (16:35)
So I mean, men know what's the reason you're looking out right now and what sort of role are you expecting? 

Speaker 1  (16:41)
Yeah, I'm looking for the same role. AI engineer and sorry. What was the other question? 

Speaker 2  (16:50)
Ah, what is the reason why? 

Speaker 1  (16:52)
Yeah, so currently I'm serving, and the reason is that My come companies in Bangalore. Okay so they are asking me to come to relocate to Bangalore, which I don't want to, because my family stay here. So that's why I'm looking for. 

Speaker 1  (17:08)
The chain. 

Speaker 2  (17:11)
Ok. And regarding the role in mentioned when you believe that same role AI in Indian, but on basically, on what areas of AI and what sort of day-to-day work are you open to? 

Speaker 1  (17:26)
Yes, I'm working on the umbrella. I've worked on the racks, so I'm looking for that. Also I want to learn the agent with a genius, whatever the things that we have in the genius. 

Speaker 2  (17:48)
Thank you. How much we have been in your passport and how much have you been like on Amazon contribution roll? Versus leadership or technical leadership in sort of room 

Speaker 1  (17:59)
Yeah, whenever I was in Morgan, I was a lead. Okay, there so because I have worked, therefore close to 9 years. Okay, so I know the business and everything I have got a chance to work with the business. 

Speaker 1  (18:13)
Also I went to onset also, so I connected with the users and getting the requirement from them. So that's also I have the experience. 

Speaker 2  (18:24)
But I also comfortable with complete hands-on or how sick 

Speaker 1  (18:29)
What does that mean? 

Speaker 2  (18:32)
Panzon meets mostly like an individual contributor to all and development role. 

Speaker 1  (18:37)
Yeah, anything would be fine fun because I forgot both. 

Speaker 2  (18:44)
However. So, have you had any chance to use MCPs or are you aware of what mcpas are? 

Speaker 1  (18:52)
Yeah, I'm CP. Yes. I'm aware of what I've didn't get chance to work on. 

Speaker 1  (18:56)
I'm CP is just a protocol for on top of the agents, agent ki. I um, so they have simplified the framework basically for communicating and extracting the data. Getting the data that's all I know. 

Speaker 2  (19:19)
But what is the protocol more useful for? 

Speaker 1  (19:25)
I'm sorry I mean I have done about it. But I'm not able to recall right now. 

Speaker 2  (19:33)
Thank you for watching haright. I saw. I think that's what I have from my end. 

Speaker 2  (19:38)
Do you have any questions before we close? 

Speaker 1  (19:41)
Yes, sure, can you tell me about the The Congress and the project sorry. What they are hiring for. 

Speaker 2  (19:50)
Yeah, sure. So. This iron is going on for captivy invent data strategy factory. 

Speaker 2  (19:57)
So the again, the locations up and PAN India based, but usually once one joins, there will again be, you know. Some client interviews, all are client based projects, so there will be a client interview. Of course. 

Speaker 2  (20:16)
The like they'll help me prepare that, etc. But the roles are usually for client roles. There is also some internal asset development going on in the fli, which will be like building small pucs and showcasing 2 customers, but that is mostly a sign apart from that. 

Speaker 2  (20:36)
The main roles will be for the client and all our development projects know support projects, but based on the client need at that point of time, the requirements that we have and based on each one's experience. And their strengths and whatever are the key areas they are wrong when we were still based on that the one can be 

Speaker 1  (21:01)
Oh, so 

Speaker 2  (21:02)
From the range of products, they are over computer vision, much processing AI am develops and adopts children today AI and electricity. Most of the projects recently are of question AI. 

Speaker 1  (21:21)
Okay, I got it. Hello, I am good. 

Speaker 2  (21:26)
Ok, yeah, thank you, prakal for joining then. Have a good day. Thank you. 

Speaker 2  (21:30)
Thank you. 
