
Speaker 1  (00:02)
Okay, schedule the customer chunk prediction subscribe Karta, discontinue doing business with the commerce service to customer in the telecom industry can choose from a variety of service providers and actively switched on one to the next. The individual customer attention is tough because most firm have the large number of customers can't afford to devote much time to each of them. The cost would be too great outweighing the additional revenue. 

Speaker 1  (00:31)
However, if a corporation could forecast which customers likely to leave ahead of the time, it could focus customer attention efforts only on these high risks. To reduce the customer, need to predict Which customers are at the risk, higher risk of the charm. To detect early signs of potential gems, 1 must first develop a holistic view of the customer and their interactions across numerous channel, including store branch, visit product purchase histories, customer service call, uh web-based transactions and social media interaction. 

Speaker 1  (01:09)
Tumne, pehle, libraries, load kari. I'll every steamery panda's Nampally, missingu missing metloot lips E bone pipelot, express graph objects sublots or a mung dull decision tree classifiers, random forest bojian, MB ke nei neighbour classifier, S VCM LP classifier, ok. And addaboost, greging, boost, extra classifier, logistics regression exglassifier, cadboost, classifier mattress, aaroosi, curve, recall score confusion matrix. 

Speaker 1  (01:52)
Poison. Hon, later, the Santa Each year represent a customer customer 750 emails, senior citizen nahin hai Teno risk ka bun hai ticket phone service nahin, Leta multiple lines nahin, hai uski internet service dsl hai uski device protection nahin, hai tax support nahin hai contract Mantu Mantri her per nukrata hai paperless, billing, Jata hai payment method, electronic chakye, bhejta hai and Mantri charges, deta hai charges, 29 ke Charan Abhi nahin hai. Data set includes information about the customer who left within within the last month to get Kolkata. 

Speaker 1  (02:52)
Chalegar, the column is called the churn servicers. Customer has signed up for one multiple lines, internet online security online backup device protection tax support and steaming TV movies. Customer account information how long they have been a customer. 

Speaker 1  (03:09)
Contract payment method, people list billing, monthly charges and putting charges demographic info about customer gender agricult, and if they have partner and dependent DF dot Sikh ahmedabas 70401. Dear dot columns dot values. Tint. 

Speaker 1  (03:31)
Any columns have apne pass who would potentially get degraded. Type with zipper types came out. As a learning visualise, the missing values been visualising a missing values using used by the missing. 

Speaker 1  (03:45)
No MSN O dot matrix DA using this pictures, we can clearly see to find the pattern of the missingness. In the data from the above vision, we can observe that it has no peculiar pattern that may stand out, in fact, there is no missing data. And determinipulation, customer, adequate NE drop kar Diya. 

Speaker 1  (04:13)
On the deep analysis, we can find some indirect missingness in our data. Okay, let's see that. And you can nekha period to the merit total charges, L Course. 

Speaker 1  (04:33)
Tumne, total charges, karke, deer banaye, or is nullshan. Here we can see the total charges is 11 missing value. Is nelka sankkaran recharge Mein gyarah, missing values. 

Speaker 1  (04:58)
Is Nain total charges? Total charges nal hai. Wo nikala moham. 

Speaker 1  (05:06)
Thomas, it can also be noted that tenure column is 0. Iskaj tenure, kitna hai renew 0. R. 

Speaker 1  (05:17)
That's why Total charges are multiple Then, usage 0 values in the tenure column 10 minutes 0 companies carry on the ground. There are no additional missing value on the Teno colour. Let's delete the roles with missing values. 

Speaker 1  (05:40)
In the tension, there are only 11 rows again. Tenu 0 ka index lekar ke jab ko drop kar, thee This dieto drop karke. Label jutha. 

Speaker 1  (06:05)
To solve the problem missing again, runner, I decided to fill in with mean of the total charges. Total charges of the bus. The deodor phir javienal means replace them. 

Speaker 1  (06:35)
Did you will not affect the data? In tanial, tadi. Tenure zeroth devun, the corner tiger. 

Speaker 1  (06:44)
XC0 McDonald row gusariat, original mappers, shooting charges se nalte uncommon Mein Is nallab pijmini significant citizenship 0 minus no one minus ticket. DF internet service. Got describe include is equal to object, calm ruling. 

Speaker 1  (07:19)
DFM internet service sunnel, describe karaoji. And tenure, monthly charges, total charges. Tun sabko, unhone dekha ki count kitna iska 7032 UN sabka hai and Meenja. 

Speaker 1  (07:41)
32 hair, especially 64 hair stand deviation 4 With this gas year Minimum, have one. And maximum is 72. Ideal data visuals The male female low and yes Column 1 row 1 column 2. 

Speaker 1  (08:17)
26% of the customers switch to answer from customer 49.5% female at 5550.5%. Wait. Take a magic Telugu, customer. 

Speaker 1  (08:42)
Tel kukuling. 

Speaker 1  (08:55)
Toh hum mujhe deta dikha. Amit churn dikhen group by the female jitna ki charm nahin hue, male chadh of 1930 or 939 crores people will journalist key equally. There Come on, dikhen, ki churn size, male female ka chakta hai or non Chun ka male female barabar. 

Speaker 1  (09:30)
Osperson. There's a grill difference in the customer percentage account who changes the service provider, both gender behaviour in a similar fashion when it comes to migrating to another service provider. Chron. 

Speaker 1  (09:51)
It's about 75% of the customer with mantum. Contact, quoted to move out as customer to 30% of the customer, with one year contact and 3%, with 2 year content. Our main payment must be mixed. 

Speaker 1  (10:08)
P SOS histogram drilling DFX capacitors are involved in the corner corner payment method. Title, first one payment method distribution with respect to German. Major customer who moved out were having electronic check. 

Speaker 1  (10:23)
As behind customer opted for trade guard, automatic transfer or bank Automatic transfer will Edward, less likely to move out. A chandering ka male hai ticket. Or innovation, select Kara, internet service and churn ka value, kaun kiya. 

Speaker 1  (10:48)
Do you female day? Uncontracted, counsekaran, Verma. A lot of customers, user fibre optics service, and it's also evident that the customer who use fibre optics have higher generate. 

Speaker 1  (11:06)
This might suggest dissatisfaction with this type of internal service. Customer having DSL services are majority in number and have less generate compared to the fibre optical service. Customer without dependents are more likely to join Customer doesn't have partner moods at richar. 

Speaker 1  (11:27)
It can be observed that a function of the senior citizen is very less most of the senior citizen churn. Whose customer check-in the absence of the online security customer with people, as buildings are more likely to be churn, customer with no tax support, how most actually divided to the anger service provider, very small. Fortunately, customer don't have a phone service and out of the ones health customer are more like a future. 

Speaker 1  (11:55)
Yuvatar, ki. Sabse. Note John. 

Speaker 1  (12:01)
Customer with highly multichagan. I would like to charge What John judge. Subrabul. 

Speaker 1  (12:30)
New customers are more likely to turn Tujhu, Marcus shivili. Correlated. 

Speaker 1  (12:51)
Firmen, data processing currently, inflation refund to train and test Blikra. Label encoder. Firram chaunkara, short values. 

Speaker 1  (13:13)
Drop karachan, column, split kardiya. Display banaya. Tenure, monthly charges and total charges ka. 

Speaker 1  (13:28)
Discard Bunny. Distribution for the total charges Since the numerical factor distributed over different value range, I will use the standard scalar to scale them down to the same range standards correlation. Payment contract internet service. 

Speaker 1  (13:56)
Standard skiller, Machine Learning model apply can care can never classify. Never specify correct, never 11th hai. Fit kramin extends vibrant predictor the accuracy is 77%. 

Speaker 1  (14:12)
Chicken Terminus physically, 80% and film random. Forest Kara. Are semari, Chrisy, 81%? 

Speaker 1  (14:28)
Estimate over 500 To number of trees bull. Hum name. Random ferras, ki, confusion, matrix NE kaha. 

Speaker 1  (14:49)
Hiram near aarusi karnoska. Logistic regression nikala, hamlon, accuracy is one logistic. Regression is 80%. 

Speaker 1  (15:08)
No decision tree classify 72%. Adda, boost classifier, 80%. Credit bossnikalam, se 80% unhone heat Mein apni gala. 

Speaker 1  (15:25)
Let's now predict the final model based on the highest majority of the voting and check its score. Find Le cruishi Amara, 81% On the confusion metrics, we can see that the cathol of 154 9 actual launch and values, and the algorithm predict 100 0 of them as non churn, and 1 for 9 of them as churn, while there are 237 + 234 is equal to 561, actual churn values, and the algorithm predict 237 If there's no enjoying values and 324 as launch value, customer channel definitely bad to a firm probability where strategies can be implemented to eliminate customer churn. 

Speaker 1  (16:17)
The best way to avoid customer churn is for the Company to truly know its customer. This include identifying customer who are at risk of journey and working to improve their satisfaction, improving customer services. Of course. 

Speaker 1  (16:33)
At the top of the priority for tackling this issue, building customer loyalty through relevant experience and especially services strategy to reduce the customer check, some firms survey customer who have already churned to understand their reason of leaving. 
