
Speaker 1  (00:01)
Okay, so here we will talk about the plot craft of TV sales versus Sales Vs the year. And here it is showing you the EV skills across the patrols, sales EV market share. Per year it is a line job, EV market share goes up. 

Speaker 1  (00:21)
EV market share, goes up from 0.03% to 24%, EV sales grown up exponentially, especially Axis of 0 dot plot UK ERA V series 0 colour width label. What fill between ear initial alpha 0.3 colour petrol car sales have pratude and started declining. Diesel remained smaller, but persistent sheer, particularly in commercial field. 

Speaker 1  (00:57)
In 2025, which country Adding leading AE V resolution, it was toin 2005X EV share is 10EV says 12000 but after 2025 country let's say ZV share is 37%. Eve, sales has gone rise to millions to 34 million X index double column −12 will give us the Rivers. DM.order by your column descending access.com bar H index. 

Speaker 1  (01:42)
You share text column, you share + 0.5 tite centre, uh, font size. Diego dot group by aggregate average of the EU market share. Or the mean, we will say So we have gotten the box clothes We tried to find the story relations, okay? 

Speaker 1  (02:09)
And 2011 EV replace petrol Rows are 1200 crores into global European trends. Over time, countries are 25 unique values EV share is 1200 mean is 633% medium is 50%, and stand division is signed at 2%. Positive skeute mean is less than the median. 

Speaker 1  (02:38)
Okay, and the sun duration is large. Nee is greater than the medium 20 years, 3 seconds is going to be ended up how fast every diesel car, which country leads to premium savement, adopt even faster than the commercial. What economic factor correlates with EV adoption to EV subsidies and emission regulation acceleration replacement of The Ic vehicle. 

Speaker 1  (03:17)
Fuel and electricity prices influences event, the GDP got increased probability of EV. To higher transport carbon emission derive, eve transition DM dot describe aggregate sales by ear across Some of EV says some of patrol sales okay so year 2020 EV says his business, petrol, says a business diesel sales. What about the total saves? 

Speaker 1  (03:50)
EV share is equal to EV sales divided by the total sales. Excluding gradient not happen because of the sigmoid swaying hidden layer old weight is 100 and current weight is 100, but difference is huge, okay. So if we're trying to minimise it, is that difference is very huge, if we're going to explore the reading Seville, to avoid for vanishing ingredients of Sigma finisher rally. 

Speaker 1  (04:21)
RMS crops, compromiser, I don't know, use. L. S TM so LS TM is long, short-term memory, which has an improved forever state and the output gate time series problem example of tweet and VG16 architecture image net. 

Speaker 1  (04:41)
ML P is NOTK space anyone entered relationship NL. U. Teacher executive, meaning it doesn't able to recognise bank. 

Speaker 1  (04:54)
Is it a river or a bank? NMONF fouric naphoric. Electrical consideration use cases, Voice Assistant of NLP ok use case of NLP is voice assistance assistant. 

Speaker 1  (05:13)
Text classification Chatbot and translation morphology. Syntax, case folding case insensitivity ok, normalisation, enhance consistency. SCR is special character removal, and it simplify the tokenization. 

Speaker 1  (05:35)
Use import RA library Handling contractions couldn't will be made to couldn't. Contraction? Library is also their tokenization's sentence, word NLT library and gram. 

Speaker 1  (05:51)
The 2 g biggram triigram unigram. 10 g prevent the sequential structure of the language aiding in context. Understanding and feature extraction unigram is a split width, in eye residing will be splitting into eye pencil. 

Speaker 1  (06:15)
It will have the 2 values with eye reside in Bangalore. The tradition is text 2 vector count vectorization T FI DF is a good girl, he's a good Boy, stopwater. Good Boy, girl, prepare metroes. 

Speaker 1  (06:32)
Okay, first, we have to prepare the metrices 100 0012 good Boy and girl. Hot encoding, we don't use in NL. P. 

Speaker 1  (06:43)
We'll use the Word embedding numerical representation of the word to sentences. Okay, types are confrequency, which is Bao T DTF ID of glove prediction is what do veco and scripts skip drum? Type types of embeddings are okay types of embedding, sir, count, frequency, or the prediction count frequency Mein amarpas, Raha, hai, back of words, ok T FI. 

Speaker 1  (07:17)
DF blue and predictions, we have Sivao and srigron bag of word is a representation of text as an unordered set of words, simplifying language for analysis. Okay, so word vector sentence one is let's say he is a good Boy sentence, 2 is she's a good girl. Okay, once you have to lower down the sentences, then remove the Stopwatch. 

Speaker 1  (07:47)
Okay, it will become good Boy. Good girl, Boy, girl good, so good Boy girl is a common and we've created the we have assigned the 110 based on the sentences. If sentence one has the good Boy, then it will be one and if does not have the girl, then it will be 0. 

Speaker 1  (08:06)
So based on that, we get a matrix of 1 and 0 And we have to count the frequency of the good in all the sentences. So good is 3 okay, boys, 2 and the girl is 2 Disadvantage of the bag of Verde's good and Boy. Both have importance is equal to one So we don't know which word is more important. 

Speaker 1  (08:36)
Count vectorized used to create bag of work, count vectorization, and multinomined is model Nile based Okay, so modern nive base is used with the contractorization. Confrontation type camera embedding Mein jaise ki bago Vs undergoes sentences sentences responding others words on that who words from the matrices. 

Speaker 1  (09:19)
Dear mediest, term weight. ATF 0 to how often Toms appear in the document and TF formulaised number of repeating words in the sentence variables number of words in the sentence. Iske idf is reality of terms across document. 

Speaker 1  (09:42)
So log of number of document divided by Number of sentences carrying that word. So Uh, T FI DFS sentences common. Sentences words are Goodbye. 

Speaker 1  (10:03)
Good girl Boy girl good in a sentence 3. So, if we count a frequency's for the good one, we have 3 girls, 2 boys too. So the term frequency would be good number of repeating words in sentences divided number of words in the sentences, so repeating word of good is 1 / 2, because there is only 12 words. 

Speaker 1  (10:30)
Good Boy in a sentence, one for sentence, 2 Italy, 1 / 2. And for sentence 3, it will be 1 / 3 okay for the good. So for the Boy, say me, 1 / 2 Boy is not there in sentence too. 

Speaker 1  (10:46)
It will be 0 and out of 3. The boys coming one time, only to 1 / 3. Okay, and idea would be log of The number of sentences okay. 

Speaker 1  (11:00)
Show the number of sentences R3. And divide by number of sentences carrying that word Panama sentences kind of words. So good is coming 3 times Okay, which is the frequency? 

Speaker 1  (11:21)
And number of sentences, 3 divided by girl, is coming to times and similar way for the girl. It will be 3 / 2 + 3 / 2. So if you calculate good Boy girl tf would be 1 / 2 for good and idea would be log of 3 / 3. 

Speaker 1  (11:42)
So that's way if we want to culinary tough idea for good incentives, one, it will be 0, because 1 / 2, into log 1 / 3, which is one log, 1 is 0. Now we're the post taken part of the speech Ram is going Ram, is the now and go is the one application is question and ask answer system Chatbot's library. Specify, specify, and IDF is commonweald Low importance surri, what will get the high importance? 

Speaker 1  (12:23)
Do you have the NR named entity relationship word to wake using a neural network? What embedding, what to vec number, so let's say I'm doing good. Ice one. 

Speaker 1  (12:36)
And if we do the one hot encoding, it will be 1000. 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1. So as I told you, the embedding sarafu, type count under predicting count is the frequency one having the bow, and the back of what under the TF idea prediction is the word to seb one siblant liberies, Janssen Jensen. 

Speaker 1  (13:04)
Okay, jansy matched the world to wake So let's say if we have king Queen men, women elephant, and then we have Rows of gender. Gender manipower weight and speaks Speak. Did children's? 

Speaker 1  (13:31)
Let's say, king is one okay? Queen is 0 man is one woman is 0? Elephant is one Similarly, money king as a money Queen, as the money man has equal equal women has equal equal money 0.3.3. 

Speaker 1  (13:46)
An elephant is 0. Power. Teen has the power one. 

Speaker 1  (13:52)
Queen has less power, minus men woman has equal and power 0.2 and elephant is 0.5. Wait, obviously elephant is heavy. King is heavy, men is heavy, and king Queen will be less than that. 

Speaker 1  (14:10)
So veteran representation, the king is 11081 crystals. It's a gender money, power weight. End speaking. 

Speaker 1  (14:22)
Siddu king minus M + 1. It will give me the semantics meaning of play to the Queen picking minus man plus Women gives me the Queen. Similar semantic. 

Speaker 1  (14:43)
What do the exhibition 5 word convert to the 3D features? Watch Jose penaltics for data science. This is 3D 1 is 3. 

Speaker 1  (14:57)
So problem given contacts, we need to predict the word Show windows 3, that means watch zeepandics. For in one window, data willing to predict, okay. So let's say, access watch for YZ data Y is for For sciences, X and data is in Y so based on that, we have credit D Matrices of watch Zep, 4 data science Watch is one word restaurant 0. 

Speaker 1  (15:32)
Zee is the 01000400100 data is 00010 science is 00001. So let's say we've made X and Y okay, watch for his will become 100 00000100. This is watch Hands app. 

Speaker 1  (15:53)
And why is Zep, which is 01000? So based on the neural network, which is a 5 × 305 cross 3 metric, we have 3 × 5. With a hidden layer, we have added 3 × 3, which became 5 × 3 metric. 

Speaker 1  (16:16)
It will give me the output of waters app for data science, okay? And then wait, initialise, first record you in Calculate loss function on your back provisions. So the main idea to reduce the loss function So let's say we have water is equal to W and HOnePlus WH2 plus this, all this, this is all about civo, this all about sea Bau works okay, now we talk water, skip grammar, skip Grammy's problem given target word predictive context word X and Y access for you to predict Y which is rapid data. 

Speaker 1  (16:59)
So the input is 5 × 3 metric hidden layer, okay, and then it will get the output layer difference, smaller data with C bar large data. We have to do with the skip graph. 2 important performance, its neural network. 

Speaker 1  (17:16)
So increasing the train data increase. The hidden layer glove is global vector part of count frequency, not prediction. So what embeddings has we know? 

Speaker 1  (17:30)
So how did the globe works? I don't know. So let's say, access, I love Zep data as the I love zap data as the mattresses, okay. 

Speaker 1  (17:45)
0101 is the matrices that we have created. So if we transpose it, okay, probability of I love Will become eye intersection. Love divided by P love, which is equal to 2. 

Speaker 1  (18:00)
Okay. So the formula will become WTX wk plus bias, which is BI plus BK is equal to Log of OnePlus X of Ik vertover Co occurrence frequency. Can we talk about the fast tax? 

Speaker 1  (18:22)
It's an updated version of word to web, which is, here's the speed and fast text is equal to character or gram capacity N is 3. Search to be cap, apaility so capability is not there in the corporate, but we have created it with a window 3, so first you character will be cap. The next 3 will be APA next year would be PAB something like that. 

Speaker 1  (18:51)
Jency missed the library for both a clove and fastest. Coffin, similarly, hello, if costs 900 and of course 0 is 1 okay, so formulize summation of a dot B divided by _. Summation of memory today. 

Speaker 1  (19:16)
He's got his purpose drop of submission of Vi O police. So this will give music for Samsung LST M and 

Speaker 1  (20:58)
BI RST M. R. GRU I'm not sure about it. 
