
Speaker 1  (00:05)
So myself a broken everything for kinders of experience. Ah locking muy de antes es con las the three years AS jenny and genial. A los usuarios looking rating mode charlet. 

Speaker 1  (00:19)
On with the m y am i en el cine. Remind the new previously i was walking with the c v s m l q four major league. Looking at the retail. 

Speaker 1  (00:35)
Um so i have a good experience uh. Turn on recent. Open junior a last d a m. 

Speaker 1  (00:44)
Él le motiva a sus problemas del luge con tu voz. Ambos what are the waters are leading before. Yeah may application is more into the education roman. 

Speaker 1  (00:57)
There are generating the air forfer in our product the ivory of the gallery project which is later chatborn. Where we are retrieving all the documentation international documentation populating it checking it down and we are envening it. Find the leader reception and then we are calling the data former. 

Speaker 1  (01:22)
A for the user. I have on the fine cleaning also. And legendly was duta breaks is nothing a calf cloud system. 

Speaker 1  (01:32)
Bad to any the position mode. Utilier usync the a Wisconsin. Um has estado muy location of the files documents de cine. 

Speaker 1  (01:43)
Are there function for us orchestrations are eclipsed we are collected. And we have used the and lender also for some of the cases. Also we are explosync in some uh and points usync the fast appa. 

Speaker 1  (02:02)
A ver there's a downsea picture no se contiene dar móvil. Ah, de Pekín, o de Microsoft servicios. Four agitations appis. 

Speaker 2  (02:14)
Ok. ¿Qué cantidad de un Cambridge murió. 

Speaker 1  (02:19)
Ya eso. Alexa show me the world. 

Speaker 2  (02:33)
Open. Show can you please walk me through one of your project and to end with respect to the jnai. 

Speaker 1  (02:44)
YouTube. Cerca de Toledo promete chatbots that vídeo created where we are um. Getting the documents in the different format and then we are we are in the changing latest relation we are ba hubiera ducha el Kim leer me he hecho alquiler de chang. 

Speaker 1  (03:04)
La onda negra usync the circumflex of the air. Um. Plus um city of my separates de reaprovid. 

Speaker 1  (03:16)
And then weather doing somewhere uh. The living i'm betting those jumps ok and then you are story them into the left store of the details. Ahm bendial under the retribution airways en la región quími. 

Speaker 1  (03:35)
We are maintaining the mmark ok how it is the drink classic open. We are having having the manchester explosive about from the red us. Uh we are going to be normalised Disney. 

Speaker 1  (03:53)
Discurded to meeting games. All those things we are taking care of generating the uh data to the user including the latercy time uh which was around eighty-nine percent uh for phone l ninety-nine and ninety-five. And then we were happy this year. 

Speaker 1  (04:16)
Para fiethfulness are the livings confixing regard all this i live your expression. Clever see lower of flags so we were fine duning this uh things. Again the deep retriever under faithfulness uh that the data reflection rating. 

Speaker 1  (04:35)
Ah. You've checking it to a big cleaning. With some mexies of this some Matrix like you are doing uh by weekly to check that we are that data difference in the model or night. 

Speaker 1  (04:50)
Find apart from data on. Fondo user side. Dancing, aparecía, tu limpia cash en Google. 

Speaker 1  (04:59)
Guardar 2 seventy cash we are building seventeen number of the air con. Andrew, clientes últimas arqueología libre. Although the coffee of system in Beijing uh there are there the returning all the documents uh part from that we have the cdcs we are we are catching only so. 

Speaker 1  (05:21)
Small for art of the data which is share the chain or the data. Al fondo de aquí a la fundación ideas high playlist better games o abril. Bad system along with the. 

Speaker 2  (05:37)
Show which mccarthy beauty news year. 

Speaker 1  (05:40)
I have used the uh the data big storied infected and better TV. 

Speaker 2  (05:47)
Recuérdamelo. 

Speaker 1  (05:51)
Sorry. 

Speaker 2  (05:55)
Ok. Call rosane New York implement cdc right change captain change data capture. See so cdc mostly what don't statcher data right i'm how did you implement for the any such a data? 

Speaker 1  (06:15)
We have a made of restructure data first and then we are dude dollar years. I'm better in everything. And IF it all about the series today de actividad. 

Speaker 1  (06:27)
Canal 3 hora. 

Speaker 2  (06:29)
A través de what's on the united neta? I'm impediéd from that of this hour. How do you convert to the statue data? 

Speaker 1  (06:37)
Are we provided the scheme us what skinner récord the text to. The id the material relative of partido the washer that i'd need to destruction. 

Speaker 2  (06:53)
Where were widely need to make it structure time and you can really need the period get into ambiting right. 

Speaker 1  (07:02)
Unresonding that we a. 

Speaker 2  (07:05)
New vídeos off. Your vídeos off. Your mirror is off time and you can come the come on the vídeo agai. 

Speaker 1  (07:12)
Lay the timer. The recent behind the time of short we are having the fires in different formats ok maybe that's playing i'm not sure about it. Pau militas 8. 

Speaker 2  (07:29)
Looking. How did you maintain the conversation history in this all application? 

Speaker 1  (07:37)
Ah yes we are having gone separate data base for it for um story the uh ids with the conversation located so holly proposes we were usync. Um no tengo usync the maryballer. Música reconoce. 

Speaker 2  (07:59)
So what is the idea behind a time in? A let's suppose IF i'm asking some some quetions send four locations on top of the drive so how many conversation you really due to the context i will decide the pressure? I'll need you a create a session and those kind of concern implementar. 

Speaker 1  (08:21)
Yeah in the retrieving for the context proposal restriving the only top five hundred last conversation. And before that it was somerishing the uh holy holy street of the conversation for that particular session uh for that particular session of the u. Similarly we have monday the memory also um which is seventy memory that we have to eat it. 

Speaker 1  (08:48)
It will also do this um. El camino de last five pm conversation that it happened and uh. And other thing will on the database? 

Speaker 1  (09:04)
Perfecto jugó un size and the context. That there's what it is reducing the context of the conversation. 

Speaker 2  (09:16)
Ok. How did you test the accuracy of the lane genre? 

Speaker 1  (09:24)
Yeah i could see we have at school city legal margis. Call to darkwood check-in there. 

Speaker 2  (09:34)
What's the reglass mcquest 2 me. 

Speaker 1  (09:37)
We are even regards matches are investigately have the four things question mark context or driver and your drawn drop. And basically uh with each one we are having a different matric Matrix before question answer it would be your uh. Mejores operaciones de it could be your answer rivers? 

Speaker 1  (09:58)
Ok for the anthony for text return you will go to other faithfulness value. A lo mejor the context and your cost will going to help their context position value. With the context and your uh ground of going to other equality. 

Speaker 1  (10:15)
So which value it feel fails we need to check the receries these few teams. Ok the police feeling we need to check order drama to tradi your interestingly we are to check for you. Um for text Richard ray. 

Speaker 1  (10:31)
¿Qué partidos genéticos? I can't from that we are used to explore the mr which is your um rank recipe player on what rank your dead uh documents comes in um. Seven. 

Speaker 1  (10:49)
Involvering the receiving the document of the. Probar context. And on for the rent position and we are exposed the nbc o two community game value. 

Speaker 1  (11:03)
We're taking the ideal relevance uh compaining the ideal released in the action released value. 

Speaker 2  (11:11)
Ok. Audio deploy this all application to the clouds on. 

Speaker 1  (11:17)
Order deployment career usync the uh city at the daughter? 

Speaker 2  (11:23)
Meet clouds ever you news there. 

Speaker 1  (11:26)
Which clothes are uh. No 0 automático. No pude vivir en tu actividad. 

Speaker 1  (11:35)
Indica 1. 

Speaker 2  (11:38)
I am not there do that applyment for your owner someone else system. Añade el proyector content. 

Speaker 1  (11:53)
Um. Yeah they know vod on. The first application with you there. 

Speaker 1  (12:02)
Eleven. Evaluating the um agent feedback ok. So there were getting lot of taste from the uh they were but system which is generating the view IP call to the text ok. 

Speaker 1  (12:19)
And then there we are getting all the transfers of the agents. Then we are teaching that data making a restructure data. And similarly we are uh having that uh checking their american eye. 

Speaker 1  (12:34)
Am. Google doing that apartment that you are used about mobile also there. Call removing DeX uh unwanted data. 

Speaker 1  (12:47)
And then we are dead will be setting on the class solution of metal normal. We are several other uh. Parametres there. 

Speaker 1  (12:56)
Ok whether the age was and full health health there's all good things to i don't want it. But based on the permitted good checking the matter normal condition and then the majority of taking and then they have the majority that out of um read then we will be wind the ratings or five occupations on the majority. Of the few pyrametres. 

Speaker 1  (13:20)
That appreciate water. How do you. 

Speaker 2  (13:26)
Oh ok. Stop which technique career news deal i make it also right about out this all it is prompting. 

Speaker 1  (13:38)
Not matter fright. It's George cooler background. 

Speaker 2  (13:46)
Pick up on the texture secret list on. 

Speaker 1  (13:50)
Chorico mode. 

Speaker 2  (13:53)
Estoy pagando de texto seco. 

Speaker 1  (13:56)
Ah yo pack more the agents or productos? 

Speaker 2  (14:01)
Text two 6 one use case. Where are users relax question in a english language and get to reflex the data from the datapace and show some jacks and saw. 

Speaker 1  (14:15)
How many good channels to work out. You can be ultimamente sin breakdable 34 a james maiden or maybe with their lantin we can dream. 

Speaker 2  (14:27)
Aunque no crees. 

Speaker 1  (14:29)
Yeah i'm visiting you to write the prompt ok of whatever the protects we are passync. Hello with accumulaty specific in the product tender discording these season. Um David multi-cal metaphones in between. 

Speaker 1  (14:43)
Um. Set the similar to my favourite los consumo show. No hay nada más meniendo probablemente excelsior rating más gente que Federico ultrodi. 

Speaker 1  (14:57)
We can protect our effect of more the landrop so we need to categorize the user well IF it is coming with a secret then i have to ride that prompt ok should go to that role of that prompt to take the particular tools that we have confided so one of the tools the secret directed going to check for that part it will win it take that to relate the secret for us and the gift they give their response for the user. Georgina grito de la andra ficción duró. No puedo ir tiempo a. 

Speaker 2  (15:36)
Open. I think recorded son from my end do you have any questions for me? 

Speaker 1  (15:44)
Channel one. 

Speaker 2  (15:47)
Bring your mode. 
