This content was generated by AI


Speaker 1  (00:03)
Show in the document which is test planned strategy. So the purpose is define a complete test strategy from the moment a user start a outlook issue report through team chat, a mobile voice until L1 resolution escalational ServiceNow ticket creation, okay. Disc documentation also clarify what functional uai language test NF test engineers and a test list manager will do across the project life cycle. 

Speaker 1  (00:38)
So they have the document control document type is Test planners, strategy solutions scope is outlook L1 support through team chat, and mobile voice channel primary integration is Microsoft team mobile authentication E. I. Raag. 

Speaker 1  (00:59)
API quality stream is functional UI UX, language text, AI racks ServiceNow, integration Okay, and gwat, readiness prepared for S IT NFTU IT production readiness, review and QA governance. Executive summary, this test plan validate the end to an outlook, a agent support journey across 2 individual team chat. And mobile voice ticket, the business process starts with user authentication continued through issue classification and guide Al one trouble shooting using the outlook knowledge base and ends, either with resolution confirmation or ServiceNow, incident creation and escalation. 

Speaker 1  (01:49)
Testing is organised by responsibility stream, so each test engineer understands exactly what to validate. Evidence to capture and what quality gates must be made before processing from sit to uten release readiness QA core principle is, every Child must prove the same business outcome only valid user can start support issue classification is accurate. Air troubled shooting is grounded in approved, knowledge and unresolved issue. 

Speaker 1  (02:18)
Create a single accurate service. Now ticket with the right context Hindi. So here we are not creating the ticket. 

Speaker 1  (02:26)
Okay, we are just checking the relevance of the data so solution is scope and end process. The solution has 2 service channel and one common support workflow team chat validate internal access and issue classification before troubleshooting mobile voice validates employee ID. Okay, these are all the things that you'll gonna see. 

Speaker 1  (02:54)
And to end outlook support processes, step business stage, primary component Q addition outcome users start outlook issue report primary component is So in the business stage, they will go to authenticate. Capture retail, classify outlook issue. Retrieve knowledge troubleshoot, resolve. 

Speaker 1  (03:16)
Escalate, create service not to get close interaction. There are scope boundaries, so in scope is basically there. There are 2 ways 1 the user can be authenticated. 

Speaker 1  (03:28)
He can also use a chatting and the other way is the user is not the user is authenticated, then he is just searching. We are storing the chats also per user, so team chat access on the Nifty. Internal user validation issue classification, L1 racked retrieval memory contact chat history. 

Speaker 1  (03:51)
Okay, out of scope is Test data creation is the out of coboke, production data access without masking. No, that should be the main part of the production data access without masking. It should not So okay, unsuppoted, outlook fixes outside approved use cases. 

Speaker 1  (04:18)
Okay, these are the out of scope test level is component testing support system integration, testing and twin testing, ok, G support, so high level tactical and functional is not this one. Then, we have the CP stages and the key test check stages entry-level authentication issue classification. Okay, diagnostic and permission check trouble shooting resolution decision ticket creation album ticket QL2 exclusion that these are not required. 

Speaker 1  (04:52)
Album ticket QL2 escalation is not required. Now we have the primary text objective is authentication classification, knowledge RAG, trouble shooting ServiceNow and the user experience And keep it a scenario would be Let's say chat ZID scenarios and the priority Okay, so authorised internal employee access chat. Web successfully disable terminated, so these are multiple scenarios. 

Speaker 1  (05:24)
And Zaraf. Okay, authentication is I dictionary, priority. These are the all the things that now we have the role based responsibility across the project area, the following metrics classify what each testing rule is expected to do across the project life cycle from intake through the service. 

Speaker 1  (05:45)
Now ticket and creation enclosure. So we have the functional test engineer whose primary responsibilities to own, to own end-to-end business protest user authentication authorisation, path issue classification validation. Okay, issue classification validation. 

Speaker 1  (06:08)
Alban trouble shoots shooting flows, resolution, escalation, outcome and service notification check. Veldetered team sa UI test enginee will be there whose who will validate the team chat renting conversation layout, but to know all those things, accessibility, language and text. First engineer NF test engineer and lead test engineer. 

Speaker 1  (06:29)
Also, there Details detailed responsibility matrix via project area project are functional test engineer, test engineering language test test engineer NF test engineer test leader manager. Stream level test strategy. So testing stream strategy, basically, we need the functional testing UI used testing language texting AI act testing NFC performance, security privacy, core functional integration scenarios, core functional services. 

Speaker 1  (07:04)
Now scenarios, let's say you have to come up with a scenarios. Then, we have the language test and hallucination testing Shortest variation could be paragraph, such as cannot sea mails, searches hanging Sender, invite missing. Classification without forcing users to use exact keeping spelling, a grammar error mixed language input unsucorted Admin requests. 

Speaker 1  (07:35)
No history available, no KB available. Now we've the NFT performance reliability and the DR strategies in the NFT and dear, we have the NFT areas. Non-functional requirement areas, response time, low distress, soak volume, reliability, and the disaster recovery. 

Speaker 1  (07:56)
Coverage, we have to tell expected evidences. Risks recommended KPI and evidence metrics. Okay? 

Speaker 1  (08:05)
Then, we have a test data requirement So user persona data type would be user perform persona outlook issue, data set RAG voice data OTP data service. Now, data and the history of the memory data. Now we have the test environment details where we have the environment, readiness, metrics, society environment UIT environment, net and FT environment secondary region service. 

Speaker 1  (08:32)
Now test instance, observability, stack ok. North 12th is the entry criteria definition of ready, where we have the requirement designed readiness, environment, readiness, test, data, redness, test asset, third, party integration governance. 13 is the definition of done on the exit criteria? 

Speaker 1  (08:52)
If the functional uaxibility language test ServiceNow an empty DR regression UIT business sign off, then we have the risk assumption dependency mitigation. Risk, you have to list on the IT and the risk involved. Income complete or changing 160 L1 use case knowledge base, AI retrieve wrong or absolute article hallucinated, troubleshooter, fabricated ticket ServiceNow duplicate or loss ticket during the retrieve voice recognition error. 

Speaker 1  (09:25)
Ok, ChatGPT, your contacts not recovered after failure. Proved outlook Alvan service. Now, test instance Key assumptions Okay. 

Speaker 1  (09:39)
Now we've dependent on the dependency trackers. Now we have the test execution governments and reporting daily test planning execution tracking defect rige, risk management quality metrics. Readiness review, recommend a QA reporting matter. 

Speaker 1  (09:58)
Matthesh or bhi execution execution coverage pass rate defect, health air quality service non integrity, and after address doctor tradeness, defect management. Then, it test discoverable, and the sign of pack test strategy and plan Detailed test scenarios. Ok. 
